<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>小RFK表示，美国应该在疫苗方面将目光投向欧洲。这可能意味着美国人会越来越少。- Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/25/rfk-jr-europe-on-vaccine-schedule-00704242</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQeUxkRDU5RmY1LWpuSHBndmxwOWRzVE50RHFpQk8zbXhyZXBBSU9YYVlkUktGSkpCeEgzeTU4TTJZT3ZzOE5fcEZaNnBJUmlZZUdxWHZnSkRlOHR3LU93ZEhmY3hrd1NhTlJScXJoNnA5U0FST0xLYXRWUEMwVnA3SmVCZ1RHMDh2clBJ</guid></item><item><title>尊敬的医生： 65岁以上的人应该多久接种一次RSV疫苗？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2025/12/dear-doctor-how-often-should-people-older-than-65-get-the-rsv-vaccination.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OWYZPM2A4RGIJB672SNCYX32DM"&gt;DEAR DR. ROACH: My husband and I are over 65. We got the respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) vaccinations two years ago. I’m reading mixed reports on how often we should be getting them. -- N.W.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZEJTBKFZDBFZHBBNWIYD5PV7HE"&gt;ANSWER: Along with influenza and COVID, RSV is yet another virus that causes respiratory disease in adults -- one that is especially dangerous for young children and older adults. It is recommended to be discussed for those who are over the age of 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3NINZBBJ6RAWPNC4B4VZJYGONY"&gt;People younger than 60 with moderate to severe immune system diseases, such as those that deal with an organ (especially lung) or a stem-cell transplant, should also consider vaccination. I recommend the vaccine to all adults over 75 and to those over 60 who have risk factors such as chronic heart or lung disease, complicated diabetes, or hemodialysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KLOLW5IA55HGTBCZH7Q65B5L6M"&gt;At the current time, booster doses of the RSV vaccine are not recommended. This may change; although there is evidence that immunity wanes after a year, repeat doses were not found to be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KVF24K3KTZDAFKOSBLDSBTYRO4"&gt;DEAR DR. ROACH: When I was about 6 years old in the early ’40s, my 16-year-old brother was sent to a sanitarium for tuberculosis patients. He was there for 18 months and was a survivor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ARJQBPK52NCF3EKSXI3NJH6XSE"&gt;During this period of time, we (the family) went regularly for chest X-rays and some kind of test that involved a needle in my forearm. Why aren’t X-rays done today -- not to detect tuberculosis but to look for cancer? CT scans are expensive and sometimes involve a long wait, so why not do a simple X-ray for starters? And then if they see something, perhaps they can do a CT scan? -- N.C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SLKL5RRCMJFI5E7NFDBF7KV73I"&gt;ANSWER: Many physicians and scientists at Johns Hopkins, Memorial Sloan-Kettering, and other first-rate institutions have sought to answer the question of whether annual chest X-rays led to a reduction in the risk of dying from lung cancer. But unfortunately, the consensus of opinion is that chest X-rays do not lead to an improvement in lung cancer mortality. There were tens of thousands of participants in these studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NBWMU2K4B5C65EQ4LGB7VJGRJU"&gt;You are also right to think that a CT scan might be more useful. Studies have shown that for a subset of people who are at a high risk, screening with a CT scan does lead to a reduction in lung cancer deaths. Specifically, lung cancer screening should be considered for people between the ages of 50-80 (Medicare will pay up to age 77) who are in generally good health; those who have smoked at least 20 “pack years” (such as a pack a day for 20 years, two packs a day for 10 years, or a half pack a day for 40 years); and those who currently smoke or have quit within the past 15 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SALM4LIHEBGN3ANNCAWUPIDQMU"&gt;The benefit from lung cancer screening is modest; it takes about 250 people to be screened annually for three years to prevent one lung cancer death. Still, this is significant, and I do discuss lung cancer screening with my eligible patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3UTZXFHD7VFW7M3GWVTCS4GIU4"&gt;Finally, the best way by far to prevent lung cancer is to quit smoking as soon as possible. If you are a smoker, your doctor has many ways to help you quit. Calling a quit line, such as 800-QUIT-NOW, will connect you with your state service. You can also text QUITNOW to 333888, and there are web-based programs such as Smokefree.gov and apps like quitSTART from the National CANCER Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JYP7VFMJNFGDBPE7SIG4MUGEHI"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dr. Roach regrets that he is unable to answer individual letters, but will incorporate them in the column whenever possible. Readers may email questions to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu"&gt;&lt;i&gt;ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; or send mail to 628 Virginia Dr., Orlando, FL 32803.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AUMP2LSRGJBWVFXGMISV4TEA2E"&gt;&lt;i&gt;(c) 2022 North America Syndicate Inc.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U7EQ3GITRJHTXMWUUBM53ZNYZM"&gt;&lt;i&gt;All Rights Reserved&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxQNlRlWC1UeWJSbjV2VEFkMEpYOS14YS1yWGljbjEyZ0pqbVdiMTIxNFFrek1IbzAyQ0x5a2V3VTB2MXl4Um1pSVlaZ19JQWdvUHc0MWs3UmV2N00tbUFoT0FBaElUUWdOTDZYQWtQSk1oTzVtRFhVR2g2S1FEdUNkb1B5Z2xRdmpqZ2VZZnc3Mm9lcnVsU09pdmxvUDZseHZnbGo4cXk0V3BfYkR4dURnbWVNV2FIQWU1QzZ0atIB0AFBVV95cUxPbjFyR29PbXVMQ0VTeEY1ZXQ5dnZTSU1EVlJtcHNWSUhza3gtYVZtekRWRC1FdjNKQkFORDB1XzE5Q1FuY2ZNdVlreUFhaUNsekkyOE5EY1RNZ25iT2ItaE03VERpVnZTT1ZaeVlDcEY0cjZUYW1iN3hneEF6ZWFZTWw0NXlxaE9ZRi1uOUU1bFl6UVVrSTNGaTh6cXJEZmk3dWZiRndVblAwb3p5cVpZbFl1emtmWndWWFNHNGNxNmEtOVp3UG0xWHprTHhiZEg2</guid></item><item><title>血液测试可以预测谁最容易患上常见遗传性心脏病--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/dec/25/blood-test-predict-risk-inherited-heart-condition-hypertrophic-cardiomyopathy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists are developing a simple blood test to predict who is most at risk from the world’s most common inherited heart condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Millions of people worldwide have hypertrophic cardiomyopathy (HCM), a disease of the heart muscle where the wall of the heart becomes thickened. It is caused by a change in one or more genes and mostly passed on through families.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some feel fine most of the time and have few or no symptoms. But others can suffer complications, such as heart failure and abnormal heart rhythms, which can lead to a cardiac arrest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The problem is there is no cure. Doctors also &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/jan/08/outdated-guidelines-mean-doctors-failing-to-spot-heart-condition-in-women" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;do not know which patients&lt;/a&gt; with the genetic condition are most at risk from deadly complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But now a team of scientists from universities including Harvard and Oxford have found a way to forecast risk for people living with HCM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The blood test could identify those patients most in danger of complications, enabling them to be monitored more closely or receive life-saving treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In a landmark study, the team measured the levels of a protein, N-terminal Pro-B-type natriuretic peptide (NT-Pro-BNP), in the blood of 700 HCM patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;NT-Pro-BNP is released by the heart as part of normal pumping. But high levels are a sign the heart is working too hard. Those with the highest levels had poorer blood flow, more scar tissue and changes in their heart which could lead to atrial fibrillation or heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A blood test measuring NT-Pro-BNP could transform the care of millions of people with the world’s most common inherited heart condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study leader, Prof Carolyn Ho, the medical director of the cardiovascular genetics centre at Harvard medical school, said the test could help “target the right therapies to the right patients at the right time”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She added: “Continued studies on blood biomarkers will lead to better understanding of HCM so that, in future, we can offer our patients a blood test to identify who is at high versus low risk of experiencing serious consequences of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“People with the highest risk could be targeted for potentially life-saving treatments as they stand to receive the greatest benefit, while those at lowest risk could avoid unnecessary treatment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Lara Johnson, 34, from Southampton in the UK, is one of many who could benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="3eeff211-4533-46b2-bfc2-0e18861b2e1f" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":13,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Parasite cleanses: why are so many people obsessed with intestinal worms?","elementId":"3eeff211-4533-46b2-bfc2-0e18861b2e1f","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/09/parasite-cleanses-people-obsessed-intestinal-worms"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Eight years ago, she began experiencing breathlessness and fatigue. After being referred by her GP for hospital tests, she was diagnosed with HCM. Several relatives on her father’s side were subsequently also diagnosed with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“One of the hardest parts of living with HCM is the constant uncertainty, never knowing what might change next,” Johnson said. “A simple blood test, which could help identify future risks earlier, would take away so much of that anxiety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She added: “It could give people like me a chance to prepare and adjust our lifestyles as needed, and help us to feel more in control. That kind of clarity wouldn’t only help me, it would make a world of difference for my whole family.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Bryan Williams, the chief scientific and medical officer of the British Heart Foundation, which funded the research, said the test “could benefit patients around the world”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“After a diagnosis of HCM, patients and their families want to know what the future holds. This study shows that measuring various proteins circulating in the blood could help predict how the heart is functioning and future risk of complications from heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This new method may also provide insights in the evolution of the structure and function of the heart in people with HCM that could point to new ways of treating this condition to reduce future risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxPUlppcm1LVVd3MDZPbEtJd25TX3Y4Z2NwdDh2d3RWcTJhLTNBN3BJaHAtX3BlMUxOdDVfSkF3Vlk1TG1NcU1JVDVWRUNkU183VFJMc0M0SEJZQWJmRm5HczA3OTFzY3pmNGJxaEtqOVcxeXpRSW5QS255QUhJODhKdkNYNV9mNWxhdTZfNl9Gai0tQ1VQQVRUOG9kTlVjNDN6ckhYQnJyMjUxcncyNkp6YWpISXR3QlNkN29jRlNuelZWRzQ</guid></item><item><title>用药过量危机正在好转- Salon.com</title><link>https://www.salon.com/2025/12/25/the-overdose-crisis-is-turning-around/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="article__content page-article"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Overdose deaths &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2024/11/15/cdc-overdose-set-to-dip-below-100000-for-the-first-time-since-2020/"&gt;are falling&lt;/a&gt; at a pace the United States has not seen in decades. Centers for Disease Control projections show a nearly &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/nvss/vsrr/drug-overdose-data.htm"&gt;&lt;span&gt;25% decline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for the twelve months ending in April 2025. But the meaning of that decline shows up long before it appears in national reports. It shows up in a son who makes it home from work, in a daughter who stays in treatment long enough to rebuild her life, in the quiet, daily act of someone returning home to the people who love them. It shows up in having another table setting at the holiday dinner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These moments of return do not happen by chance. They happen because public policy finally &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;aligns with evidence and because communities were able to use tools we already know save lives. Policymakers &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://chir.georgetown.edu/tackling-another-public-health-emergency-recent-state-and-federal-policies-to-increase-opioid-use-disorder-treatment-access/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;expanded access&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to medications for opioid use disorder, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.samhsa.gov/substance-use/treatment/statutes-regulations-guidelines/buprenorphine-telemedicine-prescribing"&gt;&lt;span&gt;protected telehealth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for addiction treatment and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pew.org/en/research-and-analysis/issue-briefs/2025/09/state-policy-approaches-to-expand--naloxone-access"&gt;&lt;span&gt;widened community access&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to naloxone. People are home for the holidays because life-saving systems were finally allowed to fully function.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="right_quote"&gt;
&lt;p class="insert-quote"&gt;Whether this progress continues depends on the choices we make now. As we head into 2026, the foundational policies that saved lives this year could disappear before the next holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Whether this progress continues depends on the choices we make now. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;As we head into 2026, the foundational policies that saved lives this year could disappear before the next holiday season.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lifesaving tools that have driven the decline remain vulnerable. Medications for &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/opioids"&gt;opioid&lt;/a&gt; use disorder — especially buprenorphine and methadone — cut the risk of death by more than half. Yet for years, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ecfr.gov/current/title-21/chapter-II/part-1306/subject-group-ECFR1eb5bb3a23fddd0/section-1306.07"&gt;&lt;span&gt;federal rules&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and insurance barriers have kept these treatments out of reach. Even now, many patients face bureaucratic paperwork hurdles, such as prior authorization requirements, which interrupt care and separate patients from necessary prescriptions. States have worked to close these gaps by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2949875924001401"&gt;&lt;span&gt;expanding mobile treatment programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://americanhealth.jhu.edu/news/bringing-addiction-treatment-primary-care-settings"&gt;&lt;span&gt;embedding addiction treatment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; into primary care, specifically in Texas and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pew.org/en/research-and-analysis/fact-sheets/2025/12/how-massachusetts-addresses-substance-use-disorders-in-primary-care-settings"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These changes increased the odds of survival, but the initiatives &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://nasadad.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/The-Substance-Use-Workforce-Crisis-Drivers-Challenges-and-Promising-Strategies_POST-2.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;remain under-resourced&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and at-risk. In recent years, telehealth has become one of the most powerful drivers of improved access. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2949875925001432"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; shows that patients who begin treatment virtually stay in recovery at similar or higher rates than those who start in person. While skeptics remain, the data confirm that telehealth provides quality care without increasing overdose risk. This is especially important to rural counties and households without reliable transportation, where telehealth means the difference between care instead of a crisis. But in 2026, those flexibilities &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/files/document/telehealth-faq-updated-11-26-2025.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;will vanish&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; unless Congress acts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Additional changes to insurance coverage expose how quickly people can lose access and be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;pushed out of treatment. &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/medicaid"&gt;Medicaid&lt;/a&gt; covers nearly half of non-elderly adults with opioid use disorder, paying for the critical treatment services that get people to recovery. But this backbone &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/03/21/cutting-medicaid-could-worsen-overdose-and-erase-recent-progress-in-treating-addiction/"&gt;is weakening&lt;/a&gt;. During the unwinding of pandemic protections, more than 23 million people have lost Medicaid coverage, which is often &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/medicaid/medicaid-enrollment-and-unwinding-tracker/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;due to paperwork errors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; rather than changes in eligibility. This number is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aha.org/news/headline/2025-07-21-cbo-projects-obbba-increase-uninsured-10-million-federal-deficit-34-trillion"&gt;&lt;span&gt;estimated to increase significantly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; following the passage of the &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/big_beautiful_bill"&gt;One Big Beautiful Bill&lt;/a&gt;, which according to the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office (CBO), will &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/medicaid/allocating-cbos-estimates-of-federal-medicaid-spending-reductions-across-the-states-enacted-reconciliation-package/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;slash Medicaid and Children’s Health Insurance Program (CHIP) spending&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by nearly $1 trillion over a decade and eliminate over 10 million people from the programs. Similarly, the CBO warns that about 1.5 million Americans will be uninsured in 2026 if Congress delays extending the ACA enhanced tax credits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want more sharp takes on politics? &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/newsletter?utm_source=onsite&amp;amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;amp;utm_campaign=standing-room-only-edit-signup"&gt;Sign up for our free newsletter&lt;/a&gt;, Standing Room Only, written by Amanda Marcotte, now also a weekly show &lt;a href="%E2%80%9Dhttps://www.salon.com/2025/06/13/standing-room-only-amanda-marcotte-salon-youtube-podcast/%E2%80%9D"&gt;on YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Congress has the power to address these lapsing policies in 2026 and needs to act — just as it did with the bipartisan reauthorization of the SUPPORT for Patients and Communities Act, which promises to continue federal funding for core recovery programs and to address overdose. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But maintaining the status quo is not enough to resolve the fracture points where people still fall out of care. In 2026, Congress should pass legislation to ensure that Americans who are most vulnerable to fatal overdose, such as those entering and leaving jail and prison, receive evidence-based, lifesaving treatment. Congress can grow the treatment workforce by funding and expanding peer recovery support workers. These proposals follow the same evidence that drove the decline in 2025.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The drop in overdose deaths this year is real. It reflects years of work by clinicians, community &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;groups, families and bipartisan lawmakers who chose data over dogma. But a decline does not &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;equal victory. It equals a narrow window of opportunity. The difference between momentum and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;reversal now runs through the legislative decisions that will shape 2026. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just like this holiday season, families will gather again next December. Some seats will be filled because of the policies that worked in 2025. Others will stand empty if those policies unravel in 2026. The country already knows which choices save lives. What remains unclear is whether it will keep making them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="layout_template_wrapper read_more"&gt;
&lt;div class="red_white_box"&gt;
&lt;p class="red_box"&gt;Read more&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="white_box"&gt;about this topic&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Salon.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:30:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTFByR0tuZUdWSmxBNWtTT3p6S3JyWlVUSTA0cE0wVDJ0Vk9qQ3RQcjkxVVRfTVl0QUZzZGhjcVpfNUI2NXJoX1g1NHZoV3QwNTdiYjZTdEEtSjFLNXZNYldfZThHdEM3alNTUnBETUhaeW5NRVM2em11LWprdw</guid></item><item><title>不明原因的体重增加？医生透露这可能是甲状腺活动不足的迹象|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gained-unexplained-weight-doctor-reveals-it-may-be-a-sign-of-underactive-thyroid-101766644639293.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/gained-unexplained-weight-doctor-reveals-it-may-be-a-sign-of-underactive-thyroid-101766644639293.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/chennai-fitness-trainer-with-18-years-of-experience-shares-4-mindful-hacks-to-prevent-weight-gain-due-to-overeating-101766492474363.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Weight gain"&gt;Weight gain&lt;/a&gt; is usually associated with a sedentary lifestyle, frequent consumption of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/dermatologist-explains-why-simply-cutting-out-junk-food-does-not-cure-acne-busts-5-common-acne-myths-101759478620994.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="junk food"&gt;junk food&lt;/a&gt;, or insufficient physical activity. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;However, when the numbers on the scale continue to rise despite mindful eating habits and regular movements, then the cause may be deeper, beyond behavioural or lifestyle factors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/weight_gain__1766645134269_1766645134504.jpg" alt="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/weight_gain__1766645134269_1766645134504.jpg" alt="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/ahmedabad-physician-shares-the-key-foods-and-nutrients-you-should-include-in-your-diet-for-a-healthier-thyroid-101765873817961.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Ahmedabad physician shares the key foods and nutrients you should include in your diet for a healthier thyroid"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ahmedabad physician shares the key foods and nutrients you should include in your diet for a healthier thyroid&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To understand one of these unseen causes, HT Lifestyle connected with Dr Gaurav Jain, senior consultant of internal medicine at Dharamshila Narayana Superspeciality Hospital, Delhi. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;According to him, unexplained weight gain can often be linked to an imbalance in the thyroid gland, which plays a crucial role in regulating the body's metabolism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;When the thyroid becomes underactive, a condition known as hypothyroidism, the body’s metabolic processes slow down, leading to gradual and often confusing weight gain,” he explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;How do you know if your weight gain is connected to a thyroid imbalance? Some subtle signs are often attributed to other causes, as they tend to overlap with common health issues. This is why paying closer attention to these symptoms is crucial so that you can distinguish and identify.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Gaurav Jain shared 5 signs:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Weight gain despite normal eating habits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Jain explained that weight gain is the first red flag with an underactive thyroid, particularly when there has been no major change in diet or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;Why does this happen? He explained, “A sluggish thyroid slows down the body's calorie-burning rate, leading to fat accumulation, particularly around the abdomen.” Another key indicator that he informed is that weight is very hard to lose, even if you are regularly exercising.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Persistent fatigue and low energy levels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exhaustion is generally linked to stress or burnout. In fact, fatigue overlaps with several mental and physical issues, which is why it is often overlooked. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;However, Dr Jain pointed out that persistent, unexplained fatigue can also be an early sign of an underactive thyroid, especially when it occurs alongside gradual weight gain and low energy levels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He described why this happens: “&lt;span&gt; Thyroid hormones are essential for energy production. When levels drop, the body feels constantly tired and sluggish. This ongoing fatigue reduces physical activity, further contributing to weight gain and a feeling of heaviness in the body.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Dry skin, hair fall and slow nail growth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/07/24/550x309/hair__1753345225207_1753345225312.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="You experience a lot of hairfall with an underactive thyroid. (Shutterstock)" title="You experience a lot of hairfall with an underactive thyroid. (Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;You experience a lot of hairfall with an underactive thyroid. (Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Changes in the skin, hair, and nails may look like cosmetic issues that require you to change your skincare, haircare or manicure routine, but sometimes they can be associated with deeper health issues.&lt;/span&gt; Dr Jain cautioned that an underactive thyroid affects the skin's ability to retain moisture, making makin it dry, rough, and less elastic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He named some changes, “Hair fall is common, and hair may become thin or brittle. Nails often grow more slowly and may appear weak or ridged.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Hormonal imbalance and menstrual changes in women&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Thyroid health is closely linked to reproductive health, which means it can impact hormone levels and make women more likely to experience problems associated with hormonal disruptions when the thyroid is underactive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Describing how the menstrual flow gets affected, “In women, hypothyroidism can disrupt menstrual cycles, making them irregular, heavy or painful.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Jain also elaborated that low thyroid hormone levels can disturb hormonal balance, leading to fluid retention and increased fat storage, which can result in unexplained weight gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Neck swelling, eye symptoms and digestive slowdown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/25/550x309/stomach_pain_1756092360701_1756092366710.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Unhealthy gut causes weight gain.(Shutterstock)" title="Unhealthy gut causes weight gain.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Unhealthy gut causes weight gain.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;Physical changes in the neck and eyes, along with digestive issues, can also point to thyroid dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Jain shared these 3 signs related to these areas:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;An enlarged thyroid may appear as a swelling in the neck and can sometimes cause difficulty in swallowing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mild vision disturbances, blurred vision and puffy eyes may also be present.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Digestion slows down, leading to bloating and constipation, which can add to weight gain and discomfort.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the doctor warned about a couple of important points. Firstly, unexplained weight gain and other subtle symptoms should not always be dismissed. Secondly, with the increasing use of non-iodised salts and changing dietary patterns, early and subclinical thyroid disorders are increasingly common.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:54:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxNUDI0ajJ4aU9yOTBrSVZERUMwc3IxZFYtR2MwQVFUMm04X1NqaDMyX0t1VjYxcW9yd2s1ZFRfOV9UQkJsa0ZIVUZGd1NkbHd2S2YzUXNPUEVsMm1BOGtuVF93eXlRXzBBUW1fOTNVZnVmUlBkTjFiTXAyMTNia2U0TkNoVnNsNnBIRVYwNUNJTk1EMnVvRkFuTkpFc2p0ZVdGYmJpTFRWOE93M21tbFRZTS1sVmJIRE1lTjdONnNhUXlsbVd0VlZzX0U4blBBSFFSNUtnMGplaDNZODNJX0pJbEpNc9IB6AFBVV95cUxOMUc1eTVjQkNLSFZyWFQ4UlpGTTByQ2ZVa0g1NzIyOTZ4cTlSbkVpbFFFdUZTRkVZd3gxTDYtaXNyc1k2NW5ibG9adHg0TEZvNkc2MVZUUHVyc3JvbW5wNHRLeWZPVEhwaEFQa1lmZGtyak5SOGdSWVdQcmFHdUJ1ZHF6M3pyRFY4VWEyb0NzOFlPd2dpcHRfckp4T2QwZEg2VmNkSm5LaHdoem1PVHAwWDZIU083VTEyR3hUaEJmLWlHUTVmYkVEZF8wbWRDeEdKek1SVVliamZNZUJTUno3UzBZem5FY0Rs</guid></item><item><title>新技术以创纪录的速度和效率消除“永久化学物质” - ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251224032401.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A research team at Rice University, working with international collaborators, has created the first environmentally friendly technology that can quickly trap and break down toxic "forever chemicals" (PFAS) in water. The results, published recently in &lt;em&gt;Advanced Materials&lt;/em&gt;, represent a meaningful advance against one of the most stubborn pollution threats worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project was led by Youngkun Chung, a postdoctoral fellow mentored by Michael S. Wong, a professor at Rice's George R. Brown School of Engineering and Computing. The effort also included Seoktae Kang, a professor at the Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST), and Keon-Ham Kim, a professor at Pukyung National University in South Korea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Are PFAS and Why Are They a Problem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PFAS, short for per- and polyfluoroalkyl substances, are man-made chemicals that date back to the 1940s. They have been used in many everyday products, including Teflon pans, waterproof clothing, and some food packaging. PFAS became popular because they resist heat, grease, and water, but that same durability also means they break down very slowly, which is why they are often called "forever chemicals."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PFAS have now spread widely and can be found in water, soil, and air around the world. Research has linked exposure to liver damage, reproductive disorders, immune system disruption, and certain cancers. Cleanup has been difficult because once PFAS enter the environment, they are hard to remove and even harder to destroy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Current PFAS Removal Methods Fall Short&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many standard approaches rely on adsorption, meaning the chemicals stick to materials such as activated carbon or ion-exchange resins. These methods are common, but they have major limitations, including low efficiency, slow operation, limited capacity, and the buildup of additional contaminated waste that still has to be handled.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Current methods for PFAS removal are too slow, inefficient and create secondary waste," said Wong, the Tina and Sunit Patel Professor in Molecular Nanotechnology and professor of chemical and biomolecular engineering, chemistry and civil and environmental engineering. "Our new approach offers a sustainable and highly effective alternative."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Breakthrough LDH Material That Works Fast&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new approach is built around a layered double hydroxide (LDH) material made from copper and aluminum. Kim first identified this type of material while he was a graduate student at KAIST in 2021. As the team explored these compounds further, Chung found that a specific version containing nitrate could adsorb PFAS with unusually high performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"To my astonishment, this LDH compound captured PFAS more than 1,000 times better than other materials," said Chung, a lead author of the study and now a fellow at Rice's WaTER (Water Technologies, Entrepreneurship and Research) Institute and Sustainability Institute. "It also worked incredibly fast, removing large amounts of PFAS within minutes, about 100 times faster than commercial carbon filters."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers say the impressive results come from the material's internal design. Its ordered copper-aluminum layers, along with small charge imbalances, create a highly favorable surface where PFAS molecules can attach quickly and strongly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tested in River Water, Tap Water, and Wastewater&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To see how well the system could perform outside the lab, the team tested the LDH material in river water, tap water, and wastewater. Across all three, it remained highly effective. It also performed well in both static tests and continuous-flow setups, pointing to possible use in municipal water treatment systems and industrial cleanup.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Closing the Loop With PFAS Destruction and Reuse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capturing PFAS is only half the battle since the chemicals still need to be destroyed safely. Working with Rice professors Pedro Alvarez and James Tour, Chung developed a process to thermally decompose PFAS after they are captured on the LDH material. When the PFAS-loaded material was heated with calcium carbonate, the researchers removed more than half of the trapped PFAS without releasing toxic by-products. The same step also regenerated the LDH, making it possible to use the material again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Early testing showed the material could go through at least six complete cycles of capture, destruction, and renewal. That makes it the first known eco-friendly, sustainable system for PFAS removal that combines rapid cleanup with repeated reuse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Collaboration and Research Support&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We are excited by the potential of this one-of-a-kind LDH-based technology to transform how PFAS-contaminated water sources are treated in the near future," Wong said. "It's the result of an extraordinary international collaboration and the creativity of young researchers."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A list of all the researchers involved in this study and their institutional affiliations can be found here. This research was supported by the Basic Science Research Program through the National Research Foundation of Korea funded by the Ministry of Education (2021R1A6A3A14044449, RS-2023-00242795), grants from the National Convergence Research of Scientific Challenges and the Sejong Science Fellowship through the National Research Foundation of Korea and funding from the Ministry of Science (NRF-2022M3C1C8094245) and ICT (RS-2024-00395438). This work was also funded by Saudi Aramco-KAIST CO2 Management, Nanosystems Engineering Research Center for Nanotechnology-Enabled Water Treatment (NEWT), the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers' Engineering Research and Development Center grant (W912HZ-21-2-0050), Rice Sustainability Institute and Rice WaTER Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 06:46:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1KN0pYLW5VMEM2T2I2R2phaU9RVEZLZEVPa210YXAtNnJQZWxTcUZGUGZRYXRtRTBBUElXWFZ2VUxfLXozVkowZHhOQzBTYjhWWDlPN0JVa1JDZG9COVpaNy1CT1hDUFE3bEp6a1pLOA</guid></item><item><title>他身边的“守护天使” ： 20岁的斯特林高地男子如何努力从中风中恢复过来-底特律新闻</title><link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/local/macomb-county/2025/12/24/sterling-heights-resident-20-continues-his-recovery-from-a-stroke/87604563007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_dt"&gt;Dec. 24, 2025&lt;span class="gnt_ar_ut"&gt;Updated Dec. 25, 2025, 9:25 a.m. ET&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;When he gathers with family at his grandparents' house for Christmas dinner this year, Edward Constantineau of Sterling Heights will be surrounded by the people who pushed him to fight to recover from the hardest thing he's ever faced in his young life, a hurdle he's still working to overcome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Constantineau was just 19, working out at his local gym in March of this year, when he suffered the unimaginable for a teenager: a stroke. He underwent immediate surgery on a bleed in his brain and later went through six weeks of inpatient rehab at a facility in Detroit, learning how to move again, talk and regain fine motor skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Detroit News</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 04:06:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4gFBVV95cUxPV0xBYzA5dEFOYjhCM2RYbUduaElVWkNPeGdBd2lraEttb1pGY2dRdlEweU51VVMxQVpTdnpRXzBpNTNkRmFUUWRVeDhpNkhfMHhPdWRuX2ZGUVdubmJrYUZEZmdjWVR6WUpTcGVYVUFUeDVEeWlncU5EcFlqTEVjNWc3b0ZKb3N3a050QzN4bUZEdTNQQXd5V21aOWtnSUpIMGNEN3k3a2VrSUpDZlpfempldk9VaTN3Y2RSQkhjT2NFTlctZFJxeEdtYi1Md0dHMFhIR3d5WFVlblFfMWhPOEJB</guid></item><item><title>医生回答：如何治疗流感和无用的药物- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/bjplqrfmwg</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="3rd6n-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="3rd6n-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="3rd6n-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;This year’s flu season began early, with five children dying from complications of the disease and hospitalizations on the rise. Family doctors are warning that influenza is not a mild winter illness, outlining its symptoms, identifying who is truly at risk and explaining how it should, and should not, be treated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="6etn1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6etn1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6etn1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Influenza is a viral disease characterized by complications of the respiratory system,” says Dr. Zehava Alon, a family medicine specialist with Clalit Health Services’ Central District. She describes it as a severe illness that typically lasts about a week and is marked by very high fever and serious respiratory symptoms, including cough, pneumonia, sinus infections, shortness of breath and bouts of bronchitis, along with body aches and profound weakness. Unlike common cold viruses, which usually cause mild symptoms and resolve within days, influenza can worsen significantly. “Patients die from the complications, when the underlying cause is influenza,” she says, noting the deaths of five children this year and severe outcomes among older adults.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="63c9c-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="cudbb-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="cudbb-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cudbb-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Adam Reiter, a family medicine specialist with Maccabi Healthcare Services, echoed her remarks. “Generally speaking, influenza is a viral disease of the respiratory tract. In most cases it begins and remains in the upper respiratory tract, meaning the nose and throat, but it can, God forbid, worsen and spread to the lower respiratory tract — the lungs. That is why it has the potential, like any viral illness and perhaps more so than other viruses, to cause significant respiratory disease with lung involvement.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="ai7j8-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.rkx003ERYQbg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/12/21/H1gRB7qHm11l/H1gRB7qHm11l_142_528_697_930_0_medium.jpg" alt='ד"ר זהבה אלון, רופאת משפחה, כללית' title="Dr. Zehava Alon " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dr. Zehava Alon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5i9be-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5i9be-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5i9be-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;One of the most common misconceptions about influenza and other winter illnesses is whether they are caused by a virus or a bacterium — a distinction that is critical for treatment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="4md5g-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="4md5g-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="4md5g-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“Not everyone understands the difference between a virus and a bacterium,” says Dr. Reiter. “Both can make us sick, but the key difference is practical: what medicine can do.” Bacterial infections can be treated with antibiotics, he explains, while viral illnesses cannot. “There are no drugs that kill viruses, so treatment for viral diseases is supportive and aimed at relieving symptoms. That is why people with fever or worsening symptoms should be examined, so we can determine whether the illness is viral or bacterial.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="fff2j-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta wrapped"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleWrappedImageComponenta"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleWrappedImageData.SJgvtB0KXWx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/12/21/BkAr7crmWg/BkAr7crmWg_511_94_619_826_0_medium.jpg" alt='ד"ר אדם רייטר, רופא משפחה, מכבי' title="Dr. Adam Reiter (Photo: Ofer Hajayov) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="caption" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dr. Adam Reiter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span disabled class="credit" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Ofer Hajayov&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2svm5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2svm5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2svm5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The confusion often leads patients to expect antibiotics even when they have influenza. “Influenza does not respond to antibiotics. It is a viral disease,” says Dr. Alon. “Antibiotics are sometimes given only for complications, such as pneumonia — not to treat the flu itself, but to treat a secondary infection that develops when the immune system is weakened.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="1ejg5-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="ed4i-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ed4i-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ed4i-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Influenza does not affect everyone the same way. While many recover within days, others can deteriorate quickly and develop serious complications, including pneumonia, severe respiratory failure requiring ventilation and even death.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="6s07i-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6s07i-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6s07i-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“When someone has a viral illness, the immune system is already weakened, which allows bacterial infections to develop on top of it,” says Dr. Reiter. “If there is no improvement, it is important to seek medical evaluation.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="b8g74-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="b8g74-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="b8g74-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;These warnings are especially relevant for high-risk groups — people whose immune systems may struggle to fight a viral infection. They include the very old and the very young, people with underlying medical conditions and those taking medications that suppress the immune system, for whom vaccination is particularly important. Dr. Alon adds that nearly everyone carries some level of risk, particularly people in close, ongoing contact with children, such as teachers and preschool staff.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2lqqo-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="9gg97-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9gg97-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9gg97-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Treatment for influenza is not the same for everyone and depends largely on the severity of symptoms, a person’s overall health and whether the illness is mild and self-limiting or requires medical evaluation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="9q6n7-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9q6n7-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9q6n7-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“It very much depends on the individual, their medical background, whether they are in a high-risk group, and how the illness presents,” says Dr. Reiter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="c0ke3-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="c0ke3-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="c0ke3-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“There is a big difference between a bit of coughing and a sore throat and a significant illness with high fever and breathing difficulty. The individual situation determines whether testing is needed. If symptoms are mild and within a day, two or three there is improvement, there is no need to seek medical care. But if the illness is severe, with high fever and significant symptoms, a medical evaluation is necessary. We have to rule out worsening, a secondary bacterial infection or lung involvement from influenza.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="1pelu-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1pelu-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1pelu-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;In recent years, home test kits sold at pharmacies have also become available, allowing for rapid diagnosis of influenza and in some cases combined testing for influenza and COVID-19. These kits can help in cases of mild symptoms and guide initial management at home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5a4t1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5a4t1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5a4t1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“In general, we always recommend looking first at the child’s overall condition,” says Dr. Efrat Wechsler, head of primary care and a pediatrician at Meuhedet Health Services. “The first step is to bring the fever down. When the fever drops, the child usually recovers somewhat — plays, eats and drinks. If there is no shortness of breath, you can wait through the first 48 hours and see how things develop.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5ndfr-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2cnij-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2cnij-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2cnij-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;If the fever lasts more than two days, especially if it is very high, as is typical of the current wave, or if other concerning signs appear, including decreased alertness, reduced eating or drinking, breathing difficulties, a troubling cough or unusual rashes — the child should be examined, she says. “These can be signs of a secondary infection or another condition that requires treatment. Of course, this is not treatment of the illness itself, but of possible complications. Some complications are rare but can be very dangerous, such as inflammation of the heart muscle.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2our4-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2our4-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2our4-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Alon adds that with any illness, preventing further spread is essential. “It’s important not to go to work for two days while sick and then collapse, after having already infected everyone. People who are ill should stay home, wear a mask, drink plenty of fluids, eat appropriately and rest. Grandma used to say chicken soup — but above all, hydration, light food and rest are key.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="63l74-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="63l74-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="63l74-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Fever reducers can be used, she adds. “There is also a medication given in severe cases, called Tamiflu, but it is prescribed only in serious cases and only in hospitals.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="6kank-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6kank-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6kank-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Reiter stresses the importance of basic hygiene. “Wash hands, cough into your elbow and keep distance from people in high-risk groups, such as infants, older adults and those with weakened immune systems.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="fjnm0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="fjnm0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="fjnm0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Alongside treating the illness itself, one of the main ways to reduce infection and complications is prevention — foremost through the influenza vaccine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2rui1-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2rui1-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2rui1-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“There are two types of flu vaccines,” says Dr. Reiter. “There is a live attenuated vaccine given as a nasal spray, and the familiar injected vaccine, which is inactivated. The live vaccine may cause very mild illness, but not significant disease, while the inactivated vaccine should not cause illness at all. Both are very similar in terms of effectiveness and the protection they provide.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="5vdo6-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="76jvc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="76jvc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="76jvc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The vaccine, he says, is safe and recommended for all residents of Israel starting at 6 months of age and should be taken once a year ahead of the winter flu season. “This is especially important for people in high-risk groups. For them, vaccination can truly mean the difference between severe illness and hospitalization and a mild illness that passes easily.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="2iv-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2iv-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2iv-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“This year alone, more than 800,000 people have already been vaccinated through Clalit, and that is not enough,” adds Dr. Alon. “At most, the inactivated vaccine can cause muscle aches for a day. Beyond that, there are no side effects. It does not cause the flu or complications. People remember the COVID-19 vaccines, which were developed quickly due to an emergency, but this is not the same. This is a vaccine that has existed for decades — safe and without side effects. Personally, I have been getting vaccinated for more than 25 years. As soon as vaccines are available, I am first in line.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="7qbk7" data-offset-key="9n92e-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9n92e-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9n92e-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;She notes that the vaccine is available as a nasal spray for children and as an injection for the rest of the population, with a formulation for older adults and nursing home residents that contains additional virus strains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 03:37:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE1tcmptQldLWWp5Q0R5V0hzREZZWWFYc0RUM0N5Nm5DU29fTmVxcy1YLUtyOFRDQXJTY3NDSWh5REZSUl9WdE55WENwUkx1VUg2QzFRakE2VGJ0TVVGTERLcU1UdHZRMjZaREE</guid></item><item><title>骨科专家分享5种食物，以预防维生素D缺乏症，并在阳光不足的冬季保持骨骼健康|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/orthopaedic-experts-share-5-foods-to-prevent-vitamin-d-deficiency-and-maintain-bone-health-during-sun-deprived-winters-101766582027818.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/orthopaedic-experts-share-5-foods-to-prevent-vitamin-d-deficiency-and-maintain-bone-health-during-sun-deprived-winters-101766582027818.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reduced sunlight exposure during winters quietly pushes a large section of the population toward &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/can-vitamin-d-levels-affect-colon-cancer-risk-florida-gastroenterologist-explains-the-link-between-the-two-101765888189094.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vitamin D"&gt;vitamin D &lt;/a&gt;deficiency. While the issue is often underestimated, its consequences are far-reaching - ranging from bone pain and muscle weakness to &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/5-ortho-experts-share-the-top-5-joint-issues-people-faced-in-2025-back-pain-knee-osteoarthritis-and-tech-neck-101765884132221.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="joint"&gt;joint &lt;/a&gt;stiffness and increased fracture risk. Medical experts warn that during winter months, diet becomes a critical tool to maintain adequate Vitamin D levels.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/24/550x309/vitd_1766582537962_1766582550017.png" alt="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)" title="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/24/550x309/vitd_1766582537962_1766582550017.png" alt="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)" title="Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Try out Dr Vaish and Dr Rathi's recommendations to optimise your vitamin D levels during winter!(Image generated via Google Gemini)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-trainer-warns-women-are-at-greater-risk-of-muscle-loss-in-winter-shares-4-tips-to-prevent-101766327891932.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fitness trainer reveals women are at greater risk of muscle loss in winter; shares 4 tips to prevent"&gt;Fitness trainer reveals women are at greater risk of muscle loss in winter; shares 4 tips to prevent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;HT Lifestyle reached out to two orthopaedic experts - Dr Abhishek Vaish, Orthopaedic, Joint Replacement and Sports Injury Specialist at Apollo Hospital, and Dr Akhilesh Rathi, Director of Robotics, Joint Replacement and Orthopaedics at Sri Balaji Action Medical Institute and founder of Rathi Orthopedic and Spine Clinic - to discuss wintertime vitamin D deficiency and the most effective ways to optimise levels through diet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Vitamin D and winters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As daylight hours and sun exposure decline during winter, vitamin D levels in many people tend to drop as well. Dr Vaish highlights, “We routinely see patients complaining of unexplained &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mumbai-orthopaedic-surgeon-explains-why-knee-pain-worsens-in-winter-shares-causes-symptoms-and-easy-tips-to-manage-it-101765811662475.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="knee pain"&gt;knee pain&lt;/a&gt;, backache, and muscle fatigue during winter. In many cases, the underlying cause turns out to be Vitamin D deficiency aggravated by lack of sun exposure.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains that vitamin D is essential for calcium absorption and bone mineralisation. When sunlight-driven synthesis drops, nutritional sources play a compensatory role - and a thoughtful winter diet can significantly help prevent deficiency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fatty fishes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Vaish, salmon, mackerel, sardines and tuna are among the richest natural sources of vitamin D. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He recommends including them regularly in your diet - at least two to three times a week - as this can help support bone density and muscle strength.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He notes, “Vitamin D from fatty fish is highly bioavailable and supports joint health, particularly in individuals with early arthritis or age-related bone loss.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Egg yolks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Rathi emphasises that egg yolks are often the most overlooked source, but they provide a steady amount of vitamin D, along with essential fats. For non-vegetarians, eggs are an easy addition to winter meals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains, “Egg yolks are nutritionally dense and help improve vitamin D intake without major dietary changes. When consumed sensibly, they benefit immunity and musculoskeletal health.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/24/original/photo-1699892726871-22e77ee1b75b_1766582217747.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Egg yolks are a great source of vitamin D.(Unsplash)" title="Egg yolks are a great source of vitamin D.(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Egg yolks are a great source of vitamin D.(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fortified foods&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fortified milk, yoghurt, cereals, and plant-based milk alternatives have emerged as practical vitamin D sources, especially for vegetarians. These foods are widely recommended during winter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Rathi notes, “Fortified foods are extremely useful for people who spend most of their day indoors - office workers, students, and elderly individuals - who get minimal sun exposure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;UV-exposed and sun-dried mushrooms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Rathi, certain mushrooms naturally produce vitamin D when exposed to ultraviolet light, making them another great source. Sun-dried mushrooms can be incorporated into curries, soups, and stir-fries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains, “This is one of the few plant-based natural Vitamin D options and works well for those avoiding animal products.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cod liver oil and select dairy products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Vaish highlights that cod liver oil remains one of the most concentrated dietary sources of vitamin D. Cheese and butter contribute smaller amounts but can support daily intake when eaten as part of a balanced diet. He cautions, “While food helps maintain levels, individuals with deficiency may still require medical supplementation after proper testing.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In a season when sunlight is limited, informed dietary planning and expert advice remain the most effective tools to safeguard long-term health. Both doctors stress that persistent bone pain, muscle cramps, fatigue, or frequent infections during winter should not be ignored. Dr Vaish concludes, “Timely screening, dietary correction, and guided supplementation can prevent long-term bone and joint complications.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Adding to this, Dr Rathi emphasises a preventive approach, stating, “Vitamin D deficiency is not just a bone issue - it impacts immunity, energy levels, and overall well-being.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Winter should be seen as a time to proactively support the body through nutrition, testing when required, and medical guidance rather than waiting for symptoms to appear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 01:31:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgJBVV95cUxOaHU3OFFESTVFZloyaTJSX1BGeHh2Mk9uQU1QSEl5QWhab2lIWktpNHkySkVmTXozVDNNTWJFZkxSak9yQ3RQMTZxbHhOOEUtaGJOdjRTbllqcHhyNnZjU0xsYk5TemRBNnQ2aW9CbEpKODNoWWN2czRyNmtnNTgxTjM2aGJqdzN6ckd2X20wRHhrcEltYzlmZF9GajV1MVdHVWFrUmxONHJmaDJoNmc4M2VjQlZIQWNxbnpDRDVwblFNbWdGN0M0MHBOZU40elZvYXBWajRMc2dfQ29mMV90dGNhVWd5NlNqb0R6Y2p5aE9UMlR0bng2RE9LMk1heEZubk5KY2xlVDRrdUswN000ZmhKYmxIQdIBmwJBVV95cUxNTkFVNWoyNEFIeU5scG5uajRRdlJVZWFiR29JNXJhQ3BGRjJnNFQ5NUlqVFJuemlyRjNWOFg0aHZWa0tPZkxhZU4tQTBxalFZWWZQMUFBT2t4QlV0d3dIMmNqRVBmMmNxUTFkdzFlQjBuSnA0Um5Kc1VGMDBPRE00c0VpTE1UUGp4Nl85UVpKa2tUTU15cl9aSVdaemx1U3JHaUdha0hrWk5LR3FNV2pRSlhqTzVxY1ptcU1WVmM2ME11dURCcTR2NFVvTE03WDlnYm1xb2dKcEdWaTQ5SjJQdmVMRVNwVnE3c04xTkJKblJBRFhCaG9SOTdrRWY2Y1pxVm1kYnlDeGoxcldheDFZTmtxQUh3QUFWalhV</guid></item><item><title>Mark Damon -频道3000</title><link>https://www.channel3000.com/obituaries/mark-damon/article_9c04abc2-5bc3-4bd5-a09e-ce8f100abfdb.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;Mark James Damon, age 61, passed away on Tuesday, December 9, 2025, at his home in Madison, Wisconsin. Mark was born on November 26, 1964, grew up in Stoughton, and attended LaFollette High School in Madison, graduating in 1984. Mark was a dedicated State of Wisconsin employee for over 35 years, delivering mail and pharmaceutical supplies throughout Central Wisconsin Center with courtesy, humor, and a movie-star smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Living with cerebral palsy that affected his arms and legs, Mark mastered the operation of a series of motorized wheelchairs outfitted with chin and foot controls for ignition, gear-shifting, and steering, and he pushed these vehicles to their limits. He had a strong bent for mechanics, an eagle eye for detail, and an unflagging enthusiasm for creative problem-solving. Generations of occupational, vocational, and social work professionals owe a debt of gratitude to Mark for being willing to experiment with new devices and systems such as a foot-controlled computer mouse and door openers; mouth-held tools for use with keyboards and dial pads; and voice-activated appliances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark was also a skilled instructor, patiently training countless aides and attendants on the intricacies of his assistive technology, as well as food preparation, household maintenance, and daily care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark was always up for adventure, exploring new trails and seeing where they might lead. Some favorite spots included Camp Wawbeek in Wisconsin Dells, his sister Bev’s house in Tacoma, Washington, and the annual Mad City Model Railroad Show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mark will be sorely missed: his kindness, intelligence, courage, humor, and friendship brought light and joy to the lives of many, many people. He was preceded in death by his loving foster parents, Ruth and Harry Kirby, and his dear friend Audrey. He leaves behind many foster brothers, sisters, nephews, and nieces; long-time friend and roommate Kevin Danz; and scores of other friends and colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many thanks are owed to the staff at Lakeview Supported Living Services, Community Work Services, FA, Inc., My Choice Wisconsin, UW Health, Unity Point Health – Meriter Hospital, and St. Croix Hospice for the care and support they provided to Mark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A memorial gathering for Mark will be held at Ryan Funeral Home, 2418 N. Sherman Drive, Madison, Wisconsin on Friday, January 9, from 4 to 6 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In lieu of flowers, donations in Mark’s memory may be made to one of Mark’s favorite organizations, Easterseals Wisconsin, to support Camp Wawbeek and Respite Camp, using their Online Giving Form | Easterseals Wisconsin or by mailing contributions to Easterseals Wisconsin at 1468 N. High Point Rd., Ste. 202, Middleton, WI 53562. To view his obituary and leave a memory, please visit: &lt;a href="https://www.ryanfuneralservice.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;www.ryanfuneralservice.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;​COPYRIGHT 2025 BY CHANNEL 3000. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. THIS MATERIAL MAY NOT BE PUBLISHED, BROADCAST, REWRITTEN OR REDISTRIBUTED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Channel 3000</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOZEdCREZxY2RsVk03VVZ1b25ydGM4NklaOFUtREJDQy1oYlpIakdGSkw1T2NmSVNSWTE5YlZOQm9JNTh4MnFyVnRfYzROWDk0OXJaQ3JkNXBNS1B6RjZtSkFndmNCc2ljMXdLVGlwc3N3Qk9NMk5YWHNENnRDRmJ4MlRKTlFMcG9GSUQyRXBaSFFKdzRWQTNpaGpfWWdSendl</guid></item><item><title>小鼠研究表明，挑鼻子与阿尔茨海默氏症有令人惊讶的联系- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/mouse-study-suggests-nose-picking-has-a-surprising-link-with-alzheimers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A study published in 2022 found a tenuous but plausible link between picking your nose and an increased risk of developing dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In cases where picking at your nose causes internal tissue damage, critical species of bacteria have a clearer path to the brain, which responds to their presence in ways that resemble signs of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="182682" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are numerous caveats here, not the least of which is that the supporting research so far is in mice rather than humans, but the findings are definitely worth further investigation – and could improve our understanding of how Alzheimer's disease starts, which remains something of a mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-simple-new-compound-reverses-alzheimers-symptoms-in-rats"&gt;Simple New Compound Reverses Alzheimer's Symptoms in Rats&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers led by scientists from Griffith University in Australia ran tests with a bacterium called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chlamydia_pneumoniae"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Chlamydia pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which can infect humans and cause  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pneumonia" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73057" data-postid="182682" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;pneumonia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;C. pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt; has &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s004300050071"&gt;also been discovered&lt;/a&gt; in the majority of human brains affected by late-onset dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video below has a summary of the study's findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was demonstrated that in mice, the bacteria could travel up the olfactory nerve (joining the nasal cavity and the brain).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, when there was damage to the nasal epithelium (the thin tissue along the roof of the nasal cavity), nerve infections got worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This led to the mouse brains depositing more of the amyloid-beta protein – a protein that is released in response to infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plaques (or clumps) of this protein are also found in significant concentrations in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-shows-how-alzheimer-s-causes-cells-to-overheat-and-fry-like-eggs"&gt;people with Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We're the first to show that &lt;em&gt;Chlamydia pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt; can go directly up the nose and into the brain where it can set off pathologies that look like Alzheimer's disease," &lt;a href="https://news.griffith.edu.au/2022/10/28/new-research-suggests-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-for-alzheimers-and-dementia/"&gt;said neuroscientist James St John&lt;/a&gt; from Griffith University in Australia, when the study was published in October 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We saw this happen in a mouse model, and the evidence is potentially scary for humans as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists were surprised by the speed at which &lt;em&gt;C. pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt; took hold in the central nervous system of the mice, with infection happening within 24 to 72 hours. It's thought that bacteria and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="182682" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt; see the nose as a quick route to the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it's not certain that the effects will be the same in humans, or even that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/researchers-have-a-new-theory-about-what-causes-alzheimers-and-its-not-plaque"&gt;amyloid-beta plaques are a cause of Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, it's nevertheless important to follow up promising leads in the fight to understand this common neurodegenerative condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_148468" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-148468" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/amyloid_plaques_642.jpg" alt="Mouse Study Suggests Surprising Link Between Alzheimer's And Nose-Picking" class="wp-image-148468 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/amyloid_plaques_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/amyloid_plaques_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-148468" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustration of amyloid-beta protein plaques, in orange. (&lt;a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/nihgov/38686503251"&gt;NIH/Flickr/PD&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to do this study in humans and confirm whether the same pathway operates in the same way," &lt;a href="https://news.griffith.edu.au/2022/10/28/new-research-suggests-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-for-alzheimers-and-dementia/"&gt;said St John&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's research that has been proposed by many people, but not yet completed. What we do know is that these same bacteria are present in humans, but we haven't worked out how they get there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/nasal-spray-may-slow-alzheimers-disease-study-in-mice-suggests"&gt;Nasal Spray May Slow Alzheimer's Disease, Study in Mice Suggests&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nose picking isn't exactly a rare thing. In fact, it's possible &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/nose-picking"&gt;as many as 9 out of 10 people&lt;/a&gt; do it… not to mention a bunch of other species (&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/weve-caught-aye-aye-using-its-wacky-long-finger-for-something-pretty-gnarly"&gt;some a little more adept&lt;/a&gt; than others).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the benefits aren't clear, studies like this one should give us pause before picking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future studies into the same processes in humans are planned – but until then, St John and his colleagues suggest that picking your nose and plucking your nose hair is "not a good idea" because of the potential damage it does to protective nose tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We don't want to damage the inside of our nose and picking and plucking can do that," &lt;a href="https://news.griffith.edu.au/2022/10/28/new-research-suggests-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-for-alzheimers-and-dementia/"&gt;warned St John&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you damage the lining of the nose, you can increase how many bacteria can go up into your brain."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_148469" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-148469" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/child_picking_nose_642.jpg" alt="child picking their nose" class="wp-image-148469 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/child_picking_nose_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/01/child_picking_nose_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-148469" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Nose picking: not just a habit for small children. (&lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/photos/kid-fruit-nose-picking-picnic-6589472/"&gt;Jupi Lu/Pixabay&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;One outstanding question that the team will be looking to answer is whether or not the increased amyloid-beta protein deposits are a natural, healthy immune response that can be reversed when the infection is fought off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-reveal-how-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-of-alzheimers"&gt;A 2024 review further advanced the hypothesis&lt;/a&gt; that nose picking could play a role in increasing the risk of developing Alzheimer's disease – revealing more about how the process could unfold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-cause-of-alzheimers-may-be-coming-from-within-your-mouth"&gt;The Cause of Alzheimer's May Be Coming From Within Your Mouth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer's is an incredibly complicated disease, as is clear from the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-might-not-actually-be-a-brain-disease-expert-says"&gt;sheer number of studies&lt;/a&gt; into it and the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-have-identified-four-distinct-types-of-alzheimer-s"&gt;many different angles&lt;/a&gt; scientists are taking in trying to understand it – but each piece of research brings us a little bit closer to finding a way to stop it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Once you get over 65 years old, your risk factor goes right up, but we're looking at other causes as well, because it's not just age – it is environmental exposure as well," &lt;a href="https://news.griffith.edu.au/2022/10/28/new-research-suggests-nose-picking-could-increase-risk-for-alzheimers-and-dementia/"&gt;said St John&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And we think that bacteria and viruses are critical."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-022-06749-9"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Scientific Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in November 2022.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:22:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxQMy02dnBUVmVOWWhrcWp5cWpTanpiNVJoaDJ6aVp0SFBnY0lpSGxvSklNSW1oTzd0eDRQZXlpYnZPXzZIalZydXR6aUJNU2hvWWxobGpLUVdhdkYyU0Y4Tks1dG12MU5NR1BkQWYzZ2VkbmxqZkthbWMwWFo2NmQ4emp2eXFySk1rRm81YVliVVh1VXUza0Z1QzRPN3ZOcUpsTUE</guid></item><item><title>ADHD药物间接提高注意力- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/24/nx-s1-5651878/adhd-drugs-work-indirectly-to-improve-attention</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;New research suggests that prescription stimulants for ADHD don't actually improve attention directly. They work on different pathways in the brain that support attention.
.&lt;/p&gt;   
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="transcript storytext" aria-label="Transcript"&gt;
    &lt;b class="icn-story-transcript-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;b class="icn-story-transcript"&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/b&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUANA SUMMERS, HOST: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Scientists are changing their view of how drugs like Adderall and Ritalin help children with ADHD stay on task. NPR's Jon Hamilton reports on a new study that found the drugs act on brain networks involved in alertness and reward but not attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;JON HAMILTON, BYLINE: About 3.5 million children in the U.S. take stimulants for attention deficit hyperactivity disorder, or ADHD. Dr. Benjamin Kay, of Washington University in St. Louis, says he finds it puzzling that these drugs actually work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BENJAMIN KAY: If we're treating predominantly hyperactivity, why would a drug that wakes you up more help with that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: So Kay, a pediatric neurologist, jumped at the chance to study how these stimulants affect a child's brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAY: This was a really personal paper for me because I prescribe these medications all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: Kay was part of a team that reviewed data from a government study that includes brain scans of nearly 12,000 adolescents. About 4% had ADHD, and nearly half of those children were on a prescription stimulant. Kay says that allowed the team to see which brain areas were affected by the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAY: What I expected to find was that the stimulants would act on the parts of the brain that modulate attention. What I actually found was that those were the parts of the brain that were least affected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: Instead, the drugs stimulated brain areas that help us stay awake and alert. They also activated areas that anticipate a pleasurable reward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAY: We really think it's a combination of both arousal and reward - that kind of one-two punch - that really, really helps kids with ADHD when they take this medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: The first punch involves norepinephrine, which prepares the body and brain for action. The study found that this response could counteract the effects of sleep deprivation, a common problem in children with ADHD. Dr. Nico Dosenbach, a coauthor of the study, says the second punch seems to help kids overcome another common problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NICO DOSENBACH: They're looking at some kind of homework and their brain goes, this is going to be terrible. This is going to be boring. I don't like this, and then you can't stick with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: Dosenbach says ADHD drugs seem to limit this negative response by boosting levels of dopamine, a brain chemical that influences motivation and pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DOSENBACH: It can make you more tolerant because you're feeling a slight sort of low-level, low-key reward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: Dosenbach says dopamine may also explain why children with ADHD can sit still and focus on an activity that they do find rewarding. He says this behavior even led one dad to conclude that his son was faking ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DOSENBACH: He was like, well, when I take him hunting, he can sit in a high stand all day long without moving a muscle. But in school, he's bouncing off the walls and leaving the classroom and wandering off the premises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: Dosenbach suspects hunting simply produced enough dopamine to offset the boy's hyperactivity. The findings appear in the journal, Cell. Neuroscientist Peter Manza, of the University of Maryland, says they show how ADHD researchers are moving away from the idea that stimulants directly improve attention. He says his own work suggests that stimulants are boosting motivation in kids with ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETER MANZA: They don't find math problems very interesting, but after a dose of Ritalin it might seem more interesting to them, and so they're willing to persist and finish the task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: Manza says the study also suggests that brain scans might eventually offer a way to confirm that a child has ADHD and will benefit from drug treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANZA: Stimulants don't work for everyone, and so we need to better target the individuals who need them and not unnecessarily prescribe them to the individuals who don't need them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: That's a growing concern as stimulant prescriptions continue to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jon Hamilton, NPR News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(SOUNDBITE OF DELICATE STEVE'S "PEACHES")&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="disclaimer"&gt;Copyright © 2025 NPR.  All rights reserved.  Visit our website &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/about-npr/179876898/terms-of-use"&gt;terms of use&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/about-npr/179881519/rights-and-permissions-information"&gt;permissions&lt;/a&gt; pages at &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org"&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/a&gt; for further information.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="disclaimer"&gt;
        Accuracy and availability of NPR transcripts may vary. Transcript text may be revised to correct errors or match updates to audio. Audio on npr.org may be edited after its original broadcast or publication. The authoritative record of NPR’s programming is the audio record.
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 22:21:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPYjNzR1Y2VWd6S09saEsyQnVuaE00X1YxVnVBRzYyazBtQ0ltdU5WbG0xRUxZU01FZDlTbjloaWQ5dWRKZjJjam5YVktzWnZGWFpmbjJ0bktEQ2t2MlphRHVwLVFHS2phRzhPVUxHMGZ2VjNfXzhxNHR3QlplYmZBNzcteF9fczNnVzEzZndjLUE1Ym1MS2JJ</guid></item><item><title>新泽西州帕特森圣约瑟夫大学医学中心的第二名患者感染军团菌死亡- ABC7纽约</title><link>https://abc7ny.com/post/second-patient-st-josephs-university-medical-center-paterson-nj-infected-legionella-dies/18312962/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;PATERSON, New Jersey (WABC) -- &lt;/span&gt;A second patient at a hospital in Passaic County, New Jersey who tested positive for the bacteria that causes Legionnaires' disease has died, health officials announced Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The patient was being treated at St. Joseph's University Medical Center in Paterson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Two weeks ago, the hospital confirmed that another patient who died after being treated for "multiple medical conditions" in July had also tested positive for Legionella, the bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Both patients had significant underlying health conditions, according to the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The patient faced significant underlying health challenges, as was the case of the earlier individual who tested positive while receiving treatment. Our thoughts remain with their families and loved ones during this difficult time," the hospital said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The first patient's death prompted a state health investigation into the hospital's water system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;On November 18, state testing results revealed there was Legionella in the water supply of one of the contained areas of the hospital. St. Joseph's University Medical Center was subsequently notified on December 8 and began cleaning and treating its water system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;At least 228 former patients who were treated and discharged from that area of the hospital between November 27 and December 8 were notified about the potential risk of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Officials say symptoms of Legionnaires' disease are similar to other respiratory illnesses and can include cough, muscle aches, fever, shortness of breath and headache. Less common symptoms can include diarrhea, nausea, or confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;----------&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;*&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/newsletters/" target="_blank"&gt; Get Eyewitness News Delivered&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;*  &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/manhattan/" target="_blank"&gt;More Manhattan news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://7ny.tv/submitnewstip" target="_blank"&gt;Send us a news tip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/apps/" target="_blank"&gt;Download the abc7NY app for breaking news alerts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;*&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCrlIS7z20CnVaCrMvdkig_g" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt; Follow us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="RxNCg ykkUm PvZ nIjPJ PMXYp LmsHF SfAHY mNgye lNbol LBPRq rBLIK "&gt;Submit a tip or story idea to Eyewitness News&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Have a breaking news tip or an idea for a story we should cover? Send it to Eyewitness News using the form below.    If attaching a video or photo, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/image-video-solicitation-and-rights-terms-of-use/5101040/" target="_blank"&gt;terms of use apply.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WABC-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 New York</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:56:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxPVzF6ekRWM2NLamk5OFpHbVVDS2xyckI3UUpFcjdrLWk5SDVHLURNd0VoOHB5TEs1eEwzSUU0TjBRZHRsaUFFb1RFZHd2UnNJSTVPT0xsVFd6TGh5TVdlTlRxWmFMbUJldEt3U09xa28tbE90ZkZUTHpmQ2x5MXctaE1Ta0I4RjBzWk9STzRtamZ0R2stcFpxazgzUEQ5dmwtM0o4UVB4OV8yVnRDVXRNYWJQcnVtX2RsYXFqOGJMQdIBxAFBVV95cUxNUXh3WWxmbkJJRmdqOGYwMll3MG9oUW9sX0lGX09YRzVRYzBmY3BjRHhuZDBsLVQ1SDRGdWxocG5NdjZGcXE5NGxNSFJPWlB4RmNMUnQ1LWtaZ0lrM2xPSk9nZkN6dVNycGEtcDdQM0NwVjRQQnVWOHhVcjQwcEtTSWFfV0JYNkpORXdjT2xZYWltcDBsekhKRG9ZcWpaSHNSSVY0V3ZjTnlEdmgxank2d0x1cEhBdVlkZ1FJVFVERldwT0Vk</guid></item><item><title>艰难的爱：我是否与我的反Vax兄弟断绝了联系？ -新闻自由</title><link>https://www.thefp.com/p/tough-love-do-i-sever-ties-with-my</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div dir="auto" class="body markup"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Welcome back to Tough Love with Abigail Shrier, the new advice column from The Free Press! Every Thursday, our contributing editor will address your conundrums, with no hesitation and no sugarcoating—just straight-up Tough Love. This week, Abigail answers a question from Julia (that’s not her real name), who’s considering severing ties with her brother because he won’t vaccinate his kids. To receive Tough Love directly in your inbox, every week, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thefp.com/s/tough-love-with-abigail-shrier" rel&gt;sign up here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dear Abigail,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I’m struggling with a painful family dilemma and I don’t know what’s left to try. My brother and his wife refuse to vaccinate their children—unless they’re forced to, like when their kids were kicked out of school for being unvaccinated, specifically for not having the measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) jab. We’ve tried to be nonjudgmental in our questions and suggested compromises on ways we can interact, but every conversation feels like we’re speaking different languages.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is part of a broader pattern of unsafe choices that make it hard to spend time together. My brother and his wife have driven more than once on the highway without putting their infant in a car seat because “he cries too much.” They also brought their kids, who had fevers, to our 100-year-old grandfather’s birthday party. Moments like these leave me feeling anxious, angry, and unsure whether I can trust them around my own family (I have three young children).&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I love my brother, and I’ve always believed family should matter. But the disconnect in our values and basic safety standards feels enormous, and I’m starting to wonder if the healthiest choice is to step back. We don’t have a cool uncle willing to intervene; otherwise, I would go that route. So what do I do? Do I sever ties? Should I keep trying to reconcile or is it okay to accept that not all relationships can be fixed?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;How do I navigate the guilt, the love, and the need to protect my own family?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Julia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Julia,&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first time I lost my little brother, he was 4. We were in our local Lord &amp;amp; Taylor, where he’d crept inside a fountain of racked clothing and ducked down so I wouldn’t see him. I tore through the racks, crying his name, until I found him smiling, thinking he had won this round of hide-and-seek.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Free Press</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 21:43:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE5xbWQ2a3R1ZGNjUzNwaFpRcWVXRDMzZkwzNFBhVFRsNzJGaEtyMFQteVBJb0prZzgzdVZkS0R0R3hkNndCaTVwODU5aHNFaVdJNkE4LUw1UWVKakFvdlplQ2xEd0MyVE9iSUE</guid></item><item><title>波士顿、威斯特伯勒可能有麻疹暴露，官员警告-《波士顿环球报》</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/24/metro/massachusetts-measles-alert/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The Massachusetts Department of Public Health is working with the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and local partners to identify and notify those who may have been exposed, officials said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Measles is a highly contagious, airborne disease, which has increased significantly in the United States because of the unfortunate decrease in vaccination rates. It is also a preventable disease,” Public Health Commissioner Dr. Robbie Goldstein said in a statement. “This current situation serves as an important reminder of the critical role vaccination plays in protecting our communities.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;While Massachusetts has not had a measles case this year, the United States has seen the highest number of nationwide cases in more than a decade – nearly 2,000 in 44 jurisdictions, which included three confirmed deaths from measles, Goldstein said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Fifteen years ago, measles had been considered eliminated in the United States, but that tremendous progress is at risk,” Goldstein said. “Vaccines are one of the most important public health interventions ever – they are safe, effective, and lifesaving.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Officials said the exposures may have occurred at Logan Airport Terminal B on Dec. 11 from 2:30 p.m. to 4:45 p.m.; at the DoubleTree hotel in Westborough from 3:30 p.m. on Dec. 11 to 9 p.m. on Dec. 12; and at Logan Airport Terminal C from 6 p.m. to 11:30 p.m. on Dec. 12.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Those who could have been exposed and begin to develop symptoms of measles should call their healthcare provider before visiting an office, clinic, or emergency department,” public health officials said in the statement. “Visiting a healthcare facility may put others at risk and should be avoided if possible.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Those who have had measles in the past or have received two doses of the Measles, Mumps, and Rubella (MMR) vaccine are unlikely to develop measles even if they were exposed, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Boston Public Health Commissioner Dr. Bisola Ojikutu also encouraged people to get vaccinated for measles.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“With multiple measles outbreaks across the country and increased travel around the holidays, now is an important time to ensure that you and your family are protected,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Ojikutu said two doses of MMR vaccine are 97 percent effective at preventing measles and provide protection against mumps and rubella. Children should receive the vaccine at 12-15 months of age and again before kindergarten, she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Children who are at least 6 months old and traveling internationally or to areas of the US with active outbreaks should receive an early dose of vaccine before traveling, Ojikutu said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It is never too late for children or adults to get the measles vaccine even if they are past the recommended age,” Ojikutu said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Early symptoms of measles occur one to three weeks after exposure and may resemble a cold, with symptoms fever, cough, runny nose, and red eyes. A rash occurs on the skin two to four days after the initial symptoms develop and usually appears first on the head, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;People with measles may be contagious up to four days before the rash appears and for four days after the rash starts, officials said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;State public health officials are urging anyone who has not been vaccinated or doesn’t know their measles immunization status to contact their healthcare provider to get vaccinated with at least one dose of the MMR vaccine. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Measles vaccine given within 72 hours of exposure may prevent measles disease,” officials said in the statement. “Vaccination beyond this window will provide protection from subsequent exposures.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Emily Sweeney can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:emily.sweeney@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;emily.sweeney@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;. Follow her &lt;a href="https://www.twitter.com/emilysweeney" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@emilysweeney&lt;/a&gt; and on Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/emilysweeney22" class="" target="_blank"&gt;@emilysweeney22&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 19:48:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE1OeVREUmk0Rl94TFdHYUFmSEJvazZtQUp6Rm5Rc1NZU2ZmUHFTMlUwcm1PWWQtX3NNS041TEpzR3dUQktKazZYMlgwT21tUnhsNlR5V21pdDVJTzk0NTJIV2hwSGw1dkxpZV9Fa2cxREotdFB5ZWhaam1SdFYzQQ</guid></item><item><title>心脑连接：国际研究揭示迷走神经在保持心脏年轻方面的作用- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-heart-brain-international-reveals-role.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 19:48:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNUW11ejRfd1hkeG1sNUM0SFJDV0l4eE1iMTU2bjZJRWZmR2tsZS1QZTlKaHQwU2FYSWpjcU5VZ0FVVWM0OTVydkFsNVFFVHdxSl9YMVlnN002NTBKdGE3a3ZNU3lKTmdsclMwRnN1MXJrb2RsY0l6T0t5eFhWWUo0Z01WeGNHV3NDSVE</guid></item><item><title>科学家意外地在实验室中创造了一种新材料，从而发现黄金是一种“反应性金属” - Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/discovery-that-gold-is-reactive-metal-by-creating-gold-hydride-in-lab-experiment/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a high-pressure lab experiment, scientists accidentally created a new compound called gold hydride. This particular hydride formed when thin gold foil met dense hydrogen at pressures hundreds of thousands of times Earth’s atmosphere and blazing temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The discovery challenges gold’s reputation as a nearly inert metal and shows how extreme conditions can push familiar materials into unfamiliar forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By creating &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/hunan-geologists-discover-a-deposit-of-more-than-1000-tons-of-gold/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; hydride in the lab, researchers opened a way to study dense hydrogen like that inside giant planets and fusing stars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-creating-gold-hydride"&gt;Creating gold hydride&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work was led by Mungo Frost, a staff scientist at Stanford Linear Accelerator Center (&lt;a href="https://www6.slac.stanford.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;SLAC&lt;/a&gt;) whose research probes materials under extreme pressures and temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold is usually chosen for experiments like this because it barely reacts, serving as a passive X ray absorber that heats surrounding material.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold was expected to remain inert during the experiment, since it is normally chemically unreactive and is routinely used as an X-ray absorber for that reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That accidental reaction produced the first confirmed solid compound made solely of gold and hydrogen atoms in any laboratory experiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-lab-built-to-study-diamonds"&gt;Lab built to study diamonds&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experiment was originally designed to clock how long simple hydrocarbons take to turn into diamond under crushing pressure and searing heat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers squeezed tiny drops of hydrocarbon between the tips of a diamond anvil cell, a device that traps samples at immense static pressures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laser heating inside such cells lets scientists study materials at extreme pressures, as shown in a recent &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2504-4494/6/5/111" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; of diamond anvil work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the &lt;a href="https://www.xfel.eu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;European XFEL&lt;/a&gt; in Germany, X-ray pulses hit a thin &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/metal-detectorist-finds-the-oldest-celtic-gold-coin-ever-recorded/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; foil in the sample, which then heated the surrounding hydrocarbons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team cranked the pressure until it rivaled Earth’s lower mantle, then blasted the sample with trains of X-ray pulses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under those conditions, the study reports gold hydride forming at temperatures above 3,500 degrees Fahrenheit and at pressures far beyond &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/geologists-found-gigantic-fortresses-deep-beneath-the-earths-crust-in-the-mantle/"&gt;Earth’s mantle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;X-ray scattering patterns confirmed that carbon atoms snapped into the tidy &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/doped-diamonds-discovery-may-reshape-quantum-computing/"&gt;lattice of diamond&lt;/a&gt;, matching what the researchers expected from earlier work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signals in the data revealed hydrogen atoms entering the gold lattice, forming gold hydride that altered how the metal scattered X-rays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-gold-hydride-and-planet-formation"&gt;Gold hydride and planet formation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under pressure and heat, hydrogen became superionic, a state where atoms move like a liquid inside a solid, making the gold hydride conductive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hydrogen usually barely scatters X-rays, so the team watched changes in the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/man-with-a-cheap-metal-detector-finds-a-huge-piece-of-gold/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; lattice to deduce how the light atoms were moving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simulations and measurements indicate that hydrogen diffuses rapidly through the hexagonal gold lattice at high temperature but separates when the sample cools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interior &lt;a href="https://agupubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/2016JE005080" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;models&lt;/a&gt; of Jupiter suggest a shell of metallic hydrogen surrounding a dense core, with pressures beyond anything on Earth’s surface.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In those environments, hydrogen is compressed so tightly that it behaves more like a dense, electrically conducting fluid than a simple gas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent &lt;a href="https://link.aps.org/doi/10.1103/PhysRevLett.128.035702" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; has shown that superionic states in silica water and silica hydrogen mixtures could help explain magnetic fields in giant planets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold hydride offers a controlled environment where dense hydrogen’s structure and motion can be measured, giving theorists a clearer target for planetary calculations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-new-lens-on-fusion-research"&gt;New lens on fusion research&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stars like the Sun shine because gravity squeezes hydrogen until nuclei fuse, and fusion researchers try to recreate conditions in experiments on Earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Accurate models of dense hydrogen, hydrogen compressed to extraordinary pressures and densities, are vital for understanding fusion fuel behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simulations indicate that even small uncertainties in hydrogen’s behavior at high-density can significantly change fusion predictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By pinning how hydrogen moves through gold at given pressures and temperatures, the measurements give fusion modelers a benchmark to test their calculations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In everyday chemistry, gold is grouped with the noble metals that rarely form compounds, which is why jewelry stays bright for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In these experiments, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-discover-how-gold-reaches-earths-surface-from-the-mantle/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; formed a hydride that held more hydrogen as pressure climbed, yet separated into plain gold again when conditions eased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings indicate that extreme pressure and heat can enable forms of chemistry that do not occur under normal conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High pressure work has shown unreactive elements like xenon can form compounds, so gold hydride underscores how chemistry changes when matter is squeezed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-high-tech-machines"&gt;High tech machines&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experiments relied on the European XFEL, a powerful X-ray laser facility that delivers thousands of pulses each second to targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those pulses deposit energy in the gold foil, allowing scientists to heat the sample rapidly while the diamond-anvil cell maintains the pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High-energy-density science, the study of matter under extreme pressures and temperatures, uses intense X-ray lasers together with diamond anvil cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As these tools improve, from tougher diamond anvils to brighter X-ray sources, researchers can probe states of matter once considered purely theoretical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-gold-hydrides-and-other-exotic-phases"&gt;Gold hydrides and other exotic phases&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/proposed-highway-route-went-through-a-lost-celtic-town-full-of-gold-silver-and-amber/"&gt;Gold&lt;/a&gt; hydride joins a catalog of exotic phases, including superionic water and silica compounds, that appear only when atoms are squeezed and heated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of these phases vanish once pressure or temperature drops, yet their existence helps explain how planets move heat and generate magnetic fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because hydrides of other metals already show properties like superconductivity, understanding gold hydride could one day help design new electronic materials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold hydride’s appearance under stress shows that even familiar elements in lab samples can behave unexpectedly when scientists push conditions beyond normal experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-lessons-from-gold-hydride"&gt;Lessons from gold hydride&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The simulation framework that captured superionic hydrogen in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/metal-detectorist-finds-the-oldest-celtic-gold-coin-ever-recorded/"&gt;gold&lt;/a&gt; can predict how other elements behave when infused with hydrogen at different pressures and temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future experiments can swap gold for other metals or mixtures that resemble planetary materials more closely, letting researchers test whether strange hydrides emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each compound uncovered at such extremes expands the periodic table of high-pressure phases and clarifies how ordinary elements behave when pushed hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40755070/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;National Library of Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:33:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxQSUJBc0pWVTR1WmF6TDdDcnlGRjU0eFppYW8ya1drQlRsRUduQVRhaERrTWYxaVotT0k1MmpVYkdoMFJpSThaRkcwYW00VmFXN1R1bG5iSzJUOUZPa21RejFGSTdYQnlXNWNoYTNmeTQ3Vm5VN0poaE13V0RQOG5jcnRzUHBsb2FGakxGY2pOQ3pSTGRxLXJEcVFTczcxZlNOWnk5SmlVeWh2QUxv</guid></item><item><title>复活的组织：在广泛损伤后实现再生的机制解决了一个有50年历史的谜团- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2025-12-resurrected-tissue-mechanism-enables-regeneration.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 18:30:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxNUkpNS2xPVjZYVTVxWlVhdnJXMEQ3c3hvTkVNdWV3Zmwyamcya0d1OVlTdE5sNGZGc2RfUzd5Q3NJQ1FKQWo3RUJ3Q29xZkxLTzdsR2NHQzZ4VFFuNTB1cWlGOTNkWnNQVmRrR0ZiMFRuSlc4OFhYZjRTRG43clN2ZExiQ0tiaHl2dksxeA</guid></item><item><title>常见ADHD药物的功能与科学家此前认为的不同- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/common-adhd-medications-function-differently-than-scientists-previously-thought/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prescription stimulants are among the most widely used psychiatric medications in the world. For decades, the prevailing medical consensus held that drugs like methylphenidate treat attention deficit hyperactivity disorder by targeting the brain’s executive control centers. A new study challenges this long-held dogma, revealing that these medications act primarily on neural networks responsible for wakefulness and reward rather than attention. The study was published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical textbooks have traditionally taught that stimulants function by enhancing activity in the prefrontal cortex. This region of the brain is often associated with voluntary control, planning, and the direction of focus. The assumption was that by boosting activity in these circuits, the drugs allowed patients to filter out distractions and maintain concentration on specific tasks. However, the precise neural mechanisms have remained a subject of debate among neuroscientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier research into these medications often produced inconsistent results. Some studies suggested that stimulants improved motivation and reaction times rather than higher-level reasoning. Furthermore, behavioral experiments have shown that the drugs do not universally improve performance. They tend to help individuals who are performing poorly but offer little benefit to those who are already performing well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To resolve these discrepancies, a research team led by neurologist Benjamin P. Kay at Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis undertook a massive analysis of brain activity. Working with senior author Nico U.F. Dosenbach, Kay aimed to map the effects of stimulants across the entire brain without restricting their focus to pre-determined areas. They sought to understand which specific brain networks were most altered when a child took these medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers utilized data from the Adolescent Brain Cognitive Development Study. This large-scale project tracks the biological and psychological development of thousands of children across the United States. The team selected functional magnetic resonance imaging scans from 5,795 children between the ages of eight and eleven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kay and his colleagues compared the brain scans of children who had taken prescription stimulants on the day of their MRI against those who had not. They employed a technique known as resting-state functional connectivity. This method measures how different regions of the brain communicate and synchronize with one another when the person is not performing a specific task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis did not rely on small, isolated samples. The researchers used a data-driven approach to look at the whole connectome, which is the complete map of neural connections in the brain. They controlled for various factors that could skew the results, such as head motion during the scan and socioeconomic status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings contradicted the traditional “attention-centric” view of stimulant medication. The researchers observed no statistical difference in the functional connectivity of the dorsal or ventral attention networks. The drugs also did not produce measurable changes in the frontoparietal control network, which is usually linked to complex problem-solving.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, the most substantial changes occurred in the sensorimotor cortex and the salience network. The sensorimotor cortex is traditionally associated with physical movement and sensation. However, recent discoveries suggest this area also plays a major role in regulating the body’s overall arousal and wakefulness levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The salience network is responsible for determining what is important in the environment. It helps the brain calculate the value of a task and decides whether an action is worth the effort. The study found that stimulants increased connectivity between these reward-processing regions and the motor systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This shift in connectivity suggests that the drugs work by altering the brain’s calculation of effort and reward. By boosting activity in the salience network, the medication makes tedious activities feel more rewarding than they otherwise would. This reduces the urge to switch tasks or seek stimulation elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Essentially, we found that stimulants pre-reward our brains and allow us to keep working at things that wouldn’t normally hold our interest — like our least favorite class in school, for example,” Dosenbach said. This explains the paradox of why a stimulant can help a hyperactive child sit still. The drug removes the biological drive to fidget by satisfying the brain’s need for reward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To verify that these findings were not an artifact of the pediatric data, the team conducted a separate validation study. They recruited five healthy adults who did not have attention deficits. These volunteers underwent repeated brain scans before and after taking a controlled dose of methylphenidate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results from the adult trial mirrored the findings in the children. The medication consistently altered the arousal and reward networks while leaving the attention networks largely unchanged. This replication in a controlled setting provides strong evidence that the drugs act on basic physiological drivers of behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also uncovered a distinct relationship between stimulant medication and sleep. The researchers compared the brain patterns of medicated children to those of children who reported getting a full night of sleep. The functional connectivity signatures were remarkably similar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stimulants appeared to mimic the neurological effects of being well-rested. Children who were sleep-deprived showed specific disruptions in their sensorimotor and arousal networks. When sleep-deprived children took a stimulant, those disruptions disappeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This “rescue” effect extended to cognitive performance as well. The researchers analyzed school grades and test scores for the children in the study. As expected, children with attention deficits performed better when taking medication. However, the data revealed a nuance regarding sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stimulants improved the grades and test scores of children who did not get enough sleep. In fact, the medication raised the performance of sleep-deprived children to the level of their well-rested peers. Conversely, for children who did not have attention deficits and already got sufficient sleep, the drugs provided no statistical benefit to performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We saw that if a participant didn’t sleep enough, but they took a stimulant, the brain signature of insufficient sleep was erased, as were the associated behavioral and cognitive decrements,” Dosenbach noted. The medication effectively masked the neural and behavioral symptoms of fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This finding raises important questions about the use of stimulants as performance enhancers. The data suggests that the drugs do not make a well-rested brain smarter or more attentive. They simply counteract the drag of fatigue and lack of motivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors of the study advise caution regarding this sleep-masking effect. While the drugs can hide the immediate signs of sleep deprivation, they do not replace the biological necessity of sleep. Chronic sleep loss is linked to cellular stress, metabolic issues, and other long-term health consequences that stimulants cannot fix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kay highlighted the clinical implications of these findings for doctors and parents. Symptoms of sleep deprivation often mimic the symptoms of attention deficit hyperactivity disorder, including lack of focus and irritability. Treating a sleep-deprived child with stimulants might mask the root cause of their struggles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Not getting enough sleep is always bad for you, and it’s especially bad for kids,” Kay said. He suggested that clinicians should screen for sleep disturbances before prescribing these medications. It is possible that some children diagnosed with attention deficits are actually suffering from chronic exhaustion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also provides a new framework for understanding the brain’s motor cortex. The researchers noted that the changes in the motor system align with the recently discovered Somato-Cognitive Action Network. This network integrates body control with planning and arousal, further cementing the link between movement and alertness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research will need to investigate the long-term effects of using stimulants to override sleep signals. The current study looked at a snapshot in time, but the cumulative impact of masking fatigue over years remains unknown. The researchers also hope to explore whether these arousal mechanisms differ in various subtypes of attention disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By shifting the focus from attention to arousal and reward, this research fundamentally alters the understanding of how psychostimulants function. It suggests that these drugs are not “smart pills” that boost intelligence. Instead, they are endurance tools that help the brain maintain effort and wakefulness in the face of boredom or fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X"&gt;Stimulant medications affect arousal and reward, not attention&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Benjamin P. Kay, Muriah D. Wheelock, Joshua S. Siegel, Ryan Raut, Roselyne J. Chauvin, Athanasia Metoki, Aishwarya Rajesh, Andrew Eck, Jim Pollaro, Anxu Wang, Vahdeta Suljic, Babatunde Adeyemo, Noah J. Baden, Kristen M. Scheidter, Julia Monk, Nadeshka Ramirez-Perez, Samuel R. Krimmel, Russel T. Shinohara, Brenden Tervo-Clemmens, Robert J. M. Hermosillo, Steven M. Nelson, Timothy J. Hendrickson, Thomas Madison, Lucille A. Moore, Óscar Miranda-Domínguez, Anita Randolph, Eric Feczko, Jarod L. Roland, Ginger E. Nicol, Timothy O. Laumann, Scott Marek, Evan M. Gordon, Marcus E. Raichle, Deanna M. Barch, Damien A. Fair, and Nico U.F. Dosenbach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 17:36:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPZ1R2R1llaDlFNXQwT01hdmxjWlpqLURNV1JvTVF5V0dLYXIzZUtaYVhMUVVacGhqVGQzaExBUjZ6NS1BX0syYUhBbjA4cGlZZm1DOVRCQjJrdWU1amgyV1ZIdVJEUVZfWnM2V1FnNzdRZERfY1MxUkRpT2diczI4ajBOcmp2aTdaQTM4M1UwaGlZcHV6cVgtaVZsYWkwXzFNOC1MUDE3Yw</guid></item></channel></rss>