<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>茶或咖啡对骨骼有益吗？ -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/24/tea-coffee-bones-osteoporosis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FYE4SUEE6ZGADAZEGNJFJ6UEIE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Both &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/interactive/2022/coffee-vs-tea-nutrition-health/" target="_blank"&gt;tea and coffee&lt;/a&gt; have various health benefits, but tea may come out slightly on top when it comes to the health of your bones, a recent study suggests. And too much coffee — five or more cups a day — might have a negative effect on your bone health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:31:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOV1dUVWVUNmtrX1FHUXlBSFpsV090Vndyc2NwT1hDT1FkR1ppRXg3S0hWdUxZanpSWFFqMV9fOHktcmJJVjZDcS1KVVFUWEZDd2RaT1ZGRkpoZFNHQklDajdGbVNGWWRRaFE1OXIxa1NCREV6UkdrNXBMcHVIWGdfV21EWTQwRGY3</guid></item><item><title>随着疫苗接种率下降，医生担心破伤风病例会上升- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/tetanus-cases-rise-vaccine-rates-down-dtap-children-shots-rcna244685</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-979779" class="body-graf"&gt;Doctors are worried about even a small uptick in the terrible infection, often called lockjaw. Symptoms, which can take &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/tetanus/hcp/clinical-overview/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;three to 21 days to appear&lt;/a&gt;, include muscle spasms that make it difficult to breathe. As the infection takes hold, a patient’s jaw clenches, forcing the face into what appears to be a wide smile, and the back muscles contort into a painful arch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6f7325" class="body-graf"&gt;“It looks terrible,” said Dr. Mobeen Rathore, chief of pediatric infectious diseases and immunology at the University of Florida College of Medicine-Jacksonville.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5f8dc7" class="body-graf"&gt;Tetanus bacteria live in soil and manure. An infection can occur from a puncture wound, and the disease can persist through weeks of medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fae9cf" class="body-graf"&gt;Treatment can be arduous and costly. A 6-year-old &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/unvaccinated-boy-almost-died-tetanus-hospital-bill-was-more-800-n981256" target="_blank"&gt;unvaccinated boy in Oregon&lt;/a&gt; racked up almost $1 million in medical bills after he contracted tetanus in 2019, according to a Centers for Disease Control and Prevention case report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-eb11cd" class="body-graf"&gt;Rathore compared the cost of vaccines to the cost of intensive care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7f9aac" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s not even pennies to dollars; it’s pennies to hundreds of thousands of dollars,” Rathore said. “It’s very expensive.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-74be7c" class="body-graf"&gt;When a 9-year-old unvaccinated patient came to Rathore with muscle spasm in Florida this year, he recognized the signs. He remembered the tetanus wards from his medical school days where patients were cared for in dark and silent isolation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fe29b0" class="body-graf"&gt;“The slightest noise would cause many of these patients to go into spasm,” Rathore said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c55b43" class="body-graf"&gt;Tetanus spasms, which can also be triggered by light (known as “photophobia”), are extremely painful and can constrict the muscles around the airway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-adb10b" class="body-graf"&gt;Amid the bright lights, loud noises and incessant beeping of the hospital’s intensive care unit, the options were limited for minimizing stimulation for Rathore's young patient. The 9-year-old was sedated, intubated and given tetanus immune globulin antibodies and the vaccine to reduce future risk of disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7d45a0" class="body-graf"&gt;The child was hospitalized for 37 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7013b7" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Matthew Davis, enterprise physician-in-chief and chief scientific officer at Nemours Children’s Health in Florida and Delaware, said that “it wasn’t until we had widespread vaccination that we saw a decline in cases of tetanus and thereby a reduction in the risk of mortality from it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9e939a" class="body-graf"&gt;John Johnson, a vaccination and epidemic response adviser at Doctors Without Borders, works in countries such as the Democratic Republic of the Congo (DRC) where tetanus remains a concern. Last year, there were 540 cases in the DRC, &lt;a href="https://immunizationdata.who.int/global/wiise-detail-page/tetanus-reported-cases-and-incidence?CODE=COD&amp;amp;DISEASE=TTETANUS&amp;amp;YEAR=" target="_blank"&gt;according to the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-013172" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s one of those things that’s so stupidly easy to prevent,” Johnson said. “If you see one case of tetanus in the U.S., it’s a shame. There’s no reason we should be seeing this disease anymore.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-93be9d" class="body-heading"&gt;'My jaw was completely locked shut'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-db2b3f" class="body-graf"&gt;After the initial series in childhood, a booster dose is recommended every 10 years for adults, although many are unaware of the need. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-73689d" class="body-graf"&gt;Nikki Arellano, 42, hadn't had a tetanus shot since 2010 when she was injured while she was helping her friend set up for a wedding last month. An accident with a metal arch at the altar led to a minor cut on her leg. The following week, she found it difficult to chew during lunch at work because of pain in her jaw. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8af84a" class="body-graf"&gt;Two days later, she couldn’t open her mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-170eb8" class="body-graf"&gt;“My jaw was completely locked shut,” said Arellano, of Reno, Nevada. “I went to the ER, and they tried to give me a bunch of sedatives and pain medicine and muscle relaxers to get my jaw to open, and nothing was making it open.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5a1d3d" class="body-graf"&gt;Arellano was diagnosed with tetanus and admitted to the hospital. She was connected to an intravenous pump so she could get antibiotics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9f7f34" class="body-graf"&gt;“Every time that it would run out, it was like a really, really loud beeping noise. When that started is when my muscle contractions would pop off,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3b39f1" class="body-graf"&gt;Arellano said her spasms initially started in one arm, then progressed to both arms and then to full body spasms. “It would arch your back really bad, like, it was really, really painful muscle spasms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-781b05" class="body-graf"&gt;Arellano began to have difficulty swallowing, prompting worries that her airway might become compromised. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3c3539" class="body-graf"&gt;“It was very scary,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-09781e" class="body-graf"&gt;She was hospitalized for nearly a week and is still recovering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-db35be" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Heightened risk with climate change&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a3a276" class="body-graf"&gt;Natural disasters such as hurricanes, tornadoes and floods are known risk factors for tetanus outbreaks. As people rummage through the wreckage, they are also likelier to be injured by loose nails or broken shards of glass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-153105" class="body-graf"&gt;“As the Earth warms, there’s already a documented increase in the frequency, intensity and duration of many extreme weather and climate events,” said Kristie Ebi, an epidemiologist and professor of global health at the University of Washington who studies the health effects of climate change. “And as there are more flooding events, then fewer vaccinations for diseases like tetanus means that people would be at greater risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-15b0b6" class="body-graf"&gt;Some states that are at highest risk of significant natural disasters, including Florida, Texas and Kansas, are recording notable declines in tetanus vaccination, according to NBC News data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxQeDYwZHdfd0N6ZlFZdkI4QVJ2SEZESVo1U250Nl81QmdLVlV6YzBwM2xmWnBxNk9KaWcxWTg4V1RpbmlqZWF0OGRpV3RfRGxxNVBMTHBEaktpZzFzX1NEbE1xaXljNFR4Tng2T1p1SmRkRmRXWGx5TnBFT1RNSmZrbGoyeV9KTXcxN3A2WFJyVmZUemxuQUxiY3UtdjdkNmVIbjdueWZ1bkNaem5lYnJlU9IBVkFVX3lxTE1ZUHpsNXRJTHNVQXhOMUl0T1FpSGFMaThoLWJFbF92aGozWnA3a19VczFiRnBnSHhCNVV1am5IdlEzaGNJVXFWRmdTRDJtX2VDZThITlh3</guid></item><item><title>减肥药物结束了他们的性生活。它会反弹吗？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/24/well/weight-loss-drugs-ended-their-sex-life-could-it-bounce-back.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 10:00:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOLTFncnVEUVFvZ0VJZ084ZHhLWVpOeWE1QWY0OTVSR3FkNDVJaFB2ZmhudVNQd1A5VTRKTkNEV2JvdG9NRkNEWDFwWEs3Nm9UOW5UWFZWOERxR19FdkRSNVp0TVNiTGVBaU9UNS0tMDV4TWRyX2dvdGNCTnRyVEhBSHZZYWNZaE5vMi1Gd3JBcm9BVTFaRnhjc0NfcmxQdllMOUNnNG05VQ</guid></item><item><title>是什么杀死了世界上最大的鳄鱼之一？对黑醋栗的尸检暗示了一个隐藏的杀手- IFLScience</title><link>https://www.iflscience.com/what-killed-one-of-the-worlds-biggest-crocs-a-necropsy-of-cassisus-suggests-a-hidden-killer-81983</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p data-pasted="true"&gt;Cassius the crocodile cheated death for more than a century until his wild life finally caught up with him last year in Australia. Now, experts dealing with his necroscopy have revealed what ultimately led to the giant's demise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="piano-gate" id="piano-gate"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 5.5-metre (nearly 18-foot) saltwater crocodile &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/rip-cassius-worlds-largest-captive-crocodile-dies-at-approximately-110-years-old-76633" target="_blank"&gt;died in November 2024&lt;/a&gt; at the Marineland Melanesia wildlife park on Green Island off the coast of Cairns, where he had been housed for four decades. At the grand age of around 110-120, he was one of the &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/at-123-years-old-henry-is-the-worlds-oldest-known-crocodile-and-hes-an-absolute-unit-76112" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;oldest known crocodiles&lt;/a&gt; in captivity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strangely enough, the world-famous reptile had been given the all-clear just a few weeks before his death by veterinarians, who noted he appeared "bright, alert and happy". Then, out of the blue, he passed away. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking to &lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2025-12-12/world-record-crocodile-cassius-taxidermied-new-exhibit/106131178" target="_blank"&gt;ABC News&lt;/a&gt;, the Darwin-based Centre for Crocodile Research says its necropsy revealed that Cassius died of an infection related to an injury he had suffered in the wild more than 40 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The injury triggered an infection that became sealed inside a tough fibrous capsule, lying dormant for decades. Over time, that protective bubble broke down and eventually ruptured, allowing the infection to swarm through the crocodile’s body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="trendmd-suggestions" data-pid-resource="RRUGNY3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sally Isberg, Managing Director at the Centre for Crocodile Research, told the media outlet that while so-called fibriscesses are “well-documented” in crocodiles, Cassius’ case was extraordinary due to how long the infection was contained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="piano-inline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With further snooping, the team concluded that the hidden infection may have been linked to an injury sustained in the 1980s when Cassius was struck by a boat propeller, resulting in the loss of his front left leg, part of his snout, and the end of his tail. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we didn't know was that the rib cage had also been damaged in that injury," said Dr Isberg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The reason was that everything was perfectly healed — there were no signs of infection or recent scarring. Upon necropsy, his left rib was distended compared to his right one, so longer," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a perfect example of the effect of old age — he was no longer able to continue that fibrous casing around that infection."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span contenteditable="false" draggable="true" class="fr-video fr-deletable fr-fvc fr-dvb fr-draggable"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/-FTIeYNvQpQ?&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="" class="fr-draggable"&gt;VIDEO&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="fr-mk"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cassius was captured in 1984 in the Finniss River near Darwin and transported by road and boat, eventually arriving at Marineland Melanesia in 1987. Owing to his size and power, he was named after Cassius Clay, the birth name of boxer Muhammad Ali.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was recognized as the world’s largest captive crocodile for some time, according to &lt;a href="https://www.guinnessworldrecords.com/news/2023/8/largest-crocodile-cassius-went-from-terrifying-predator-to-dreamy-eyed-dad-756676" target="_blank"&gt;Guinness World Records&lt;/a&gt;, although the title was snatched by an &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/at-62-meters-lolong-was-the-largest-crocodile-ever-recorded-and-captured-80905" target="_blank"&gt;even larger individual called Lolong&lt;/a&gt; in 2012. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the legacy of Cassisu lives on. The taxidermied body of the Aussie beast (still missing its left leg and tail tip) has just arrived home to Marineland Melanesia, where it is now on display at a new exhibition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>IFLScience</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 09:17:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxNaWkxWmJIcUVVeG41Yi1FSktvWGxNLUNTZWVnQlQteDJmUVVWcG1yU2hyOXYxYWdkQ042S0RHZmFuZ3piYTY5d2NGY3NCdzUxcWZiLXpHRVBXRVRTdlNQc0RIS0c5WElNRFQwZHhheTJvRzc1TlQweDYtVloyY2NoT2poU245bTlGVWVTMl90aWFVb1JzUVFqenpIWmg5Q0pwWVV4OGo2cmR2QkdEX0xrYmpoblJCS0xZWEdoS0l1YWFfUQ</guid></item><item><title>专栏|询问Eric ：告诉朋友她没有被邀请参加团体旅行？还是让她知道？ -《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/advice/2025/12/24/asking-eric-cruise-excluding-friend/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="763I6PNCHVFMPEU53KTH3C7CB4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dear Eric:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; Three friends and I are planning an eight-day cruise in January.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WC5FGPYYCZBBRCVAIMKF3TPM3I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Two other people found out about the trip and are now coming as well. We are fine with that but are not looking to make it a larger group and I am definitely not looking to turn into the “cruise director” for the group as often seems to happen.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 06:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOT3ZRc1RXTC1DZ0VJRUptdWVXMkFvamxOTFlYSHJOc1N5MXo3Qm03c1l0QlFpNUtEVmF5Zl9wSGJaSTdhUm1WZFlONkREX3g0cTB5MTlXbjRUWlVFNHRfb2NoSEFTdGtOZlIxSEdSdDlsSTg0alIzVEZWaldEbUNpdUpfb1hmM051cWR6Qm53</guid></item><item><title>斯坦福大学科学家发现为什么基于mRNA的COVID-19疫苗会导致心肌炎- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/stanford-scientists-discover-why-mrna-based-covid-19-vaccines-can-cause-myocarditis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 05:05:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdjA5QlJXclE4X3lGNXYzaDd5TGJmdE1HUFBudC04REVBaWQ4SVBsNFJ1NWowWEo2aG9tVy1MV3o0c25XbG4yYkdoQVEzcjlYTDZEa2ZleVRQS1BlQkZmdXRJMkluVGZOU1F2NFZPU051NlQ1X1d1c0oxYWVWbElpTmZJVjRwUkx0dW9FZnU0S01iV0VWRVVhRE0tQUZGXzB3b1pqNFhBSVhqUWprb2c</guid></item><item><title>你的大脑年龄在五个不同的阶段，新的研究表明-华尔街日报</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/health/wellness/brain-stages-aging-five-study-nature-a015101e</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 04:00:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOTmczTV83LXBBRm1sTG1ZWl9OdjVRRkczR01MQVZEeF9PYW1UTG1zQ0ZqTWRSZzB1RmxQSG9KYTlMcWlFbGFRb3FDNnhvVXhLaU80X0pmaVZraWRKU25UeElWRjlWajBBazVuSnF3UTlJRnlfX19SbV9oYjI0SFdZZTRUTTk0d1Fw</guid></item><item><title>关于飙升的“冬季呕吐虫”及其传染性新变种- Axios的须知事项</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2025/12/24/norovirus-winter-vomiting-bug-variant-symptoms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 02:03:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxORWh2SllPS19RSTUzUHZ3UldrUUpWLTk2M1VNUTU2eTU5Vkl3UWRhMzFhemhTT21QQVRlM0M4blVoVE04NHNEVDBNNjc2X3dmN3RkVkZMSGkwVTdtM19fZlJTVDZpWWVTMldJWGZIUkVTUkwzNzUtNnZaMUw0VW5HNjJPR2Zudw</guid></item><item><title>新的流感变异袭击南加州，引起公共卫生专家的担忧- ABC7洛杉矶</title><link>https://abc7.com/post/new-flu-variant-hits-southern-california-raises-concerns-among-public-health-experts/18310392/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;LOS ANGELES (KABC) -- &lt;/span&gt;Holiday travel is in full swing and flu cases are ramping up. Some experts are pretty worried about a new flu variant making its way to Southern California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;So now is the time to take the steps to protect you and your loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Many schools across the nation closed early for winter break because of an onslaught of illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Mother of two, Audrey Garrett, says flu-like symptoms hit her family hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We actually are just coming back from being sick. He caught a fever. My daughter had that nasty cough, you know that honking cough at night," Garrett said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Last year was a pretty bad seasonal flu year for Los Angeles, so it is scary to hear that this year might be worse," Dr. Dawn Tereshita said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Dr. Tereshita monitors acute communicable disease at L.A. County's Department of Public Health. She warns of an emerging H3N2 flu variant that's difficult for our immune systems to recognize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"This subclade K is new," Dr. Tereshita said. "We don't know what's going to happen yet, but since it is circulating pretty widely, we are watching it very carefully."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The new variant isn't a match for this season's flu vaccine, but experts believe a flu shot will still help reduce the risk of severe illness, including hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Any reason to not go to the hospital is, in my mind, very worth it. There are also antivirals, which you can take if you get sick," Tereshita explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;These include Tamiflu and the new Xofluza. Talk to your doctor if you have a fever, sore throat, cough and body aches because these meds should be taken near the onset of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The main messages are wash your hands, stay home when you're sick, and if you have to go out, wear a mask," Dr. Tereshita said&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;While we are seeing a lot of respiratory illnesses, Dr. Terashita says flu activity in California remains low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But, now is the time to get a flu shot if you haven't because the flu usually peaks in January and February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 KABC Television, LLC. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 Los Angeles</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:39:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxNWk9vcTBSNmtlcFhadGRwMkFRZVhrTW5fOTNJNGpkcGdHX0JiOWZaZkJIbUdhajg4MTRwVW1wVzdHU2VLalUzRVhVdHQySER2VS1zV1pXYlFMWkxyWkVhVGZPenliVTlrNTl2eDQ4cmNBc2RGVXRBRmJ0REcxLXBZZWRpSjR0bm1nVTdHR0NlMExyQjRVemxZbmNuZDNhMnpNNGo3Nzc2T1NDTHpyQ19zYlZSazdsdzjSAbwBQVVfeXFMT1dKSk84ZExtdm43REtkUWRKR0x3Yjc3WnFrTnVWSURWeHI2SjZFbHpRS1lwbnlxdHVXUXRoNV95R0ZQak1sNFNKaTZhR1plejJtakxtX2xHZ01qNHVSRm4ta1d3RG52YV9kcDdNTTlsU2F0eVQ4MU43akhnSEIxcjVMckFXSmZoSjNsR2RHWnhpbEFHc3o5S3hybDMtNjZ5LWlTaW9VX3VDa01fMHY2akN5Z2d0TnJnR3pGY3o</guid></item><item><title>拉什大学医学中心的Steven Flamm博士谈论酒精使用，肝脏疾病，新年前饮酒的影响- ABC7芝加哥</title><link>https://abc7chicago.com/post/rush-university-medical-centers-dr-steven-flamm-talks-alcohol-use-liver-disease-impact-drinking-ahead-new-year/18310620/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;CHICAGO (WLS) -- &lt;/span&gt;As a new year approaches, many people are rethinking their habits, including how much alcohol they're drinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Rush University Medical Center's Dr. Steven Flamm joined ABC7 on Tuesday night to talk about alcohol's impact on the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="shortcode-centertext EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Flamm talked about how much alcohol it takes to develop liver disease and how alcohol impacts men and women differently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Flamm also weighed in on the Illinois Department of Public Health's &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://dph.illinois.gov/resource-center/news/2025/december/release-20251215.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;alcohol use survey&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="RxNCg ykkUm PvZ nIjPJ PMXYp LmsHF SfAHY mNgye lNbol LBPRq rBLIK "&gt;Facts about alcohol:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;People who consume alcohol can have severe alcohol-related liver disease with as little as two drinks per day in women and three drinks per day in men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The liver-related toxicity for alcohol is double in women compared to men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Alcohol-associated hepatitis is a severe and life-threatening condition that can develop in a matter of weeks. It frequently happens in young people, has no good medical therapies and has a high mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The only therapy for alcohol-related liver disease is alcohol abstinence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;There has been a dramatic increase in alcohol associated liver disease in the U.S., including Illinois, since the start of the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WLS-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 Chicago</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 01:29:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxNY2NIZGo5MlE2QmdwcjJPVkxZa2pVU1RYZ09LNVhUMHhlaXk4bmFIcnRIRkFsQi1NTl9uV0E5SjlfNGtWMDFEbEwzZW1jNUNHeGJRWHFmaGtwNTNjSUVBY2RfTG9aRTlTSzZMNEhnWHlId3NzWHdBLS1fRV9WUEpjSWJ1SXJZNjdYd295RnZTc3dYZURiRWRIY2l6SjhMMlBVX0ViNUhVTHJ6dGtOdHlydnlvY2hXSThHaWR5MEtEUWJCV1VIRW1hREcwemp3TTljdkh5RXZiZXJ1M0NpNTd3SHI2SdIB6AFBVV95cUxQY3NJd3ZIM3JfTVdvU3lZc1c0MURScHZtcGdnNHV0bkhTaEpCUDdJTkFKaENKb1ZmN0o3bU81QmNvZUQxT1VGNHF6STY3V0Y3TWJIRGRibXk0UTdvX09lS3pKVGdQRDJMMHRlODNJMWFkenppZXJQQkhuOUYtaHJUdUdZMnQxaHBGbnJzcHdBNFZmVTdGbDI4Xy13YlA5Nzl2N0xFMGhMMWx6RFB1R3NRdGRRZ3VaZmR5azAtSFRRVVZEM09JZU55WGotdzB4MzFOTTFMSXZPTE9JczV0VWZDRTREaWNVQmsz</guid></item><item><title>科学家说，人类实际上可能有30多种感官- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/humans-may-actually-have-over-30-senses-scientists-say</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Stuck in front of our screens all day, we often ignore our senses beyond sound and vision. And yet they are always at work. When we're more alert, we feel the rough and smooth surfaces of objects, the stiffness in our shoulders, the softness of bread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the morning, we may feel the tingle of toothpaste, hear and feel the running water in the shower, smell the shampoo, and later the aroma of freshly brewed  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="186802" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aristotle told us there were &lt;a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/2184311"&gt;five senses&lt;/a&gt;. But he also told us the world was made up &lt;a href="https://www.cabinet.ox.ac.uk/fifth-element-and-medieval-cosmology-2"&gt;of five elements&lt;/a&gt;, and we no longer believe that. And modern research is showing we may actually have dozens of senses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-scientist-reveals-5-amazing-facts-about-your-sense-of-smell"&gt;A Scientist Reveals 5 Amazing Facts About Your Sense of Smell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost all of our experience &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/senses-1914"&gt;is multisensory&lt;/a&gt;. We don't see, hear, smell, and touch in separate parcels. They occur simultaneously in a unified experience of the world around us and of ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What we feel affects &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1163/22134808-bja10003"&gt;what we see&lt;/a&gt;, and what we see affects &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fpsyg.2014.00725"&gt;what we hear&lt;/a&gt;. Different odours in shampoo &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0950329309000202"&gt;can affect how you&lt;/a&gt; perceive the texture of hair. The fragrance of roses makes hair seem silkier, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Odours in low-fat yogurts can make them feel richer and thicker on the palate without adding more emulsifiers. Perception of odours &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0304394006010020"&gt;in the mouth&lt;/a&gt;, rising to the nasal passage, is modified by the viscosity of the liquids we consume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186808" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186808" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/child_eating_yoghurt_642.jpg" alt="child eating yoghurt" class="wp-image-186808 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/child_eating_yoghurt_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/child_eating_yoghurt_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186808" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The odours of liquids in our mouth affect how they feel. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEEqTBRquA/"&gt;Antonio D'Albore/Getty Images Signature/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;My long-term collaborator, Professor Charles Spence from the Crossmodal Laboratory in Oxford, told me his neuroscience colleagues &lt;a href="https://www.sciculture.ac.uk/files/2014/07/AHRC-Rethinking-the-Senses-Case-Study.pdf"&gt;believe there are&lt;/a&gt; anywhere between 22 and &lt;a href="https://www.gla.ac.uk/research/az/cspe/projects/rethinking-the-senses/"&gt;33 senses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These include &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/science/proprioception"&gt;proprioception&lt;/a&gt;, which enables us to know where our limbs are without looking at them. Our sense of balance draws on the &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/science/ear/The-physiology-of-balance-vestibular-function"&gt;vestibular system&lt;/a&gt; of ear canals as well as sight and proprioception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another example is interoception, by which we sense changes in our own bodies, such as a slight increase in our heart rate and hunger. We also have a sense of agency when moving our limbs: a feeling that can go missing &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nrn.2017.14"&gt;in stroke patients&lt;/a&gt; who sometimes even believe someone else is moving their arm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/brain/article/147/2/390/7319594"&gt;sense of ownership&lt;/a&gt;. Stroke patients sometimes feel their arm is not their own, for instance, even though they may still feel sensations in it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the traditional senses are combinations of several senses. Touch, for instance, involves pain, temperature, itch, and tactile sensations. When &lt;a href="http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v486/n7403_supp/full/486S6a.html"&gt;we taste something&lt;/a&gt;, we are actually experiencing a combination of three senses: touch, smell, and taste – or gustation – which combine to produce the flavours we perceive in food and drinks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gustation covers sensations produced by receptors on the tongue that enable us to detect salt, sweet, sour, bitter, and umami (savoury). What about mint, mango, melon, strawberry, raspberry?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We don't have raspberry receptors on the tongue, nor is raspberry flavour some combination of sweet, sour, and bitter. There is no taste arithmetic for fruit flavours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We perceive them through the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/smell-triggers-the-same-brain-response-as-taste-does-even-if-you-havent-eaten-anything-264922"&gt;combined workings&lt;/a&gt; of the tongue and the nose. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/foods11121686"&gt;It is smell&lt;/a&gt; that contributes the lion's share to what we call tasting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not inhaling odours from the environment, though. Odour compounds are released as we chew or sip, travelling from the mouth to the nose through the nasal pharynx at the back of the throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://scholar.archive.org/work/sn5ora556nerbd2gwndzdut5t4"&gt;Touch plays its part too&lt;/a&gt;, binding tastes and smells together and fixing our preferences for runny or firm eggs, and the velvety, luxurious gooeyness of chocolate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sight is influenced by our vestibular system. When you are on board an aircraft on the ground, look down the cabin. Look again when you are in the climb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will "look" to you as though the front of the cabin is higher than you are, although optically, everything is in the same relation to you as it was on the ground. What you "see" is the combined effect of sight and your ear canals telling you that you are tilting backwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186809" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186809" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/aircraft_cabin_seats_642.jpg" alt="aircraft cabin" class="wp-image-186809 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/aircraft_cabin_seats_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/aircraft_cabin_seats_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186809" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The rise of the aisle in an aircraft cabin is determined by your vestibular system. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGZKtbMSrc/"&gt;Jeffry S.S./Pexels/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The senses offer a rich seam of research, and philosophers, neuroscientists, and psychologists work together at the Centre for the Study of the Senses at the University of London's School of Advanced Study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2013, the centre launched its Rethinking the Senses project, directed by my colleague, the late Professor Sir Colin Blakemore. We discovered how modifying the sound of your own footsteps can make your body feel lighter or heavier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We learned how audioguides in the Tate Britain art museum that address the listener as if the model in a portrait was speaking enable visitors to remember more visual details of the painting. We discovered how aircraft noise interferes with our perception of taste and why you should always drink tomato juice on a plane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While our perception of salt, sweet, and sour is reduced in the presence of white noise, umami is not, and tomatoes and tomato juice are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/2044-7248-3-2"&gt;rich in umami&lt;/a&gt;. This means the aircraft's noise will enhance the savoury flavour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-think-theyve-identified-an-unknown-taste-in-human-cells"&gt;Scientists Think They've Identified an Unknown Taste in Human Cells&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At our latest interactive exhibition, &lt;a href="https://www.kingscross.co.uk/event/club-curling"&gt;Senses Unwrapped&lt;/a&gt; at Coal Drops Yard in London's King's Cross, people can discover for themselves how their senses work and why they don't work as we think they do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, the size-weight illusion is illustrated by a set of small, medium, and large curling stones. People can lift each one and decide which is heaviest. The smallest one feels heaviest, but people can then place them on balancing scales and discover that they are all the same weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are always plenty of things around you to show how intricate your senses are, if you only pause for a moment to take it all in. So next time you walk outside or savour a meal, take a moment to appreciate how your senses are working together to help you feel all the sensations involved.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/270697/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/barry-smith-128876"&gt;Barry Smith&lt;/a&gt;, Director of the Institute of Philosophy, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/school-of-advanced-study-university-of-london-1058"&gt;School of Advanced Study, University of London&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/humans-could-have-as-many-as-33-senses-270697"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 00:32:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQcGdUZTYyb25pQmtSYThyUm5GNm9Ybm84R2p2TFNuM0hZajdkT2dKN19xWHB1RXJUM3ZzNl9sanJHR1E4dVJ0NFN4STg0SGdBNUZlZjFnd1FfbUNIajI0TExNSENZM0ZWYmxLVVJVTHQzR3QzUXBOdnIzLXZ6UXlkMnVuX3ZibklsVWow</guid></item><item><title>我是一名皮肤科医生—如何知道一个人长大后是否会皱纹更多- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/m-dermatologist-always-tell-person-110000964.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Everyone gets wrinkles, but some people are more likely to have early lines and deeper grooves. Dr. Kseniya Kobets reveals three major tell-tale signs of accelerated aging.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Call ’em laugh lines, battle blemishes or experience etchings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wrinkles are a natural and universal part of aging. &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/01/12/health/what-causes-wrinkles-groundbreaking-new-study-may-have-found-answer/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:These creases primarily form;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;These creases primarily form&lt;/a&gt; as the skin loses collagen and elastin, which provide structure, firmness and elasticity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain habits can accelerate this process, making lines and grooves appear earlier and deeper. Blame genetics, hormones, dehydration, insufficient sleep, poor diets, stress and repeated facial expressions such as squinting, smiling or frowning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Everyone gets wrinkles, but some people are more likely to have early lines and deeper grooves. Dr. Kseniya Kobets reveals three major tell-tale signs of accelerated aging. courtesy of Montefiore Einstein Advanced Care&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Stress has a lot to do with aging and reactive oxygen species,” &lt;a href="https://doctors.montefioreeinstein.org/providers/1912296674/kseniya-kobets" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Kseniya Kobets;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Kseniya Kobets&lt;/a&gt;, director of cosmetic dermatology at &lt;a href="https://montefioreeinsteinadvancedcare.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Montefiore Einstein Advanced Care;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Montefiore Einstein Advanced Care&lt;/a&gt;, told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Someone who doesn’t have a healthy lifestyle and doesn’t eat healthy vegetables or fruits once in a while is also more likely to have less healthy skin.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kobets reveals three major ways she can tell if someone is more likely to develop smile souvenirs as they age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Steady sun-worshipping&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sun is good for you — it helps your body make &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2023/11/27/health/vitamin-d-recommended-levels-should-be-10x-higher-report/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vitamin D;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; for strong bones, enhances mood by boosting serotonin and regulates your body’s internal clock for better sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But too many rays can be really bad for skin. Just ask New Jersey “tan mom” &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2022/05/23/tan-mom-patricia-krentcil-im-a-totally-different-person/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Patricia Krentcil;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Patricia Krentcil&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Sunscreen prevents wrinkles by protecting skin from UV rays, which break down collagen and elastin. verona_studio – stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kobets worries about fair-skinned people who live in sun-soaked areas or participate in outdoor activities like hiking, biking, skiing or vacationing in the tropics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They are more prone to developing wrinkles and especially other issues like sun damage and, God forbid, precancerous lesions and &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/08/25/health/abcdes-of-skin-cancer-9-clues-you-shouldnt-ignore/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:skin cancers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;skin cancers&lt;/a&gt;,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;UV rays generate free radicals that destroy collagen and elastin, damage DNA, trigger inflammation and speed up skin aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How much sun is OK is really dependent on your skin type and the daily UV index.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone needs protection, including hats, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/article/best-sunglasses-brands-men-women/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sunglasses;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;sunglasses&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/06/09/health/what-to-know-about-picking-sunscreen-including-2-key-ingredients/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SPF 30+ sunscreen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;SPF 30+ sunscreen&lt;/a&gt;, when the index reaches 3 or higher (moderate risk).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Rawdogging skincare&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunscreen is the cornerstone of any good skincare regimen, which is key to fending off wrinkles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If someone doesn’t really have a consistent skin care routine, particularly one that includes daily sunscreen use, even if they’re not outdoors, they are more likely to develop wrinkles over time,” Kobets said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;A good skincare routine emphasizes sun protection, hydration (moisturizers, hyaluronic acid), retinoids for cell turnover and antioxidants like vitamin C. Rido – stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/article/best-mineral-sunscreens-per-experts/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:mineral sunscreen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;mineral sunscreen&lt;/a&gt;, which reflects and scatters UV rays, Kobets recommends topical and oral antioxidants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That means consuming vitamin C, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/05/03/health/im-a-dietitian-eat-this-to-get-more-collagen/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:collagen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;collagen&lt;/a&gt; and peptides, short amino acid chains that tell skin cells to pump out more collagen and elastin, and applying topical peptides and occasionally, a topical retinol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These are very important factors, not to mention wearing hats and staying in the shade, even if you are wearing sunscreen,” Kobets said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Puffing pores&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baking in the sun is lousy for your skin, but smoking is often considered worse because it narrows blood vessels, breaks down collagen and elastin and amplifies sun damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nicotine constricts blood vessels, limiting the flow of oxygen and essential nutrients to the skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If the person is smoking — although there are a lot of genetic and environmental factors at play — they’re more likely to have thinner skin and wrinkles, especially around their mouth,” Kobets said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s a nice way to describe &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2019/11/01/study-confirms-that-cigarettes-will-give-you-ugly-smokers-face/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“smoker’s face,”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;“smoker’s face,”&lt;/a&gt; a phenomenon characterized by deep wrinkles around the eyes and lips from the smoker constantly drawing on cigarettes and repeatedly squinting to keep smoke out of their eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smokers also often suffer from sagging skin, a dull, yellowish-gray complexion and premature contours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:31:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQNmFwQ0FpY2NGeW9ZVVluZUZtOVNHNF9QeHNLdnBLdTJvTTR2MjZadzF2aHR2Rzl5eGhNLUhsODZYb0tHTXBxaUxiY0k3TEtpZC1lcEZPMFdUMV9PSDIwUlBJTWtfdEJDSlZSMmtuUWNKU2o0RTlodEdFbkVjaGxvWFdpMmg</guid></item><item><title>每天只喝一杯与印度口腔癌风险增加50 ％有关- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/just-one-drink-a-day-linked-to-50-higher-mouth-cancer-risk-in-india/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 23:30:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxOanJ1UEEzU2RnbHQtYWtFSWNZY2NqbDZKVFBvMUFCWG5wX09GWE00S3I0V3ZUMV9fWWR2dUpXUVcwdjBlU21ZWjdNSjJzaWJOXy1LYjF4QXEtTTVkdF9TbkZEZVlORkdlM1FiWFpJOFh6UHRKeVoxQkwzaVgzeHJWR2lJMU9ZZHoyc1ZhbTgzV18tUTBkNG9EMw</guid></item><item><title>近80年的法律可能会妨碍RFK Jr.重新制定疫苗接种计划的动力- CIDRAP</title><link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/nearly-80-year-old-law-could-hamper-rfk-jr-s-drive-remake-vaccine-schedule</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS), Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has broad powers to shape federal vaccine policy. In June, he &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/adult-non-flu-vaccines/kennedy-removes-all-acip-members-eyes-replacements"&gt;fired all 17 members&lt;/a&gt; of an influential panel on immunization policy, then handpicked their replacements. In August, he &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/public-health/cdc-director-fired-after-she-refused-rubber-stamp-kennedys-vaccine-directives"&gt;fired the director&lt;/a&gt; of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) after they clashed over vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But even Kennedy’s authority has limits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Making a unilateral decision to scrap the US pediatric immunization schedule and replace it with recommendations from Denmark, as Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/18/health/hhs-childhood-vaccine-changes"&gt;was reportedly ready&lt;/a&gt; to do last week, requires far more than a press conference, legal experts told CIDRAP News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy and other agency heads must obey the Administrative Procedure Act (APA), a law passed by Congress that requires federal officials to follow an open, deliberative process when issuing rules and regulations, said Lawrence Gostin, JD, founding director of the O'Neill Institute for National and Global Health Law at Georgetown University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As a matter of law, Secretary Kennedy has final authority to make federal policy,” Gostin said. “But he must follow a reasoned process.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;A drive to reduce the number of vaccinations&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy’s announcement was canceled at the last minute. Although the HHS office of public affairs blamed a scheduling conflict, Politico has reported that Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/20/rfk-kennedy-danish-vaccine-schedule-denmark-00701999"&gt;backed off from a plan to overhaul&lt;/a&gt; the vaccine schedule—which had been described to the press as an “announcement regarding children’s health”— after advisers told him it was legally and politically risky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an email to media, HHS suggested the press conference would be rescheduled, noting that it was “postponing our children's health announcement to after the first of the new year.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A spokesman for HHS declined to confirm that Kennedy planned to overhaul the vaccine schedule at the press conference. “Unless you hear it from HHS directly, this is pure speculation,” spokesman Andrew Nixon said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy, a long-time anti-vaccine activist, has made no secret of his eagerness to revamp the immunization schedule. After President Trump &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/"&gt;issued a memo earlier this month&lt;/a&gt; directing HHS to align the vaccination schedule with that of countries such as Denmark, Kennedy &lt;a href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1997104582128754854?s=20"&gt;posted on X,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; “&lt;/span&gt;Thank you, Mr. President. We’re on it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Kennedy needs to proceed cautiously to prevent any policy changes from being dismissed by a judge, said Dorit Reiss,&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;PhD, a law professor at the University of California Law, San Francisco. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a matter of law, Secretary Kennedy has final authority to make federal policy....But he must follow a reasoned process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the APA, courts can “hold unlawful and &lt;a href="https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/5/706"&gt;set aside agency action&lt;/a&gt;, findings, and conclusions found to be arbitrary, capricious, an abuse of discretion, or otherwise not in accordance with law.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simply holding a press conference to announce that the United States will now recommend Denmark’s vaccine schedule would leave the Trump administration “very, very vulnerable to an arbitrary and capricious claims,” Reiss said. “Short videos simply don't do it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Following established procedures&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;For six decades, vaccine recommendations have been formulated by the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP), which normally votes on national recommendations after reviewing medical evidence and soliciting input from experts and the public. The CDC director can accept or reject those recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC’s recommendations are not mandates. Even if Kennedy were to switch the current vaccine recommendations to match those of Denmark, states would not have to follow along. Although CDC recommendations carry great weight, states make individual decisions about school vaccine requirements, Gostin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A court is likely to take a dim view of any federal vaccine policy changes that don’t go through the ACIP, Reiss said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the administration wants to follow Denmark’s example, “they need to address the major issues and explain why they are changing from a schedule developed in a deliberative manner over years.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Trump’s memo carries little to no legal weight, Reiss added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The president's memo is not cover, because the will of the president is not enough to justify a change of position under Supreme Court jurisprudence,” Reiss said. “The agency also has to justify the decision on the merits.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Legal challenges to Trump administration policy&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous lawsuits filed against the Trump administration in recent months claim that he and federal agency heads have violated the APA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American Academy of Pediatrics (AAP) and other medical groups, for example, &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/covid-19/medical-groups-sue-hhs-kennedy-over-covid-vaccine-policy-changes"&gt;filed a law suit against Kennedy&lt;/a&gt; in July claiming that he violated the APA when he &lt;a href="https://litigationtracker.law.georgetown.edu/litigation/american-academy-of-pediatrics-et-al-v-robert-f-kennedy-jr-et-al/"&gt;issued a directive&lt;/a&gt; removing the COVID-19 vaccine from the CDC immunization schedule for children and pregnant women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The concerns and legal issues all come back to whether he followed a process and looked at evidence,” said Richard H. Hughes IV, JD, MPH, who teaches vaccine law at George Washington University and represents the AAP and other plaintiffs in their lawsuit against Kennedy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous medical societies and public health groups &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/pediatricians-reject-cdc-advisers-guidance-plan-continue-vaccinating-all"&gt;have criticized Kennedy&lt;/a&gt; and the ACIP for more recent changes to the vaccination schedule, such as removing a recommendation to routinely vaccinate all newborns against hepatitis B. Scientists and public health advocates predict that decision &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/doctor-groups-form-united-front-against-rfk-jr-s-efforts-limit-vaccine-access"&gt;will allow many children to suffer&lt;/a&gt; and die needlessly from a vaccine-preventable illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither Kennedy “nor the ACIP is taking the proper steps to evaluate the full range of evidence that is normally reviewed prior to recommendation changes,” Hughes said. “All of that is textbook ‘arbitrary and capricious’ under the Administrative Procedure Act.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that doesn’t mean that Kennedy can’t find other ways to alter the vaccine schedule, Gostin noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If he follows a deliberative process, the ultimate decision is his,” Gostin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the APA could be interpreted to mean that Kennedy needs to work with the ACIP to change vaccine recommendations, “that is not a high bar for Kennedy since he handpicked ACIP's members,” Gostin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justifying a change to vaccine recommendations would be easier than changing federal regulations, a process that typically takes months and includes proposals and opportunities for public comments, Gostin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy “would have even more onerous procedures to follow if he proposed a legal regulation,” Gostin said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 21:59:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxQREd5aFpWYzJQb2huYVBnTnc3ZFZwTUxSTDRaRWJpVDdaWlhiNVR0MS1FSTlhUl9MUlF6VTFOM3dsYUd3RWxvWWotZTByZXFsOUl3a0FVb1JFdUNXUzRvRUlQazhpaHNfand1bXktOUROYVdheE4xMHNISGtSNW1qZDd3MjBwTmtYSjUwTG01OThJaW1TQnA1b1AzMWI4V1BGQnBCN09lTUdpMnFJY1o5eUNZVzFldVdMbzJNcg</guid></item><item><title>如果我听医生的话，我现在早就死了- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/women-doctor-cancer-tumor-hysterectomy_n_694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most doctors are intelligent, compassionate human beings, but they &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; human. And medicine is a business, which means doctors can be overworked, pressed for time and dismissive of patient complaints, &lt;a href="https://www.northwell.edu/katz-institute-for-womens-health/articles/gaslighting-in-womens-health" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="especially if that patient is a woman" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.northwell.edu/katz-institute-for-womens-health/articles/gaslighting-in-womens-health" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;especially if that patient is a woman&lt;/a&gt;. In my case, the casual dismissal of my symptoms almost cost me my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was October 2019 when my new OB-GYN ― let’s call her Dr. Can’t Be Bothered ― gave me what I considered to be life-changing news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You have a two-centimeter tumor on your uterine cervix,” she said, without even a hint of concern. For me, those words felt like a knife to the gut. A tumor? Me? How?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then her phone rang, and she left the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the time she returned, tears had welled up in my eyes. “Do I have cancer?” I asked, terrified and confused. As a non-doctor, when I hear the word “tumor,” my first thought is cancer. Hers was not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No, no,” Dr. Can’t Be Bothered assured me. “This is not how cancer behaves.” Then she added a sentence I’ll never forget: “For you to have cancer at this age, with this medical history, it would be like winning the lottery.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This did not make me feel better. She seemed unconcerned about the tumor growing in my pelvis, but I was not. She explained I would need a biopsy, but assured me it was probably fibroids, a benign growth, maybe a polyp, or a million other little non-cancer things. I would have to go under anesthesia for the biopsy, and it would be an “all-day” affair. Not wanting this tumor-thingy hanging over my head, I asked to schedule the surgery as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. CBB once again told me there was no rush, even though the radiology report stated the tumor was “of concern.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, she was going on vacation for two weeks and her schedule was full. We would have to put off the procedure for at least four weeks. I asked if I could get in sooner ― perhaps a different doctor could perform the biopsy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not necessary,” she said. “Just be patient.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“I let it go ― after all, she'd gone to medical school and I hadn't. She wore a white coat, and I was a 34-year-old whose work wardrobe still included yoga pants.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She made me feel like I was overreacting, like I was ignorant of how “these things work.” I peppered her with questions about the Big C, to which she kept saying, “No, no, that’s not how cancer behaves.” I let it go ― after all, she’d gone to medical school and I hadn’t. She wore a white coat, and I was a 34-year-old whose work wardrobe still included yoga pants. It was not my place to argue with her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;On my drive home I called my mother. I explained everything the doctor told me, but I couldn’t stop crying. I felt that something was wrong ― like, &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; wrong. And I was angry the doctor wasn’t taking this seriously. My mother agreed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;On instinct, I called up my old OB-GYN. Sobbing, I explained my situation and begged for an urgent appointment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to certain cancers, time matters. Forty-eight hours later I was once again sitting in a doctor’s office, only this time, it was a completely different experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;My old doctor spoke to me with kindness and concern. He explained exactly what the ultrasound revealed, and went over all the tests he was about to perform, including another ultrasound, a colposcopy, and an in-office biopsy with no anesthesia and no surgery required. He even said to me, “I know you’re scared, but we’re going to do everything we can to figure out what’s going on.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turns out, I &lt;em&gt;had&lt;/em&gt; won the lottery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biopsy revealed I had a &lt;a href="https://tarynhillin.medium.com/a-rare-cancer-thats-killing-young-women-and-no-one-knows-how-to-cure-dc4a4d91d9ed" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="very rare cancer called high-grade small-cell neuroendocrine" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://tarynhillin.medium.com/a-rare-cancer-thats-killing-young-women-and-no-one-knows-how-to-cure-dc4a4d91d9ed" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;very rare cancer called high-grade small-cell neuroendocrine&lt;/a&gt;. I would need a radical hysterectomy ― where they remove the uterus, cervix, ovaries, fallopian tubes, a third of the vaginal canal, and multiple pelvic lymph nodes ― along with adjuvant chemotherapy and radiation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;After my diagnosis, my entire world turned upside down. It was an onslaught of appointments, scans, and hard bathroom-floor crying. My imaging showed only “local disease,” which means it had not metastasized to other parts of my body. My surgical oncologist said she was relieved. “Often patients with neuroendocrine cancer walk in at stage 4 ― it’s that aggressive,” she said. “You’re lucky you came when you did.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;The author with her husband, Max Gamble, after she completed chemotherapy for stage 3C neuroendocrine cancer.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, that’s an understatement. Even with the quick biopsy, I ended up at stage 3C. My odds of survival were a mere &lt;a href="https://ijgc.bmj.com/content/29/6/986" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="0% to 7%" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://ijgc.bmj.com/content/29/6/986" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;0% to 7%&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The truth is, high-grade small-cell neuroendocrine cancer is highly aggressive, with poor prognosis rates. Even at stage 1, the survival rate is only about 30%. The time between my scans, which showed local disease, and my surgery, which found cancer in one lymph node, was just five days. Had I waited for Dr. CBB to care about my condition, I would have been stage 4 at diagnosis and probably dead now. Median survival is less than 16 months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weeks later, after my surgery was completed, I finally got a call from Dr. Couldn’t Be Bothered’s office. They wanted to schedule the&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;biopsy she’d put off. I laughed. “Are you kidding me?” I asked. “I’m about to start chemotherapy!” Then I angrily hung up the phone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know I am lucky to be alive. I have now been cancer-free for two years. My oncologist recently said I was a “miracle.” In order for me to survive this cancer, &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt; had to go my way. I was fortunate that the second doctor I saw spent over an hour with me, listened to my concerns, tested me for everything on the spot and cared enough to pay attention to me. If my surgery, chemotherapy or radiation had been delayed by four weeks ― as Dr. CBB wanted ― it would have cost me my life. Instead, a team of doctors stepped up and recognized a needle-in-a-haystack cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;My intention is not to vilify doctors, but rather the system they are forced to operate in. According to studies, 56% of primary care physicians &lt;a href="https://mobius.md/2021/10/09/how-much-time-do-physicians-spend-with-patients/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="spend less than 16 minutes" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://mobius.md/2021/10/09/how-much-time-do-physicians-spend-with-patients/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;spend less than 16 minutes&lt;/a&gt; with patients, and much of that time is &lt;a href="https://www.fiercehealthcare.com/practices/for-each-patient-visit-physicians-spend-about-16-minutes-ehrs-study-finds" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="spent filling out electronic health records" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.fiercehealthcare.com/practices/for-each-patient-visit-physicians-spend-about-16-minutes-ehrs-study-finds" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;spent filling out electronic health records&lt;/a&gt;. Indeed, the bureaucratic side of American health care &lt;a href="https://www.ama-assn.org/practice-management/physician-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-physician-burnout" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="is not what doctors signed up for" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ama-assn.org/practice-management/physician-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-physician-burnout" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;is not what doctors signed up for&lt;/a&gt;. Between growing pressure to see more patients, &lt;a href="https://www.ama-assn.org/practice-management/physician-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-physician-burnout" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="insurance pre-authorization codes" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.ama-assn.org/practice-management/physician-health/what-doctors-wish-patients-knew-about-physician-burnout" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;insurance pre-authorization codes&lt;/a&gt;, after-hours phone calls, portal messages, peer-to-peer insurance consults, &lt;a href="https://www.hhrinstitute.org/exploratory-study-identifies-key-factors-associated-with-time-pressure-in-primary-care-clinicians/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="patient paperwork" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.hhrinstitute.org/exploratory-study-identifies-key-factors-associated-with-time-pressure-in-primary-care-clinicians/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;patient paperwork&lt;/a&gt; and medical history reviews, many physicians are burned out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“Women are underdiagnosed for depression, cardiovascular disease and many types of cancer, often seeing multiple doctors and waiting more than a year for a diagnosis.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, studies have shown women are &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/j.1553-2712.2008.00100.x" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="often dismissed" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/j.1553-2712.2008.00100.x" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;often dismissed&lt;/a&gt; in health care settings. They’re told severe abdominal pain can be chalked up to period cramps, while painful conditions like uterine fibroids, endometriosis and ovarian cysts &lt;a href="https://labblog.uofmhealth.org/rounds/understanding-racial-disparities-for-women-uterine-fibroids" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="go undiagnosed for months or years" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://labblog.uofmhealth.org/rounds/understanding-racial-disparities-for-women-uterine-fibroids" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;go undiagnosed for months or years&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists estimates that endometriosis &lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20180607/why-women-are-getting-misdiagnosed" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="takes an average of six to 10 years for a diagnosis" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20180607/why-women-are-getting-misdiagnosed" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;takes an average of six to 10 years for a diagnosis&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not to mention, women in America have the &lt;a href="https://www.vox.com/2020/1/30/21113782/pregnancy-deaths-us-maternal-mortality-rate" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="highest maternal mortality rate" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.vox.com/2020/1/30/21113782/pregnancy-deaths-us-maternal-mortality-rate" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;highest maternal mortality rate&lt;/a&gt; compared to other developed nations, and for Black women, it’s even worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But the dismissal of women’s pain is not exclusive to gynecological or pregnancy-related conditions. Women are underdiagnosed for depression, cardiovascular disease and many types of cancer, often seeing multiple doctors and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0127717" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="waiting more than a year for a diagnosis" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0127717" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;&lt;span&gt;waiting more than a year for a diagnosis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Women are 50% more likely to be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20180607/why-women-are-getting-misdiagnosed" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="misdiagnosed for cardiovascular disease" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.webmd.com/women/news/20180607/why-women-are-getting-misdiagnosed" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;&lt;span&gt;misdiagnosed for cardiovascular disease&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; than men, and 30% more likely to be misdiagnosed when presenting symptoms of a stroke. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Women have to advocate for themselves the moment they walk into a doctor’s office, because that’s the health care system we live in. We have to fight to get tests, labs and appointments, all while being labeled pushy, hysterical and overdramatic. And don’t even get me started on weight stigma. News flash: Not every condition can be solved by losing weight (cancer comes to mind). What’s more, too many women (and too many people in general) don’t have access to insurance, affordable health care or the resources and time to take advantage of it, but that’s a whole other battle. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ultimately, if battling a rare and deadly cancer has taught me anything, it’s to never stop fighting for yourself. I spent countless hours fighting with insurance, begging labs and imaging centers for earlier appointments, and emailing every oncologist in the country for help. It’s your health, and your life. If you have to ruffle a few white-coated feathers, so be it. You’re worth it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This piece was originally published in January 2022 and we’re rerunning it now as part of HuffPost Personal’s “Best Of” series.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Taryn Hillin is a journalist, screenwriter and cancer survivor. She is currently in the Sony Television Diverse Writers program. Prior to that, she was a writer and producer at TMZ, HuffPost and Fusion. When she’s not writing, Taryn helps cancer patients, and people suffering from chronic illness, through her Instagram, &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/theanticancerlife/?hl=en" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="@TheAntiCancerLife" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/theanticancerlife/?hl=en" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="14"&gt;@TheAntiCancerLife&lt;/a&gt; and TikTok, &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@theanticancerlife" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="@TheAntiCancerLife" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.tiktok.com/@theanticancerlife" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="15"&gt;@TheAntiCancerLife&lt;/a&gt;. She is a graduate of Yale.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you have a compelling personal story you’d like to see published&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt; on HuffPost? Find out what we’re looking for &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/how-to-pitch-huffpost-opinion-personal_n_5a5e0726e4b0fcbc3a1388f0" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="here" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="5a5e0726e4b0fcbc3a1388f0" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="16"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="send us a pitch" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694b0046e4b0d09497f9e0b1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;send us a pitch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:52:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQU2xvbFQzcWZ4LUcwMHgzSFhnYW9SX1cxQkt6N3NYSmRuZW5YVDRrNEN2d2JiTEprcFFHa0JRbGpJeERfdXhGZGNnRGE1NUZxTlNhWXN1aVV0bEpoeDJva3hNUkhlMi1CcDI4U1l1NU5yTE9LTXczUXl2bTRfMDgzVGtGQTBTRTVsYk8tRHBuQmFaNkNLYTBLOXlVTzHSAaIBQVVfeXFMTUxqUlBQLUp0N1BrLTJqcjh3VFFQM0E4eUtYeDJfU0djT0xsd1NXLWR5cFNOYkQtNlJaVVFKdHJITEJCaGRKUlFscnItVVZvdjJiWGc4OV9IZnFDY3lySm9VTC01RDZDdHRCcW4wRDZHd3g3R1hsREpkOEhkWVRXM1RsT1lVMU1iQXZXdUo3Q09TZEFSdTNJaTNrcUdmS3NCYW5n</guid></item><item><title>波士顿卫生官员在114%的流感病例激增中发出警告- Boston.com</title><link>https://www.boston.com/news/health/2025/12/23/boston-health-officials-issue-warning-amid-114-spike-in-flu-cases/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="content-well content-well--article" role="main"&gt;
									&lt;p id="presentedby"&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;header class="m-article-header m-article-header--standard"&gt;
												&lt;span id="article-header-primary-term"&gt;
								&lt;a class="a-term a-term--primary" href="https://www.boston.com/tag/health/"&gt;
								Health								&lt;/a&gt;
							&lt;/span&gt;
							
					&lt;h1 class="m-article-header__headline"&gt;Boston health officials issue warning amid 114% spike in flu cases&lt;/h1&gt;
					&lt;h2 class="m-article-header__sub-headline"&gt;The city’s flu surge is happening about a month earlier this year, health officials said.&lt;/h2&gt;

					&lt;figure class="a-photo m-article-header__photo "&gt;
&lt;img src="https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg" class="attachment-16:9 size-16:9 wp-post-image" alt="" decoding="async" srcset="https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=200 200w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=300 300w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=400 400w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=500 500w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=600 600w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=700 700w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=800 800w, https://bdc2020.o0bc.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/ZLJV25IMCKTLAERPZSTCMV3RW4-694af8e4bd7a4-768x432.jpg?width=900 900w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px"&gt;	&lt;figcaption class="a-photo__caption"&gt;
	&lt;em&gt; Joe Raedle / Getty Images, File&lt;/em&gt;	&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

					&lt;div class="m-article-header__meta"&gt;
						&lt;div class="m-article-header__byline"&gt;
							&lt;p class="m-article-header__author"&gt;
								By &lt;a class="a-link a-link--inline" href="https://www.boston.com/author/abby-patkin/"&gt;Abby Patkin&lt;/a&gt;							&lt;/p&gt;

															&lt;time class="m-article-header__date"&gt;
									December 23, 2025 | 3:41 PM								&lt;/time&gt;
							
															&lt;p class="m-article-header__word-estimate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1 minute to read&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
													&lt;/div&gt;
						
					&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/header&gt;

				&lt;p&gt;Boston public health officials are warning of an earlier &lt;a href="https://www.boston.com/news/local-news/2025/09/25/boston-to-offer-free-covid-and-flu-vaccines-at-more-than-a-dozen-locations/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;flu surge&lt;/a&gt; this season, reporting a dramatic 114% spike in cases just days before Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu-related trips to the emergency room have also increased 44% in recent days, and the rate of infection is increasing most rapidly among children, the Boston Public Health Commission said in a &lt;a href="https://www.boston.gov/news/city-boston-and-public-health-commission-warn-residents-significant-increase-flu-cases" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The city’s flu surge is happening about a month earlier this year, health officials said; last flu season, Boston didn’t hit these case numbers until January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Flu cases are on the rise in Boston, and we are urging residents to protect themselves and their loved ones from respiratory illnesses which can cause hospitalization and severe illness,” said Dr. Bisola Ojikutu, the city’s public health commissioner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The city is urging residents to get their annual flu vaccine, particularly children and high-risk adults. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Flu spreads easily during this time of the year when we gather together indoors,” Ojikutu said. “It is not too late to get vaccinated. Vaccination is the best tool we have to prevent serious illness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the Public Health Commission has vaccinated more than 2,500 people across 27 free vaccination clinics to date, only 30% of Boston residents had received their flu shot as of Dec. 6, according to the press release. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ojikutu said health officials will be hosting &lt;a href="https://www.boston.gov/government/cabinets/boston-public-health-commission/viral-respiratory-illness-protection" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;additional clinics&lt;/a&gt; throughout Boston in January. The Public Health Commission also advised hand washing, masking, and staying home when sick to help cut down on the spread. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tuesday’s warning came as seasonal flu activity continues to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/data/activity-levels.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ramp up nationwide&lt;/a&gt; amid chatter about a new &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/22/metro/super-flu-virus-children-kids/?p1=Article_Inline_Text_Link#:~:text=a%20newer%20flu%20strain%20known%20as%20subclade%20K%2C%20a%20subvariant%20of%20the%20H3N2%20subtype%20of%20influenza%20A%20that%20has%20drawn%20attention%20for%20driving%20an%20earlier%2Dthan%2Dusual%20spike%20in%20flu%20cases%20in%20the%20UK%20and%20several%20other%20countries." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;“super flu” variant&lt;/a&gt;. Data from the Massachusetts Department of Public Health indicates the level of influenza-like illness is &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/influenza-reporting" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;“high” or “very high”&lt;/a&gt; throughout most of the state.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="o-author-single has-avatar"&gt;

	
	&lt;section class="author-info"&gt;
		&lt;div class="m-author__section"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abby Patkin is a general assignment news reporter whose work touches on public transit, crime, health, and everything in between.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;	&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="m-block m-generic-cta
	 m-generic-cta--post-content	 m-generic-cta--dark	 m-generic-cta--homepage	 m-generic-cta--email-signup		 m-generic-cta-block-style--default 
	t-amp__generic-cta"&gt;
		&lt;div class="m-generic-cta__wrap"&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div class="m-generic-cta__content"&gt;
							&lt;h3 class="m-generic-cta__title"&gt;Sign up for the Today newsletter&lt;/h3&gt;
			
							&lt;p class="m-generic-cta__subtitle"&gt;Get everything you need to know to start your day, delivered right to your inbox every morning.&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
		

			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

								&lt;p class="content-below-article"&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;
				
		&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;


			&lt;/article&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Boston.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:41:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPWFJNRGs2djJTR1RoR0ctMEpGSVZPbThVZWhxT0czaGVLZkR3M2NPMURUX210QVRVUVN1dkFISU9JdFl5V0VoT2RfY1FwTHk5bFM4QWRqR0oxSmZQdmpBVkRxYVhsc0txcTh1eHpXNkk5dFA3VTl1VEhHN182RzVVOUYxVjRvck44X0Z6RGJTUU9vbEVUQ3JyOEd6OHdyLUtHS3NEWWpnQzU5RnQtajZiT3dR</guid></item><item><title>PAWS芝加哥关于芝加哥狗狂犬病病例的官方声明- PAWS芝加哥</title><link>https://www.pawschicago.org/news-resources/news-features/paws-chicago-news/paws-chicago-news-item/showarticle/paws-chicago-official-statement-on-rabies-case-in-chicago-dog</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PAWS Chicago</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 20:29:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAJBVV95cUxPLWs4a19INkZjYW1XOS1TVGJpN0dkV0ZYWGhlVGkzQVRyQXdDVTBnRHZMMU9BWlU0aVg4RWpaUzd1NUo0Q3ZOT3RoSGVrLUlmVFJwWm5fd0xpYTR5bkExeWRTQVRBeHNQT2lOZFBIM2w5eEFjcEVkX2hoS1hzYkcxZHdGVzJiSks3WGlDeXFVaVAwTzkxUlA5M3h1N1otZzR5QUNFT0d3bmhyVTRoUkNVcTdEWnhRenRaUUMwTTRGb3VlWTM5VHV1M1ViTEZyZDdjaVZTRXBDbjAxX1NVa3dFb2RKMW4wbmVYa0hRUFJlbGoxZGZ4dzZLc1otQjVDdFpR</guid></item><item><title>哲学专家分享亚里士多德的简单方法，了解您是否有“伟大的头脑” - Upworthy</title><link>https://www.upworthy.com/philosophy-expert-shares-aristotle-s-simple-way-to-know-if-you-have-a-great-mind</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the strangest things about &lt;a data-linked-post="2674400997" href="https://www.upworthy.com/these-10-weird-habits-might-be-an-indicator-of-high-intelligence" target="_blank"&gt;highly intelligent people &lt;/a&gt;is that they are very aware of what they don’t know. The psychological phenomenon known as the &lt;a data-linked-post="2659482310" href="https://www.upworthy.com/dunning-kruger-effect" target="_blank"&gt;Dunning-Kruger &lt;/a&gt;effect suggests that the more&lt;a data-linked-post="2674282254" href="https://www.upworthy.com/8-emotionally-intelligent-phrases-that-will-strengthen-your-marriage" target="_blank"&gt; intelligent&lt;/a&gt; someone is, the more they fixate on their perceived gaps in intelligence, leading them to underestimate themselves. Conversely, those who aren’t very intelligent overestimate their &lt;a data-linked-post="2656403033" href="https://www.upworthy.com/jimmy-kimmel-men-test-female-anatomy-rp7" target="_blank"&gt;knowledge&lt;/a&gt; on a subject.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The great mind might be more preoccupied with the gaps in its knowledge than the smaller mind that thinks it knows everything. How can someone see if they have a great mind? &lt;a href="https://www.good.is/research-on-600000-college-students-shows-that-studying-philosophy-makes-them-better-thinkers" target="_blank"&gt;Philosophy&lt;/a&gt; expert Julian de Medeiros says it all goes back to Aristotle's “rule of thumb.” De Medeiros &lt;a href="https://julianphilosophy.substack.com/" target="_blank"&gt;writes a Substack&lt;/a&gt; on philosophy and has over 1.4 million&lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@julianphilosophy?" target="_blank"&gt; followers on TikTok&lt;/a&gt;, where he analyzes the mysteries of love, intelligence, and friendship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to know you are brilliant&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="rm-shortcode" data-rm-shortcode-id="a5f7e6afc780f8b9cd59cad0a626a032" data-thumbnail="" id="ec62a"&gt;&lt;blockquote cite="https://www.tiktok.com/@julianphilosophy/video/7295512220010794286" class="tiktok_lazy_shortcode" data-video-id="7295512220010794286"&gt;&lt;section&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@julianphilosophy" target="_blank" title="@julianphilosophy"&gt;@julianphilosophy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simple theory about intelligence #intelligent #intelligence #smart #genius #creative #power&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Here's a simple sign that you are intelligent, that you have a great mind, and it's a simple theory, a rule of thumb, that goes back to an observation by the philosopher Aristotle, who once wrote: ‘No great mind has ever existed without a touch of madness,’” de Medeiros says. “By which he meant that there's a fine line indeed between being a genius and being a madman.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Schopenhauer on what makes a genius&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As the philosopher Schopenhauer once wrote: ‘Talent is when you can hit a target no one else can hit. Genius is when you can hit a target no one else can see,” de Medeiros continued. “Now to have a great mind, therefore, means that you can see and think things that other people can't. But this puts you on a kind of border where there's a liminal line between what is real and what is not. Your mind is a double-edged sword, both a blessing and a curse, and that very intelligent people can also fall off the edge into the abyss.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aristotle lived more than 2,300 years ago, when our knowledge of mental and physical health was a fraction of what we know now. But, interestingly, he was correct in believing that highly intelligent people may face greater psychological struggles than those of normal intelligence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study&lt;a href="https://www.us.mensa.org/learn/about/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt; published by&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Mensa foundthat knowledgeable people are are 20% more likely to have an autism spectrum disorder (ASD) diagnosis. They are 80% ore liekly to be diagnosed with ADHD and 182% more likely to have a mood disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is it that highly intelligent people are more likely to suffer from mental disorders? &lt;a href="https://www.hanleycenter.org/why-are-intelligent-people-more-prone-to-mental-illness/" target="_blank"&gt;A study found&lt;/a&gt; that it may be caused by psychological excitability. Highly intelligent people are known to fixate on things. This can be a big help when you are problem-solving at work, but it can become a problem when you become preoccupied with a comment from your boss or a social interaction that you can't stop playing over and over in your head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a funny way that life always seems to balance things out. You can either be unintelligent and think you know everything, or be brilliant and focused on everything you don’t know. It shows that, with respect to intelligence, having a psychological understanding of yourself is one of the keys to living a healthy and happy life. Or, as Aristotle once put it: “Knowing yourself is the beginning of all wisdom.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Upworthy</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:07:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPSjNDdndhYmFiZFo4V2w0dHhjTXhxUXJXS2dISUE4WHJueHFabEd3VlV0aXFqRzROS2o0OWpxYlBOUnczdlJtNURjRUtWMkViTVluTFhOc0x1czFxSFpodVExRFFFdnBYTENTbUszSG9nZEpJaFREOUY4aVFGUEcybTFRdVV6TW9kVUF6SUVUUUdLRHlucWF0M0lyVVhuNEI1NHVVWEMtd2U</guid></item><item><title>科学家创造人类子宫内膜复制品并植入早期胚胎-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/dec/23/scientists-create-replica-human-womb-lining-and-implant-early-stage-embryos</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Researchers have created the lining of a womb in a dish, which promises to shed light on the mysterious early stages of human pregnancy and the glitches that can lead to miscarriage and medical complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In laboratory experiments, early-stage human embryos donated from couples after &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/ivf" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;IVF&lt;/a&gt; treatment successfully implanted into the engineered lining and began to churn out key compounds, such as the hormone that results in a blue line on positive pregnancy tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The approach allowed scientists to eavesdrop on the chemical chatter that arises between the embryo and the womb lining as it embeds and begins to be nourished in the first weeks of gestation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s incredible to see it,” said Dr Peter Rugg-Gunn, a senior author on the study and group leader at the Babraham Institute in Cambridge. “Previously we’ve only had snapshots of this critical stage of pregnancy. This opens up a lot of new directions for us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Implantation takes place a week or so after fertilisation when the developing embryo attaches and then embeds itself into the uterus wall. It is a crucial phase in pregnancy, but the process is poorly understood because it is so hard to observe. Much of what is known comes from studies of hysterectomies that were performed in early pregnancy more than half a century ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To build the replica womb lining, Rugg-Gunn and his colleagues obtained uterine tissue from healthy women who donated biopsy samples. From this, the scientists isolated two different types of cells: stromal cells that give structural support to the womb lining, and epithelial cells, which form the lining’s surface. They encapsulated the stromal cells in a biodegradable material called a hydrogel and put the epithelial cells on top.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The researchers tested the engineered womb lining with donated early-stage IVF embryos. Writing in &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01232-2" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the journal Cell&lt;/a&gt;, they describe how the microscopic balls of cells attached and implanted as hoped. They then ramped up secretion of a hormone called human chorionic gonadotropin (hCG), the biochemical marker detected by pregnancy tests, along with other pregnancy-related compounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The technique enabled scientists to watch embryos grow for up to 14 days post-fertilisation, the legal limit for research. During the process, the embryos formed specialised cells and other cells involved in the growth of the placenta.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To understand the process more deeply, the scientists zoomed in on the spots where embryos had embedded in the engineered womb lining and decoded the molecular signals that passed back and forth. Such signals are critical for achieving and maintaining a healthy pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:9,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:4156,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;morning-briefing&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Our morning email breaks down the key stories of the day, telling you what’s happening and why it matters&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;First Edition&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;We'll send you First Edition every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;news&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="77432e95-1196-4fe5-b3b3-287a709945f5" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":10,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Equivalent of one child in every British classroom now born via IVF, data shows","elementId":"77432e95-1196-4fe5-b3b3-287a709945f5","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/jun/26/one-child-every-british-classroom-born-via-ivf-fertility"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists will now use the approach to investigate how pregnancies become established and what can go awry. “We know that half of all embryos fail to implant and we have no idea why,” Rugg-Gunn said. Finding answers could provide a much-needed boost to IVF success rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Further experiments will explore what happens after implantation when the placenta starts to form. Many serious complications of pregnancy are thought to arise at this stage. In the study, the researchers used a chemical to block a particular signal between the embryo and the lining, producing severe defects in the tissue that forms the placenta, demonstrating its power for testing the impact of signalling problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01230-9" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;separate study&lt;/a&gt; in the journal, Chinese researchers created their own replica womb lining and identified drugs that might improve implantation rates in patients with recurrent implantation failure (RIF), where good-quality IVF embryos fail to establish a pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;John Aplin, a professor of reproductive medicine at the University of Manchester, said that during 40-plus years of assisted reproduction, implantation rates had remained stubbornly low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“As the embryo implants, a programme is initiated to begin development of the placenta, which will supply nutrients and oxygen to the foetus,” he said. “The earliest stages are crucial to the progression of the pregnancy, are not well understood, and frequently fail. This work will allow treatments to be explored that seek to improve implantation efficiency.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:56:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxObGxvOTVkbnRQd2dtZWxQbTBuRWxJYnEzQkZMSERVaDNXdmVKTTZ0ak85NXcyc2U3eHZpa0x4RlJPT3Fqc2pJUXpLTVJ4UnIxYU1WLVBlMHRIUnc2N3Rud1hSaHhITjVvOU80SVFRcnIxY2NObzFiZWlhWFpkRmF5YnBEWUxXWURGaE45MWhSSmNlRXg2R1l1SWlIbGgyemhFWmNYa1RCajhaM3ZFRTBrOG4yWlJ2a0hUSkltN0g3eTg</guid></item><item><title>不考虑任何事情：迈向心灵消失的大脑特征- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-brain-signature-mind-blanking.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:45:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBiR05ldFdDR3Z0a1p4VEZ4cnRCVlVmeHc5dl9tc2h6R0VxS2ZPemFvTFJOTG0yaWZmVU5EaDU1dGV1RE1YYllyMmZ5Rm01eEFJNktWVHJtWm4yZF95ZVRJQnFDRUtETURLM3RYbnJGdWlOSVZmMURVTThzZFNNUQ</guid></item><item><title>医院在呼吸道疾病增加的情况下暂时实施访客限制- WHIO TV</title><link>https://www.whio.com/news/local/hospitals-temporarily-limit-visitor-restrictions-amid-increase-respiratory-illness/EMQ7PUCYF5DZPMVYZYFNF3PBZA/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;DAYTON — Hospitals across the region are implementing temporary visitor restrictions amid a recent increase in respiratory illness beginning Dec. 26. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[DOWNLOAD: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free WHIO-TV News app for alerts as news breaks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Area hospitals are currently seeing higher-than-normal volumes of patients with positive cases of respiratory illnesses, including influenza, COVID-19, and other seasonal viruses, according to the Greater Dayton Area Hospital Association &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRENDING STORIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;When implemented, the restrictions will be as follows: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;No visitation by anyone who is ill with any respiratory symptoms including coughing, fever, chills, headache, vomiting, sore throat, muscle aches or diarrhea&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;No visitation by anyone under age 14 even if they have received the seasonal influenza vaccine or receive the appropriate vaccine when it becomes available&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Hospitals are asking community members to postpone visiting if they are feeling unwell, especially if experiencing symptoms such as fever, cough, sore throat, or congestion. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Visitor restrictions are temporary and will be reviewed regularly, GDAHA said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;GDAHA is a member-service organization representing 29 hospitals and health systems in the Dayton region. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters" target="_self" rel="" title="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHIO-TV Daily Headlines Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHIO TV</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:25:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2gFBVV95cUxOWG5OV0V1aVoxSkRIeTYwa1FqNF95TFVPR25NS3BERUJQR0tOSVVTb0pnWkNjTENtQ1hGUlFpUXd1c1NzdTVMS0xuRTVsN2NiZ3A4c1J0emRoNktkSnFJMzFhUEJQTEJQcjZ1QmtfSXU2TDA3Y0hDd2ZjcTNFTjZtWG1UaUtxSmNCa0VJb3FlUE5Mcy1WbFJMSEx1YWdiRTFFZjNJY1hNTEVlcTY4aVdPVDlqeWV3QmdBRzA2TnViZGZwUmE1eF9kSmRjOTN2SUctc0pocjkzQUREZ9IB7gFBVV95cUxNQmpQVkNuTkhnNnJUbGFqYk9MQjI2b3QtZzFjZVdBbnNQbnRBZkd2TlJyVHRoeUxnaXl3cHJGakJRY0pTejYxR3ZLa0ZJSGJDTHNqMWxmbnNaU2Ywd0VydWgwX2w2RDNYWEg4bXlXRTRMMDZPYnJzMkRUV3pOUlV5RmVYd0tEMVNBRlZiMDVrSFRqSlFKNGRKXzBBS2Z0V0VWY09iMGdIQ2NYak1DN1dDcUdLZVVkNW9yZjRtb2ZWUlBnZDg1LVVjNFRZR0lCci1IbEFUVE9iajA4RDhPaVo1dngwV2VKWXp1MEVpM3VR</guid></item><item><title>数据是减缓与年龄相关疾病的关键- WIRED</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/data-holds-the-key-in-slowing-age-related-illnesses/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;In 2026, we&lt;/span&gt; will see the beginning of precision medical forecasting. Just as there have been remarkable advances in weather forecasting with the use of large language models, so will there be for determining an individual’s risk of the major age-related diseases (cancer, cardiovascular, and neurodegenerative). These diseases share common threads, such as a long incubation phase before any symptoms are manifest, usually two decades or more. They also have the same biologic underpinnings of immunosenescence and inflammaging, terms that characterize an immune system that has lost some of its functionality and protective power, and the accompanying heightened inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The science of aging has given us new ways to track these processes with body-wide and organ clocks, along with specific protein biomarkers. That enables us to determine whether a person or an organ within a person is aging at an accelerated pace. Along with that, new AI algorithms can see things that medical experts cannot, such as accurately interpreting medical images like retinal scans to predict cardiovascular and neurodegenerative diseases many years in advance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="GenericCalloutWrapper-IJXIe ejayGs callout--has-top-border" data-testid="GenericCallout"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;These added layers of data can be combined with a person’s electronic medical records, which include their structured and unstructured notes, lab results, scans, genetic results, wearable sensors, and environmental data. In aggregate, this provides an unprecedented depth of information about the person’s health status, enabling a forecast for risk of the three major diseases. Unlike a polygenic risk score which can detect a person’s risk for heart disease, the common cancers and Alzheimer’s, precision medical forecasting takes it to a new level by providing the projected temporal arc—the “when” factor. When all of the data is analyzed with large reasoning models, it can provide a person’s vulnerabilities, and an individualized, aggressive preventive program.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;We already know the risk of these three diseases can be reduced with lifestyle factors, such as an optimal anti-inflammatory diet, frequent exercise, and a regular, high-quality sleep pattern. But, along with attention to these factors, which are far more likely to be implemented when an individual is cognizant of their risk, we will have medications that will promote a healthy, protective immune system and reduce body-wide and brain inflammation. Already the GLP-1 medicines have been shown to be a front-runner for achieving these goals, but many more medications are in the pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The potential for precision medical forecasting has to be demonstrated and validated via prospective clinical trials that show, using the same metrics of aging, that a person’s risk is decreased. An example for people with increased risk of Alzheimer’s is the blood test known as &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41398-024-03084-7"&gt;p-tau217&lt;/a&gt;, and that risk can be markedly reduced with improved lifestyle factors, especially exercise. That could be confirmed with a brain organ clock and body-wide aging clocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;This is a new frontier in medicine—the potential for primary prevention of the three age-related major diseases that compromise our health span and quality of life. It would not be possible without the advances in both the science of aging and AI. For me, this is the most exciting future use of AI in medicine: an unparalleled opportunity to prevent the major diseases from occurring, something that has been dreamed about but has not been possible at scale due to the deficiency in data and analytics. In 2026, it finally will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 18:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQMXVjb0dGSW1kYnQta3ptaTBUZmJYVENWbnFTR3hWUl9NTzVFMzVUa0JHM2t2TmFJdUVVY013WTBRNmlNSlhOTDlNRlpHNlA3VU9namk5OFkxSXFuYnJwdzZZUEtzaEVjbndtV1VVTXlib2dXS1hsZWNHTjg2dnc2dl9rWnB0RGc</guid></item><item><title>流感很早就袭击了加利福尼亚州。为什么医生担心今年对孩子来说会特别困难-洛杉矶时报</title><link>https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2025-12-23/flu-season-hits-california-early-doctors-worry-itll-be-hard-on-kids</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-element="story-body" class="ct-rich-text-children font-cms-font-brand-text font-normal text-lg leading-7.75 [&amp;amp;_&amp;gt;p]:text-cms-story-body-color-text clearfix mb-10 md:max-w-170 md:mx-auto" data-subscriber-content&gt; &lt;p&gt;Fueled by a new viral strain, flu is hitting California early — and doctors are warning they expect the season may be particularly tough on young children. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concentrations of flu detected in wastewater have surged in the San Francisco Bay Area, and the test positivity rate is rising in &lt;a class="link" href="https://ph.lacounty.gov/acd/respwatch/" target="_blank"&gt;Los Angeles County&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.ochealthinfo.com/respiratoryvirus" target="_blank"&gt;Orange County&lt;/a&gt;, according to &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdph.ca.gov/Programs/CID/DCDC/Pages/RespiratoryVirusReport.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;state&lt;/a&gt; and county data. Hospitalizations and emergency room visits for flu are also rising in L.A. and Orange counties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are at the point now where we’re starting to see a sharp rise in flu cases. This is a few weeks earlier than we usually experience, but very much akin to what was seen in the Southern Hemisphere’s experience with flu during their winter,” said Dr. Elizabeth Hudson, regional physician director of infectious diseases at Kaiser Permanente Southern California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Kaiser, flu cases are primarily being seen in clinics so far, but hospitalizations typically rise after Christmas. “We expect to see the same this year, too,” Hudson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The number of cases appears to be higher at an earlier time in the usual flu season than we’ve seen in years past,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu levels are high in San Francisco’s sewage as well as in wastewater across San José, Sunnyvale and Palo Alto, &lt;a class="link" href="https://data.wastewaterscan.org/" target="_blank"&gt;according to&lt;/a&gt; WastewaterSCAN and the &lt;a class="link" href="https://publichealth.santaclaracounty.gov/health-information/health-data/respiratory-virus-data" target="_blank"&gt;Santa Clara County Public Health Department&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One area of concern this winter has been the rise of a relatively new flu subvariant, known as H3N2 Flu A subclade K, which appeared toward the end of summer. That was months after officials decided which strains this fall’s flu vaccine would target. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subclade K “is causing an active, early flu season, with more cases occurring in some countries within the Northern Hemisphere,” the California Department of Public Health &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdph.ca.gov/Programs/CID/DCDC/Pages/RespiratoryVirusReport.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear whether subclade K will reduce the efficacy of this year’s flu shot. Data recently released in Britain showed this season’s vaccines were 70% to 75% effective against hospitalization for children from the flu, and 30% to 40% effective in adults, which is within expectations, the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-49.html" target="_blank"&gt;noted.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This suggests “that influenza vaccination remains an effective tool in preventing influenza-related hospitalizations this season,” according to the agency. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the intended effectiveness of the flu vaccine against symptomatic disease caused by the new subvariant remains uncertain, the World Health Organization said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, flu rates in L.A. County remain relatively low, but are on the rise. Across California, flu hospitalizations are likewise low but increasing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a national level, severity indicators remain low, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the experience in other nations have led some experts to worry &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2025-02-11/worst-flu-season-in-5-years-hits-california"&gt;another severe flu season&lt;/a&gt; could be on deck for California. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia’s flu season, which is seasonally opposite from California’s, came far earlier than usual, hit with record strength and was particularly hard on the nation’s children. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan, Taiwan and Britain have also reported early spikes to their flu seasons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Whether or not this season will be more severe, only time will tell,” Hudson said of California. “We know that we have a mutation ... which may make the flu vaccine work less well. But the vaccine still offers excellent protection against hospitalization and death, even with the mutated strain in circulation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on what happened in the Southern Hemisphere — particularly in Australia — “we are expecting this season to have a disproportionate impact on children under the age of 10,” Hudson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Already, three flu-associated pediatric deaths have been reported nationally this season, including two &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-50.html" target="_blank"&gt;Friday&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the flu season that ended in September, 280 &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2025-05-02/cdc-reports-216-child-deaths-this-flu-season-the-most-in-15-years"&gt;children died from flu&lt;/a&gt; — the most since the swine flu pandemic season of 2009-10. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, the 2024-25 season was considered the worst flu season since 2017-18, and hit adults hard as well. At least 38,000 people died from the flu &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7436a2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;last season&lt;/a&gt;, health authorities estimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only a little more than half of the children who died from flu had an underlying medical condition, and 89% of those who died were not vaccinated, according to the &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7436a2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;CDC’s National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the children who died from flu last season, the most common &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7436a2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;complications&lt;/a&gt; experienced before death were shock or sepsis, pneumonia, acute respiratory distress syndrome, seizures and damage to the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early diagnosis of flu can help stave off the worst by giving those who are sick time to take antiviral medications like Tamiflu. Three out of five children who died from the flu during the 2024-25 season never received antiviral medication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/signs-symptoms/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Emergency warning signs of flu complications&lt;/a&gt; in children include trouble breathing; bluish lips or face; ribs pulling in with each breath; chest pain; severe muscle pain, in which a child may refuse to walk; dehydration, signs of which include no urine for eight hours or no tears when crying; seizures; fevers above 104 degrees that are not controlled by medication; fever or cough that improve but return or worsen; and any fever in newborns younger than 12 weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the official start of &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.latimes.com/world-nation/story/2025-11-04/during-cold-flu-season-youngest-students-germiest"&gt;the respiratory virus season&lt;/a&gt; Oct. 1, the CDC estimates there have been at least 1,900 flu-related deaths, 49,000 hospitalizations and 4.6 million illnesses nationwide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors have been urging everybody to get the flu vaccine — the CDC recommends it for everyone age 6 months and up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But vaccination rates have been lagging. Among children age 6 months to 17 years, an estimated 40.8% had been vaccinated as of the first week of December, according to the &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/children-vaccination-coverage.html" target="_blank"&gt;National Immunization Survey&lt;/a&gt;. In the last season before the COVID-19 pandemic, flu vaccination rates were notably higher by this time of year, at 51.2%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of last flu season, only 49.8% of children and teens had been vaccinated, the survey estimated, down from the 62.4% who had gotten their shots by the end of the 2019-20 flu season. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decline in flu vaccinations has been seen locally, too. “Notably, fewer influenza vaccines have been administered this year compared to the same period last year,” the Orange County Health Care Agency &lt;a class="link" href="https://myemail.constantcontact.com/CD-HEALTH-ALERT--2025-2026-Respiratory-Virus-Season-Update---Increasing-Influenza-and-Respiratory-Syncytial-Virus--RSV-.html?soid=1128423022889&amp;amp;aid=vDIRaAQ0y1w" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It takes about two weeks for protection to build, but getting vaccinated as soon as possible before travel or seeing friends and family “helps keep you and your loved ones safer,” the L.A. County Department of Public Health said in a statement to The Times. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Los Angeles Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:20:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxOZjdYLXk2dFZFRWZoc1JWbHdGRTFPWUs1UlRkSUJ5bFRaTDdLYUV0Smk2bUxHOGtNcnFfVDF1dkk4YURROUdXdnBtVGZaRkRDUVpRcVFiSTZ4VUdCT3VwVkl1cE1MMmdQdXBySGZOaHFVbXVYaVJpSkdhbUpsZlN5Znp1RWFTWE9CMTdDMW9USHktbjY0Y003WUhiT05NZEZ6SXhkMUg5dXBkZWVrVFEzRGJpaU4wOWQydGNn</guid></item><item><title>安德鲁·齐默恩（ Andrew Zimmern ）在食用普通香料后收缩的无法治愈的状况-外卖</title><link>https://www.thetakeout.com/2022093/andrew-zimmern-burning-mouth-syndrome-cumin/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="content" class="article"&gt;
            

            &lt;article class="news-post"&gt;
    
    
    
                &lt;p class="news-article"&gt;
                &lt;h1 class="title-gallery" data-post-id="2022093" id="title-gallery" data-has-pixel-tags="1" data-pixel-tag="thetakeout" data-author="Lindsey Reynolds" data-category="food-tv" data-content_type="Short Article" data-mod_date="2025-12-23" data-layout="Infinite" data-post_id="2022093" data-pub_date="2025-12-23" data-day="Tuesday" data-dayhour="Tuesday-12PM" data-pubhour="12PM" data-num_slides="2" data-num_words="500" data-pitcher="Trevor Lowry" data-trello_board="News" data-intent="short-term" data-ideation="oo-hits"&gt;The Incurable Condition Andrew Zimmern Contracted After Eating A Common Spice&lt;/h1&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;

    
                &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                                
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap lead-image-holder" data-post-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2022093/andrew-zimmern-burning-mouth-syndrome-cumin/" data-post-title="The Incurable Condition Andrew Zimmern Contracted After Eating A Common Spice" data-slide-num="0" data-post-id="2022093"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p9a0ab81c523860a2b4ed9c0b1f0fd71c"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-incurable-condition-andrew-zimmern-contracted-after-eating-a-common-spice/intro-1758867228.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-incurable-condition-andrew-zimmern-contracted-after-eating-a-common-spice/intro-1758867228.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-incurable-condition-andrew-zimmern-contracted-after-eating-a-common-spice/intro-1758867228.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2022093/andrew-zimmern-burning-mouth-syndrome-cumin/" data-post-id="2022093" data-slide-num="0" data-slide-title="The Incurable Condition Andrew Zimmern Contracted After Eating A Common Spice: " alt="Chef Andrew Zimmern poses in front of lanterns"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Jason Koerner/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                
                
                &lt;p&gt;Television host and culinary adventurer Andrew Zimmern has eaten everything from fermented shark in Iceland (&lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/1578916/hakarl-shark-meat-anthony-bourdain/" target="_blank"&gt;which Anthony Bourdain refused to eat ever again&lt;/a&gt;) to still-beating snake hearts in Vietnam. But even with all of his experience, he was caught off guard by a painful, lingering condition he says he picked up while filming in northern Africa: burning mouth syndrome (BMS). Sometimes called glossodynia, BMS is characterized by a chronic, often unexplained burning or tingling sensation on the tongue, lips, or entire mouth. In an "Ask Me Anything" event on &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/3f63r4/comment/ctlown6/" target="_blank"&gt;Reddit&lt;/a&gt;, Zimmern explained what happened: "In 2005, I contracted a virus from eating tainted cumin in Northern Africa. Occasionally once a year I have a flare-up of a rare disease called burning mouth syndrome. I pass it off as a simple casualty of war." &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an interview with &lt;a href="https://abcnews.go.com/Entertainment/bizarre-foods-andrew-zimmern-things-famous-tv-chef/story?id=26815920" target="_blank"&gt;ABC&lt;/a&gt;, he elaborated further: "I carry medication around with me in case it flares up. It's been about two years since a flare-up, it's viral ... there are only a handful of people in the world who have it." At first, Zimmern believed he'd simply overwhelmed his taste buds — obviously an occupational hazard for someone whose job was once to literally consume weird meats around the world (&lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/andrew-zimmern-picks-the-best-and-worst-tasting-animal-1798251700/" target="_blank"&gt;here are his best- and worst-tasting animals&lt;/a&gt;). But even after returning home, the burning did not subside. Doctors eventually diagnosed him with the neuropathic condition, and its exact causes remain mysterious. Though there's more than a "handful" of people who have it, global estimates suggest that about 1–3% of the world's population experiences the condition.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;Tainted spices are a documented concern&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2022093/andrew-zimmern-burning-mouth-syndrome-cumin/" data-post-title="The Incurable Condition Andrew Zimmern Contracted After Eating A Common Spice" data-slide-num="1" data-post-id="2022093"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p8a0934f7abf755a6b2335765594379fa"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-incurable-condition-andrew-zimmern-contracted-after-eating-a-common-spice/tainted-spices-are-a-documented-concern-1758867231.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-incurable-condition-andrew-zimmern-contracted-after-eating-a-common-spice/tainted-spices-are-a-documented-concern-1758867231.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/the-incurable-condition-andrew-zimmern-contracted-after-eating-a-common-spice/tainted-spices-are-a-documented-concern-1758867231.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2022093/andrew-zimmern-burning-mouth-syndrome-cumin/" data-post-id="2022093" data-slide-num="1" data-slide-title="The Incurable Condition Andrew Zimmern Contracted After Eating A Common Spice: Tainted spices are a documented concern" alt="open air spice display featuring bulk cumin"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Ellionn/Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;But is a tainted spice really to blame? To be sure, cumin is one of the most heavily traded spices in the world, and because it's often sold ground, it is indeed vulnerable to both intentional and unintentional adulteration. The bulk spice is used daily in cuisines across North Africa, the Middle East, South Asia, and Latin America. Often sold in open sacks or scooped loose in outdoor markets, it's certainly possible for it to be exposed to dust, bacteria, and other nasty bits floating through the air. In 2015, one of the largest spice recalls in the U.S. involved cumin contaminated with peanut protein. Perhaps unsurprisingly, undisclosed allergens are actually one of &lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/1853246/common-reasons-food-recalls/" target="_blank"&gt;the most common reasons foods are recalled&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It doesn't seem that Zimmern has slowed down on his spicy foods or changed his adventurous behavior, other than carrying a steroidal rinse in case of flare-ups. He continues to travel and film internationally, but these days his focus is on his current show, "Wild Game Kitchen," where he cooks wild food over an open fire. His spicy experience is certainly a high-profile example of how even seasoned culinary professionals can develop chronic conditions from repeated sensory exposure. Today, North Africa remains one of Zimmern's favorite food regions, and he even still uses cumin in his recipes. But just in case we've scared you from ever using the earthy spice again, we've got &lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/1754931/cumin-substitute-spices/" target="_blank"&gt;four substitutes for cumin in recipes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

    
&lt;/article&gt;                        
            
                            
                           &lt;p id="div-ad-1x1a" class="google-ad-placeholder clear placeholder placeholder-1-1" data-ad-height="any" data-ad-width="any" data-ad-pos="1x1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Takeout</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNUjUtZk1yeDZYM0F4Y1NCTlpqdkwxN0xkOTdEeno4dWM2ZGJ2SW1YYUQ5cmNrUTNVZ2ppQnJjVWlLZFF1NTJVOGNmUmloTElCR3VaZGtGNTN0OGVzeGs5UXlyN3h3T2tkTlZrM2tlSTRNOFBNdnVRTWQ3WGRremI1bXlrRHZDQQ</guid></item><item><title>55岁后，扁平腹部的5种椅子锻炼比腹部锻炼更快-吃这个不是那个</title><link>https://www.eatthis.com/chair-exercises-flatten-belly-overhang-after-55/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content single-post-content"&gt;
																			&lt;p class="tagline"&gt;Belly overhang after 55? Do these 5 chair moves to burn calories and tighten your core.&lt;/p&gt;
												
																			
																		
						
						
						&lt;p&gt;If you’re over 55 and frustrated with stubborn belly overhang that you just can’t seem to get rid of, you’re not alone. According to a &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9582849" target="_blank"&gt;2022 survey&lt;/a&gt;, more than half of Americans have abdominal obesity. But that doesn’t mean you should throw in the towel and give up on your weight loss goals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest myths in fitness is that endless ab workouts are the best way to flatten your midsection. But in reality, crunches and sit-ups alone rarely deliver visible results, especially as you age. &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.jci.org/articles/view/158451" target="_blank"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; shows that hormonal changes, slower metabolism, and natural muscle loss all shift how and where your body stores fat. That’s why many traditional ab workouts stop working as you age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, what works better for weight loss are chair exercises that burn calories, engage large muscle groups, and strengthen your core without harming your joints. Far from being a watered-down option, chair-based training allows you to stay active, elevate your heart rate, and build muscle safely, especially if balance, joint pain, or mobility issues make floor exercises uncomfortable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To find out which chair exercises are best for melting away unwanted belly fat, we chatted with&lt;b&gt; Abbie Watkins, CPT&lt;/b&gt;, a certified personal trainer with &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.origym.co.uk/blog/author/abbiew/" target="_blank"&gt;OriGym&lt;/a&gt;, who shares her top best chair moves for older adults to combine strength and movement in a way that’s accessible and sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But before we dive in, it’s crucial to note that no exercise can “spot reduce” belly fat. Instead, performing exercises that engage your core while activating your legs and upper body can help your body burn more total calories. Eventually, that calorie burn combined with strength training can reduce belly overhang and improve how your waistline looks and feels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Read on for Watkins’ five most effective chair exercises for adults over 55.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed karma_unit--halfpage"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(And when you’re finished, check out &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/4-standing-moves-elite-fitness-at-60/" target="_blank"&gt;If You Can Master These 4 Standing Moves at 60, You’re Fitter Than Most 40-Year-Olds&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="seated-knee-drives" class="o-slide-title" data-num="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seated Knee Drives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/PRDy1pZvkJg?si=PYXvD1FWRPKaT1gw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seated knee drives are one of the best ways to elevate your heart rate and activate your core without impacting your joint health. Because the movement alternates sides, it also challenges coordination and keeps your abdominal muscles engaged throughout the exercise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watkins says seated knee drives are effective because they “elevate your heart rate, burn calories, improve coordination, and strengthen your abdominal muscles without putting stress on the joints.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Do It:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit up tall near the front edge of a sturdy chair with your feet flat on the floor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Place your hands lightly on the sides of the chair for support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brace your core by gently pulling your belly button toward your spine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift one knee toward your chest while keeping your torso upright.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower your foot back to the floor with control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alternate sides in a steady, marching rhythm.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aim for 15 to 20 reps per leg for two to three sets. Rest for 30 to 60 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="chair-squats" class="o-slide-title" data-num="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Chair Squats&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GIz1C3yfE1s?si=MEOrg3oRkn35HnHv&amp;amp;start=5" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Squats are one of the most effective compound exercises you can do, and this variation is perfect for those 55 and older. “Chair squats mimics a traditional squat, but with extra support, making them a more accessible alternative,” explains Watkins. “Similar to squats, they target large muscle groups like the glutes and thighs.”&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;6254a4d1642c605c54bf1cab17d50f1e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Do It:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Begin seated with your feet shoulder-width apart and your toes pointing forward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shift your weight slightly forward so your chest is over your feet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press through your heels to stand up tall without using your hands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fully extend your hips at the top while keeping your core engaged.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slowly lower yourself back toward the chair over two to three seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lightly touch the chair before repeating the next rep.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete two to three sets of 12 to 15 reps with 45 to 60 seconds of rest between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="seated-punches" class="o-slide-title" data-num="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seated Punches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FyaEGllqGDc?si=9qWpSI1PohepJDWz&amp;amp;start=5" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seated punches add an upper-body cardio element that many ab workouts lack. They also get your heart pumping while activating muscles in your shoulders, arms, and core. “Seated punches combine upper body strength work and cardio, making them a great way to burn calories even in a seated position,” Watkins says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Do It:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit up straight with your feet flat on the floor and your knees bent at 90 degrees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tighten your core and keep your chest lifted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raise your fists to shoulder height with your elbows bent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Punch one arm straight forward while slightly rotating your torso.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Retract your arm back to the starting position with control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alternate arms while maintaining a steady, controlled pace.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform this movement for 30 to 45 seconds at a time. Aim for two to three sets with 30 to 45 seconds of rest between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="chair-leg-extensions" class="o-slide-title" data-num="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Chair Leg Extensions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/R3jwIVNi7PY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leg extensions strengthen your thighs, which helps support walking, standing, and daily activity—all of which contribute to increased calorie burn. Watkins tells us, “Leg extensions are a simple exercise that helps build lower body strength, supporting daily movement and overall activity levels.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Do It:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit up tall with a straight back and relaxed shoulders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Place your hands on the sides of the chair for balance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage your core and extend one leg straight out in front of you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Squeeze your thigh muscle at the top for one to two seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower your leg slowly back to the floor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Switch legs and repeat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete 15 reps per leg for two to three sets. Rest for 30 to 45 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="seated-torso-twists" class="o-slide-title" data-num="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seated Torso Twists&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RYbFJgSYcWw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Seated torso twists target your obliques (side abs) and deep core muscles that help shape and support the waistline. Unlike fast twisting motions, controlled rotations keep tension on your core and reduce strain on your spine. “Seated torso twists engage the core and obliques, strengthening the midsection and burning calories,” Watkins says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Do It:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit upright with your feet flat on the floor and your knees hip-width apart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross your arms over your chest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flex your core and rotate your torso to one side.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your hips facing forward as you twist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return to center with control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rotate to the opposite side and continue alternating.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform two to three sets of 20 reps. Rest for 30 to 45 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

																		
																	&lt;/div&gt;
										&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio"&gt;
	&lt;p class="c-article-short-bio__name"&gt;Adam Meyer, RHN&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
		Adam is a health writer, certified holistic nutritionist, and 100% plant-based athlete.					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="c-article-short-bio__more" href="https://www.eatthis.com/author/adam-meyer/"&gt;Read more about Adam &lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Eat This Not That</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:07:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE81eEljQUxuZnFieXBTaHc5VkRsaTV1RDdXOTR4emZxVXgtaV83RW9jTGJhZUlYRU1qN2otN1VVRTVlVjJOOUp5STctTFNXbGxpUmdzSFJucjVISmhUR05TSVV2amQtNWZOQWRSUEZFdF96Y2NtcnMzQXN2TUI</guid></item><item><title>结肠僵硬可能预示着早发性结直肠癌的风险- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-stiffer-colon-early-onset-colorectal.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 17:00:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQZjRtbzU2c0hWcmpMWFVJY2Q4Yi1pMF9FNGlRRUh0eXpvUFBoNDByX1JydmlRQ1VwMHRHalh3UFJRNXJoc3VqNFRlT0tSWVFLU2JGcm1EYThHVUxXVHdyckJxWnNkTTd5elJfeDVHNEpKN1owNVpkWnZKMTVaOFFMTjN1LUF5Tms</guid></item><item><title>流感季节正好赶上圣诞节。阿拉巴马州的这些地区受到的打击最为严重。- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/flu-season-is-here-just-in-time-for-christmas-these-areas-in-alabama-are-getting-hit-hardest.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7AQOSAIIJJETFIOIQX2TWBFAWI"&gt;Flu season has come to Alabama, with new cases doubling in a week just in time for the holidays. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EXLFEU7CDJET7GABOHYLURMKMQ"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html"&gt;Alabama Department of Public Health&lt;/a&gt; reports roughly 2.7% of emergency room visits in the week ending Dec. 3 were for flu-like illness. That’s more than twice the rate from the previous week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:3HSK7G62ENFITPDDPOTQSAAPZU" data-fusion-component="3HSK7G62ENFITPDDPOTQSAAPZU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rawhtml"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:3HSK7G62ENFITPDDPOTQSAAPZU" data-fusion-component="3HSK7G62ENFITPDDPOTQSAAPZU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="36DPWJA6VBEVHLKXSMSUEXJI7M"&gt;[Can’t see the chart? &lt;a href="https://www.datawrapper.de/_/9kWZ4/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.datawrapper.de/_/9kWZ4/"&gt;Click here.&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YR4JFZAQKVBR7AXJPS7RMSWZJA"&gt;“ADPH is monitoring influenza activity statewide through our routine surveillance systems, and we are seeing increased flu activity consistent with the seasonal trend,” Ryan Easterling, director of health media and communications at ADPH said in an email to AL.com this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PI6WATWYHZFSLJ3CG4WVCCCPPQ"&gt;&lt;b&gt;RELATED: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/super-flu-hitting-these-states-the-hardest-here-are-the-symptoms.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/super-flu-hitting-these-states-the-hardest-here-are-the-symptoms.html"&gt;&lt;b&gt;‘Super flu’ hitting these states the hardest: Here are the symptoms&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HPIRHUO24VABJNS7M5LH6S4HNA"&gt;The current rate of nearly 3% is typical for this time of year. This time last year, the rate was even higher, at nearly 4%. Last flu season the rate peaked at 8%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CPBDIPVE7RERRAIF4LSVA77XXM"&gt;Early in the 2025-2026 flu season, some parts of Alabama are already getting it worse than others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:LPUA3EZF2RFTVIX3WFNX44HNVU" data-fusion-component="LPUA3EZF2RFTVIX3WFNX44HNVU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rawhtml"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:LPUA3EZF2RFTVIX3WFNX44HNVU" data-fusion-component="LPUA3EZF2RFTVIX3WFNX44HNVU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3GZPAEDBK5FSJGRQJEM5QUB3RU"&gt;[Can’t see the map? &lt;a href="https://www.datawrapper.de/_/J0Xlo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.datawrapper.de/_/J0Xlo/"&gt;Click here.&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IJWLNLXUNVGM3CUXE5DVWR4CZU"&gt;ADPH divides the state into eight different health districts. The East Central district, which includes Montgomery and Auburn, currently has the state’s highest rate, with nearly 5% of ED visits being for flu. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z6DGVXCKOBCDLCR67VHK4KHQNE"&gt;In Jefferson County, home of Birmingham and the most populous county in the state, the rate was 3%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FZKTYQ57JZCVRJ5EOWM2WGEI2E"&gt;“As flu activity increases, ADPH encourages persons to take steps to reduce their risk of influenza and help prevent spread within their communities,” Easterling said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PLQCCXWAMJFSFLGY2UAKSV4Y54"&gt;Some tips include: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="6UQCUCOI7NHEZD7LXWEK3EKIV4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Get an annual flu shot. ADPH says this is the most effective way to prevent flu and severe illness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="O7OZ5A5O2FCRTITMJT5PQZMU6Y"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Avoid close contact with people who are sick.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="6SOP6FWPRFFWPB7WQAJIERTCMY"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wash your hands often with soap and water or hand sanitizer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="IM2GR77DVFECDDQK4Z6JOT3GEQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cover coughs and sneezes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="R34D4ZFKPNDVZC2GLO2TUDVQTA"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stay home if you are sick to prevent spreading illness to others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="5ZZONCDFBZCDZFZJ36AAVK66ZQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clean and disinfect frequently touched surfaces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="DCNJRZ2IBVBDJAVKLPB33APRMI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Avoid touching your face, including the eyes, nose, and mouth. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiyAFBVV95cUxQeVNPandCNnFHVVZaTmJhNlF2NDRmSnNKVlZNdXRQLVVrdi1QdzBKZ2Q5LWE1UjZfUVhmTlQ5dmJjdW50Y3hYdVd6QXBEM2hSaTR1dlRfTzk1Nkw4S3paclI1N3lNeGtiVnFlV2pkYnExeERGNjFiZTlsWDdCOVIyV3NoRzlCVEJLeHdOOEdFQ2NuNHdHU0tsaWxBdWFIOXlVUlZvYlRoemprVWhRTjNfQ296cVA3WTQzOWZscE9WbUl3anRfOURSMtIB3AFBVV95cUxPb2pOTFJpdkJNQ2FFc25hbDZlVHhQRnpwZTJpT1QxUFVPOTRSMUdTS0ZQN1ZqZWtFbzNPQnMwckRSRFF0aFluTld3c2duSHBqVTFaSFFINjJ3WTNzNnY4VGs0WWlncm9qeC10eHAzamRxY2pRdzVmb1hUOGpRbHg2ZS1TWDFnRVllUUdSZEVrckU5Xy0yMHhNRGZHeHZaTGpUeGxwYXAyVmc4dWhieUNZbjFQeUVnM0MtQkhaeWY2M0g4VTRTMHdEY1RtbmU2RVRiSXBtTXJvOW1OaEtx</guid></item><item><title>城市表示，波士顿的流感疫情激增；接种疫苗还为时不晚- Universal Hub</title><link>https://www.universalhub.com/2025/flu-surges-boston-still-not-too-late-get-vaccinated-city-says</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="cf-column"&gt;
            &lt;h2 data-translate="blocked_why_headline"&gt;Why have I been blocked?&lt;/h2&gt;

            &lt;p data-translate="blocked_why_detail"&gt;This website is using a security service to protect itself from online attacks. The action you just performed triggered the security solution. There are several actions that could trigger this block including submitting a certain word or phrase, a SQL command or malformed data.&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Universal Hub</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:03:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNZFhJWVE1aHAtTW5oX3ZUcWw3dGZQc3RzMnQxYVdra2lYY2NLTi14UjI5UTdvZlAwaDNQV1YxWERPUkktYTlVR3ktdi1tdGVwQmhvOXk0aWlrM3d5VExaSzVVVzVqUlBYTVVSblBUYWEwUVBjTVdFclcxZVo4NzBxLUN3QUNBVmlXbHY5cTdwWml1WU5pakZzdDZyMA</guid></item><item><title>科学家进一步了解人类胚胎如何使用人工子宫植入- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/23/nx-s1-5646649/human-embryos-implantation-artificial-womb</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-103451" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Microscopy image of a day 14 human embryo that has implanted in the new artificial womb.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Matteo Molè at the Babraham Institute.
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Matteo Molè at the Babraham Institute.
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Scientists have gotten an unprecedented look at how the human embryo implants in a uterus. They did this by creating very primitive, womb-like environments in the lab.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The goal is to help people have healthy babies by finding new clues to the causes of miscarriages and infertility. But the research raises tough ethical concerns. It was &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01232-2" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday in &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01230-9" target="_blank"&gt;three&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell-stem-cell/fulltext/S1934-5909(25)00436-9" target="_blank"&gt; papers&lt;/a&gt; in the journals &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Cell Stem Cell.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"This is really important work that's moving embryo research forward – an important advance in the search for scientific answers for what makes a pregnancy healthy," says &lt;a href="https://www.thehastingscenter.org/expert/insoo-hyun-phd/" target="_blank"&gt;Insoo Hyun&lt;/a&gt;, a bioethicist at The Hastings Center, a bioethics think tank, who was not involved in the research. "However, it also presents a technology that could be used for other purposes that are concerning."&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;That includes the possibility of some day using this kind of technology to enable embryos to develop much further – perhaps even completely – in the lab. This process, called ectogenesis, has the potential to make a natural human womb unnecessary.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"That is very troubling," says &lt;a href="https://philosophy.wfu.edu/faculty-and-staff/current-faculty/" target="_blank"&gt;Ana Iltis&lt;/a&gt;, a bioethicist at Wake Forest University.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But the scientists working on this research argue that possibility remains theoretical, and the work could yield important clues to early human development.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"This is very exciting," says &lt;a href="https://profiles.utsouthwestern.edu/profile/175076/jun-wu.html" target="_blank"&gt;Jun Wu&lt;/a&gt;, a molecular biologist at the University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center involved in the research.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;One of the most important moments in a human embryo's journey to becoming a baby is when the microscopic ball of cells burrows into the womb. But that pivotal step of embryonic implantation has long been mysterious because it unfolds hidden inside the body.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Human implantation is essentially a black box — a mystery," Wu says. "Implantation happens very early on during pregnancy. Essentially we don't know when, we don't know where. It's happening in a womb we cannot have access to."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insights into the causes of miscarriage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In the new research, Wu and colleagues in China obtained cells and tissue collected from the lining of wombs during routine medical procedures and figured out how to recreate a key part of the lining of the womb inside tiny plastic devices in their labs.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"You can call it: A womb on a chip," Wu says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The scientists then placed human embryos donated for research after infertility treatments, as well as primitive embryo-like entities created from stem cells — called &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2017/03/02/516280895/embryo-experiments-reveal-earliest-human-development-but-stir-ethical-debate" target="_blank"&gt;embryoids&lt;/a&gt; — inside their tiny wombs on chips and peered through a microscope to watch what happened next.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"For the first time, we observed the entire sequence of human implantation," Wu says. "We are very excited about this."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The researchers have already used their wombs on chips to discover clues about how embryos and wombs interact, which can "help us understand the implantation process at the molecular level," Wu says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The researchers also compared artificial wombs using cells from healthy wombs with &lt;strong&gt;artificial wombs&lt;/strong&gt; using cells from wombs of women who had miscarriages.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We observed implantation failure right in front of our eyes, which is very surprising and also exciting," Wu says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Wu's team even screened more than 1,100 drugs to see if any might prevent miscarriages, and identified some that look promising.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A separate team in the U.K. did similar research in their lab in Cambridge.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We've been able to observe some really fantastic aspects of human embryo development, many of which have never been seen before," says&lt;a href="https://www.babraham.ac.uk/our-research/epigenetics/peter-rugg-gunn" target="_blank"&gt; Peter Rugg-Gunn&lt;/a&gt;, a developmental biologist at the Babraham Institute. "To be able to see these events for the first time, it was fantastic."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Other scientists hailed the research&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's very exciting," says &lt;a href="https://www.crick.ac.uk/research/labs/robin-lovell-badge" target="_blank"&gt;Robin Lovell-Badge&lt;/a&gt;, a developmental biologist at the Francis Crick Institute in London who was not involved in the research. "I think they will allow more information to be developed about this absolutely critical stage of human development which has to date been otherwise pretty much impossible to study."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;An ethical slippery slope?&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Among the difficult ethical issues raised by the research are questions about destroying human embryos for research.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"For those of us who believe that humans are humans and deserving of ethical respect, whether embryonic, adolescent, or elderly, these experiments are unethical," says Dr. &lt;a href="https://gufaculty360.georgetown.edu/s/contact/00336000014TpfuAAC/daniel-p-sulmasy-phd" target="_blank"&gt;Daniel Sulmasy&lt;/a&gt;, a Georgetown University bioethicist.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The experiments also raise questions about using these devices to study human embryos past 14 days of development, which is considered off limits in many places. (The researchers did not use their devices to try that.)&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There are also concerns about implanting even primitive embryo models created from stem cells into anything that resembles a human womb.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Some might be concerned with how far this might go," says Hyun, the Hastings Center bioethicist. "It is a little bit on a slippery slope scientifically."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Indeed some bioethicists are very concerned about how far this may go.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's research that could facilitate future attempts to support not only research on early embryos but on growing embryos for significant periods of time in labs, perhaps eventually to the point of fetuses," says Iltis, the Wake Forest University bioethicist.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If that ever became possible, it raises the prospect of producing human fetuses for "spare parts," Iltis says. "They could be grown to be sources of organs and tissues for transplantation. That is very troubling."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The researchers doing the work say their research is nowhere near that, and they have no intention to pursue it.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Development entirely outside the uterus is a science fiction," Wu says. "I don't think we're anywhere close to that."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But Iltis argues other scientists are &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2024/04/12/1241895501/artificial-womb-premature-birth" target="_blank"&gt;already testing much larger artificial wombs &lt;/a&gt;to save very premature babies. So what sounds like science fiction today, could become a reality much sooner than many people think.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We have this long history of saying, 'Don't worry. The science isn't there. That's not the goal. That's not what we're trying to do.' And then being presented with a breakthrough that signals that the train has left the station."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"I don't think it's far-fetched to think that eventually it might be possible to create lab-generated tissues and organs through something like this technology."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxOR0xZZkFUQW9UTXVOX21NQUlxZXlyUFpnNHJrM3h2TlVPcjVjOVhqMDNhcGkzNFRPdWc1cE9MLVprcHI0S0swZXp5aXBsU01NUmx4b2djUXQ0Wm80eFVJOVl0QWJOaWwydGhyTVdMWTJPaWpvT1VUVzVYNzBPaWpqWU03VGItX3RSNk91d2pKN1k</guid></item><item><title>心脏病专家分享您可以在最初几分钟内遵循的心脏病发作挽救生命的技巧： “监测呼吸和……” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-shares-life-saving-tips-for-heart-attacks-you-can-follow-in-first-few-minutes-101766502781253.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-shares-life-saving-tips-for-heart-attacks-you-can-follow-in-first-few-minutes-101766502781253.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Heart attacks can happen unexpectedly, and the way you respond in the first few minutes can be critical. While waiting for &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mumbai-pulmonologist-explains-how-mumbai-aqi-attacks-throat-symptoms-to-watch-when-to-seek-medical-help-101764496996158.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="medical help"&gt;medical help&lt;/a&gt;, knowing the right steps to take and the mistakes to avoid can save lives. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;In an interview with HT Lifestyle, Dr Gajinder Kumar Goyal, Program Clinical Director–Cardiology, Marengo Asia Hospitals, Faridabad, shares essential first-aid tips, including what to do and what to avoid immediately.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; (Also read: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/bhagyashree-shares-quick-workout-that-covers-both-cardio-and-strength-training-do-it-anywhere-anytime-without-gym-101766498114966.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Bhagyashree shares quick workout that ‘covers both cardio and strength training': Do it anywhere, anytime without gym"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bhagyashree shares quick workout that ‘covers both cardio and strength training': Do it anywhere, anytime without gym &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/23/550x309/heart-attack-gaa563025f_1920_1668138776077_1766503335584.jpg" alt="Dr Goyal shares life-saving tips for heart attack emergencies. (Image by Tumisu from Pixabay )" title="Dr Goyal shares life-saving tips for heart attack emergencies. (Image by Tumisu from Pixabay )"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/23/550x309/heart-attack-gaa563025f_1920_1668138776077_1766503335584.jpg" alt="Dr Goyal shares life-saving tips for heart attack emergencies. (Image by Tumisu from Pixabay )" title="Dr Goyal shares life-saving tips for heart attack emergencies. (Image by Tumisu from Pixabay )"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Goyal shares life-saving tips for heart attack emergencies. (Image by Tumisu from Pixabay )&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Recognising the warning signs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In a heart attack patient, time is muscle. The longer we provide real treatment, the more heart muscle gets damaged. Early intervention is critical to minimise damage, so the first step in &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/heart-attack" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="heart attack"&gt;heart attack&lt;/a&gt; first aid is to reach the nearest hospital equipped with heart attack facilities as soon as possible,” explains Dr Gajinder.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Before helping someone, it’s important to recognise the warning signs. “&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Symptoms of a heart attack include tightness or heaviness in the chest, continuous pain in the chest, jaw, shoulder, neck, back, arms, or stomach, cold sweat, pale skin, shortness of breath, weakness, palpitations, dizziness, or nausea,” says Dr Goyal.&lt;/span&gt; “If you suspect someone is having a heart attack, call an emergency helpline immediately. Every minute counts.”&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2024/12/23/original/pexels-towfiqu-barbhuiya-3440682-14569658_1734957756809.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Dr Goyal stresses the importance of quick response during a heart attack, noting that the first hour is crucial for treatment. (Pexels)" title="Dr Goyal stresses the importance of quick response during a heart attack, noting that the first hour is crucial for treatment. (Pexels)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Goyal stresses the importance of quick response during a heart attack, noting that the first hour is crucial for treatment. (Pexels)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Goyal emphasises the importance of the “Golden Hour.” “The first 60 minutes after a heart attack are crucial. Effective treatment within this period can even completely reverse the damage suffered by the heart.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;First-aid steps until help arrives&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Goyal shares key steps you can follow while waiting for professional help:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep the person calm and seated.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitor breathing and pulse until the ambulance arrives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Check if the person has any prescribed medication for &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/chest-pain" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="chest pain"&gt;chest pain&lt;/a&gt; and help them take it.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Administer aspirin if not allergic. “Chewing one tablet of aspirin acts quickly to thin the blood, reduce heart damage, and can even save lives if taken early. Sorbitrate tablets under the tongue can also be used in acute cases,” he explains.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Loosen tight clothing to make the person more comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Perform hands-only CPR if the person is unconscious and not breathing normally. “&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Place the heel of one hand in the centre of the chest, the other hand on top, and push hard and fast, about 100–120 compressions per minute, letting the chest rise fully between compressions.&lt;/span&gt; Continue until help arrives or the patient regains consciousness or normal breathing,” says Dr Goyal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/23/original/71d10a4a-d313-4366-867a-93c7f2656700_1766503159918.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Recognizing heart attack symptoms and acting quickly is essential, according to Dr. Goyal.(Freepik)" title="Recognizing heart attack symptoms and acting quickly is essential, according to Dr. Goyal.(Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Recognizing heart attack symptoms and acting quickly is essential, according to Dr. Goyal.(Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Advice for people experiencing heart attack&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Goyal also shares critical advice for anyone who suspects they may be having a heart attack:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Call emergency services immediately.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do not drive yourself to the hospital; have someone else drive you. “Exerting yourself or driving puts both you and others at risk,” he warns.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taking aspirin early can help reduce &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/women-with-type-2-diabetes-face-double-risk-of-undetected-heart-damage-study-101752591437333.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="heart damage"&gt;heart damage&lt;/a&gt;. “Chewing one regular tablet or four baby aspirin during a heart attack can prevent blood clotting and limit heart muscle damage,” Dr Goyal adds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Remember, a heart attack is a medical emergency. Quick action, recognising warning signs, and following first-aid measures correctly can save lives,” concludes Dr Goyal.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 15:41:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8AFBVV95cUxPY3U1TXdDODZVVURfd3lHZzRlbUpGcTA1WWt0aGttbXFBODVOOFNpVDc5d2pzNzFUWXJTUzF0MHo5cnV2REczd2Z4eGJaNGROWXd1QlNzMnp5Smh0WldHd1hhMmdJdWNNSkpydWR5NGZEYTlpbFlQMFRFUWhJajFUdWZObE5GQkJsbFJMRlBjbEx3SGREZ1hCMDlpbWRDOXNSQTc1SUNLMlJjNkNaLVVXeG1FYUIyQ3ZnQ2tYS2xhaGswc2t5Z0x3WmpqdEVOcHRqRG5fTWxpamd4OG9HLU9MdXFONGFDU05WeWo4c0IxdXXSAfYBQVVfeXFMT2Fza1Rmd1pFT1FEbXhrd1Z2NWNxZ003Q3ItTzY0dVRkNUp2UGlQRE5Kd0l3dC1xRG9vSGl6cVRsOUN6dlBvajJ1aF9kS2xhTmNCeDVLcWprc181UVBQZDdQQmVBSU9FUl9QeXQtY1FfVFhNR1hYYVJqOWNsMEF5SXByZ1BLY05tRUE4eVJxd0tlT1FFejNiUjFKQ1QzRzhWNnlyaW1LUlYteG5MY1I0b2JOY3EzdFZrOFhwYmVWNU5EOEFvZHBGZ2VFeHZRcjFHeWd1SFlaWXFGcnJERGw4SUxWRG9OU1VhUzdFVUlfc0ZHVDNNUGRB</guid></item></channel></rss>