<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>专家警告：世界正沉睡在禽流感中- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/the-world-is-sleeping-on-bird-flu-expert-warns</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;There's an unwritten rule in publishing, or so I've been told: Don't write about COVID. Our collective attention span has been saturated by those endless months holed up in attics and cramped corners of apartments, staring out at a world we could no longer take part in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the worst of it passed, we felt an urge to close that chapter, to padlock it behind a heavy latch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in doing so, we also tuck away the hard-won lessons of that time: how quickly systems buckle, how two decades of &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/coronavirus-5830"&gt;coronavirus&lt;/a&gt; warnings &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ejim.2022.07.009"&gt;accumulated without adequate preparedness&lt;/a&gt;, and how the very mechanisms we rely on for safety can become the scaffolding of a next disaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/worlds-first-death-from-h5n5-bird-flu-strain-reported-in-us"&gt;World's First Death From H5N5 Bird Flu Strain Reported in US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This matters now as another threat is taking shape: highly pathogenic avian  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt;, known as bird  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bird flu still poses a low‑probability threat of sustained human transmission. But that doesn't make the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; harmless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The H5  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt; are &lt;a href="https://www.dw.com/en/virus-has-killed-almost-9-million-birds-and-counting/a-74972319"&gt;brutally lethal&lt;/a&gt; to birds – 9 million have died outright, and hundreds of millions have been culled to contain the spread. &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/h5n1-bird-flu-cases-spike-in-europe-how-worried-should-we-be-269962"&gt;Alarming&lt;/a&gt; is the virus's expanding reach into mammals. So far, at least 74 mammal species, from elephant seals to polar bears, have suffered die‑offs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The individual cases are situated within a broader shift. Dense poultry farms create opportunities for the virus to hop species. Over a &lt;a href="https://www.avma.org/resources-tools/animal-health-and-welfare/animal-health/avian-influenza/avian-influenza-virus-type-h5n1-us-dairy-cattle"&gt;thousand US dairy herds&lt;/a&gt; have tested positive in the past two years, and viral fragments have even been detected in milk – &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/11/06/nx-s1-5600125/bird-flu-risk-outbreak-trump-administration"&gt;a worrying route&lt;/a&gt; of spillover. Every jump is a probe for new footholds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Europe is &lt;a href="https://www.efsa.europa.eu/en/news/avian-influenza-europe-enhanced-surveillance-and-strict-biosecurity-needed-detections-surge?"&gt;seeing a surge too&lt;/a&gt;. From early September to mid-November 2025, 1,444 infected wild birds were found across 26 countries: a quadrupling compared with the year before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human cases remain rare: only &lt;a href="https://cdn.who.int/media/docs/default-source/influenza/h5n1-human-case-cumulative-table/cumulative-number-of-confirmed-human-cases-for-avian-influenza-a(h5n1)-reported-to-who--2003-2025ac90dee8-f1c4-4ff6-b891-f92e0df414cb.pdf?sfvrsn=447db8c4_3&amp;amp;download=true"&gt;992&lt;/a&gt; confirmed H5N1 infections worldwide since 2003, though with a near‑50% fatality rate. But the numbers are increasing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Americas have logged 75 cases since 2022, and in November, the US recorded its &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/391/bmj.r2480"&gt;first H5N5 death&lt;/a&gt; in a patient with existing health problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186710" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186710" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm-642x361.jpg" alt="Multiple cows on a dairy farm" class="wp-image-186710 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm-642x361.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm-600x338.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186710" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;More than 1,000 US dairy herds have tested positive in the past two years. (TinaFields/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;And although no human cases have been reported in Europe, the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control &lt;a href="https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/sites/default/files/documents/Zoonotic_influenza_pre_pandemic_scenarios_SARMS%20FINAL%20VERSION2.pdf"&gt;warns&lt;/a&gt; that the widespread animal circulation raises the risk of spillover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My research focuses on how warnings collapse before catastrophe, from geopolitical shocks to intelligence failures and industrial accidents. The pattern is often the same. Frontline observers spot something early, but the signal fades as it moves upward, diluted by bureaucracy, competing interpretations, or institutional forgetfulness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent Hong Kong fire is yet another tragic example: residents at Wang Fuk Court &lt;a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2025-hong-kong-fire/"&gt;had raised multiple alarms&lt;/a&gt; about the styrofoam boards that ignited with a lighter, the uncertified netting and the pattern of ignored safety notices long before the blaze, yet those concerns never gained traction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The failures I study share recurring blind spots: weak signals drowned out by noise, bureaucratic habits that slow or soften uncomfortable messages, and the political instinct to downplay problems that threaten established narratives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you see warning as a chain running from detection to decision, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/isr/article/27/1/viaf009/8109154"&gt;collapse is often partial&lt;/a&gt;. Some links hold. Others jam at the moment they are most needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bird flu now sits inside that kind of chain. The technical ability to detect change is there: veterinarians, virologists and surveillance systems are picking up signals, sequencing viruses and logging outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the infrastructure meant to catch the virus in its early stages is &lt;a href="http://npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/11/06/nx-s1-5600125/bird-flu-risk-outbreak-trump-administration"&gt;fraying&lt;/a&gt;. The agencies that once charted the terrain of emerging  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pandemic" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73047" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;pandemic&lt;/a&gt; threats have been hollowed out – budgets trimmed, staff evaporated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Surveillance falters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study of 31 European nations warned that COVID exposed a &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurpub/article/34/2/402/7603330"&gt;"critical gap in preparedness"&lt;/a&gt; and urged standardised indicators and open data as the foundation for any future response. The EU's freshly launched &lt;a href="https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/scenarios-pre-pandemic-zoonotic-influenza-preparedness-and-response"&gt;pre-pandemic plan&lt;/a&gt; is a good step, but it cannot mask the gaps in day-to-day monitoring and response that still leave countries exposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across the Atlantic, &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/12/01/nx-s1-5619764/months-of-tumult-and-waves-of-staff-cuts-take-a-toll-on-the-cdc"&gt;cuts&lt;/a&gt; have left the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention scrambling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American scientists warn that federal reporting has slowed: the United States Department of Agriculture &lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2024/04/23/health/h5n1-usda-gisaid-genetic-sequences"&gt;shared&lt;/a&gt; too little genetic data on the outbreak in cattle and other affected animals, released it late, and in formats researchers could not use. It left scientists unable to track how the virus was evolving or spreading across herds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.midlandfarmer.co.uk/2025/12/04/uk-poorly-prepared-for-animal-disease-outbreaks/"&gt;the UK&lt;/a&gt;, domestic surveillance capacity has equally faced strain, with reduced access to European disease intelligence and chronic vet shortages weakening early detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the signal dims within institutions, it dims for the public as well. And a weak warning rarely travels far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent &lt;a href="https://ajph.aphapublications.org/doi/10.2105/AJPH.2025.308080"&gt;poll&lt;/a&gt; shows this clearly: most Americans don't even register bird flu as a credible threat. What doesn't help is that symptoms in humans can be so mild that they slide past notice. A &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/insights/2024/05/bird-avian-flu-h5n1-cows-pandemic-threat.html"&gt;case&lt;/a&gt; in a dairy worker earlier this year looked like nothing more than conjunctivitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this means a new pandemic is imminent. Health authorities still say the chance of an efficient human-to-human outbreak &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bird-flu-poses-risk-pandemic-worse-than-covid-frances-institut-pasteur-says-2025-11-27/"&gt;is low&lt;/a&gt;. These viruses rarely make that leap. And we're not helpless. We're &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/insights/2024/05/bird-avian-flu-h5n1-cows-pandemic-threat.html"&gt;better prepared&lt;/a&gt; than we were before COVID: We have vaccine candidates, clearer protocols and agencies that learned painful lessons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spikes-of-bird-flu-in-cats-could-be-a-warning-of-a-future-pandemic"&gt;Spikes of Bird Flu in Cats Could Be a Warning of a Future Pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But low isn't none. And if it were to occur, the consequences could be catastrophic. Most people have some immunity to the seasonal flu strains. We probably have &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bird-flu-poses-risk-pandemic-worse-than-covid-frances-institut-pasteur-says-2025-11-27/"&gt;none&lt;/a&gt; to H5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And influenza doesn't restrict itself to the frail in the way COVID often did; past flu epidemics killed healthy adults in large numbers. Adding to the concern, health expertise itself &lt;a href="https://www.apha.org/topics-and-issues/public-health-under-threat"&gt;has come under attack&lt;/a&gt;, weakening the very authority that should turn signals into action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we avert our eyes from the bird flu threat because our systems have grown inattentive, underfunded and unprepared, we risk repeating that same pattern. And the next alarm will arrive too late for anyone to claim they didn't see it coming.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/271765/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/nikki-ikani-346615"&gt;Nikki Ikani&lt;/a&gt;, Assistant Professor Intelligence &amp;amp; Security, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/leiden-university-935"&gt;Leiden University&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/kings-college-london-1196"&gt;King's College London&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/bird-flu-warnings-are-being-ignored-ive-seen-this-pattern-before-271765"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 18:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQODBwWFM4YlJpR0s5aVZwYkpVYmJMNXc0YmxRT1RfbWdiWFZ3TUlJR0F6NDBCbWkyN01KTno4Wjk2RDgwQm81VU9jNzZSSEtSNDdIZllLTkgtaHBKbERnVkcxdUxlMEs2Um9fWFhISjhUeGRLZ0cxdExKTm55UGZZZw</guid></item><item><title>我非常想尝试团体性爱。一个又小又可怕的东西在阻挡我。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/group-sex-advice-threesome-feeld-orgy-alone.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna3a7g009n63mc72vw6sp2@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjnacyxc00363b78kk4ov2kh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="156" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93js001n3b78set17ghu@published"&gt;I have always been curious about group sex. I’ve dabbled in the world of Feeld lately, and have received some interest from hot men for potential threesomes/more and have been tempted to try it but something keeps holding me back. I’m so afraid of feeling like the odd one out or the less enticing person in the party. It’s an insecurity I would say I have in many areas of life beyond sex—I often feel like the one who gets left out in the friend group or the social gathering and I’m so afraid of feeling rejected in that way in a sexual context. Is there a way to protect against that? Am I completely off base to even worry that someone would inevitably get left out, and that someone would be me? I just don’t want to walk away from something that was supposed to be really hot, feeling like I didn’t get picked again.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93my001o3b78kx685v31@published"&gt;—Group Project&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93r1001p3b78j5ptzsbs@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Group Project,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="153" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93us001q3b786d0sx1ub@published"&gt;The fear of being left out is so common it must be up there with fears of heights and snakes. This can be especially pronounced in vulnerable situations like sex, when rejection feels that much more personal as a result of what has been revealed (your body, your desires, etc.). However, when it comes to pursuing sex, rejection is always a possibility, and that’s how it has to be. People must have the ability to revoke consent at any moment for whatever reason, and the hurt feelings of those who are denied is merely collateral. It can suck, but you know what makes it suck less? Being rejected! You get used to it. You see that it’s not really a big deal, that it’s often not personal, and that you’ll live to see another dick. It can actually be character-building and I think it would be a good thing for you to experience.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="64" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93yi001r3b78cm748l37@published"&gt;If you can’t bear the thought of being rejected, I don’t think you should be on Feeld or any app for that matter—it’s just a matter of time before you find yourself enormously disappointed. Working through this fear of rejection via means other than exposure could also benefit you. For example, you may want to talk to a therapist about your strong feelings here.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="205" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna942b001s3b78acegjfrt@published"&gt;However, I do think that your fear in the context you wrote about is somewhat overblown. You are afraid of being left out of group sex that you will have coordinated. While it is true that interacting on apps and in person are two very different modes of communication, you can assume that people are going to be showing up because you have attracted them via what you look like, what you’re offering, and your overall vibe. When people leave their house to have sex (or open their home to host it), they want to have a good time. No one is joining in this group with the objective of leaving you out—that would contradict the point of getting together in the first place. You can help safeguard against being left out, though, by enlisting only straight guys to participate. I don’t think it would be wrong of you to say that you want to be the focus and so all action should involve you. I know gay bottoms that take this approach to group sex/gangbangs and it works out for them. This is one situation where it’s really OK to express your selfishness. I think a lot of guys will just find that hot.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjnabva2002i3b788w3r6e5c@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmjnabyuk002l3b78671lmnl2@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjnac4me002p3b78gbw89bpu@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna945q001t3b78qvl8y8sq@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="49" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna949i001u3b78ssh6imbi@published"&gt;I am a 48-year-old man, and for the last year I thought I was suffering from ED, but it turns out that I just can’t get it up for my wife anymore.  When it comes to porn, I’m back in business. What can I do to rekindle the flame with her?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="8" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94cq001v3b78ch45e36l@published"&gt;—Rising to Every Occasion but the Right One&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="9" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94fw001w3b78y3ano819@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Rising to Every Occasion but the Right One,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="70" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94jl001x3b78p7z2suxf@published"&gt;Your assessment sounds right—usually when erectile dysfunction is situational (that is, you can get hard in some situations but not others), it’s regarded as being a psychologically rooted issue (as opposed to a physiological one as a result of, say, diabetes). That said, you are 48 and it’s likely that your testosterone levels aren’t what they used to be. If you aren’t regularly seeing a doctor/getting bloodwork, now’s the time.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="193" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94nm001y3b78c39txzum@published"&gt;Rekindling could look like a lot of things. If you are having wood issues with your wife, she must be noticing and so a conversation may be useful. It’s common in long-term relationships for desire to wane—Esther Perel’s &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Mating-Captivity-Unlocking-Erotic-Intelligence-ebook/dp/B000UODXP0/ref=sr_1_1?crid=2KFLDW9XS3D4&amp;amp;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.9TBgqJH8OXaXJ6KF-p0h2kiUlcEoJVKlMs9LiYHOqbmj3Ltj7tID5mjXlzIy3vFrG-ffA-RkeZjl5zQROs7-3kM8mUhqQUWNxRLL3FauXHkiHYn8o8qVtOT_87IekJCsF76G9rzN0dgy_WDoRNyLXuy62WJsygbNVXDhP6yrk2mODHIW0D6GwNKpTZH-ZlPyxA09WKWnURyMj5NUW4QmHLe1hhXeCS78p77v1q5h6S0.CEYYxaVRazv_Twik-AToMJu7pLXiTSTRs2ZBbnKTNlI&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;keywords=mating+in+captivity+esther+perel&amp;amp;qid=1766454898&amp;amp;sprefix=mating+in+ca,aps,137&amp;amp;sr=8-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mating in Captivity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (my go-to recommended read for these types of situations) explores how closeness is often at odds with eroticism. It wouldn’t be surprising at all if your wife were having similar issues. If you can have an honest (but considerate!) conversation about the underwhelming state of your sex life, you can begin a collaboration to get things back on track. This might mean trying things (like kink, toys, and roleplay) that you’ve been curious about but have been too timid to ask for. It might mean exploring consensual non-monogamy. It might mean putting into practice some of the distancing techniques that Perel writes about (such as moving your sex outside of your home to, say, a hotel with some kind of regularity). It might mean something as simple as enjoying porn together instead of watching it alone. It might mean ongoing conversations and/or enlisting the help of a couples counselor or sex therapist/coach.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="64" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94qn001z3b784gyxx4uv@published"&gt;Your letter is phrased as though this is your issue that you want to resolve yourself. It’s noble to take responsibility, but you aren’t in this alone and in fact, you’re going to have a much better shot at success if you work with your wife here. The initial conversation may not be easy, but the process should be much smoother with her participation.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjnac9d4002s3b78c33tblbs@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmjnacdgl002v3b78c1z8xzvx@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="36" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjnacj0c002z3b786n67spoa@published"&gt;The columnists behind our advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjnacnai00333b78hffkytb8@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94tq00203b78e8dt1d7a@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="68" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94wr00213b78o24s2u3u@published"&gt;I got my lower right leg amputated almost three years ago (diabetes). Well, they might as well have cut off another organ. My erections are much less frequent and not the same as they used to be. I don’t think I can get hard enough for penetration (haven’t tried). Pills do nothing. Yet I still think about sex a lot, so the drive is there. Is this normal?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94zv00223b78tbko02z1@published"&gt;—Lost a Leg and a Dick&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna953u00233b78zlq40y5m@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Lost a Leg and a Dick,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="186" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna957f00243b78uqk3s12y@published"&gt;Sexual dysfunction is common in people who have undergone limb amputation. In a 2015 &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26030200/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; of people with a limb amputation in the Netherlands, the intro/review of previous literature points out that post amputation, people “may be confronted with a variety of sexual problems, such as problems with arousal and/or orgasm, due to both the physical and/or psychological consequences of a limb amputation.  Furthermore, depression, (sexual) performance anxiety and an altered body image may influence the amputee’s sexual adjustment. Moreover, pain related to the amputation and medication use (to treat this pain) may also affect both sexual interest and activity.” There is a lot stacked against you, and one of the findings of this study’s survey was that there was very little discussion of sexuality during the rehabilitation process. Again, this was a study of Dutch subjects, but it’s hard to believe that elsewhere is doing much better to support these patients. In this study, 56 percent of participants reported at least one sexual problem and 20 percent reported sexual dysfunction(s). The problems included sexual desire (31 percent), sexual arousal (25 percent), and orgasm (21 percent).&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="69" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna95cg00253b780lu1x163@published"&gt;A more recent &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28359182/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; from 2018 of only people with lower limb amputations found that only half were sexually active, and of that group, about 60 percent were sexually dysfunctional. The study’s authors highlighted the need for psychological and psychosexual assessment and intervention after amputation. “Depression, anxiety and body image issues were significantly associated with sexual dysfunction in the current sample of individuals with lower limb amputation,” they wrote.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="143" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna95fr00263b78eeuuqsbk@published"&gt;So yes, it’s hardly surprising that your erections aren’t what they used to be. Diabetes, also, can have detrimental effects on erection quality. You have tried pills, but you may need to look into other options like injectable ED meds (like Trimix) or even an implant. Have you been to therapy or sex coaching regarding your amputation and/or sexual dysfunction? That might also be helpful. You should search for a provider who specifically deals with amputation that is near you or otherwise reachable. You may also want to think about expanding your definition of sex to incorporate things that don’t require an erection—toys, roleplay, forms of BDSM and kink, dressing up, even talking dirty. Don’t give up on your search for a reliable erection, but this is an opportunity to think beyond that and to enter a realm that many take for granted.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="57" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna95j400273b78r3c1sas6@published"&gt;In the meantime, some community may help. There are subreddits like &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/amputee/"&gt;r/amputee&lt;/a&gt; that would allow you to share your issues and hear from others who have gone through the same thing. (Here is &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/amputee/comments/cqr2ct/being_an_amputee_affecting_sex_life/"&gt;one such thread&lt;/a&gt; about the effect of amputation on one’s sex life.) You shouldn’t be dealing with this alone, nor do you have to.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjnaapdr002b3b78ckw4ek2q@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmjna3a7g009q63mcq7zjjfo2@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOY19qX2hLdXZhV0FiZ2xFdmxRakwxYl91c1ZpNy02MlVzblRoSXJjbGxnM0dGR1pqcmpjMTkyazFYQ2RfVndtenAxQkY2QmljWDZaLXk5dDFrODRwam5KVE16OENlY0FrTkpxVmk0ajZYdXBIWXVBRzRNMHFZcS1hTEcyNW9aME9i</guid></item><item><title>这种常见疫苗可能会减缓甚至预防痴呆症的进展-雅虎加拿大新闻</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/common-vaccine-may-slow-progression-170000003.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The shingles vaccine may slow the progression of dementia or offer protection against developing it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Research published in the medical journal &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt; shows that the vaccine “slows or prevents disease progression across the entire disease course … of dementia”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“We’re much more confident that what we’re actually looking at here is cause and effect,” the study’s senior author said&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://people.com/health/shingles-vaccine-shingrix-what-to-know/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:shingles vaccine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;shingles vaccine&lt;/a&gt; may show the progression of dementia and “prevent early memory decline.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers looked at health records from more than 300,000 people in Wales between 2013 and 2022, and found that the herpes zoster (HZ) vaccine (the medical term for shingles) “slows or prevents disease progression across the entire disease course … of dementia,” according to new research published in the medical journal &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674%2825%2901256-5?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0092867425012565%3Fshowall%3Dtrue" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cell.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The researchers found that for those living with dementia, the vaccine reduced their risk of death by 29.5%; For those who had not been diagnosed, the vaccine lessened the likelihood of being diagnosed with cognitive impairment by 3%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Stock image of a doctor preparing a vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The effect of HZ vaccination — both on reducing new diagnoses of MCI and deaths due to dementia— was larger among women than men,” the study noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“That means that the vaccine doesn’t just have a preventive potential, but actually a therapeutic potential as a treatment, because we see some benefits already among those who have dementia,” &lt;a href="https://profiles.stanford.edu/pascal-geldsetzer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Pascal Geldsetzer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Pascal Geldsetzer&lt;/a&gt;, assistant professor of medicine at Stanford University and senior author of the new study, told &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/02/health/shingles-vaccine-dementia-progression-study-wellness" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CNN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;CNN&lt;/a&gt;. “To me, this was really exciting to see and unexpected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-puzzler-8620185" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The shingles vaccine is a two-dose series of shots given at age 50, or to immunocompromised adults once they turn 19, the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/shingles/vaccines/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:U.S. Centers for Disease Control;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;U.S. Centers for Disease Control&lt;/a&gt; explains. One in three adults will develop shingles, which causes an itchy rash on one side of the body and significant, often long-term, nerve pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s caused by the same virus as chickenpox, the CDC explains — but even if you’ve had chickenpox, you should be vaccinated as the “virus stays dormant (inactive) in the body. It can reactivate years later and cause shingles.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Stock image of an older adult with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://forms.dotdashmeredith.com/people-news-inline" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers accounted for eligibility requirements for the shingles vaccine in Wales and explained they were able to compare groups who were eligible with those who were not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“We know they should have similar physical activity level, diets, et cetera,” Geldsetzer said. “So, we’re much more confident that what we’re actually looking at here is cause and effect, rather than just correlation.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/this-common-vaccine-may-slow-the-progression-of-dementia-11862390" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOYUpKQVVBTFVhWE5iZm0yLTlzbGc2dnptSFY4aDFndTBub2hKQWtjeUt0TDFyWEtDZ0FHZ1NlMXVMVFkzbHJvazhuWjhTTmhWeE55eXB0S2d2b0lTZ0E3YUpVMWlLQTNIVHJ0U0c2d3pST3VYaG1LSVJvZlZ2OExicFZn</guid></item><item><title>听起来很健康流行语的食物可能会将添加的糖隐藏在显而易见的地方- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/foods-hiding-added-sugar-rcna251215</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1dd8cb" class="body-graf"&gt;Many consumers feel pride in avoiding the glazed pastries in the supermarket and instead opting for “all natural” granola that comes packed with extra protein. Same goes for low-fat yogurts “made with real fruit,” “organic” plant-based milks and bottled “superfood” smoothies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-397936" class="body-graf"&gt;Buyer beware: Healthy grocery buzzwords like those often cover up an &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/heat-hot-climate-sugar-soda-diabetes-dee1cb27322afb3e556fd2c6f8ecf1ae"&gt;unhealthy amount of sugar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-de4347" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://apnews.com/c147e0085eb842ac9144e8214dddd063"&gt;Added sugars&lt;/a&gt; are difficult to quickly spot because many companies use clever marketing to distract consumers, said Nicole Avena, a professor of neuroscience and psychiatry at Mount Sinai Medical School and Princeton University who has studied added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c89e47" class="body-graf"&gt;Avena said while some health-forward brands know people are starting to become aware of the hazards of added sugars, “a lot of the bigger brands don’t worry so much about people’s health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c4b8eb" class="body-graf"&gt;Here’s how to spot hidden sugars and what to do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-68f3fd" class="body-heading"&gt;What to look for&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5aa2d0" class="body-graf"&gt;Along with saturated fat and salt, eating excess sugar is linked to &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/033b68db8ce342cd9cfdcda57a628027"&gt;heart disease, obesity, diabetes and other health risks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0b2e4b" class="body-graf"&gt;The average American consumes 17 grams of added sugar a day, which adds up to 57 pounds (26 kilograms) per year, &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/sugar-shrink-the-sweet-spot-for-blood-sugar-health"&gt;according to the American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;. About half of that comes from beverages, but much of the rest is sneaked into cereal, salsa, prepared sandwiches, dairy products, bottled sauces and baked goods, including many brands of whole-grain bread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ea3274" class="body-graf"&gt;To help control sugar intake, start by checking the nutrition label. Since 2021, food companies have been required to list the quantity of added sugars separately from total sugar content. But the plan backfired, Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d3d9ff" class="body-graf"&gt;Companies reduced common sweeteners like refined beet sugar and high-fructose corn syrup but added alternatives, such as monk fruit and the sugar alcohol erythritol, which aren’t considered “added sugars” under FDA regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-622a60" class="body-graf"&gt;“Now our foods are even more sweet than they were back in 2020,” Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-b21085" class="body-heading"&gt;What should you do?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f2bc00" class="body-graf"&gt;Collin Popp, a dietitian and professor at NYU Langone Health, said the current FDA recommendation allows for some flexibility. People should get no more than 10% of their calories from added sugar, which amounts to about 50 grams per day if eating 2,000 calories, or a bit more than what’s in a typical can of soda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9e3502" class="body-graf"&gt;But that might be too flexible, Popp said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2c5e2a" class="body-graf"&gt;“I would actually like to see that be less than 5%, and closer to zero for some, if they have diabetes or prediabetes,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-23db2f" class="body-graf"&gt;The key is to &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/hub/food-safety"&gt;be mindful of what you’re eating&lt;/a&gt;, even if the product &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/28e626562c88439b96056e843215aa8d"&gt;seems healthy&lt;/a&gt; or if the package is labeled organic, Popp said. Roasted nuts, plant-based milks and wasabi peas, for example, can include a surprising amount of added sugars. So can English muffins and Greek yogurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b317d3" class="body-graf"&gt;One Chobani black cherry yogurt, for example, has zero grams of fat but 9 grams of added sugar, or more than 2 teaspoons. Silk brand almond milk has 7 grams per cup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b28053" class="body-graf"&gt;Popp recommends taking control of how much sugar goes into your food. That could mean buying plain yogurt and adding honey or berries, or asking the barista if you can put your own oat milk into your coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-311372" class="body-heading"&gt;Taking from one column to add to another&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e05cdd" class="body-graf"&gt;Although they lower the calorie content of foods, &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/coke-cane-sugar-corn-syrup-better-d7a70ebd4aef1564e409dd087f6a69c3"&gt;artificial sweeteners&lt;/a&gt; like stevia and sugar alcohols may not be better because they can encourage people to overeat, Avena said. She said research shows that sweet flavors are what activate the reward center of the brain, not the sugar itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-57ead7" class="body-graf"&gt;That’s not to write off sugar alternatives, including allulose for people with Type 1 diabetes since it doesn’t affect blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c63c93" class="body-graf"&gt;But for the general public, minimizing dependence on the overall sweetness of food is key to improving health, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-093690" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“Don’t let the food companies decide how much sugar you’re eating,” Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:40:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQRXdZdFBxYlpCdHc5bExyaDNTVm1PYmx1TU1CczlTck1MVkNEeHVmVXBWdjdwTjdabWV2TDByYVE3Wm5YM2dWTENKYVFSVHZqNVc4cG5uMzZtUWNfODVfcVZTWE1GS05SSk9aWV9UUTdUQTh4blFXVFN4QzNZZ2RWMVBNREXSAVZBVV95cUxNbkZoN2p1blhKY3pGdFdPcndzNU1RbXFzbDV1cGtFS2lGNGxLakpZTTJQeVZZUEhPTmwtMzZTcmRNQ18zMGZZdnpVY3d6UGVyMUhMdmEzQQ</guid></item><item><title>流感比过去2年更严重、更早。新泽西州的水平已经“非常高”。- NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/12/flu-hitting-harder-and-earlier-than-past-2-years-levels-in-nj-already-at-very-high.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5OT7WMBL2BGBLFBZAFD4JKFXOQ"&gt;Sick for the holidays with fever, chills and muscle aches? So is the rest of New Jersey, it seems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6AWCLG6YJFFFJPK365FTGGA6AI"&gt;The flu is hitting New Jersey harder and earlier in the season than the past two years, state and federal data shows. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="S7M6M7TDCNEXRGVNCX2EGXYKRY"&gt;New Jersey is one of five states currently experiencing “very high” levels of flu activity, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;United States Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. The others are New York, Rhode Island, Louisiana and Colorado. The numbers are based on the proportion of outpatient visits to healthcare providers for flu-like illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3JQQBHA6D5D6NGUYEEWPTXSTDI"&gt;The most common type being reported is the Influenza A virus, the CDC said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M7TANUSCQ5GPHDGBFYSUMQO554"&gt;Wondering if it’s something else like COVID-19, RSV or adenovirus? They’re out there, too, just not at the same rates as the flu, &lt;a href="https://www.nj.gov/health/respiratory-viruses/documents/reports/respiratory-illness-report-week51-2025.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;the Department of Health is reporting.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6SEAGS4NU5APPP42HM5NSUO2DU"&gt;While flu viruses are detected year-round in the U.S., the virus activity usually peaks between December and February. Last season, New Jersey saw its peak the first week of February, with more than 14,000 cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="X3EPCODT5ZGDJDGTYDKQ5DNYAQ"&gt;But during the week ending Dec. 20, there were 11,472 cases of the flu in New Jersey, &lt;a href="https://www.nj.gov/health/respiratory-viruses/documents/reports/respiratory-illness-report-week51-2025.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to the state’s most recent data&lt;/a&gt; — a jump from the previous week’s report of 6,940.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Q5QS3V2DYNBNJN2RVHH4WPHWJQ"&gt;During the last flu season, the state didn’t see those levels until late January. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="article__image"&gt;&lt;div class="article__image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="low" loading="lazy" decoding="async" alt="flu rates in new jersey" class="article__image-content" src="https://www.nj.com/resizer/v2/PB3NEQEWKBCV5N4OG3IZCALROU.png?auth=c6b783fc0c176dee86cdb4ac02b482190b3743c0f8945e8b37b15ade32bace29&amp;amp;width=1280&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90" srcset="https://www.nj.com/resizer/v2/PB3NEQEWKBCV5N4OG3IZCALROU.png?auth=c6b783fc0c176dee86cdb4ac02b482190b3743c0f8945e8b37b15ade32bace29&amp;amp;width=500&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90 500w, https://www.nj.com/resizer/v2/PB3NEQEWKBCV5N4OG3IZCALROU.png?auth=c6b783fc0c176dee86cdb4ac02b482190b3743c0f8945e8b37b15ade32bace29&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90 800w, https://www.nj.com/resizer/v2/PB3NEQEWKBCV5N4OG3IZCALROU.png?auth=c6b783fc0c176dee86cdb4ac02b482190b3743c0f8945e8b37b15ade32bace29&amp;amp;width=1280&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 500px) 100vw, (max-width: 800px) 80vw, 60vw"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="article__image-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="article__mm-image-caption-text"&gt;There were more than 11,000 cases of the flu reported in New Jersey the week ending Dec. 20, 2025 according to state data.&lt;span class="article__mm-image-credit"&gt;N.J. Department of Health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FKG7V4QQ3FGBTJVPMZBLNLFQ4Y"&gt;And they may only increase for the season once the data from the holidays — after all those indoor gatherings — are included. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LOXY45HD55DDZMOORTZH24GSMY"&gt;Before winter break, K-12 schools had already reported 42 influenza outbreaks for the month of December. There were just 4 outbreaks at the same time last year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RDGEW3ZZLNAJFDY4JSJMQWCAEU"&gt;Hospitalizations have also increased. About 8% of patients showing up to an emergency department are coming because of the flu, data shows. There were 500 hospitalizations reported for flu, COVID-19 and RSV for the week ending Dec. 20, with most of them being for the flu. The same week last year, there were about 150. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="T6MLALNTGNEOFGKDYPF6RRIS3E"&gt;Outbreaks remain lower in long-term care centers compared to previous Decembers, the data shows. There have been 68 respiratory illness outbreaks in the facilities so far this month, with more than half of them being the flu. The same month last year saw more than 100 outbreaks. However, the month isn’t over. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ABWKOVD3M5H3XF7KNZE2532LCM"&gt;While the majority of those being hospitalized for the flu are ages 65 and older, kids are becoming severely ill as well, according to state data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7WBNJJDQLNEGJHY7IOYRBM4NG4"&gt;There have been 31 severe pediatric flu cases this year so far in New Jersey. Last season there were 149 and 5 pediatric deaths. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3RN7TT7QDJANBDTSIV3Z5HVEEU"&gt;The CDC suggests everyone 6 months and older get vaccinated against the flu. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WK7ULKSKLBA5LL5FZLHIIGI33Q"&gt;Symptoms of the flu include fever, cough, sore throat, runny or stuffy nose, muscle or body aches, headaches and fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPZ294eklfRjlpWS02bmFad0oxNEswY0RDTElic2ZaNjU1WlFGTGdKMmNJa3VvOHNCNXVQeHlfby1qdk1ka1BWTG9IRGFGX0pSTTVrVndpMXpQRElBWUF6OGt0U2hHMjFBQVhrR2dPdE1zZGdfMktNLUt1NDJwTXV3REpsTHhfem9mZjZWMmRsMnFXR0s3ZFlUVm9wdXdpdWF5b0tjVXQ3WWQ5eWVrcWQ3NkotYkZaUjREVlhHcVo2b2I2QQ</guid></item><item><title>精神科医生揭示无药物治疗，成功率为70% --《每日邮报》</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15364771/psychiatrist-antidepressants-gym-exercise-depression-anxiety.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Arnold Gilberg is on a mission to help people live happier and healthier lives without antidepressants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nearly 29 million Americans currently take antidepressant medication, but Gilberg believes these pills should be an absolute last resort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And it seems his drug-free methods can work, with the doctor boasting a 70 percent success rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For &lt;span&gt;Gilberg, a leading psychiatrist at Cedars-Sinai Hospital, deep dialogue is key in tackling the root cause of issues rather than opting for a quick chemical fix.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Exercise is also a nonnegotiable &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-10751875/Adults-exercise-75-minutes-week-18-likely-depression.html"&gt;for his patients&lt;/a&gt;, and he insists that if they want him to be their psychiatrist, they must start working out. &lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'I write prescriptions for gym memberships, not pills,' Gilberg told the Daily Mail. He claimed nearly three-quarters of his patients have improved since beginning an exercise regimen.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt; 'The psychoanalytic way of thinking has always been that there were other approaches other than the use of medications,' said Gilberg, who also helps A-list actors delve into the minds of their characters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'You get some benefit from the medication, but it does have a numbing effect… that's why I'm very reluctant about them.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Arnold Gilberg (pictured) is a leading psychiatrist at Cedars-Sinai in Los Angeles and trained psychoanalyst who is reluctant to prescribe antidepressants&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Gilberg's method of treating patients with mild to severe anxiety and &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/depression/index.html" id="mol-e67d12d0-d799-11f0-a57f-b5ccfc25dd93"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt; was shaped by the teachings of his mentor Franz Alexander, a psychoanalyst who learned the theories and techniques from Sigmund Freud himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alexander, who is widely considered the father of psychosomatic medicine, instilled in Gilberg the importance of treating the whole person within the context of their life, not just a set of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;During a patient's first 50-minute session at Gilberg's office, the primary focus is delving into current crises they are experiencing rather than exclusively exploring more profound childhood trauma. This might be a divorce, bereavement, problems with a child or job stress, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Gilberg is also a big fan of yoga, framing it as an 'opportunity' for patients to actively participate in their own healing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I'm very holistic,' he told the Daily Mail. 'I encourage all my patients to do yoga and meditate, and there are all these modalities of care that we have available to us.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Exercise acts as a powerful, natural antidepressant by increasing the brain's production of endorphins and other mood-regulating neurotransmitters like serotonin and norepinephrine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It also reduces the body's stress hormones, such as cortisol and adrenaline, helping to alleviate both depression and anxiety. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Harvard researchers reported in 2019 that committing to a manageable bout of exercise, such as 15 minutes of brisk walking, can reduce the risk of depression &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/mind-and-mood/more-evidence-that-exercise-can-boost-mood"&gt;by 26 percent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This isn't to say that Gilberg and other psychoanalysts have stopped rooting out trauma.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead they address the most immediate problem, such as a sudden loss, first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We all have traumas in development. That's just the way it goes,' he said, describing a foundational Freudian concept. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'And as a psychoanalyst, over time, you do explore those issues. But when a person's going through an acute trauma, that's not the time to start peeling away at the onion.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So essentially, he seeks to put out the fire first and find the cause later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Freud believed the mind was a fortress that guarded painful memories and secrets rooted in traumatic experiences, which the psyche buried deep in your subconscious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Recent data indicates over 47 million American adults currently have or are being treated for depression, while statistics show over 21 million adults and five million adolescents experienced a depressive episode in the past year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Between 2009 and 2018, antidepressant use rose significantly among women, climbing from 13.8 percent to 18.6 percent. For men, however, the rate remained relatively stable, rising only slightly from 7.1 percent to 8.7 percent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He theorized that when these memories broke through the mind's defenses, they manifested as symptoms like anxiety or dissociation from your body or surroundings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The path to healing, in Freud's view, was slow, deliberate work facing scarring memories head-on. The goal was to gently unearth this unconscious material and integrate it into a conscious narrative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Today's psychoanalytic thinking is different,' said Gilberg, who is also the author of &lt;a target="_blank" class="" rel="nofollow" href="https://www.amazon.com/Myth-Aging-Prescription-Emotional-Well-Being/dp/B0FKN9WVMS"&gt;The Myth of Aging: A Prescription for Emotional and Physical Well-Being&lt;/a&gt;. 'We're not interested in going back to what happened when they were a child, but we want to stay on top of what's going on now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So we explore how badly he or she feels. We want to talk about what they're doing to make things a bit better.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Gilberg has not shunned antidepressants completely, and acknowledges they can be 'worthwhile and good options' for severe, biologically rooted conditions such as major depression or bipolar disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But he worries that pills have gone from being just one facet of a mental health treatment plan, which typically includes regular therapy, to the default approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Uptake of antidepressants has risen steadily for decades, particularly since the 1987 release of Prozac, the world's first selective serotonin reuptake inhibitor (SSRI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prescriptions of SSRIs and similar SNRIs (serotonin-norepinephrine reuptake inhibitors) soared in the years that followed. Americans filled 42 million prescriptions in 2010, a figure that rose 108 percent to more than 88 million by 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In 2010, Americans filled 42 million SSRI or SNRI prescriptions - this number surged by 108 percent to more than 88 million by 2023&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'While I believe in antidepressants for major illnesses like bipolar and schizophrenia, I have been concerned about the use of antidepressants, which are dished out so easily, because of the impact they have on the individual,' Gilberg told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He added that SSRIs have been used so widely that they have become not just the default treatment approach among many doctors but among patients as well - many of whom have been led to think they cannot solve internal conflicts through non-medical modes like psychotherapy, or that they will provide a quick fix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I think that for myself, anyway, we have to be very discriminating about how we use the medications that we have available to us, because the medications themselves have side effects,' he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many patients taking the medications experience sexual dysfunction, including low libido, delayed orgasm or numbness, which can strain relationships and lower quality of life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other frequent complaints include weight gain, feeling detached or less responsive - known as emotional blunting - and digestive issues like nausea or constipation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While not everyone is affected, he said these side effects are common enough for around a quarter of patients to stop taking their medication as a result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;You can &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;pre-order Gilberg's new book&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;, The Myth of Aging: A Prescription for Emotional and Physical Well-Being, out on January 13, 2026. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:58:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxPQ1NZeUNLWElmWkxRX2o0MzVhWHRvdkNWVC1DWDlkTmFyQ1R4TTk1RnhRZkRJQ3lZU2w2S1I4MFJhcFNwbElqcVVHWVBEVkR6b1F4a1g1N1NRRkpobEVIV0pZMWlTaGhkbXJYZ1ZUamdvSWdXMDBxb1BVNFcyOTJTVDJEWUQzOWh2bWN1MFotMW1rRGF4TW5NUnhZeDNzYjhyYkdHSGxOb1RRSkQ0TWRTNFRLYzdOR1JW</guid></item><item><title>2026年8种吃得更好、吃得更少的方法- Salon.com</title><link>https://www.salon.com/2025/12/28/8-ways-to-eat-better-for-less-in-2026/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="article__content page-article"&gt;&lt;p&gt;I could tell you a dozen stories about cooking on a budget. Some are triumphant—like the time I hosted my entire MFA cohort with a DIY &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2019/03/02/crispy-creamy-loaded-baked-potatoes-recipe-fully-loaded_partner/"&gt;baked potato&lt;/a&gt; bar and some donated &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/01/21/no-time-for-celebration-champagne-sales-are-reportedly-on-the-decline-new-report-finds/"&gt;champagne.&lt;/a&gt; Others are sadder: the week a breakup coincided with unexpected medical bills, when I stood at the self-checkout feeding $23 worth of quarters (my last money until payday, and yes, it takes exactly as long as you’re imagining) into the machine so I could buy &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2020/06/20/alton-brown-good-eats-grilling-pantry-salon-talks/"&gt;chicken thighs&lt;/a&gt;, vegetables and rice. All I wanted then was to sink into a pot of chicken-and-rice stew and weep.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This story is different. This one is about quiet confidence — the sort that only comes from surviving enough $23-in-quarters days to know you’ll be okay.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It began innocently. I’d swapped handbags for the season — a slouchy straw tote with a teak handle traded for a forest-green suede pouch — and my wallet, apparently, hadn’t gotten the memo. Because of my deep and abiding distrust of &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/01/31/a-patriot-economy-media-expands-into-fintech-with-truthfi/"&gt;fintech&lt;/a&gt; (a story for another day), I keep a little emergency cash tucked into my bags. Still, there I was in the supermarket, wallet-less, armed with $12, a dying phone and my transit card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a moment, I panicked. And then I didn’t. I realized I had everything I needed to get home and make a good dinner. What, exactly, was I pressed about?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started in the produce aisle, as I often do, scanning the marked-down netted bags — imperfect, but still sturdy and fragrant. I grabbed one with a few &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2020/12/25/how-to-make-savory-sweet-shallot-jam-with-three-ingredients_partner/"&gt;shallots &lt;/a&gt;and a &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/03/19/youre-cooking-with-one-onion-you-should-be-cooking-with-four/"&gt;head of garlic&lt;/a&gt;, added a carton of cheap white mushrooms, then a ninety-nine-cent box of pasta, a small wedge of Parm from Murray’s “under $5” bin and a carton of six eggs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back home, after the train ride, I washed and dried the mushrooms and sent them sizzling into a pan with shallots, garlic, salt, pepper and an indecent amount of smoked paprika. They crisped and darkened, developing a savory depth that stood in happily for pork. Tossed with pasta, egg, cheese, and a little of the starchy cooking water, they became a mushroom &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2021/04/24/my-10-year-carbonara-journey/"&gt;carbonara&lt;/a&gt;—rich, smoky, and deeply satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It felt decadent. And there was enough for two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want more great food writing and recipes? &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/newsletter?utm_source=onsite&amp;amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;amp;utm_campaign=the-bite-edit-signup"&gt;Sign up for Salon’s free food newsletter&lt;/a&gt;, The Bite.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I keep thinking about that meal, especially because this year has been rough. Groceries cost more, time feels thinner and the idea that eating well — both pleasurable and nourishing — should be attainable on a modest budget can feel almost quaint. As we head into a new year, many of us are doing the same math over and over: trying to square taste with nutrition, care with constraint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If this feels familiar —if you’re feeling tired, hungry and underpaid all at once—let me just say: you’re not imagining it. You’re not alone. I’ve teared up in grocery aisles myself, realizing the little treat I’d budgeted for (or some weeks, the extra bit of meat) wasn’t actually in the cards. I’ve experimented extensively with how far a pot of chicken-and-rice stew can stretch with just a little extra broth. I’ve taken two trains to pick up &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2024/11/30/too-good-to-go-the-second-life-of-leftovers/"&gt;Too Good To Go &lt;/a&gt;leftovers from restaurants I couldn’t normally afford. I could tell you a dozen ways to use Bisquick to fill out a meal — and I’m fairly certain I could discover a dozen more.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;But here’s the thing: good food doesn’t have to be expensive. We know this, even if it’s easy to forget. There is something elementally heavenly about the smell of alliums cooking in butter. Spoon it over a comforting bulk grain — pasta, rice, polenta, &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2022/05/30/everything-you-need-to-know-about-growing-beans_partner/"&gt;beans&lt;/a&gt; — top it with a single egg, and it will set you right almost every time. You can scale up if you like: some grated cheese, a scatter of fresh herbs, maybe crispy pork. But you don’t have to. Sometimes, that restraint is the nicest thing you can do for Future You.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What follows are a few principles I’ve learned for cooking this way. Not perfectly, but with steadiness, pleasure and budget in mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Nurture a rolodex of “rent week” recipes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a special kind of comfort in having a short list of meals you know, with almost mathematical certainty, will land. In the culinary world, this is often called “rent week” cooking—a term popularized by Alex Delaney in &lt;a href="https://www.bonappetit.com/misc/rent-week?srsltid=AfmBOoqPezkgb7NaXpjfChEJP2XkPOxgmqobSrar3fhCyi5j0FBSrWUi"&gt;his Bon Appétit column &lt;/a&gt;from 2016 to 2019. Delaney’s recipes had a magic trick: they were cheap, fast, and reliably delicious. Think “&lt;a href="https://www.bonappetit.com/story/overdraft-protection-polenta?srsltid=AfmBOopUkOqvJx71Rw2GKhFLWlFjvjXQUIT5zyIhaNEL9AjBs3EhtyQR"&gt;overdraft-protection polenta&lt;/a&gt;” or a “&lt;a href="https://www.bonappetit.com/story/rent-week-chorizo-tostada?srsltid=AfmBOoqzeevK15fXCuzfN6N8o7m9l5xw6HD9YBIIZuPQATTXvrkm-E8y"&gt;cheap chorizo tostada&lt;/a&gt;” — meals that somehow still felt cheffy, like a little wink at your former foodie ambitions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I discovered that column shortly after graduating, when my love of food far outstripped my paycheck in public media. It hit just at the right time. For me, my own rent-week roster looks like the mushroom carbonara I’ve told you about, a smoky chickpea curry, feta-eggs on rice with avocado slices, or a black bean stew that can stretch either with a bit of chorizo or a rotisserie chicken scavenged from the sale bin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The point isn’t perfection—it’s predictability, pleasure, and the quiet relief of knowing that, even when the week is long and the budget short, dinner is still a thing you can get right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Learn the rhythms of your grocery store&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every supermarket has a secret life, if you know how to watch. There’s a cadence to sales, a pattern to coupons, a small ecosystem of rewards programs and “oops” bins where imperfect or surplus food waits quietly for someone to notice. At my Mariano’s, there’s a section labeled “Oops! We baked too much,” which houses overstock bread and &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/10/14/fig-jam-hand-pies-for-the-hesitant-host/"&gt;pastries&lt;/a&gt;. There’s also a section for imperfect produce, as well as a tiny corner of discounted meat, like a tiny treasure trove for those paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not just about snagging a deal; it’s about knowing where the value is and when. Some stores have unbeatable per-unit prices on pantry staples, while others shine with proteins or prepared items. The Vietnamese grocery down my street, for example, always has the best Jasmine rice and canned coconut milk, though the protein prices are steeper. Knowing this allows me to plan trips that actually make sense: sometimes it’s worth a detour for a specialty ingredient, other times it’s smarter to stick to one store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think of it like learning the rhythm of your own kitchen, except bigger, louder, and fluorescent-lit: once you understand it, your budget stretches in ways that feel almost effortless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Plan a little for Future You&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll admit it: I am a dork about pre-planning. I keep a household binder that I update quarterly, a habit that became strangely essential while recovering from lingering post-COVID brain fog. One section is devoted entirely to food, subdivided into tiny compartments of order: nutrition goals for the quarter, menus and budgets for holidays or birthdays, recipes I want to try (already printed and annotated with shopping lists), and finally, the pièce de résistance—my quarterly dinner queue.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dinner queue is a concept I first encountered in Kendra Adachi’s “&lt;a href="https://www.thelazygeniuscollective.com/kitchen"&gt;The Lazy Genius Kitchen&lt;/a&gt;.” It’s deceptively simple: a curated list of meals you intend to make for dinner. You might be thinking, “Isn’t the whole internet a list? Aren’t all my cookbooks lists?” Yes, but those lists are too big. Overwhelming. And overwhelm is the state in which I make most of my bad financial decisions. Adachi &lt;a href="https://www.thelazygeniuscollective.com/lazy/falldinners"&gt;puts it beautifully&lt;/a&gt;: “A dinner queue can be ten meals you repeat, thirty meals you do for an entire month and repeat, or maybe even more than that if you’re not a fan of repetition.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need a binder or a full-blown quarterly system to reap the benefits. Even a little pre-planning—whether for a week, a month, or a cooking “season”—lets you approach dinner with confidence, reduces stress, and keeps your budget in mind without having to reinvent every meal from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;But stay flexible (and realistic)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some nights, you come home late on a snowy evening and the last thing you want to do is make whatever dinner you had meticulously planned. That’s when a little self-compassion—and a small arsenal of freezer and pantry favorites—becomes your secret weapon. &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/11/26/let-trader-joes-help-you-plan-a-budget-thanksgiving-dinner-for-30/"&gt;Trader Joe’s &lt;/a&gt;orange chicken. A bag of dumplings. Stouffer’s lasagna. White cheddar shells. Even a frozen pizza that’s not quite artisanal but somehow perfect.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These “easy wins” bridge the gap between exhaustion and sustenance without forcing you to spend $72 on a pair of sad burrito bowls from a takeout app. The trick is building a little wiggle room in your budget for them—so that a fallback meal feels like a relief, not a splurge. Flexibility isn’t about throwing plans out the window; it’s about giving Future You the kindness and tools needed to survive the week with dignity, warmth and, yes, occasional cheese.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Nerd out on technique&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a surprising joy to be found in coaxing the absolute most from humble ingredients—if you can be bothered to notice. Stewing a piece of meat until it transforms from leather into something tender and succulent. Turning the odds and ends of vegetables—peels, stems, bruised bits—into a fragrant stock that makes even weeknight soup feel luxurious. Toasting spices in oil until they bloom and scent the kitchen with something almost magical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s not about impressing anyone. It’s about seeing potential in the ordinary, finding pleasure in the small transformations and discovering that even the simplest ingredients can carry a richness you’d almost forgotten was possible. Technique is not a chore. It’s a quiet way to honor your food, your time and Future You.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Give everything a second life&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite lessons came from a restaurant manager at a small, hip café: “Give everything a second life.” It sounds obvious, but it’s amazing how often we toss what could be treasure. Take carrots, for instance. Carrot peels became stock. Extra shredded carrots were saved for &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/10/28/a-better-pumpkin-bread-made-with-coffee-citrus-and-chocolate/"&gt;bread&lt;/a&gt; or pickled for a salad. Carrot tops were transformed into pesto. Nothing went to waste and everything found a purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Carleigh Bodrug’s “&lt;a href="https://plantyou.com/category/scrappy-cooking/"&gt;Scrappy Cooking&lt;/a&gt;” and Tamar Adler’s “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Everlasting-Meal-Cookbook-Leftovers-Z/dp/1476799660"&gt;The Everlasting Meal Cookbook&lt;/a&gt;” are brilliant companions for this mindset, offering clever, unexpected ways to elevate what might otherwise be scraps. It turns the ordinary into something that feels thoughtful, deliberate, and yes—a little magical.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Build a solid pantry, bit by bit&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was lucky enough to grow up in a household where basics were taken for granted, which made adulthood a bit of a shock: decent toilet paper, a shower curtain that doesn’t disintegrate in the wash, a rug that actually fits under the bed — all these small necessities suddenly had a cost. But the real challenge, and the real joy, was building a pantry beyond salt, pepper and oil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s the honest truth: the difference between a budget meal that tastes like one and one that doesn’t is often just time (a soup simmered for 90 minutes instead of 15 will taste richer) and decent spices. It’s worth investing slowly. International markets often have the best deals on spices, but your local supermarket can surprise you too — especially during holiday or New Year sales. For nonperishables, picking up an extra can or two of beans, a jar of tomato paste, or a staple oil can quietly change the trajectory of your weeknight cooking. Even dedicating a small portion of your grocery budget — $20 a month, say — to new spices, vinegars or oils can steadily bolster your collection, making your pantry a toolkit for meals that feel abundant, not scrappy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Master a few “fridge clean-out” meals&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a different beast from your rent-week recipes, but just as essential. The idea is simple: have a few go-to templates for using up the bibs and bobs lurking in your kitchen, depending on your mood and what’s in the crisper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2022/06/05/the-frittata-that-bought-us-a_partner/"&gt;frittatas&lt;/a&gt; or egg bakes, perfect for dispatching vegetable scraps, wilting herbs, bits of cheese or that lone slice of bacon that’s been begging for a job. Or a &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2022/01/24/cozy-up-to-this-new-chicken-and-wild-mushroom-stew-with-schmaltzy-croutons/"&gt;sturdy stew&lt;/a&gt;: a can of tomatoes, an errant link of sausage, a handful of chickpeas, all brightened with greens that need a home. Stir-fries, &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/11/13/better-oatmeal-made-at-home/"&gt;savory oats&lt;/a&gt;, rice bowls, flatbreads, &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/08/19/i-rescued-a-panini-press-it-saved-dinner/"&gt;paninis,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/11/18/a-magical-maple-pumpkin-pasta-sauce/"&gt;pasta&lt;/a&gt;—whatever suits your style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The joy of these meals is in their freedom: they’re forgiving, flexible, and somehow deeply satisfying. Fridge clean-out cooking turns potential waste into dinner that feels intentional, resourceful and, above all, comforting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="layout_template_wrapper read_more"&gt;
&lt;div class="red_white_box"&gt;
&lt;p class="red_box"&gt;Read more&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="white_box"&gt;about this topic&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Salon.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:30:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE96UzlZUEtQc2UtUFlONmp4M1NGT1V1UGVyM3dsamc4RkMtZFRkQXpyZ0R0NHpYc3pzZzJGb2puT1QwZDc4OFBvZkpiek9XUEwzWWJqYkpjR3dQWDJtbEFNZ2NTeGt4RE56QnhTVzN4UllxcXFkNDhqWUticw</guid></item><item><title>根据科学家的说法，这是一天中喝咖啡的最佳时间- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/best-time-day-drink-coffee-141800538.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Scientists Say When to Drink Coffee for Longevity&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;FG Trade - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There is a strong link between the time of day that people drink coffee and their longevity, according to one study.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Researchers found that morning coffee drinkers had a lower all-cause mortality risk and a lower risk of heart disease compared to people who drank coffee all day or didn't drink it at all.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Morning coffee consumption seems to align best with the body's circadian rhythms, promoting better sleep and supporting healthy hormone secretion.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies continue to pile up on the health benefits of drinking coffee. Researchers say that it may help &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a62414579/caffeinated-coffee-and-tea-reduce-heart-disease-risk-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reduce your risk of stroke and heart attack;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;reduce your risk of stroke and heart attack&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a62137526/coffee-muscle-mass-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:boost muscle mass;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;boost muscle mass&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and even &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a63187043/drinking-coffee-could-add-2-years-to-your-life-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:add years to your life;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;add years to your life&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, provided you aren't adding heaps of sweetener to every cup. What's more, research suggests that just as there is a &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/a69417366/best-time-to-drink-coffee/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:best time of day to drink coffee for energy;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;best time of day to drink coffee for energy&lt;/a&gt;, there is also a best time of day to drink coffee for longevity. Read on to discover why the timing of your coffee intake matters for how well you're aging and how many benefits you can get from your sip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meet the experts: &lt;a href="https://sph.tulane.edu/epid/lu-qi" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lu Qi, M.D., Ph.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Lu Qi, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, professor at the Celia Scott Weatherhead School of Public Health and Tropical Medicine at Tulane University; &lt;a href="https://www.eatrightpro.org/about-us/for-media/meet-our-spokespeople/melissa-ann-prest" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Melissa Mroz-Planells, D.C.N., R.D.N.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Melissa Mroz-Planells, D.C.N., R.D.N.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, national media spokesperson for the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics and member of the &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/about/g26577234/medical-review-board/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Prevention Medical Review Board;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Prevention&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;u&gt; Medical Review Board&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="https://baptisthealth.net/doctors/adedapo-adeyinka-iluyomade/2103193" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Adedapo Iluyomade, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Adedapo Iluyomade, M.D.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, preventative cardiologist with Baptist Health Miami Cardiac &amp;amp; Vascular Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurheartj/advance-article/doi/10.1093/eurheartj/ehae871/7928425?login=false" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:European Heart Journal;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;European Heart Journal&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; looked into the timing of drinking &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/food-nutrition/healthy-eating/a69286619/is-coffee-actually-good-for-you/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:coffee;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt; and how it relates to longevity. The analysis involved 40,725 adults in the U.S. National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey (NHANES) between 1999 and 2018, in which participants were asked about all the food and drink they consumed on at least one day, including whether they drank coffee, how much, and when. It also included a sub-group of 1,463 people who were asked to complete a detailed food and drink diary for a full week. This information was then linked with records of deaths and causes of death over a period of nine to 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that compared with people who did not drink coffee, morning coffee drinkers were 16% less likely to die of any cause and 31% less likely to die of cardiovascular disease. However, there was no reduction in risk for all-day coffee drinkers compared to non-coffee drinkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morning coffee drinkers were found to have a lower risk of all-cause mortality and &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a69277325/top-heart-disease-risk-factors/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:heart disease;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, whether they had two to three cups per day or more than three cups. In comparison, those who had one cup or less in the morning benefitted from a smaller decrease in risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings indicate that it’s not just whether you drink coffee or how much you drink, but the time of day when you drink coffee that’s important,” senior study author &lt;a href="https://sph.tulane.edu/epid/lu-qi" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lu Qi, M.D., Ph.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Lu Qi, M.D., Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, professor at the Celia Scott Weatherhead School of Public Health and Tropical Medicine at Tulane University said in a &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1069398" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:news release;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;news release&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. “We don’t typically give advice about timing in our dietary guidance,” Dr. Qi continued, “but perhaps we should be thinking about this in the future.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, how does coffee benefit health? In addition to making you feel upbeat and energized, coffee also contains phenolic acid and flavonoids—antioxidants that protect your body from the damage caused by free radicals, said &lt;a href="https://www.eatrightpro.org/about-us/for-media/meet-our-spokespeople/melissa-ann-prest" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Melissa Mroz-Planells, D.C.N., R.D.N.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Melissa Mroz-Planells, D.C.N., R.D.N.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, national media spokesperson for the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics and member of the &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/about/g26577234/medical-review-board/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Prevention Medical Review Board;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Prevention&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;u&gt; Medical Review Board&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, this study suggests that morning coffee consumption, as opposed to an all-day pattern, may be linked to even lower risks of all-cause and cardiovascular mortality. “This association may be due to coffee’s interaction with circadian rhythms," said &lt;a href="https://baptisthealth.net/doctors/adedapo-adeyinka-iluyomade/2103193" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Adedapo Iluyomade, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Adedapo Iluyomade, M.D.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, preventative cardiologist with Baptist Health Miami Cardiac &amp;amp; Vascular Institute. "Consuming caffeine later in the day can &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/sleep-energy/a69197866/melatonin-vs-magnesium-for-sleep/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:disrupt sleep patterns;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;disrupt sleep patterns&lt;/a&gt; and melatonin secretion, potentially negating some of its health benefits.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having coffee earlier in the day is usually recommended so as not to disrupt your circadian rhythm, agreed Mroz-Planells, as “poor sleep quality and lack of sleep can affect your health and wellbeing.” A study published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38007301/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Sleep Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Sleep Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/em&gt;even found that poor sleep quality was associated with an increased risk of all-cause mortality among middle-aged and older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study highlights that both the timing and amount of coffee you drink matter when assessing its health benefits, said Dr. Iluyomade. “Regular, moderate coffee intake in the morning appears to confer a greater protective effect against cardiovascular and overall mortality compared to sporadic or late-day consumption, emphasizing the importance of aligning dietary habits with natural circadian rhythms,” he explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coffee’s health benefits are not limited to cardiovascular protection, Dr. Iluyomade continued. “Moderate intake has also been linked to a reduced risk of several chronic conditions, including type 2 diabetes, certain cancers, and neurodegenerative diseases.” However, these associations are based on observational data, so individuals should consider their own tolerance and response to caffeine, he pointed out. Either way, if you like to start your day with a cup or two of coffee, feel free to keep at it—just consider switching to other beverages like water later in the day to get the most health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 15:25:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE8wV2dOT3hYY3FRTjhpUFc5Uk9BRmNGaHFhd2hxYm5VQzBhWjJ6WE5VZHY4dUNNRWNiS0pRMnhEM1VhcjdTd1B5T3A2c29GdUFNX1kwTTdNUEtRcldHR0VDemFxTUxtOF9DaVF6dVg5bGxvazlmV015a1Fn</guid></item><item><title>医生揭示了可以帮助您长寿的早餐习惯- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/breakfast-habit-to-live-longer-11870650</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A doctor says eating a breakfast with protein, fiber and healthy fat may help you live longer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This formula helps manage blood sugar, fights inflammation and protects against weight gain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For more benefits, add berries, veggies and probiotic-containing foods to your breakfast.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Breakfast sets the stage for your day ahead, which is why doctors recommend eating a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7874786/best-healthy-breakfast-foods-to-eat/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthy, satisfying morning meal&lt;/a&gt;. For longevity, cardiologist &lt;a href="https://www.palmhealth.com/our-team/lauren-munsch-dal-farra-md/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Lauren Dal Farra, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, recommends building your breakfast around three nutritional pillars: protein, healthy fat and fiber. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, what does this look like? It starts with protein. “A protein-forward breakfast is one of the simplest ways to protect your metabolism and long-term health,” Dal Farra says. You can get that protein from eggs, strained (Greek-style) yogurt, beans, tofu, smoked salmon or even tuna fish or turkey. For healthy fats, we have olive oil, avocado, nuts, nut butter and seeds. And for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/small-changes-that-helped-me-eat-more-fiber-11775341" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber, focus on whole grains, fruits and veggies&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Whether you’re a breakfast eater or not, you can follow this advice no matter what time of day you have your first meal. If that sounds good to you, read on to learn why this approach is so great for longevity, plus other breakfast habits to keep you healthy, longer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-protein-fat-and-fiber-at-breakfast-can-help-you-live-longer"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Protein, Fat and Fiber at Breakfast Can Help You Live Longer &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Protein and Healthy Fats Help Stabilize Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Going on a blood sugar roller coaster first thing in the morning doesn’t feel great—and it doesn’t do your body good in the long term either. “A cornerstone of longevity is stable blood sugar, which will protect your heart and brain health over time,” says Dal Farra.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; As she explains, repeated glucose spikes will push insulin levels higher, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7902105/stress-causing-inflammation-what-you-can-do-about-it/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;increasing inflammation and oxidative stress&lt;/a&gt; that can cause vascular damage and accelerate cellular aging.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Breakfast is a key meal that sets the tone for your blood sugar patterns throughout the day,” she says. That’s where protein and healthy fats come in. Both these nutrients are digested gradually, helping to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8066203/habit-to-break-insulin-resistance/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;slow the absorption of carbs&lt;/a&gt; from your meal and keeping blood sugar on an even keel throughout the morning.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; It Can Help Protect Against Weight Gain &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Protein, fat and fiber are a powerful hunger-quashing trio that work together to help you feel full, says Dal Farra.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And feeling satiated and satisfied after a meal can help you &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2056824/16-weight-loss-tips-and-tricks-that-actually-work-according-to-dietitians/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;maintain a healthy weight&lt;/a&gt;. Gaining weight with age, on the other hand, has been linked to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7898812/how-food-can-help-you-look-and-feel-more-youthful-heres-what-the-science-says/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;faster biological aging in women&lt;/a&gt;—speeding up cellular aging by several years.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Fiber Supports Healthy Aging &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; White toast, granola bars, sweetened cereal, pancakes and waffles are go-to breakfast foods for many of us. Although all foods can have their place in a healthy eating pattern, a heavy intake of these kinds of refined carbohydrates (or “naked carbs,” as Dal Farra likes to call them) has been linked to a lower odds of healthy aging. On the other hand, research has shown that focusing on fiber-rich carbohydrates from foods like fruits, vegetables, legumes and whole grains is associated with a greater likelihood of healthy aging.&lt;span data-cite="10" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One of the easiest ways to work some fiber into your morning is with a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/our-best-high-fiber-overnight-oats-recipes-11744812" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;bowl of oatmeal, overnight oats or unsweetened whole-grain cereal&lt;/a&gt;. But when you don’t have time for a sit-down breakfast at home, grab an apple, an orange or a pear to eat with your breakfast later. They’re &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/our-best-high-fiber-snack-recipes-11727352" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;high in fiber and easy to take on the go&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Healthy Fats Quash Inflammation &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fat may help keep you full. However, the type you choose matters—a lot. Research suggests that saturated fat, in foods like butter, cream cheese, pastries, sausage and bacon, may speed up cellular aging. On the flip side, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/swap-to-lower-risk-of-heart-disease-and-diabetes-8679543" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;monounsaturated and polyunsaturated fats&lt;/a&gt; may help slow down the aging process in our cells, possibly by &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-inflammation-ages-you-8744048" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reducing damaging inflammation and oxidative stress&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span data-cite="11" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; You can get these healthy fats from avocados, olive oil, nuts, nut butter, seeds, smoked salmon and herring and even eggs. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-breakfast-habits-for-longevity"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Breakfast Habits for Longevity &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’d like to squeeze more &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7900915/foods-associated-with-living-longer-according-to-research/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;longevity-promoting foods&lt;/a&gt; into your morning, these simple tips can help:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat breakfast in the first place: &lt;/strong&gt;One meta-analysis of more than 2 million people found that those who &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-skip-breakfast-8417958" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;skipped breakfast&lt;/a&gt; were 17% more likely to develop cardiovascular disease, including coronary artery disease and stroke, than those who ate a morning meal regularly.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;So, try to eat something, even if it’s just a container of yogurt with a handful of nuts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Serve up a side of berries: &lt;/strong&gt;Whether it’s strawberries, blueberries, raspberries or blackberries, people who eat berries are 21% less likely to die from any cause than people who don’t eat these fruits.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt; Experts suspect this is due to berries’ &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-antioxidant-packed-foods-11813913" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;ample antioxidant compounds called flavonoids&lt;/a&gt;. Berries are also a tasty way to score extra fiber.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add a source of probiotics: &lt;/strong&gt;Foods that contain probiotics (live microbes), like yogurt and kefir, may help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290445/3-foods-to-ditch-for-a-healthy-gut/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;improve the microbial environment in your gut&lt;/a&gt;. This improved gut health may reduce inflammation, which is one reason why consuming these probiotic-rich foods may help slow biological aging.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat a serving of vegetables: &lt;/strong&gt;Getting your five-a-day really &lt;em&gt;is &lt;/em&gt;important. This magic number is associated with a lower risk of death from any cause, especially cardiovascular disease, cancer and respiratory disease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; However, if you really want to get granular, researchers say the best way to break it down is &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290393/what-does-a-day-of-fruits-and-vegetables-look-like/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;three daily servings of vegetables and two servings of fruit&lt;/a&gt;. Given that most of us eat three meals daily, aim to get one serving of veggies at breakfast, and you’ll be well on your way to shoring up your body’s natural disease-fighting defenses. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; We asked a doctor to share the best breakfast habit for longevity, and she said it’s eating a balanced breakfast that contains a mix of protein, fiber and healthy fats. This trio of nutrients works in several ways to help you live longer, including &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/simple-ways-to-keep-blood-sugar-in-check-11791785" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;stabilizing blood sugar&lt;/a&gt;, protecting against weight gain and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-top-nutrients-to-fight-inflammation-8675325" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reducing inflammation&lt;/a&gt;. What foods should you choose? Eggs, cottage cheese, strained (Greek-style) yogurt, tofu and beans make for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/proteins-to-eat-every-week-11684415" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;nutritious protein sources&lt;/a&gt;, while &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/287743/6-high-fiber-food-swaps-to-make-right-now/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;good sources of fiber&lt;/a&gt; come from fruits, vegetables, whole grains and seeds. Finally, don’t forget to top it all off with a little healthy fat from avocados, nuts, nut butter, seeds or smoked fish. Together, these foods aren’t just a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-pantry-staples-for-healthy-aging-11730036" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;winning recipe for longevity&lt;/a&gt;. They taste great, too!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE8tY3J5akZyOWl3MVkySktZakhvXzMtM3BMRkhBODlyX0doVjN4UXAyZVFHWVd5a0RjRVhKSWdPRFplZTJjdTZ0NTRXVVdYN2JqMFEtOWdDRXZiY2UzN3ZVa0lualp5TzltaU9LeFBOdVVvOC1f</guid></item><item><title>在伊朗导弹摧毁她的实验室后， Yifat Merbl教授被《自然》杂志评为“2025年塑造科学的10人” - VINnews</title><link>https://vinnews.com/2025/12/28/after-iranian-missile-destroyed-her-lab-prof-yifat-merbl-named-in-natures-10-who-shaped-science-2025/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content tagdiv-type"&gt;
            
            &lt;p&gt;JERUSALEM (VINnews) — Prof. Yifat Merbl, a researcher from the Department of Systems Immunology at the Weizmann Institute of Science, is summing up an almost unimaginable year, as reported by Israel’s Channel 12. At the age of 48, at the height of a complex and turbulent period in Israel, she was selected by the prestigious journal Nature as one of the ten people who shaped the face of science in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="whatsapp-promotion-mobile"&gt;

	&lt;a href="https://vinnews.com/2020/01/07/vin-whatsapp/"&gt;
		&lt;i class="td-icon-whatsapp"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
		Join our WhatsApp group&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
	&lt;a href="https://vinnews.com/subscribe/"&gt;
		&lt;i class="td-icon-mail"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
		Subscribe to our Daily Roundup Email&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The discovery that brought her to the forefront of global attention concerns a new immune mechanism hidden within the process of protein degradation in the body. Prof. Merbl chose to study what she calls the cell’s “trash cans” — the place where proteins are broken down and shredded. She discovered that some of the fragments produced in this process are capable of directly fighting bacteria, a finding described as a “gold mine” for the development of potential antibiotics and innovative cancer therapies. Speaking about her persistence in pursuing the research despite skepticism around her, she said: “In the end, what determines everything is natural curiosity and passion — and I wasn’t willing to give that up.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, Prof. Merbl’s path to the top of academia was far from conventional. Numerous certificates hang in her office, but one is conspicuously missing: a high school matriculation certificate. In her youth, the education system failed to accommodate her. In 10th grade, she was told she was unfit for the framework, and in 11th grade it was decided not to allow her to take the matriculation exams, including in chemistry, a field in which she is now deeply engaged. She left school with a deep sense of failure and confusion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For years, she was considered “wasted potential,” as she describes it, and worked in temporary jobs. The turning point came when she scored 752 on the psychometric exam (out of a maximum 800 points), a result that surprised even herself. From there began an impressive academic journey: from studies in computational biology at Bar-Ilan University to a PhD at the prestigious Harvard University. Despite her success, feelings of not belonging and fear of failure accompanied her throughout the way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only at the age of 43 was Prof. Merbl formally diagnosed with attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD). She said that had she been diagnosed earlier, she might have spared herself much suffering, but today she understands that her different way of perceiving reality may have enabled her to find scientific solutions in places where others did not think to look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The past year posed both physical and political challenges for Prof. Merbl’s laboratory. Last summer, an Iranian missile struck the laboratory building at the Weizmann Institute directly, completely destroying the equipment on which her research depended. She did not give up: she ran to the ruined building in flip-flops to salvage whatever she could, and within less than two months, she had reestablished a fully functioning laboratory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alongside the physical destruction, Prof. Merbl is also contending with the academic boycott of Israel. She described cases in which Israeli researchers were excluded from research grants and invitations to conferences were made conditional on future approval of Israeli participation. Nevertheless, as a Zionist and a former military officer, she is determined to continue her work in Israel. For her, the goal is clear: “The question is not whether we will leave, but how we will make it happen here.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prof. Merbl’s vision for the future is especially ambitious. She aims to establish an international center that will leverage research into protein quality-control mechanisms to treat severe diseases such as Alzheimer’s and cancer. She is no longer afraid to set lofty goals and hopes to achieve breakthroughs that will have a tangible impact on humanity. When asked about the possibility of winning a Nobel Prize in the future, she admitted it would be an immense source of pride for the country.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Her story has become a source of inspiration for many parents and children struggling with similar difficulties in the education system. After Nature published its list, she received moving messages from parents thanking her for the hope she gave their children. She emphasized that “it’s allowed not to succeed, but it’s forbidden not to try,” and encouraged the younger generation to hold fast to their curiosity and passion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, when asked what she would say to 16-year-old Yifat Merbl who had been expelled from school, she answered simply: “Well done. I’m proud of you.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="td-a-rec td-a-rec-id-content_bottom  tdi_3 td_block_template_6"&gt;

&lt;p id="avp_zid_73_mobile_bottom_of_article"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;




                &lt;p class="addthis_inline_share_toolbox"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

            

&lt;div class=""&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Follow VINnews for Breaking News Updates&lt;/h3&gt;




 






&lt;/div&gt;






&lt;/div&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VINnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:00:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxQZFlyS2lESEhyb0M5bTk5bzZkVHZuSjR4N3FNLVhNVFh3WjIxS3hzaTNwbXA2cW1US3ljSnl6SEZEbXdIVE9WeXV2WHo1bEhkV0pMelpJaXpMZWp1Y3JpMUF1Y2ktaHJuUTBiN3E4WVpoQU9fQXdmTUxOX3c2OTFDWHBxOWtOeFQ5TS1jTGx4RGstMFV2Nmp0NnJfU1AxdU5uWFpYYkIzVl95R0NTVy1tcFh0MElhbXZreWJWUzNQS2Rtbmt1VXM5WEp5bDI</guid></item><item><title>人民药店：长期使用氯沙坦会导致手部震颤吗？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2025/12/peoples-pharmacy-can-long-term-use-of-losartan-lead-to-hand-tremors.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BWVOY24CQBDELDXQ6NXPISPPEE"&gt;Q. I have been taking losartan for 25 years to control blood pressure. Recently, I developed a hand tremor, so my doctor prescribed a beta blocker to help with the tremor. Could long-term use of losartan have led to the tremor?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OURRWWIZYJA57MGJD34KNNQNFA"&gt;A. Prescribing information for losartan, a popular medication for high blood pressure, does not warn of tremor as a side effect. We found one case report in the medical literature, but that man developed the problem early in treatment (Cureus, Dec. 13, 2019). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N2HB7XHCABEHLMC6HRVUYA7AX4"&gt;The most prescribed blood pressure medicine in the U.S. is lisinopril. Like losartan, it acts on the Renin-Angiotensin system to relax blood vessels and lower blood pressure. We have received a number of reports from people who have experienced hand tremor associated with lisinopril.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VQMTVPP6SFBQBGB5LFPVZQNJOE"&gt;One reader wrote: “I have been taking lisinopril for the last six months and started having hand tremors. They are most noticeable when I pick up something like a cup of coffee or a glass of water. It’s very uncomfortable and annoying. I mentioned this to my doctor, but he completely ignored me.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IVZDIPEVAVH2JNTGBHX2PTJQ4M"&gt;You don’t say if you are still taking losartan. If you and your doctor will be considering a different antihypertensive drug, you may want to read our “eGuide to Blood Pressure Solutions.” This online resource is located under the Health eGuides tab at www.PeoplesPharmacy.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AW27S6DSHFCL3LRTWJSJCAN7NU"&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV6MCHOH2VEWXPLJQLBNMTAT4M"&gt;&lt;i&gt;In their column, Joe and Teresa Graedon answer letters from readers. Write to them in care of King Features, 628 Virginia Drive, Orlando, FL 32803, or email them via their website: www.PeoplesPharmacy.com. Their newest book is “Top Screwups Doctors Make and How to Avoid Them.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxPUmhwb0xDd1F6am1UZDBRNDRzSW9HN0s4eHZuVW01VWdBZHVra0ZwLXVPYjlPZlh3cHZYaVhoeUx3aENQbDJmUW1FaGdlNjFZRW1iS0lsc1F1Y2lFUlNUVWlZZ29xemNPclBGZGlIaVlIZDdnbVh4OUY5SG9mYm13WExEYXRxbUNsZm42UDBPWHhnWURzU1VUTjhqM1pfclRnMzhFNHF4eTdtR2gwai1YcWk5OWnSAcgBQVVfeXFMTWs1Y2Q2OV9GM3U0MDE2cExicHRubmJZOGlYSEhnbm5TSk1vdGM4M1gySWxjN1FLcTJRUFd6b0tFNGdzWTJpbmJwMXctalRmNWZyWnpmYkwzdDR3VGRLek0tLUx2cF93OWpYU2R4OEV6WUhqbHFkdHZrQkJlZVV3RjVickItRDVpVVIwVjN6XzJ4eUtlQ1NtMXlLRlJUX256TTEtVlI1dEMyb1g1aGE2TGR0enljNmFEbnVQUVNuMEVUVkI2ckRGQXQ</guid></item><item><title>微塑料钻入血管并引发心脏病- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/microplastics-burrow-into-blood-vessels-and-fuel-heart-disease/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:48:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPUjNneDJVb2ozdW1OWVBxYjVGMWlOV2pfbG1zSHUtQzNJZTlBclk5cko4bUlBU1N4aThhdWEzRW4tOU0tUVlFdVZIb21GMHE3b2tSeDRFUWNBSWhkZExlYWdYMXRvc3RyaEFfQ2lvRXMxYUp2R1ZYbjEwUDlkZDFrVUJzbmpvanc1bGo3Vjk3STdQQQ</guid></item><item><title>不服用他汀类药物，胆固醇减少三分之一：促进心脏健康的4种天然方法-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/cut-cholesterol-by-a-third-without-statins-pills-4-natural-ways-to-boost-heart-health/articleshow/126215386.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;High cholesterol does not have to be a mystery or a one-size-fits-all medical prescription. For decades, statins have been the cornerstone of managing high cholesterol but mounting research shows that diet, movement and everyday habits can significantly improve your cholesterol profile, especially when the changes are intentional and sustained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is credible research showing that diet and lifestyle changes alone can lower LDL (“bad”) cholesterol by about a third (30%) in some cases without statins and it comes from peer-reviewed clinical trials and respected health organisations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Late Dinners Linked to High Cholesterol Levels, Experts Warn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the science says about slashing “bad” LDL cholesterol by about 30% without statins&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/196970" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2003 study published in JAMA: The Journal of the American Medical Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, participants following a dietary portfolio rich in plant sterols, soy protein, viscous fiber and almonds saw LDL cholesterol fall by 28.6%, nearly as much as the statin group (30.9%), without taking statin medication. The researchers noted, “The dietary portfolio group had a mean decrease in low-density lipoprotein cholesterol of 28.6% (P&amp;lt;.001).” This is the original portfolio diet metabolic study and is often cited as evidence that specific diet combinations can lower LDL ~30% without statins. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="From Oats to Olive Oil: The Everyday Habits That Slash “Bad” Cholesterol" msid="126215947" width="" title="From Oats to Olive Oil: The Everyday Habits That Slash “Bad” Cholesterol" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-126215947/from-oats-to-olive-oil-the-everyday-habits-that-slash-bad-cholesterol.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;From Oats to Olive Oil: The Everyday Habits That Slash “Bad” Cholesterol&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A follow-up &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/1104262" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;6-month randomised trial in JAMA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in 2011 confirmed that a plant-food portfolio diet significantly lowers LDL cholesterol more than a conventional low-saturated-fat diet, though the exact percentage varies with adherence. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found, “Use of cholesterol-lowering dietary components in combination produced significantly greater LDL-C lowering than a control low-saturated-fat diet.” The metabolic (~30%) results under controlled conditions are strongest evidence of diet-alone effect close to statin-level LDL reductions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was also backed by the organisation, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.heartuk.org.uk/dietary-patterns/portfolio-diet" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Heart UK (UK’s Cholesterol Charity)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, which claimed that under tightly controlled metabolic conditions, the Portfolio Diet has been shown to lower LDL cholesterol by up to ~35%, broadly comparable to early statins. Heart UK also noted that even in “free-living” conditions (outside labs), LDL reductions are meaningful, around 17%–20%, depending on adherence. In other words, this major heart-health charity explicitly states that under metabolic study conditions, reductions of up to ~35% are possible with diet alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="No Pills, No Panic: How Science Says You Can Cut Cholesterol by 30%" msid="126215951" width="" title=" No Pills, No Panic: How Science Says You Can Cut Cholesterol by 30%" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-126215951/no-pills-no-panic-how-science-says-you-can-cut-cholesterol-by-30.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt; No Pills, No Panic: How Science Says You Can Cut Cholesterol by 30%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While these metabolic trials support diet-alone LDL lowering near statin-like levels in controlled settings, real-world results depend on how closely the diet is followed and individual responses vary. However, this research does demonstrate that statin-free LDL reductions of ~30% are scientifically documented with evidence-based dietary patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Lifestyle shifts that can make measurable differences&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Diet Matters, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Soluble Fiber and Plant Sterols Work Together: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;As per a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/12489074/" data-type="tilCustomLink" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;study in Journal of the American College of Nutrition&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, “The combination diet reduced low-density lipoprotein (LDL) cholesterol by 29% and improved the ratio of LDL to HDL cholesterol significantly.” This classic research shows that foods high in soluble fiber (like oats and barley), plant sterols and soy proteins can have a potent combined effect on lowering LDL, even in people already eating a low-fat diet. Another &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33762150/" data-type="tilCustomLink" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;major review on cholesterol-lowering foods&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; found solid evidence that soluble fiber-rich foods (like oats, barley, psyllium), plant sterols/stanols and &lt;keyword id="40735" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="healthy" source="Orion"&gt;healthy&lt;/keyword&gt; unsaturated fats (e.g., from nuts and olive oil), each contribute to moderate reductions in LDL cholesterol. Increasing your intake of soluble fiber is one of the best-studied ways to lower LDL (“bad”) cholesterol without medication. Soluble fiber binds to cholesterol in the digestive system and helps remove it before it enters the bloodstream. A British Journal of Nutrition meta-analysis found that beta-glucan (the soluble fiber in oats) causes consistent reductions in LDL when consumed regularly. Health authorities like the US Food and Drug Administration and Healthline’s LDL guidelines recommend soluble-fiber-rich foods such as oats, legumes, fruits and vegetables to help reduce LDL levels. Soluble fiber is not just a trend, it is a dietary corner-stone in heart disease prevention and is recommended by heart health authorities around the world. Choose healthy fats and plant sterols to improve your lipid profile. Not all fats are equal. Replacing saturated and trans fats with unsaturated, plant-focused fats can improve cholesterol levels. The American Heart Association (AHA) advises reducing saturated fat intake (e.g., butter, processed meats) and replacing it with healthier fats from olive oil, nuts and avocados. Harvard Health Publishing notes that eating nuts (like almonds and walnuts), about 2 ounces a day, can help slightly lower LDL Plant sterols and stanols (found naturally in vegetables, nuts and fortified foods) can reduce LDL absorption in the gut. About 2g a day may lower LDL by up to ~10 %.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lifestyle Overhaul With Diet and Exercise Works, Sometimes Dramatically - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Researchers in a &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/fullarticle/615295" data-type="tilCustomLink" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;JAMA Internal Medicine (Arch Intern Med) study&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; noted, “Most adults can significantly reduce serum lipid values and the risk for atherosclerosis… through lifestyle modification consisting of diet and exercise.” In this large study of more than 4,500 adults, a 3-week program that combined a high-fiber, high-complex-carbohydrate, low-fat diet with daily aerobic exercise produced a 23% drop in total cholesterol and LDL. That is comparable to what many medications achieve, just with food and movement. Move more as even moderate activity improves cholesterol. Physical activity does not have to mean gym marathons. Regular movement itself supports better cholesterol numbers. The Mayo Clinic and AHA recommend at least 150 minutes of moderate aerobic activity per week, which can help raise HDL (“good”) and lower LDL cholesterol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exercise, Weight and Smoking &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;cessation Are&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Than Just Good Habits - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/21291669/" data-type="tilCustomLink" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;review in Clinics in Chest Medicine (review on HDL)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; found, “Regular physical activity, attaining a healthy weight, and cessation of cigarette smoking are associated with beneficial HDL cholesterol changes.” This systematic review pulls together evidence showing that exercise can increase protective HDL (“good”) cholesterol, weight loss enhances favourable lipid changes and smoking cessation improves both HDL and overall heart risk. Together, these lifestyle changes do not just shift numbers, they influence whole-system cardiovascular risk. Lose extra weight and manage body composition. Even small changes in body weight can make meaningful differences in cholesterol. The Mayo Clinic notes that weight loss, even just 5–10 lbs, is linked to lower LDL and total cholesterol. Maintaining a healthy weight improves HDL and lowers LDL. Quit smoking and limit alcohol. Two everyday habits that influence cholesterol are smoking and alcohol use. Quitting smoking is linked with improved HDL levels and lower heart disease risk, with benefits appearing quickly after cessation. Alcohol can raise triglycerides and potentially worsen lipid profiles when consumed in excess. Even beyond cholesterol, quitting smoking and moderating alcohol helps overall cardiovascular health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stress, Sleep and Cholesterol Have a Hidden Connection - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Not all lifestyle factors are dietary or physical. Your body’s stress levels and sleep patterns influence metabolism and appetite, both of which affect cholesterol. Evidence from clinical guidance reveals that stress can trigger hormonal changes that alter fat metabolism. Good sleep helps regulate hunger hormones, reducing cravings for high-fat foods.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Actionable swaps to boost heart health without statins, as per studies&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Start your day with oatmeal or oat bran.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Add beans, lentils, apples and pears to meals.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sprinkle ground flaxseed on yogurt or salads.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use olive, canola or sunflower oil instead of butter.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Snack on a small handful of nuts daily.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Add avocado and other plant sterol-rich produce to salads.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go for brisk walking, cycling or swimming.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exercise for 30 minutes, most days of the week.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strength train for additional metabolic benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Track what you eat using a journal or app.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Combine regular movement with mindful eating.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduce sugary beverages and excess refined carbs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aim for 7–9 hours of quality sleep per night.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduce stress with mindfulness, yoga or breathing exercises.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prioritise routines that support regular circadian rhythms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;These swaps work in addition to, not instead of, an overall balanced diet. Sustained movement helps the body remove LDL while boosting protective HDL, improving cardiovascular risk across the board. While less direct than diet and exercise, managing stress and sleep amplifies other cholesterol-lowering efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bottom line&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/education/TLC-Therapeutic-Lifestyle-Changes-Lower-Cholesterol" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;National Heart, Lung and Blood Institute (NHLBI), part of the US National Institutes of Health, has long recommended the Therapeutic Lifestyle Changes (TLC) diet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; as an evidence-based strategy to help lower LDL cholesterol and suggest, “Increase soluble fiber… add plant stanols and sterols… and reduce saturated fat and cholesterol to lower LDL.” This official guidance reflects decades of clinical evidence, including the studies above, supporting lifestyle approaches that complement or sometimes reduce the need for medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soluble fiber and plant sterols bind cholesterol in the gut and reduce absorption into the bloodstream. Healthy fats and nuts help replace saturated fats and support better lipid profiles. Exercise and weight loss help the body shuttle cholesterol more effectively and improve heart health. Smoking cessation reduces harmful processes that heighten cardiovascular risk and lowers bad fats indirectly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major peer-reviewed journals and national health guidelines agree that you can make meaningful changes to your cholesterol profile through lifestyle, sometimes comparable to medical therapy, especially when done consistently. If you are managing high cholesterol and interested in non-statin strategies, these tips provide science-backed tools that you can talk about with your clinician.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwJBVV95cUxNSHcwd3lZR3VTYkhhTmhYRzVrXzBRMzFmMnRRNnMzM0p6SU16RGh2cmNxLXREQ2c4aTVodjQ4QXphNGFFTmhZMFJab19LdWtmejNUMG5iLXp1MlBGMlhKMmttSTdqR05xS2kxTFAxR1pVXzFUcUwtdHVJaG1HOUtVOW9ibnNiX1VqS1kwRkY5S0dzZUJzQ3ZzYU80UVZEU3lVaVRaaHpRNkxxMldqcXRIaVlBMzFubmdZTzVjYWRRSTBXQlVicFpNNUoweUJuNUU2akhLc2ZMSVpFc19EeU0tNkdELTFCTmNZRlQxemVwenBYWXFGU2pnRHhGNjE0WUZTVmVQVldLdXdaS0dVZmhXdHk0QdIBmAJBVV95cUxQV0tOOUNia0luZFRmYkNKQWd6N01ObG93dkFvSWRKWGtmOWVyY3pfcXpEU3JYWWdOMjFOWDI3VEM2U0JzaHpZX3E1Q3lrNm5OY095NDY4WGNlSk1oS2RJbWpyajFkZk1qMFFFSmN2eXJuVnI3V1ZSRmJnS0t0SjRFQ3BKdmpMeU1LZlBvQUJQNTNnOC1mNFlvUVk3clVGa0ZqMDFQU1cyZndDa1FtMXNwUDZ1UFUtYnAtWTlETVhUOThkRE01U3ktYnVTZTlTd2JSbUVZT0tVRGN2WDRfOERYTmsteHB1cEp3dW1TSlRJTl95VUxOeWQwRFBDYkQ4V3dWS3FtN29KdU50S1p0RThyV296RGNZdVRa</guid></item><item><title>根据科学，这是你孩子在手机和社交媒体上的大脑-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/28/adolescent-brain-development-screen-time/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VYSDLW7ZZVGCJN56XI7VVHOKLQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;University of Pennsylvania researcher Ran Barzilay is a father of three. His first two children received cellphones before they turned 12. But this summer, as early results from his own study on screens and teen health rolled in, he changed course. His youngest? Not getting one anytime soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 13:01:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPMGRucUhGT0E2OGVacUQ2alFMSm5jd05mY0RTOFNZVjRJRDJMaTA3Y0EzcERBeEwzdDdkbm8tMnpnWTNjWFE5MWw1cloydWJ4NjJjb2wzRDZLRW1fUUVsNEVudkM5T0o3S01GSzJRRWNxZHg2UTRzNnhWQldib3BxTVFjeVp5RFVmelB3SWc5MEZMYTNH</guid></item><item><title>人体有多少个洞？ - Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/physics-mathematics/mathematics/how-many-holes-does-the-human-body-have</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;

&lt;p id="f8106e8b-534d-4126-a62c-6e4a5c8efaea"&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/37009-human-body.html" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/37009-human-body.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;human body&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is extraordinarily complex, with several openings and a few exits. But exactly how many holes does each person have?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It sounds like a simple enough question to answer — list the openings and add them up. But it's not quite that easy once you start considering questions like: "What exactly is a hole?" "Does any opening count?" And "why don't mathematicians know the difference between a straw and a doughnut?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="f8106e8b-534d-4126-a62c-6e4a5c8efaea-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;Before we start counting, we need to agree on what constitutes a "hole." &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.katiesteckles.co.uk/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.katiesteckles.co.uk/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Katie Steckles&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a lecturer in mathematics at Manchester Metropolitan University in the U.K. and a freelance mathematics communicator, told Live Science that mathematicians "use the term 'hole' to mean one like the hole in a donut: one that goes all the way through a shape and out the other side."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="1c8f1268-9769-48d8-b34b-ac0991cba467"&gt;But if you dig a "hole" at the beach, your aim is probably not to dig right through to the other side of the world. Many people would think of a hole as a depression in a solid object. But "this isn't a true hole, as it has an end," Steckles said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, mathematical communicator &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://jamesa.xyz/" target="_blank" data-url="https://jamesa.xyz/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;James Arthur&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, who is based in the U.K., told Live Science that "in topology, a 'hole' is a through hole, that is you can put your finger through the object."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When digging a tunnel under the sea, like the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/technology/engineering/could-we-ever-build-a-transatlantic-tunnel" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/technology/engineering/could-we-ever-build-a-transatlantic-tunnel"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Channel Tunnel&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that connects the U.K. and France, engineers started off by digging two openings. But as soon as those two digging projects joined up, the Channel Tunnel became a fundamentally different object (what Arthur and engineers would call a "through hole") — like a straw, or a tube with an opening at either end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://yougov.co.uk/topics/politics/survey-results/daily/2022/08/11/50da6/3" target="_blank" data-url="https://yougov.co.uk/topics/politics/survey-results/daily/2022/08/11/50da6/3" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt; &lt;u&gt;if you ask people how many holes a straw has&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; you will get a range of different answers:&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://x.com/Kit_Yates_Maths/status/1558015146844471296?s=20&amp;amp;t=3YZgsRL02devfyqoRNbsxA" target="_blank" data-url="https://x.com/Kit_Yates_Maths/status/1558015146844471296?s=20&amp;amp;t=3YZgsRL02devfyqoRNbsxA" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt; &lt;u&gt;one, two and even zero&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This is a result of our colloquial understanding of what constitutes a hole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To find a consistent answer, we can turn to&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/physics-mathematics/mathematics" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/physics-mathematics/mathematics"&gt; &lt;u&gt;mathematics&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. And the problem of classifying how many holes there are in an object falls squarely within the realm of topology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="a9edf537-ed45-4711-b3c8-ca4279d414c6"&gt;To a topologist, the actual shapes of objects are not important. Instead, "topology is more concerned with the fundamental properties of shapes and how things connect together in space," Steckles said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In topology, objects can be grouped together by the number of holes they possess. For example, a topologist sees no difference between a golf ball, a baseball or even a Frisbee. If they were all made of plasticine, or putty, they could theoretically be squashed, stretched or otherwise manipulated to look like each other without making or closing any holes in the plasticine or sticking different parts together, Steckles argued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, to a topologist, these objects are fundamentally different to a bagel, a doughnut or a basketball hoop, which each have a hole through the middle of them. A figure of eight with two holes and a pretzel with three are different topological objects again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="d3d0d883-d899-40e5-98b6-5ab6f0fc43bf"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;This delicious pretzel has three holes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="789b8ce9-3c8a-4915-8151-b925d409909a"&gt;A useful way to get into the mathematicians' way of thinking about the straw problem is to "imagine our straw is made of play dough," Arthur said. "Let's take this straw and slowly squish the top down and down and down towards the bottom, making sure the hole in the middle stays open. We will squish it until we are in a shape that looks like a doughnut." Mathematicians, Arthur said, would say that "the straw is homeomorphic to a doughnut."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The long, thin aspect ratio of the straw, and the fact that the two openings are relatively far apart, are perhaps what gives rise to the suggestion of two holes. But to a topologist, bagels, basketball hoops and doughnuts are all topologically equivalent to a straw with a single hole. "The hole in a straw goes all the way through it, and the opening at the other end is just the back of that same hole," Steckles said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-b5cc1ea5-00ed-4969-8f77-0396988e0e5b" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="back-to-the-human-body-3"&gt;Back to the human body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="70468600-b6e4-48ce-ad0c-77057eae822c"&gt;Armed with the topologists' definition of a hole, we can tackle the original question: How many holes does the human body have? Let's first try to list all the openings we have. The obvious ones are probably our mouths, our urethras (the ones we pee out of) and our &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/why-does-pooping-feel-so-good" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/why-does-pooping-feel-so-good"&gt;&lt;u&gt;anuses&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, as well as the openings in our &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/breathing-nose-sides" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/breathing-nose-sides"&gt;&lt;u&gt;nostrils&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and our &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/52287-ear-anatomy.html" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/52287-ear-anatomy.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;ears&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. For some of us, there are also milk ducts in nipples and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/36516-facts-women-vagina-health-myths.html" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/36516-facts-women-vagina-health-myths.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;vaginas&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are also four less-obvious openings that we all have in the corners of eyelids closest to our nose — the four&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/medicine-and-dentistry/lacrimal-punctum" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/medicine-and-dentistry/lacrimal-punctum" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt; &lt;u&gt;lacrimal puncta&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which drain tears from our eyes into our nasal cavities. At an even smaller scale there are the pores that enable sweat to escape our bodies and sebum to lubricate our skin. In total there are potentially millions of these openings in our bodies, but do they all count as holes?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="94f6e41f-09b8-4a8c-9a83-b5cdf8ff698a"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;The two lacrimal puncta drain tears from the eye down the lacrimal canals and through to the nasolacrimal duct which connects to the nasal cavity. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="464a9889-ccde-4bd2-8ae0-ca9957dc99c2"&gt;To make the question interesting, think about whether we could pass a very thin string into one hole and out of another. If we set the size of this string to be about 60 microns (60 millionths of a meter) then it's possible that the string could enter an opening as small as a pore. However — and this is key — it wouldn't be able to leave. It wouldn't be able to come out the other end. It would be blocked by the cells at the bottom of the pore — too thick to pass through into the vasculature that supplies the pore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They're not actually holes in the topological sense, as they don't go all the way through," Steckles said. "They're just blind pits."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By this definition we can rule out all the pores, milk ducts and urethras. We couldn't thread a string in one of these openings and out of another. Even the ears canals have to go as they are separated from the rest of the sinuses by the ear drums.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have our mouth, our anus, and then our nostrils. They are four of the … openings that form a hole," Arthur said. "But we actually have eight. The remaining four come from the tear ducts, we each have two in each eye, an upper and a lower."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this doesn't mean eight holes. Steckles pointed out ."When the holes that pass through a shape connect together inside the shape, it makes it harder to count how many there are."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-8184ab61-6fb6-4b74-be84-22f7c8a186b3" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="looking-at-underwear-3"&gt;Looking at underwear&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="3c5b7774-e8ba-4718-80d2-101a830baf8b"&gt;A pair of underwear, for example, has three openings (one for the waist and one for each of the two legs), but it's not immediately clear how many holes a topologist would say it has. "A useful trick is to think about flattening it out," Steckles said. — "If we were to stretch the waistband of the pants out onto a big hula hoop, we'd see the two trouser legs sticking down, each being one hole."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="f1136cf4-b448-4f24-b651-1dbc98269fc6"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;Underwear has three openings but only two holes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="faf4a078-5ca6-43e5-9623-6accbb316cb9"&gt;So despite having three openings, the pair of underwear has only two holes. "So when the holes connect together in the middle, there's one fewer hole than there are openings," Steckles argued. Correspondingly, topology tells us that, despite eight interconnected openings, the human body has seven different holes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there might be one more. Although often counted as a blind hole, the vagina leads to the uterus, which then leads to one of two fallopian tubes. These tubes are open at the far end and lead to the peritoneal cavity near the ovary. It is the job of the finger-like projections of the funnel-shaped infundibulum at the end of the fallopian tube to catch the egg when it is released from the nearest ovary. However, it has been demonstrated that &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23381619/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23381619/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;eggs released from one ovary can be captured by the fallopian tube on the other side&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, so that passage between the two open ends of the fallopian tubes is possible. Our tiny string could therefore be threaded all the way through the female reproductive tract and back out, counting as one more hole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="903b39fd-1a7e-4ee3-b261-d8a0c23dd5bb"&gt;So the mathematician's answer is that humans have either seven or eight holes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the end, the question is not just about counting openings but about understanding connections. Topologically speaking, our bodies are less like Swiss cheese and more like a carefully constructed onesie for an octopus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr id="07bb39e1-c0e3-4a5a-a785-58954b45f4fd"&gt;&lt;a id="elk-0f35b3b4-f37c-4228-9b8f-c0e9c9678dd4" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="human-skeleton-quiz-what-do-you-know-about-the-bones-in-your-body-3"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.livescience.com/health/anatomy/human-skeleton-quiz-what-do-you-know-about-the-bones-in-your-body" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/anatomy/human-skeleton-quiz-what-do-you-know-about-the-bones-in-your-body"&gt;Human skeleton quiz&lt;/a&gt;: What do you know about the bones in your body?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQQTFUMjdadWI2VVBZWHh2MmtZNVB5YlVOMEJXR25DTjRjYXZNTW9fTzdkMjhkVUowTXBiQnp6b1VJWW45NFdMSXdaZzBrdThOQVVfWkVaNWVaR2RHNlliS1Q3aDVvUXMtbWtNNm1VRXpmS0FnaHpCQWgtb2h5enlMS25fcmJ3MDVRUkVBNnFXVFMxYUxEbGtJcDN4akFjamRr</guid></item><item><title>来自班加罗尔，德里，孟买的顶级医院的3名医生分享了5个脂肪肝的警告标志写在你的脸上|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/3-doctors-from-top-hospitals-in-bengaluru-delhi-mumbai-share-5-warning-signs-of-fatty-liver-written-on-your-face-101766912076278.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/3-doctors-from-top-hospitals-in-bengaluru-delhi-mumbai-share-5-warning-signs-of-fatty-liver-written-on-your-face-101766912076278.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/is-fatty-liver-disease-irreversible-fortis-gastroenterologist-shares-3-best-drinks-to-reverse-fatty-liver-naturally-101764475024883.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fatty liver disease,"&gt;Fatty liver disease,&lt;/a&gt; often called a 'silent killer', is reaching epidemic proportions in India, with a 2021 &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9168741/" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="study"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; suggesting that nearly 39 percent of adults are now affected. While the liver sits deep within the abdomen, leading hepatologists and gastroenterologists warn that the organ's struggle often manifests in plain sight. &lt;strong&gt;Also read |&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fatty-liver-causes-and-expert-tips-to-combat-the-disease-101709623060882.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fatty liver: Causes and expert tips to combat the disease"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Fatty liver: Causes and expert tips to combat the disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/28/550x309/6663697_1748406405560_1766912359201.jpg" alt="Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)" title="Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/28/550x309/6663697_1748406405560_1766912359201.jpg" alt="Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)" title="Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Fatty liver disease can progress to fibrosis and chronic liver failure if untreated. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;The face serves as an early external indicator of internal metabolic stress,” Dr Vikram Raut, senior consultant, liver transplant and HPB surgery, Fortis Hospital Mulund, Mumbai told HT Lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt; Because the liver is central to hormone regulation, toxin clearance, and nutrient processing, its dysfunction can trigger visible dermatological and vascular changes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Medical experts from across the country have identified five critical facial signs that could signal your liver is under siege. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;According to them, your face may be telling a story your liver can't – heeding these warnings early could be the key to preventing long-term complications like cirrhosis or liver failure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;1. Yellowing of the skin and eyes (jaundice)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most classic sign of liver distress is a yellow tint, known as Jaundice. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Mallikarjun Sakpal, consultant, HPB and transplant physician, Aster CMI Hospital, Bengaluru, explained that this occurs when the liver fails to process bilirubin — a waste product from red blood cell breakdown.&lt;/span&gt; “When the liver struggles, bilirubin levels rise, causing a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/doctor-gastroenterologist-shares-7-early-signs-of-liver-cirrhosis-know-5-tips-to-prevent-liver-damage-101747305290844.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="mild yellowing"&gt;mild yellowing&lt;/a&gt; of the whites of the eyes or facial skin that should never be ignored,” he told HT Lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;2. Facial puffiness and under-eye swelling&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you wake up with a consistently bloated look around your cheeks and eyes, it may not just be a lack of sleep. Dr Sudeep Khanna, senior consultant, gastroenterology, Indraprastha Apollo Hospitals, pointed to fluid retention as the culprit. “When the liver is overloaded with fat, it produces less of the proteins needed to keep fluids inside blood vessels. This leads to leakage into facial tissues, causing&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/suffering-from-swollen-puffy-eyes-dermatologist-shares-why-this-may-happen-and-how-to-reduce-puffiness-101756377953013.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="persistent puffiness,"&gt; persistent puffiness,&lt;/a&gt;” he explained in an interview to HT Lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;3. Adult acne and oily breakouts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudden breakouts, particularly around the jawline, cheeks, and forehead, can be a sign of metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD). According to Dr Sakpal, a fatty liver cannot remove toxins or balance hormones like androgens efficiently. This imbalance triggers overactive oil glands and stubborn pimples that resist standard topical treatments.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;4. Red 'spider' veins and rosacea-like flushing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiny red lines branching out like a spider’s web — known as spider angiomas — are frequent markers of severe liver scarring or cirrhosis. Dr Raut explained these are caused by dilated capillaries. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Khanna added that 'rosacea-like flushing' often arises from poor estrogen breakdown, which increases blood flow to the facial skin and triggers visible vascular networks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;5. Dullness, itching, and patchy skin&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liver disease can rob the skin of its natural glow. Dr Sakpal shared that a fatty liver often reduces the absorption of vitamins A and E, leading to dry, flaky, and itchy skin. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Furthermore, Dr Raut added that patients may experience a 'grey-brown' darkening or patchy appearance on the face due to hormonal imbalances and the accumulation of bile salts in the bloodstream.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;A silent epidemic: can it be reversed?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While these signs are alarming, the medical consensus is hopeful. Dr Khanna shared that fatty liver is often asymptomatic in its early stages, usually only detectable via ultrasound. However, once facial signs appear, it is a clear signal to act. “Weight loss of just 5 to 10 percent can significantly shrink liver fat and even reverse disease progression,” Dr Khanna said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Recommended lifestyle swaps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;⦿ Diet: Switch to greens-rich meals and cut out sugary sodas.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Activity: Incorporate at least 30 minutes of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/walking-just-7k-steps-daily-can-reduce-risk-of-death-47-lower-cardiovascular-disease-incidence-25-lancet-study-10k-101753334398446.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="daily walking"&gt;daily walking&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Supplementation: Adding anti-inflammatory spices like turmeric can aid recovery.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Screening: If you have risk factors like obesity or diabetes, consult a doctor for a FibroScan or ultrasound.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 09:11:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgJBVV95cUxQdFlBdzE2TkM5RmE0dDRlenNmQnVjR3VlTWNXY2ZSRExlN2tRaTYtMXpzYjhCSmhuQUN3WkRFS0ZzZWRhNGliVTdDeEpTeTZoSUVUZnVRTzB0cDFjUWhkMTFzUTRpV01rNzBSMWhMVGhoOU5BSjYwTGY4V1ZUNEtQRTJTcGNPaDFhOXJVWUJodUpHaEJWTzItcEZiYWpjLXg4Nl9oaFRmMUItU21BeGpNUm1xa2IwNjBUMnF1UzhyTUJROHhQcGQ0VUljb3BqOVlqNWdtVmVzbm01dTc1MzFHVXdGX2N2djU0akNfNmRxTDc3M1JpdFZ3b2lLbTRYRmNZWkozZXJnYk5jWWhWWHfSAZMCQVVfeXFMTXoxVnNLOE5nZk5aUXdQczF5WUF1Y09WX3BlcTNaQVl2RmJEOUtQVExhVUJoWVBybzFSSDlpVzRXREw0QWh5S2JMNldJYnROTlhfX1JYUlNNYWprajNrTUgwQ2c0NVZFZ3ZqZFN6d3A4azdaMHU4TXJaVS1TUE5mTjVWUmVjeEt1Y1RrdF9peWZfQjJVdGZXNTlpUzYwemRRaW5TNjVwMlM3TE01dGpPRnRnUG5RS256VmNEdDM3Mk1lci1rYkNnWUhTakhwZmxmbWZvQ2l4Z0VhV1VfbTh2UUQ1SHlRa294dkh1bXpPbDc2d1oxRUZwbTllc0FmaE1BWXc5WGpRSWhMbVBCM3M3NTdhRjg</guid></item><item><title>中年减肥可能隐藏着大脑成本- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251228020004.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Obesity remains one of the most serious health challenges worldwide, and weight loss is often encouraged as a way to lower the risks tied to excess weight. But growing research suggests that the effects of weight loss may change with age. During midlife, losing weight may not always produce the same health benefits seen in younger adults and in some cases, it may also influence brain health.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a new study from Ben-Gurion University of the Negev (BGU), researchers examined how diet-induced obesity and later weight loss affected young adult mice compared with mid-aged mice. In both groups, weight loss successfully restored healthy blood glucose control, showing that key metabolic improvements occur regardless of age. However, the scientists also observed an unexpected difference. In mid-aged mice, weight loss led to increased inflammation in the hypothalamus, a part of the brain involved in regulating appetite, energy use, and other essential functions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain Inflammation Raises New Questions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This increase in brain inflammation was detected at the molecular level and through detailed microscopic imaging of microglia (the brain's immune cells). The inflammatory response lasted for several weeks before gradually declining. While the long-term effects of this response are still unclear and may even play a role in achieving metabolic improvements, the findings raise important concerns. Persistent or poorly regulated inflammation in the brain has been linked to memory problems and neurodegenerative conditions such as Alzheimer's. As a result, the study highlights new questions about how weight loss during midlife may interact with brain health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Researchers Urge a More Nuanced View of Midlife Weight Loss&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our findings show that losing weight in midlife is not a simple copy-and-paste of what works in young adulthood," said Alon Zemer, an M.D.-Ph.D. candidate and the first author of this paper. "Weight loss remains essential for restoring metabolic health in obesity, but we need to understand the impact of weight loss on the mid-age brain and ensure brain health is not compromised."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Alexandra Tsitrina added: "Our study characterizes the body's adaptive response to weight loss through two complementary dimensions -- molecular and structural. This high-end imaging by advanced microscopy and image analysis with advanced computational analysis enable detection of sensitive changes with potential health ramifications."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps for Protecting Brain Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research team stresses the importance of additional studies to better understand why this temporary but concerning brain inflammation occurs during midlife weight loss. Future work could help scientists develop approaches that maintain the metabolic advantages of weight loss while also protecting brain health as people age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study, titled, "Weight loss aggravates obesity-induced hypothalamic inflammation in mid-aged mice" was published in &lt;em&gt;GeroScience&lt;/em&gt; and supported by an internal grant at BGU (with the Ilse Katz Institute of Nanoscale Science and Technology), and grants from theUS-Israel Binational Science Foundation (Grant no. 2021083) and the Israel Science Foundation (Grant No. 194/24).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 08:41:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBHUkxGTnF5c1UtVERqUWlpZlIzUFZ2UTh2MFR1cFBqbFFQanZWUUZZRWc0NmxHN2QyS0NvMy1PZHBMZnBWcnFLYlh0QlJ1cFFOM2VORlp2ODFwenZTbFY0S0NsNnpUMTBsY2lfNC12TQ</guid></item><item><title>4种加速肾脏损伤的水果和3种健康替代品-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/4-fruits-that-accelerate-kidney-damage-and-3-healthy-alternatives/photostory/126212951.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This fruit is rich in a compound called bromelain, which can help reduce inflammation and support kidney health. As per a &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8534447/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;, pineapple is said to support the kidney  through its bromelain enzyme, vitamin C, and high water content, which provide anti-inflammatory, antioxidant, and diuretic effects that may aid digestion, reduce swelling, and promote hydration in early-stage kidney issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Images Courtesy: istock&lt;br&gt;Disclaimer: The information provided in this article is meant for general knowledge only and should not be taken as medical advice. Always talk to your doctor before starting any new routine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:26:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4AFBVV95cUxQYkxTY1hCUER2WjNtZHo4R1BkeHFLUUVpVlFyRTBvVE5kMFl6NDRJNk1xUU9oOFg3ZnJaakd0b0Z2eENqSExqLW9ubG9uM2N6amFGUXB2Sy02dXdqWlprU0ZHVEJKci1vSWYxSnN4VGNJT0dLNjNlc3Rycnhrck5BRGgzMzdHMWFudWdqcWZ0OXJxbHpsRmxiTkx3bXl1dkpnOTRZTnFuU0ZkMkdPWHhKeHF0Q2wtSkQwdGhzeVVQbHRmWHN0bWNGN3luTVVBaTdCQTJnclp3c2IzbXJ4Qzc5eNIB6AFBVV95cUxPRU93OTRhWlFNQlpUd2cwd0JJb1hvTmRkeUtLWWhrdmU0eDZxNWRsOWpmR3lqZ3Y0djJ3WEtjaU4xcjhkZTJ0Vk1pQTJSVzlXaEhKeTU1LUV1d01Gekg2bjhZZ0RNdkZjaHA0Qnp4Tlo2UldvamlqVkUxcFZtOXRqVWRDVXg4SC1nWmg2ak9ZUnhQLUVUUGp0Y0VZWnMwU0JxQWJmMklxZE10UndkMF90cVcwS2dOR2JQQld2ZG1NUGwtMWJzR1VBbEJTb1k0R2I1Vmdsc2hpRTdpMHBFRHBZdzRXZ0JDWmJR</guid></item><item><title>带有健康流行语的食物可能会将添加的糖隐藏在显而易见的地方- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/foods-healthy-sounding-buzzwords-hiding-added-sugar-plain-128728905</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;Many consumers feel pride in avoiding the glazed pastries in the supermarket and instead opting for “all natural” granola that comes packed with extra protein. Same goes for low-fat yogurts “made with real fruit,” “organic” plant-based milks and bottled “superfood” smoothies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Buyer beware: Healthy grocery buzzwords like those often cover up an &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/heat-hot-climate-sugar-soda-diabetes-dee1cb27322afb3e556fd2c6f8ecf1ae"&gt;unhealthy amount of sugar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/c147e0085eb842ac9144e8214dddd063"&gt;Added sugars&lt;/a&gt; are difficult to quickly spot because many companies use clever marketing to distract consumers, said Nicole Avena, a professor of neuroscience and psychiatry at Mount Sinai Medical School and Princeton University who has studied added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Avena said while some health-forward brands know people are starting to become aware of the hazards of added sugars, "a lot of the bigger brands don’t worry so much about people’s health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Here’s how to spot hidden sugars and what to do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Along with saturated fat and salt, eating excess sugar is linked to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/033b68db8ce342cd9cfdcda57a628027"&gt;heart disease, obesity, diabetes and other health risks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The average American consumes 17 grams of added sugar a day, which adds up to 57 pounds (26 kilograms) per year, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/sugar-shrink-the-sweet-spot-for-blood-sugar-health"&gt;according to the American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;. About half of that comes from beverages, but much of the rest is sneaked into cereal, salsa, prepared sandwiches, dairy products, bottled sauces and baked goods, including many brands of whole-grain bread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;To help control sugar intake, start by checking the nutrition label. Since 2021, food companies have been required to list the quantity of added sugars separately from total sugar content. But the plan backfired, Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Companies reduced common sweeteners like refined beet sugar and high-fructose corn syrup but added alternatives, such as monk fruit and the sugar alcohol erythritol, which aren’t considered “added sugars” under FDA regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“Now our foods are even more sweet than they were back in 2020,” Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Collin Popp, a dietitian and professor at NYU Langone Health, said the current FDA recommendation allows for some flexibility. People should get no more than 10% of their calories from added sugar, which amounts to about 50 grams per day if eating 2,000 calories, or a bit more than what’s in a typical can of soda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But that might be too flexible, Popp said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“I would actually like to see that be less than 5%, and closer to zero for some, if they have diabetes or prediabetes,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The key is to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/hub/food-safety"&gt;be mindful of what you’re eating&lt;/a&gt;, even if the product &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/28e626562c88439b96056e843215aa8d"&gt;seems healthy&lt;/a&gt; or if the package is labeled organic, Popp said. Roasted nuts, plant-based milks and wasabi peas, for example, can include a surprising amount of added sugars. So can English muffins and Greek yogurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;One Chobani black cherry yogurt, for example, has zero grams of fat but 9 grams of added sugar, or more than 2 teaspoons. Silk brand almond milk has 7 grams per cup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Popp recommends taking control of how much sugar goes into your food. That could mean buying plain yogurt and adding honey or berries, or asking the barista if you can put your own oat milk into your coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Although they lower the calorie content of foods, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://apnews.com/article/coke-cane-sugar-corn-syrup-better-d7a70ebd4aef1564e409dd087f6a69c3"&gt;artificial sweeteners&lt;/a&gt; like stevia and sugar alcohols may not be better because they can encourage people to overeat, Avena said. She said research shows that sweet flavors are what activate the reward center of the brain, not the sugar itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;That’s not to write off sugar alternatives, including allulose for people with Type 1 diabetes since it doesn’t affect blood sugar. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But for the general public, minimizing dependence on the overall sweetness of food is key to improving health, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“Don’t let the food companies decide how much sugar you’re eating," Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Albert Stumm writes about food, travel and wellness. Find his work at &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.albertstumm.com/"&gt;www.albertstumm.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:23:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxNM21iQVNyTlVyQjR5N2VOYU5xOVZ6Zm9WTFV5S3ZpWGk3TXJ5RHNsSkNSLW1YMWtQWmxPTVE0b0tYVzJ2VE9lOXAxSkR3dWRtYjNMdTYzREN6YmJyLTdrLXhhcUgtbnd0TDlsRDd4VUUya1NVblltSmEzQmlnQjBSbl9TVHVLSGdFM3l3WHM3c2t6TThJWmRtbDBhNkFiQTQ3TG1TTTlyVFZtVmvSAbABQVVfeXFMT3VpMDVtSUUwSy1QMmFMOTBENXo5ZDBPaW9BVEl4a3pySGw1ZGRNVFlIWjB2cWMtQkFXTUdheTVyY1VlUl81a1dCTE04WDM3MmMwaTN0czYxZFRJV1FEeWs0SXhTVDc2WVI1RGJKdllaZ015NUNSZkZKcWV1WjF4amNWS0hBd1VMcUhaWHZJSFpwdXBNazR0QjNTVkt0SUtoUmNCR05FamJVdkQzN0JLQjQ</guid></item><item><title>以下是您在生命中的每一个十年中应该保持多强的抓地力- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/strength-workouts/grip-strength-norms-by-age</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;

&lt;p id="dca42cf4-f321-4d33-a7e0-47f1fdedf753"&gt;I recently took a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/i-took-a-longevity-fitness-test-here-are-the-five-things-it-taught-me-about-my-body" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/i-took-a-longevity-fitness-test-here-are-the-five-things-it-taught-me-about-my-body"&gt;longevity fitness test&lt;/a&gt;, an element of which included a grip strength assessment with a hand dynamometer. &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/jcsm.13619" target="_blank" data-url="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/jcsm.13619" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; links grip strength to longevity, as it is considered a good indicator of overall physical strength and risk of frailty, as well as neuromuscular function (or the connection between brain and muscle).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-how-is-grip-strength-linked-to-longevity" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-is-grip-strength-linked-to-longevity"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How is grip strength linked to longevity? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="830ee13c-5b12-4d45-a273-ba0d8ad6e8b3"&gt;“Handgrip strength is measured with a handheld dynamometer as the peak force produced by a maximal isometric contraction of the forearm muscles. From research, it is proven to give a quick, reliable snapshot of global muscle strength and is considered a biomarker for physiological reserve, rather than just hand function,” explains Athanasios Tzoumaris, strength and conditioning coach at London-based gym and health clinic &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.hooke.fit/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.hooke.fit/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Hooke Fitness&lt;/a&gt;, where I took my test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="830ee13c-5b12-4d45-a273-ba0d8ad6e8b3-1"&gt;“Lower grip values are strongly associated with higher all-cause and cardiovascular mortality independent of age, existing medical conditions and body size,” he continues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Physiologically, weak grip reflects loss of muscle mass and neuromuscular function. It may also indicate chronic inflammation, greater frailty, as well as poor nutrition—factors that accelerate biological ageing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Clinically, it is used to case-find probable sarcopenia [age-related muscle loss] and to add prognostic information to routine assessments as it is inexpensive, reproducible and predictive of functional decline.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with muscle strength in general, grip strength naturally declines with age, “reflecting changes in muscle mass, neural drive and overall physiological resilience,” says Tzoumaris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In general, healthy adults reach peak grip strength in their late 20s to early 40s. From about age 50 onward, strength tends to fall by roughly 10% per decade, but maintaining resistance training and physical activity can significantly slow down this decline, keeping grip strength, and the health and longevity benefits it reflects, well above age-based norms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-FksH83USHZtfFrgNwmzjLV" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-FksH83USHZtfFrgNwmzjLV slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a id="elk-what-are-the-best-ways-to-monitor-grip-strength" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-what-are-the-best-ways-to-monitor-grip-strength"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What are the best ways to monitor grip strength?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="ea2a2713-14df-47df-b5c7-b24ba156d4a9"&gt;Experts agree that grip strength can be reliably monitored using handheld dynamometry testing. “For the sake of consistency of assessment, in-depth insights and interpretation of the results, as well as training recommendations, you would ideally refer to exercise specialists using a professional-grade dynamometer,” says Tzoumaris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He told me that his high-tech contraption measures not only peak force (or maximal strength), “but also how quickly you get to that peak force, in milliseconds. The software then calculates asymmetries between limbs and other quite scientific metrics that involve a fair amount of physics, which you wouldn’t be able to replicate with an at-home device.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For at-home testing, “there are fairly inexpensive dynamometers you can buy that produce acceptable testing results which may allow you to monitor progress, however they don’t offer the same insights into how an individual has achieved that score,” he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At-home devices are likely not as sensitive, he adds, potentially leading to less accurate and certainly less detailed results. “But if you follow the same process each time you use it, you should be able to spot changes and trends over time in your scores.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-collectionwidget-c9c3c57376f015cf8c788b46314846c1" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="4cbb00d2-32f3-4b36-b56d-1a5282b4730f"&gt;There are ways to track grip strength without a dynamometer, too. This could involve seeing how long you can hold a dumbbell or kettlebell in one hand and timing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Set a target time and see if you can achieve it. If you are not able to, stick to the same weight until you do achieve it. Once you are able to hold that weight for the target time, pick a slightly heavier weight and follow the same process,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Testing this way would not give a direct representation of maximal grip strength, as it measures grip strength endurance—still a strength quality but different to maximal strength. However, it can still provide some insight into someone’s grip strength progress.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-grip-strength-norms" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-grip-strength-norms"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Grip Strength Norms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="2880c739-42e5-4bd0-81cc-23914e2361f2"&gt;So, roughly how strong should you expect your grip strength to be in each decade of your life? If you want to gauge your own grip strength, to see if you’re on track for your age, here, Tzoumaris has shared some examples of normative value ranges—below average, average and above average, by age and sex, that the gym uses to calculate the results of its handgrip test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-table-FksH83USHZtfFrgNwmzjLV-8qJhq9xBUfdakHF5lV0KFDZPBgSsghKE" class="slice-container table-wrapper table-FksH83USHZtfFrgNwmzjLV-8qJhq9xBUfdakHF5lV0KFDZPBgSsghKE slice-container-table"&gt;&lt;div class="table__instruction"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swipe to scroll horizontally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 23 30" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M21.554 15.726a2.878 2.878 0 0 0-1.705-.374 2.881 2.881 0 0 0-1.388-3.068 2.877 2.877 0 0 0-1.992-.333 2.884 2.884 0 0 0-.1-.766 2.865 2.865 0 0 0-1.346-1.75c-.47-.27-.996-.4-1.527-.385l2.742-4.73a2.87 2.87 0 0 0 .323-.83h2.612V2.084h-2.661A2.861 2.861 0 0 0 15.18.385a2.903 2.903 0 0 0-3.952 1.055l-.373.644H2.983l1.003-1L2.99.09 1.28 1.793l-.999.995L2.99 5.484l.998-.994-1.003-.999h7.054L6.505 9.586c-.34.066-.905.186-1.523.366-1.405.41-2.321.895-2.8 1.483-.742.911-1.159 2.513-1.277 4.898l-.001.01c-.067 1.816.946 6.943.99 7.16a.688.688 0 0 0 1.35-.266c-.01-.051-1.023-5.177-.963-6.84.127-2.556.598-3.64.97-4.098.133-.163.602-.587 2.104-1.027l.206-.058-1.425 2.458a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.937c.33.19.75.077.94-.251L12.42 2.126a1.52 1.52 0 0 1 2.07-.552c.35.2.6.527.705.916.105.39.051.797-.15 1.145l-4.767 8.222a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.937c.33.19.75.077.94-.25l.794-1.368c.201-.348.529-.597.92-.702a1.508 1.508 0 0 1 1.854 1.066c.105.39.052.796-.15 1.144l-.377.652-.002.002-.898 1.55a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.938c.329.189.75.077.94-.251l.9-1.551c.201-.348.528-.597.92-.702a1.512 1.512 0 0 1 1.703 2.21l-1.223 2.11a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.938c.33.189.75.076.941-.252l.5-.862c.202-.348.529-.597.92-.702.392-.104.8-.051 1.15.15.723.416.972 1.34.554 2.06l-3.525 6.08c-.517.892-1.57 1.795-3.044 2.611-1.156.64-2.163.998-2.173 1.002a.685.685 0 0 0 .23 1.333.688.688 0 0 0 .229-.04c.18-.062 4.419-1.575 5.952-4.22l3.524-6.08a2.878 2.878 0 0 0-1.059-3.934Z" fill="#333"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="table__container"&gt;&lt;table tabindex="0" class="table__wrapper table__wrapper--inbodyContent table__wrapper--sticky table__wrapper--divider"&gt;&lt;caption class="table__caption table__caption--top table__caption--left"&gt;Men’s Grip Strength Norms By Age&lt;/caption&gt;&lt;thead class="table__head"&gt;&lt;tr class="table__head__row"&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below average (kg)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Average (kg)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Above average (kg)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody class="table__body"&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;20s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;41.7 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;48.3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;55&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;30s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;38.7&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;46.8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;55&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;40s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;37.1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;44.7&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;52.4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;50s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;35.4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;42.3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;49.3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;60s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;30.6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;37.6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;44.6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;70s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;27.3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;33.7&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;40.1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;80s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;21.9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;28.1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;34.2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-table-FksH83USHZtfFrgNwmzjLV-A2BVtxzWfoYB048p9HmKohnmtTPl3Igx" class="slice-container table-wrapper table-FksH83USHZtfFrgNwmzjLV-A2BVtxzWfoYB048p9HmKohnmtTPl3Igx slice-container-table"&gt;&lt;div class="table__instruction"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swipe to scroll horizontally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 23 30" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M21.554 15.726a2.878 2.878 0 0 0-1.705-.374 2.881 2.881 0 0 0-1.388-3.068 2.877 2.877 0 0 0-1.992-.333 2.884 2.884 0 0 0-.1-.766 2.865 2.865 0 0 0-1.346-1.75c-.47-.27-.996-.4-1.527-.385l2.742-4.73a2.87 2.87 0 0 0 .323-.83h2.612V2.084h-2.661A2.861 2.861 0 0 0 15.18.385a2.903 2.903 0 0 0-3.952 1.055l-.373.644H2.983l1.003-1L2.99.09 1.28 1.793l-.999.995L2.99 5.484l.998-.994-1.003-.999h7.054L6.505 9.586c-.34.066-.905.186-1.523.366-1.405.41-2.321.895-2.8 1.483-.742.911-1.159 2.513-1.277 4.898l-.001.01c-.067 1.816.946 6.943.99 7.16a.688.688 0 0 0 1.35-.266c-.01-.051-1.023-5.177-.963-6.84.127-2.556.598-3.64.97-4.098.133-.163.602-.587 2.104-1.027l.206-.058-1.425 2.458a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.937c.33.19.75.077.94-.251L12.42 2.126a1.52 1.52 0 0 1 2.07-.552c.35.2.6.527.705.916.105.39.051.797-.15 1.145l-4.767 8.222a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.937c.33.19.75.077.94-.25l.794-1.368c.201-.348.529-.597.92-.702a1.508 1.508 0 0 1 1.854 1.066c.105.39.052.796-.15 1.144l-.377.652-.002.002-.898 1.55a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.938c.329.189.75.077.94-.251l.9-1.551c.201-.348.528-.597.92-.702a1.512 1.512 0 0 1 1.703 2.21l-1.223 2.11a.685.685 0 0 0 .252.938c.33.189.75.076.941-.252l.5-.862c.202-.348.529-.597.92-.702.392-.104.8-.051 1.15.15.723.416.972 1.34.554 2.06l-3.525 6.08c-.517.892-1.57 1.795-3.044 2.611-1.156.64-2.163.998-2.173 1.002a.685.685 0 0 0 .23 1.333.688.688 0 0 0 .229-.04c.18-.062 4.419-1.575 5.952-4.22l3.524-6.08a2.878 2.878 0 0 0-1.059-3.934Z" fill="#333"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="table__container"&gt;&lt;table tabindex="0" class="table__wrapper table__wrapper--inbodyContent table__wrapper--sticky table__wrapper--divider"&gt;&lt;caption class="table__caption table__caption--top table__caption--left"&gt;Women’s Grip Strength Norms By Age&lt;/caption&gt;&lt;thead class="table__head"&gt;&lt;tr class="table__head__row"&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decade&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below average (kg)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Average (kg)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th class="table__head__heading table__head__heading--left" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Above average (kg)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody class="table__body"&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;20s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt; 24.1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;28.8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;33.6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;30s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;24.9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;29&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;33.2&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;40s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;24.8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;29.3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;33.9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;50s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;22.4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;26.6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;30.9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;60s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;18.4&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;22.8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;27.3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;70s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;16.8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;20&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;24.3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr class="table__body__row"&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;80s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;17&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;19.9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td class="table_body__data" colspan="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;22.9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a id="elk-how-can-you-improve-your-grip-strength" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-can-you-improve-your-grip-strength"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How can you improve your grip strength?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="4311def6-ebdf-4c84-94c3-50e2f8cc4497"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="inline-layout "&gt;&lt;div class="caption-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A loaded carry is one way to work on your grip strength&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / SDI Productions)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="6bfc20a6-5d5d-45dd-b213-adef6973eb8a"&gt;Training grip strength can be done in and out of the gym, according to Tzoumaris. “You can improve your grip strength by consistently training the muscles of your hands, forearms, and wrists. The goal is to build both maximal strength (your peak force) and endurance (how long you can sustain it for).”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the gym, some simple but effective exercises include dead hangs from a pull-up bar, farmer’s carries with dumbbells or kettlebells, plate pinches for thumb strength (where you hold a weight plate in one hand with your thumb on one side and fingers on the other for as long as possible), and wrist curls to target the forearm flexors,” he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Outside the gym, even everyday actions like squeezing a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://target.georiot.com/Proxy.ashx?tsid=110083&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2Fhand-gripper%2Fs%3Fk%3Dhand%2Bgripper%26tag%3Dhawk-future-20%26ascsubtag%3Dfitandwell-gb-8253993319126482745-20" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.amazon.com/hand-gripper/s?k=hand+gripper" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://target.georiot.com/Proxy.ashx?tsid=110083&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Famazon.com%2Fhand-gripper%2Fs%3Fk%3Dhand%2Bgripper%26tag%3Dhawk-future-20%26ascsubtag%3Dhawk-custom-tracking-20" data-merchant-name="Amazon US" data-merchant-id="1471" data-merchant-network="Amazonus" data-merchant-url="amazon.com" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;hand gripper&lt;/a&gt;, tennis ball or carrying heavy shopping bags can help. Over time, this type of training improves your neuromuscular efficiency, enhancing both performance and everyday function.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxONUJ1azVINGNOTEdiNmxMOW93eXE3NW1WdHNNSDFWS0ROaF9qamtydmJxd2xkNWx3eWhEeUxxbDhKSE1GYks1YkRkMEJpektHRXJveGFtMDVEOUNPRkNscU8zQ0ViSGtqdksxOVFKYWVlY0ltekE4YUlSNXB0SEkzQloyZFYtSFE</guid></item><item><title>心脏外科医生解释了“积极毒害”您身体的事情，以及为什么您应该“绝对避免”它们- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/heart-surgeon-avoid-food-drink-heart-health-690012-20251227</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:56:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNTTZWMU5GNXFtVG5naWgxQkQ0a21xdlhoNFJRMWVtcFVuQXE3b2RERUFfeE9fT0JNR1JmU3kwVDUtWllWTjNIZHZOVzBjYnRQNmhWaXNSTHdxTmlONGFuUkFsQ3p6OGt3dWprMmJYSkhCVEhKSFUyQk9hT3FmTFpCQVBjVWRpMHMycVdneGVWNURlbVRzY0dHUHhncmE</guid></item><item><title>听起来很健康流行语的食物可能会将添加的糖隐藏在显而易见的地方-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/hidden-added-sugar-health-brands-f1bf6cd53aa3be569e5952b5bc8c773f</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;Many consumers feel pride in avoiding the glazed pastries in the supermarket and instead opting for “all natural” granola that comes packed with extra protein. Same goes for low-fat yogurts “made with real fruit,” “organic” plant-based milks and bottled “superfood” smoothies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Buyer beware: Healthy grocery buzzwords like those often cover up an &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/heat-hot-climate-sugar-soda-diabetes-dee1cb27322afb3e556fd2c6f8ecf1ae"&gt;unhealthy amount of sugar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/c147e0085eb842ac9144e8214dddd063"&gt;Added sugars&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are difficult to quickly spot because many companies use clever marketing to distract consumers, said Nicole Avena, a professor of neuroscience and psychiatry at Mount Sinai Medical School and Princeton University who has studied added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avena said while some health-forward brands know people are starting to become aware of the hazards of added sugars, “a lot of the bigger brands don’t worry so much about people’s health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how to spot hidden sugars and what to do about it.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;What to look for&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Along with saturated fat and salt, eating excess sugar is linked to &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/033b68db8ce342cd9cfdcda57a628027"&gt;heart disease, obesity, diabetes and other health risks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The average American consumes 17 grams of added sugar a day, which adds up to 57 pounds (26 kilograms) per year, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/sugar-shrink-the-sweet-spot-for-blood-sugar-health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;according to the American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. About half of that comes from beverages, but much of the rest is sneaked into cereal, salsa, prepared sandwiches, dairy products, bottled sauces and baked goods, including many brands of whole-grain bread.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To help control sugar intake, start by checking the nutrition label. Since 2021, food companies have been required to list the quantity of added sugars separately from total sugar content. But the plan backfired, Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Infobox" data-module data-gtm-region="This article is part of AP's Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. Read more Be Well." data-align-center&gt;
    
    &lt;div class="Infobox-items RichTextBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is part of AP’s Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/hub/be-well"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read more Be Well.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Companies reduced common sweeteners like refined beet sugar and high-fructose corn syrup but added alternatives, such as monk fruit and the sugar alcohol erythritol, which aren’t considered “added sugars” under FDA regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Now our foods are even more sweet than they were back in 2020,” Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;What should you do?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Collin Popp, a dietitian and professor at NYU Langone Health, said the current FDA recommendation allows for some flexibility. People should get no more than 10% of their calories from added sugar, which amounts to about 50 grams per day if eating 2,000 calories, or a bit more than what’s in a typical can of soda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that might be too flexible, Popp said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I would actually like to see that be less than 5%, and closer to zero for some, if they have diabetes or prediabetes,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key is to &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/hub/food-safety"&gt;be mindful of what you’re eating&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, even if the product &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/28e626562c88439b96056e843215aa8d"&gt;seems healthy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; or if the package is labeled organic, Popp said. Roasted nuts, plant-based milks and wasabi peas, for example, can include a surprising amount of added sugars. So can English muffins and Greek yogurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Chobani black cherry yogurt, for example, has zero grams of fat but 9 grams of added sugar, or more than 2 teaspoons. Silk brand almond milk has 7 grams per cup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Popp recommends taking control of how much sugar goes into your food. That could mean buying plain yogurt and adding honey or berries, or asking the barista if you can put your own oat milk into your coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Taking from one column to add to another&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although they lower the calorie content of foods, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/coke-cane-sugar-corn-syrup-better-d7a70ebd4aef1564e409dd087f6a69c3"&gt;artificial sweeteners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; like stevia and sugar alcohols may not be better because they can encourage people to overeat, Avena said. She said research shows that sweet flavors are what activate the reward center of the brain, not the sugar itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s not to write off sugar alternatives, including allulose for people with Type 1 diabetes since it doesn’t affect blood sugar. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But for the general public, minimizing dependence on the overall sweetness of food is key to improving health, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t let the food companies decide how much sugar you’re eating,” Avena said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Albert Stumm writes about food, travel and wellness. Find his work at &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.albertstumm.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;www.albertstumm.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPN0M0a2dHNDFFRHZLNlNOSElNWVd0N3E3cWctSVMwakdmUWs5UUJoN3UtTm9aX1pWR0Q4T0VwYUVNdThaNmJqQnU0N1hpYkF5ZVVpa2xBbldqS3FqWDVsREd2Z3h3dV9hMWV2UlhoSVZJckp5ZERaNjFITm44eVMtbldWeENlaDFLdmZVc1J6UXVBZjNVbXZN</guid></item><item><title>11岁的阿拉巴马州男孩因患流感而死亡- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/11-year-old-alabama-boy-sickened-with-the-flu-dies.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BD2UG5ESSFFE3H44E5A7GIRO3I"&gt;An 11-year-old boy from Hueytown has died after spending nearly a week in the hospital battling the flu, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/sAbRiNa.eRiN10" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.facebook.com/sAbRiNa.eRiN10"&gt;post shared by a family member on Facebook &lt;/a&gt;Saturday and &lt;a href="https://www.wbrc.com/2025/12/28/11-year-old-hueytown-boy-dies-after-battling-severe-case-flu/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.wbrc.com/2025/12/28/11-year-old-hueytown-boy-dies-after-battling-severe-case-flu/"&gt;confirmed by WBRC-TV. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Q23UL3KCTZEUZLCDJEX37XQJFU"&gt;Jace Watkins, 11, had been hospitalized at Children’s of Alabama in Birmingham since Saturday after suffering a seizure. He became ill just two days earlier, first showing symptoms on December 18. Over the Christmas holiday, Jace remained in critical condition as his family held onto hope and asked the community for prayers for his recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WK73NODLJVBJRG2KCS7E24LM4M"&gt;Watkins was a 5th grade student at Hueytown Intermediate School. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UHKEWAZ67ZEMHN52IVVDRUH6MM"&gt;On Saturday, his aunt, Sabrina Erin Parsons, shared a heartbreaking update earlier Saturday evening on Facebook, asking people to continue praying for Jace as the family prepared to say their final goodbyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CQ6EFD3UGFH4TI7EJEFH7YUBJI"&gt;“Just wanted to come on here and update everyone, I want thank everyone for praying for Jace.. Please pray for our family as we say our goodbyes to Jace.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YB25C2J7XVBLJLR4PCI556IVMQ"&gt;Within an hour of the update about Jace’s condition, hundreds of comments poured in, many from people offering comfort, prayers, and shared grief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WUB7H2MHTZH3BMEEYRHKUOTCNU"&gt;“As a mom who lost her little boy many years ago, my heart is broken for you and your family,” one commenter wrote. “There is nothing more devastating than losing your child. My sister also lost her son almost 10 years ago and has created a Facebook support group for bereaved mothers. I am so very sorry that you are going through this awful loss.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VT6JZHSHJRELTIFZAZ2UTFYMPY"&gt;In the week since Jace fell ill, residents of Hueytown have been holding prayer vigils for him and his family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV3PMTGOGFBORBL2FOJQEGPS34"&gt;Jace’s death comes as Alabama is seeing a sharp rise in emergency room visits related to influenza.&lt;a href="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.alabamapublichealth.gov/data/respiratory.html"&gt; According to the Alabama Department of Public Health&lt;/a&gt;, about 6.3 percent of emergency room visits during the week ending December 21 were for flu like illness. That figure is more than double the rate from the previous week and five times higher than it was on December 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BHOVW5KGSNANDL2JTIHO4IOLCI"&gt;Nationally, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported that 14 states experienced high or very high levels of outpatient visits for influenza like illness during the week ending December 13, the most recent data available. At that time, Alabama was classified as having moderate flu activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:CJCVVKZOSZAXZEWFSDLLOJOKPQ" data-fusion-component="CJCVVKZOSZAXZEWFSDLLOJOKPQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:CJCVVKZOSZAXZEWFSDLLOJOKPQ" data-fusion-component="CJCVVKZOSZAXZEWFSDLLOJOKPQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 05:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQRHNQQ0RaYWxPT19UWlZKRTJHaWlQMzJlVGV1YW1tSkFuMGNsVDdTaHdPZDJyQUJqdWFOOUxvdVljU28tYkU2SmRxZ2NOY2pLNXJ3ZFFiTlhEOXctZGVqMTZrMG5LZlBXeWp3RFFvQ0wwZnBFY2lTS1JfWExtUElkVHhxajlNczBoX0JvbTlDeGzSAaQBQVVfeXFMTzZwOV9RRkNtQlBNSGNod21VcUt4QUdVY19kQmpCSzRlcDN2MTJ4bmI0NFBhbExxVDRKZW16a1dIcHItMWk5TGVQem1MMjN1dVItS2VrVEhWSG45VmtISWx5XzJiNE1JSVFsMVBtOEE1UUk5MWNGbGlnVVp5ei1OcFlVZEtLNUhKeEVrMzN5Wl9KVHRmNnFwQUdSOWFwZlhYamlNd2Q</guid></item><item><title>RPD ：房东与房客的冲突导致逮捕，步枪由军官保管- 13wham.com</title><link>https://13wham.com/news/local/rpd-landlord-tenant-clash-leads-to-arrest-rifle-secured-by-officers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText_storyText__C3hWI StoryText_storyText__C3hWI"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rochester, N.Y. — One person was arrested on Saturday after an alleged landlord-tenant dispute in Rochester.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Rochester Police Department said officers responded to the area of Mt. Hope Avenue and Sanford Street for the report of a "menacing with a rifle." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The department said officers learned that a dispute between a landlord and a tenant had occurred, during which police said the tenant threatened their landlord with a rifle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The landlord wished to pursue criminal charges, the tenant was arrested, and the rifle was secured. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officers said there were no injuries, and the area is open after being taped off for some time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>13wham.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 03:31:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPbjZKV1RENTBBQlZvYmkydy14emh6OG12OTM2cnRuczZsdldtX2lweEVwcEF6Wk1OTUJHcl85d2FDRWdQZkNNUVBtZVY1RWJxaVVja3lvOWxpZVloS0d0T2txcU41NnNwOW9DSlIwUWZ2aVRqQnFDdnNKQWNNLVpaWlFrX3NyYldNRnptR0JUdzlsRkFQTzRlZjdLbDI0QQ</guid></item><item><title>医生解释雪松热疗法和药物- KXAN Austin</title><link>https://www.kxan.com/news/local/doctor-explains-cedar-fever-remedies-and-medication/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>KXAN Austin</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 02:51:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOMktQM3BJNHZEWW5rLTIzOFBUVEhVYzd5b2E0amFqYzVXMVkxa25adEEwTWE3cjZLdkJ4ODFmSUluTXlXR2p5TmUxeF85aFBILVdzQUlnQnZKOGFiNG5wZkcxMDN5bUVqeWJFTFBuaGIwXzBnZTZEblRQSWxvd2JDdnBhUm5yWDFTWWxoZNIBkgFBVV95cUxQZXh1ZlRaSWw2SHoySVd2Nk9WTDFhaGgxSXpaSkxLUnBFay1FblloX245OWpjZGx4QUtzWExBQ3FMRXJuVzNlVHBIYWtlMldydDVVXzFyUkhuTWt2MjZpUXA1ckxYOVNtdEpDYlVDVlN4RjhNWkZLNXVfY1R0bms4UlIyWHJ1aVQ5MjJSdEkyR2MxZw</guid></item><item><title>新泽西州卫生部门表示，纽瓦克机场的乘客可能已经让其他人接触过麻疹- ABC7纽约</title><link>https://abc7ny.com/post/newark-airport-passenger-may-have-exposed-others-measles-new-jersey-health-department-says/18325181/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;NEWARK, New Jersey (WABC) -- &lt;/span&gt;A passenger at Newark Airport may have exposed people to measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;New Jersey's Health Department says someone with the disease passed through the airport on Friday, December 19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The person was in terminals B and C between 7 a.m. and 7 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The Health Department hopes to track down people who were likely exposed. It also suggests anyone who is not vaccinated to get the MMR shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Measles symptoms include a high fever, cough, runny nose, watery red eyes, and a rash that usually appears between three and five days after symptoms begin. The rash usually begins as flat red spots that appear on the face at the hairline and spread downward to the neck, torso, arms, legs, and feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;----------&lt;br class=" "&gt;*&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/newsletters/" target="_blank"&gt; Get Eyewitness News Delivered&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br class=" "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/new-jersey/" target="_blank"&gt;More New Jersey news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br class=" "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://7ny.tv/submitnewstip" target="_blank"&gt;Send us a news tip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br class=" "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/apps/" target="_blank"&gt;Download the abc7NY app for breaking news alerts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br class=" "&gt;*&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCrlIS7z20CnVaCrMvdkig_g" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt; Follow us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br class=" "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="RxNCg ykkUm PvZ nIjPJ PMXYp LmsHF SfAHY mNgye lNbol LBPRq rBLIK "&gt;Submit a tip or story idea to Eyewitness News&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Have a breaking news tip or an idea for a story we should cover? Send it to Eyewitness News using the form below.    If attaching a video or photo, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/image-video-solicitation-and-rights-terms-of-use/5101040/" target="_blank"&gt;terms of use apply.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WABC-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 New York</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:59:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxQdnJfNkpIR0xhU1ZuVjJXc1lld1ZNYVJXZ1NiV3VibklpVzg2dzd6NWh5MTBCS3g3RWM1cURSRzZaejI0Yk9FZE04aEJIVjFKVmwwMWE2YUdMYm1kUnlpVEtPTG5uTHlfWWh6T0tGcEZadFBtdmlTRXFxN09lMFhFZkJNVWxqeUpWQjlHdWlOZWhyNF9QUGtyMWFtUm1zTXJMTkgxc08wSDlUTnZucmVNcTN5TE43RWNiRGFRWmtLTi04QdIBxwFBVV95cUxQY0Rrc2I3b2NQZ3FNTEQxalAyVmdrb1NGcDBsMldZUHNNcUJDVzVhYWQyMmFLaWllOXdwbnFTemZVeUoteWJET09BS21PSms5aFZIZF90WTdMekEzdUZ5SF9ZMENZbG5FX0RmN0VTZWZRRkhBRDZ0LXdkSnIyQmhJaVQzNG5fYks2aUQ5d1JSRE0zbUQxR1VsQU1xdGgwVTdVUWJGNTRzZ1lyalExUFpVZ2twMzRLYXQ1cncyUUtMdU01dml2ay1R</guid></item></channel></rss>