<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>常见的测试医生担心甲状腺癌激增的背后-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15095311/common-medical-test-doctors-fear-thyroid-cancer.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just 31 and in good health, Jess Cain was horrified to discover a small lump in her neck, which she had thought little of, was &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-006a86e0-90bf-11f0-b6f9-d9b47bd516c7"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The special needs teacher felt well, with no symptoms, and went to the doctor only after a massage therapist spotted the growth and urged her to get it checked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Expecting reassurance, she was instead diagnosed with thyroid cancer and told she would need surgery almost immediately, followed by months of treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘My surgeon told me I’d likely had the tumour for almost a decade,’ recalled Jess. ‘But I hadn’t had any pain or any other symptoms. I’d never heard of thyroid cancer. It was such a shock.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Similar cases are becoming increasingly common. Thyroid cancer – which affects the small, butterfly-shaped gland in the neck – has soared over the past two decades. In the UK, diagnoses have risen by 62 per cent in just ten years and are expected to climb by nearly three-quarters by 2035.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The thyroid makes and releases hormones that control many important functions, including metabolism – how the body uses energy – as well as heart rate, temperature and growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is one of five cancers rising in younger adults, according to the American Cancer Society, alongside throat, prostate, kidney and colon. And cases of thyroid cancer are nearly four times higher in women than men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Colombian-American actress Sofia Vergara, British actress Marisa Abela, and Love Island star Demi Jones have all spoken publicly in recent years about their diagnoses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Actress Sofia Vergara underwent treatment for thyroid cancer when she was 28&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Each of them developed the disease before the age of 30.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say the surge in thyroid cancer cases may partly be explained by improvements in medical technology, with more tumours detected that might otherwise have gone unnoticed and never caused problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatRHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-739e2530-90c0-11f0-b6f9-d9b47bd516c7" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15095311/common-medical-test-doctors-fear-thyroid-cancer.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;IT'S A FACT &lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nearly 7,000 children developed thyroid cancer in Ukraine, Belarus and Russia in the aftermath of the Chernobyl disaster &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But some doctors point to a more controversial reason: that medical technology itself is actually fuelling the rise. They warn that excessive use of X-rays and CT scans expose patients to unnecessary radiation, which can raise the risk of developing the cancer. Children are most at risk, as exposure at a young age is more likely to cause problems decades later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It sounds alarming, yet in June a major study reached a similarly stark conclusion. Researchers found that about 5 per cent of all new cancers in the US could be linked to CT scans – a toll comparable to those caused by alcohol. About 4,000 people in the UK are diagnosed with thyroid cancer each year, most of them aged between 70 and 74. But cases have almost tripled over the past three decades, with young women the fastest-growing group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The wider rise in cancers among younger adults has drawn considerable attention in recent months, with experts pointing to ultra-processed foods, obesity and even certain strains of gut bacteria as possible drivers. However, when it comes to thyroid cancer, specialists say the explanation is less straightforward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘There’s no doubt of an increase in the incidence of thyroid cancer over the past 25 years,’ said Professor Fausto Palazzo, an endocrine surgeon at Hammersmith Hospital in west London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘In large part, we believe it’s related to the fact that we’re simply detecting more disease.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, he added, that doesn’t mean more cancers aren’t developing than before. ‘It just makes it more difficult to interpret.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Doctors warn that excessive use of X-rays and CT scans expose patients to unnecessary radiation, which can raise the risk of developing the cancer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The key question, he said, is whether there is something that is making thyroid cancer more common in young people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘The only two things we know that increase the chance of thyroid cancer are genetic history and radiation exposure,’ he continued. ‘And while there has been some theorising that an increase in radiation exposure in the environment in recent decades could be contributing to cases, it’s very difficult to prove.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some experts are attempting to do just this. Dr Riccardo Vigneri, emeritus professor of endocrinology at the University of Catania in Italy, has spent decades studying thyroid cancer. In a 2020 paper he analysed 18 years of data from the Californian death registry. If the surge were due only to overdetection, the records would show a rise mainly in small, slow-growing tumours – the kind that may not cause harm. Instead, they showed a marked increase in larger, more advanced cancers, along with a rise in deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That, he argued, was clear evidence the trend could not be explained by scanning alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘All evidence indicates the causes of worldwide increase in thyroid cancers are recent, environmental and multiple,’ he wrote in the journal Cancers. The ‘most likely contributing factor’, his team concluded, was increased exposure to radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Historically, the most severe exposures followed nuclear events – from the atomic bombs in Hiroshima and Nagasaki to Chernobyl – where children nearby developed thyroid tumours at high rates. But today, the greatest source of man-made radiation comes from medicine –diagnostic tests such as X-rays and CT scans, which use high-energy beams to produce detailed images of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatRHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-93c95050-90c0-11f0-b6f9-d9b47bd516c7" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15095311/common-medical-test-doctors-fear-thyroid-cancer.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;IT'S A FACT &lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The thyroid gland is responsible for producing the hormones that control the body’s temperature.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A landmark analysis by researchers from several US universities showed that, between 1980 and 2006, the average radiation dose received by Americans had doubled – with CT scans responsible for more than half of that exposure. Around a third of all CTs were directed at the head and neck. Children face the greatest risk, as their developing tissues are especially sensitive to radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A study of more than 11 million Australians found that children who underwent CT scans had a 40 per cent higher risk of thyroid cancer later in life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2010, endocrinologists at Mercy Hospital and Medical Center in Chicago warned that the surge in medical radiation was running in parallel with rising thyroid cancer rates, and urged doctors to limit the use of CT scans in young patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But experts stress that the scans are often lifesaving – they’re vital for detecting tumours, internal bleeding or serious infections – and that the overall risk to any individual patient remains very small.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some studies suggest thyroid cancer may also be linked to radon gas – a natural by-product of uranium in the ground that seeps into homes. Already known to cause lung cancer, a 2020 study from the University of Guam found signs it could raise thyroid cancer risk too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But many experts say it is too soon to draw firm conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘In medicine, we’re stuck with epidemiology – the study of disease in a population – to guide us in deciding whether or not a certain factor is responsible,’ said Prof Palazzo. ‘And without this type of large-scale research, we can’t say anything with certainty.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other research is looking beyond radiation, including the role of iodine – a trace mineral essential for producing thyroid hormones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Iodine is found in fish, dairy products and eggs, yet a 2010 study of more than 700 UK schoolgirls showed over two-thirds were deficient. Historically, about half of Britain’s iodine intake came from milk – but levels have fallen with the decline of free school milk and the rise of vegan and dairy-free diets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Regions where iodine deficiency is common also tend to report higher rates of thyroid cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This is because the thyroid needs iodine to make hormones, explained Dr Jahangir Ahmed, consultant ENT surgeon at OneWelbeck in London. ‘If you’re not getting enough iodine, the thyroid gland can become bigger, thinking it will help it make more,’ he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘When this happens, the growth driver might also cause mutations in the thyroid cells, which is the precursor to cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘The same thing happens in pregnancy – the baby demands more iodine, which can make the mother deficient.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other research has pointed to hormone-disrupting chemicals and air pollution as possible drivers. A 2022 study by the University of Beijing found thyroid cancer rates were higher in areas with poor air quality. Scientists at the Center for Disease Control and Prevention in Shenzhen, China, also reported links between the disease and endocrine-disrupting compounds found in everyday products such as flame-retardants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a 2020 study, researchers from Tulane University in the US and Egypt’s Suez Canal University concluded there was ‘strong evidence’ that certain man-made chemicals can impair thyroid function, raising the risk of future tumours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As for why women seem to be more affected than men, the answer is similarly speculative. ‘It’s most likely hormone related,’ said Dr Ahmed, ‘as we know after menopause that the rates of men and women getting thyroid cancer start to come together.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Women may also be at higher risk because of their increased likelihood of autoimmune conditions, where the body begins to attack the thyroid gland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Ahmed added: ‘This causes chronic inflammation, and can make the thyroid more prone to cell mutation.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It’s important to remember that thyroid cancer generally has an excellent prognosis. While some forms are more aggressive, the two most common types – papillary and follicular – are usually slow-growing and highly treatable. ‘If you catch it in a reasonable time, more than 90 per cent of patients can be cured,’ said Dr Ahmed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Warning signs and symptoms of thyroid cancer include a lump in the throat or neck, a hoarse voice lasting more than three weeks, breathing problems or difficulty swallowing. Anyone with these symptoms should see a doctor without delay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Treatment often involves surgery to remove part or all of the thyroid, sometimes followed by radioactive iodine therapy to destroy any remaining thyroid cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For very small tumours, less than a centimetre across, doctors may recommend monitoring rather than operating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I reassure the majority of my patients that they’ve got time,’ said Dr Ahmed. ‘With a few exceptions, thyroid cancers have an excellent prognosis.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;I was diagnosed aged 31... and there were no warning signs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It was during a rare attempt to relax that special needs teacher Jess Cain, right, now 35, first discovered the lump in her neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I was having a massage and the masseuse immediately told me something didn’t feel right,’ said Jess, pictured right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I felt it too and agreed. It was like a marble under the skin, beneath my ear, that became more prominent when I turned my head.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Concerned, Jess booked an appointment with her GP, who reassured the then 31-year-old it was most likely a swollen lymph node from an oncoming cold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A week later she still felt fine but the lump hadn’t gone. After insisting on being seen again, Jess was referred for a scan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Months later, an ultrasound revealed a suspicious mass in her neck. And just five days before Christmas, she was told it was cancerous. A biopsy and surgery in January confirmed it was thyroid cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I was so confused,’ she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I had had no symptoms and, when I was diagnosed, I didn’t know anyone with thyroid cancer at all.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Since then Jess has had her thyroid removed, undergone radioactive iodine therapy, and endured further surgery to shave down part of her neck. Now she wants others to understand how destabilising the disease can be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘People refer to it as “the good cancer” because it’s easily treated, but it’s already been two years with it for me and I’ve already had a resurgence within three months of getting the all-clear,’ she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘There’s no such thing as a good cancer.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 00:41:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQOGw2NUw4Wnk3UWlYWWhPV3FtcTdUZ2JFc05DRXlXSkJHb2Vsd3BlVlFyVjZWbmNmVWNUTF91TDFkY19zSTB5QUVZZTRhcVFIYVhQRUVRZTl6dHNJbmgwVVRRRUdmaGF3djBEaGJjSnNfcS1ETlVhR2tfVkhackNNZzJwQWRuckNacExsOEZqODhVVmkxY1ZMcmZUQk1RTElGZFBQZjQyUQ</guid></item><item><title>健康警报：伊达尔戈县的手足口病- ValleyCentral.com</title><link>https://www.valleycentral.com/news/local-news/health-alert-hand-foot-and-mouth-disease-in-hidalgo-county/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content article-body rich-text "&gt;
		
		


&lt;p&gt;HIDALGO COUNTY, Texas (&lt;a href="http://valleycentral.com" data-type="link" data-id="valleycentral.com"&gt;ValleyCentral&lt;/a&gt;) — The Hidalgo County Health and Human Services has issued a warning following the recent outbreak of the Hand, Foot and Mouth Disease. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;According to a statement issued by the Hidalgo County Health and Human Services, over 60 cases of Hand, Foot and Mouth Disease have been reported in four schools in Hidalgo County.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Hidalgo County Health Authority Dr. Ivan Melendez informs the public that the disease primarily affects children but can spread to adults.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p hidden data-minutemedia-viewport="mobile" data-player-id="btah1kyr" data-stn-player="" data-s2n-api="minuteMediaS2NApi"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Dr. Melendez explains that the symptoms include fever, chills, a scratchy throat, nausea, and blisters that typically appear on the hands, feet, and mouth by the third day after being infected with the disease. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p hidden data-minutemedia-viewport="desktop" data-player-id="btah1kyr" data-stn-player="" data-s2n-api="minuteMediaS2NApi"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;“The most infectious moment is during the first three days, when most people don’t know they even have it, because it’s spread through mucus, droplets, coughing, not washing hands and any bodily fluids,” he added. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Health experts added that there is no cure for this virus, but doctors will provide symptomatic care by providing medications such as Tylenol and Motrin. Additionally, they will recommend patients to eat easy-to-chew foods such as macaroni and mashed potatoes, as the blisters can cause pain while eating. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Melendez advised that children can go back to school once they have gone a full day without a fever and their blisters are drying out. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For more information, contact &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/hidalgocounty.health?__cft__[0]=AZWxL1UpIo4O6lDy_mz-YvfJ7BgAQ_J9XIyS-W4ogeWhA70xFTdfnfpcOuqkCB3Zpdoo5dO88u-k9x4SkAFKyNxFhsQ1cl3A2zPhRsSPc-hmY0mC8lksbvF4qneK_THcydONGLSv4ycahE5S9mbstj0kBVsYMLSKHny-FQ-OiFPQ8bpLHkLUTUuw1vif1ZtQd3VDVlGZzHA5010GUL-5to9B&amp;amp;__tn__=-]K-R"&gt;Hidalgo County Health &amp;amp; Human Services&lt;/a&gt; at 956-318-2426.&lt;/p&gt;

		&lt;div class="article-content-cta-group"&gt;
			&lt;div class="modal--suggest-correction article-content-cta-group__cta" data-component="modal"&gt;
				&lt;button data-modal-trigger class="suggest-correction-button"&gt;Suggest a Correction&lt;/button&gt;
				&lt;div class="modal__dialog"&gt;
					&lt;div class="modal__dialog-content"&gt;
						&lt;button class="modal__close-button" aria-label="Close Modal Content"&gt;
							&lt;span class="icon"&gt;
								&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" tabindex="-1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16.85 16.875"&gt;
									&lt;title&gt;Close Modal&lt;/title&gt;
									&lt;path fill="#fff" d="M9.65 8.454l6.88-7.063a.809.809 0 0 0 0-1.15.782.782 0 0 0-1.14 0L8.52 7.305 1.37.241a.782.782 0 0 0-1.14 0 .809.809 0 0 0 0 1.15l7.15 7.063-7.15 7.063a.809.809 0 0 0 0 1.15.824.824 0 0 0 .6.219.787.787 0 0 0 .59-.219l7.15-7.063 6.87 7.063a.824.824 0 0 0 .6.219.619.619 0 0 0 .54-.219.792.792 0 0 0 0-1.15z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
								&lt;/svg&gt;
							&lt;/span&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;h3 class="modal__dialog-title"&gt;Suggest a Correction&lt;/h3&gt;
						
					&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ValleyCentral.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 20:53:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOODB5WHhoX1BCeTMyeVczaWdiekpleGJpZ1NOTzQxRi1kY0E4MVUtUFRCSkZPby1hZy03UkNMS2hBN3pSQzlFejg4X1BXbTMzdlVtUHN5a3VWbnVzQUQ3aVNia1ZQbDQwWWRLU3EyMDRoUjNUUUlaUnVZWlo0ZDlTMVFTR0FDNXp4dTladEcyeGUzcEFTY1FQYzdwd19oc0FCbzQtNm9ZZGLSAa4BQVVfeXFMTnNVSDJ4RjVIaEtxazRaQXpMejhQaVRVY1hlTVp0dFBrbHJ0cUZxTWpPTGhYc1g0LWhOQXhYcWxMekUtT0ZiZFdtYU9MUTB2Nzd6Rk5LT1NGUG9xUGhFSXdoT0tHSXlGNktodXFIZEkwSGx6ZE1kRGs4OHExOU9pY1BfM29SWGwwTGhrbkR4bTN3QnJYWU5yX2xFSG1ac0RRYkVWMDlSMGtMbm93V0Jn</guid></item><item><title>痴呆症专家揭示了新患者令人心碎的特质-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15022377/Dementia-experts-reveal-heartbreaking-trait-new-patients-common.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dementia has long been considered a disease of old age. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In general, about one in 14 people develop &lt;a target="_self" href="/sciencetech/alzheimers-disease/index.html" id="mol-b7eef7f0-7eb4-11f0-b5ad-81bf18a35866"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease, the most common form, by age 65. By 85, it strikes one in three. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Most patients are still of retirement age or older, but doctors warn the disease is striking Americans younger than ever before. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In fact, the number of dementia cases in people under 65 more than doubled between 1990 and 2021. And the risk of developing dementia any time after age 55 is upwards of 40 percent, the latest research shows. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lesser known forms of the disease like frontotemporal dementia, which tend to affect adults as young as 40, have also become more common in recent years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Speaking to Daily Mail at the world's largest dementia conference in July, neurologists warned they are seeing patients younger and younger stepping into their offices, claiming they can no longer keep track of their meeting calendar or remember where they put their keys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They said part of this &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14663791/symptoms-early-warning-sign-young-onset-dementia.html"&gt;surge in early-onset dementia&lt;/a&gt; could be due to young people getting tested earlier than their parents and grandparents, especially if they have a family history.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, they also sounded the alarm about chronic diseases and other lifestyle factors increasingly plaguing young people such as diabetes, obesity, depression and stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In one of the most tragic early-onset dementia cases, Robin Williams was found to have been suffering from Lewy body dementia after dying by suicide in 2014 at age 63. He is pictured here with actress Zelda Williams in 2009&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Adrian Owen, a professor of cognitive neuroscience and imaging at the University of Western Ontario in Canada and chief scientific officer at dementia detection company Creyos, told Daily Mail: 'We're seeing people younger, and we're seeing people with different types of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In the last 15 or 20 years, we've sort of gone from the focus being squarely on Alzheimer's disease, that's all people used to talk about, to now broad recognition of frontotemporal dementia, vascular dementia, Lewy body dementia, many different types of dementia, and they present in sometimes subtly different ways.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dementia is an umbrella term used to describe a range of progressive neurological disorders that impact memory, thinking and behavior. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Common symptoms include memory loss, poor judgment, confusion, repeating questions, difficulty communicating, taking longer to complete normal daily tasks, acting impulsively, and mobility issues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alzheimer's disease, which affects about 7million Americans, is the most common form, and it typically affects those over 65, with the risk increasing with age. But around 200,000 have early-onset Alzheimer's, the latest research shows.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Joel Salinas, adjunct professor of neurology at NYU Langone in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/new_york/index.html" id="mol-e69c1000-8cfc-11f0-827f-b725c85fde96"&gt;New York City&lt;/a&gt; and Chief Medical Officer of telehealth platform Isaac Health, told Daily Mail that while most people with dementia are diagnosed after age 65, the disease often strikes much earlier before patients realize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He told this website: 'We know that these conditions start to develop 10 or even 20 years before you even obviously notice symptoms, and these symptoms are present in a continuum where the earliest symptoms may be really subtle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We want to get better at detecting things where they're in that subtle range.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both doctors told Daily Mail that younger patients who come into their clinics are less likely to come in with stereotypical signs like wandering or forgetting who their loved ones are. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mol-fe-xpmodule-comment-cta="true" data-article-id="15022377" data-channel="health" data-environment="production" data-platform="mol.web.desktop" data-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15022377/Dementia-experts-reveal-heartbreaking-trait-new-patients-common.html" data-version="1.1.4" data-reactroot=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Wendy Williams was diagnosed in 2023 frontotemporal dementia and aphasia at age 59&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Salinas said: 'Anxiety can give an early presentation. Social isolation can be an early presentation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I think we're still figuring out whether those symptoms are either tied to having cognitive deficits that are suddenly getting worse, like having difficulty remembering so I'm getting anxious about it, or they're manifestations of the disease in the brain itself.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Younger patients may also notice trouble staying organized at work or around the house, which shows a decline in working memory. Obsessive behaviors are also common&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Salinas also pointed to the example of a writer having trouble coming up with a typical word they would use in a piece and that difficulty worsening over time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He said: 'If I have a harder time reaching those words, and that's getting worse over time, that actually would be a red flag, kind of like forgetting keys, or walking to a room and not remembering why I walked into the room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But the key is actually to see are these changes that are persistent and getting worse slowly over time over like six months to a year or two years. Then I would consider that as something that really is a red flag that should be addressed.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While much is unknown about why dementia is increasingly affecting younger Americans, lifestyle factors likely play a significant role. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Last year, a &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13688417/factors-raise-risk-dementia-REVEALED-half-cases-avoided-people-changes-life-experts-say.html"&gt;Lancet Commission study&lt;/a&gt; found about 40 percent of Alzheimer's cases could be tied to 14 modifiable risk factors, including high cholesterol, diabetes, obesity and depression. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And a study unveiled at the Alzheimer's Association International Conference (AAIC) in July of 2,000 Americans at risk of dementia found that strict diet and exercise regimens helped them &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14947279/doctors-reveal-simple-lifestyle-changes-prevent-dementia-study.html"&gt;perform significantly better at cognitive tests&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many of these risk factors are on the rise across America, including in young people. CDC data shows the prevalence of obesity, for example, has doubled in adults from 1990 to 2021, and 40 percent of adults are now considered obese. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above chart shows changes in cognitive scores over time among people who implemented structured changes and those who implemented self-guided ones in the US POINTER study&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Diabetes prevalence has also increased from about 10 percent in 2000 to 14 percent in 2023, and prevalence among people under 44 has increased about 20 percent in 2024 compared to 2017. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These conditions trigger inflammation throughout the body, including in the brain, that damages cells and promotes the accumulation of toxic proteins that kill brain cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Owen said: 'I think in the past, dementia was always a really mysterious illness that seemed to just hit some people randomly and not other people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Now you're seeing more people with cognitive changes and potentially dementia at a younger age. It's almost a byproduct of the fact that younger people are developing diabetes, younger people are getting obese, younger people have anxiety and depression. There are increased levels of mental health challenges that tend to affect young people.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mental health is another key factor, he emphasized. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;CDC data shows the percentage of adults with anxiety symptoms has increased from 16 percent in 2019 to 18 percent in 2022. Meanwhile, depression is up from 10.5 percent in 2015 to about 18 percent in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Owen said: 'There are many other factors in today's world that young people are that are contributing to this sort of cognitive mental health crisis is probably better than epidemic, but I think one of them is anxiety and stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'No question, young people are more stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'People are worried about their futures. They're worried about their employment. They're worried about their health earlier on. We know stress has detrimental effect on brain functions.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Salinas also noted that while lifestyle factors and mental health are at play, he has seen more patients get evaluated for dementia as a precaution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He said: 'I would say we are seeing more and more people who are coming to get evaluated at a younger age, partly because I think [there are] cultural changes around the importance of addressing these issues early.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Owen urged younger Americans who notice issues like trouble focusing, personality changes, issues remembering words and other subtle signs to seek medical care, as early intervention opens the doors for more effective treatments and getting into clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He told this website: 'Early detection is so crucially important. The earlier you get in, the more effective it's going to be.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 18:39:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxPdHdHSnRfNlhtR0hsS0Zfc3lvUEYtanU2aHBCTGpFRm5qNnZHaEMzVzgyZmh2bWlMNk1Eekp1alB0VlFzb2QxLVJsZFY5U1dqZG1iRTJnYVhRQ3dNTTZjMTNfZ1BhXzNNaGgxZnFXSHVsUnI5Z2RaZzVtOWlyRXVXbDJYbE5PSG9WMkZfRzlzZ0ZLWGNDS1ZRY2JPUzFPd09MLTlFX2hFb1NDUEl2SGJXS3JNclY3eVNqZzhGY9IBwgFBVV95cUxPUEh2UW9tSjdDaGhYQ1JTOVNUcGlFVXRNSEJ5MUlxTnNLQy1GM0RFb0ExTDJhUF9obmxhaWdUOGhfdENaU0JGRXh6RG0yZHpLako4eFY0bm9lRXA0LVpjTTIteHgzNkRDa0dYVDFZcmw2cVlhUzZOcUduX1g0OHZETjBtZ1NBMWZVdkNMTzVzZnlxYTNLUVdmRUV1djBJc0ZRZlpQT3ROR3JlOHU2OERiN2NxNFBDT1VZWEJnc2pBVjQydw</guid></item><item><title>作为脱发专家，有一种食物我永远不会吃... -每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15094913/hair-loss-expert-food-never-eat-causes-balding.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When a study last month linked drinking lots of fizzy drinks to hair loss, it underlined the crucial role of diet in a condition affecting millions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now experts have revealed other everyday foods that could have a similar effect – including pasta, sliced bread and nuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Healthy hair needs a steady supply of nutrients, and although illness and genetics play a part in hair loss, what people eat and drink can make these factors better – or worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Ellie Rashid, consultant dermatologist at the private OneWelbeck clinic, said: ‘Diet is so important. Deficiency of the right nutrients will lead to brittle hair, less hair growing or hair being shed more readily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Iron deficiency, for example, impacts hair growth, while a vitamin D deficiency is linked to hair thinning.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The most common cause of hair loss is pattern baldness, influenced by genetics and hormones. Another trigger is the autoimmune condition alopecia areata, in which the immune system attacks hair follicles. Dr Rashid believes diet plays a role in both. ‘Many things can cause hair loss, but diet is like a switch that can ramp up the effects of these other factors or dial them down,’ she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She recommends blood tests for iron, zinc, vitamin D and folate (vitamin B9), and adopting a balanced diet. Iron can be boosted with red meat, lentils and leafy greens such as spinach and kale. Vitamin D can be topped up with sunlight and supplements and zinc can be increased through supplements and foods such as pumpkin or sesame seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While good foods support healthy hair, evidence suggests others may trigger or accelerate balding. Here, The Mail on Sunday highlights some of the foods that could harm your hair... and those that will give it a boost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Ellie Rashid is a consultant dermatologist at the private OneWelbeck clinic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Ditch white bread, cakes and sweets &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Refined carbohydrates include foods high in processed sugar, such as cakes, sweets and fizzy drinks, along with white bread and pasta made from grains stripped of natural fibre. Because they are digested quickly, they cause spikes in blood sugar and insulin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2016 study in the journal Menopause Review concluded: ‘Consumption of highly processed foods, rich in simple sugars, is one factor causing excess hair loss.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers found insulin spikes led to ‘disturbances’ in blood vessels, reducing oxygen supply to the scalp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Rashid advises switching from white bread and pasta to wholemeal. She said: ‘Refined carbs are a driver of inflammation. They negatively impact&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;cellular processes such as keratin formation – meaning hair doesn’t grow as well as it should.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Don't overdo Brazil nuts  &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Brazil nuts are rich in selenium, a mineral that supports the thyroid, the immune system and reproductive health – but too much can damage hair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Paul Farrant, consultant dermatologist at Experts In Skin And Hair, said: ‘The recommended dose of selenium can come from as little as one brazil nut a day. It’s easy to take too many. Selenium toxicity is linked to brittle hair and disturbs the hair cycle.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Warning over a sandwich favourite&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;T, particularly larger species such as yellowfin and bluefin, can contain mercury from feeding on contaminated prey. Mercury can damage the nervous system, the kidneys and even hair follicles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Farrant said: ‘It’s not something most of us eat in sufficient quantities to get toxicity, but you can get heavy metal poisoning from tuna. Hair needs good nutrition, and if you add things that are effectively poisons it will affect hair growth and cause hair loss.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;The best food for your hair? Eggs! &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;EGGS are among the best foods to nourish healthy locks. Packed with protein and key vitamins, they help keep hair strong and glossy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Farrant said: ‘If you eat lots of eggs, your hair will benefit. Hair is a protein-rich structure, based on keratin, which means you need plenty of protein in your diet to grow strong hair. Eggs are a great source of protein.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They are also high in vitamin B12 and folate, and are a source of vitamin D, which plays a vital role in the hair growth cycle. ‘If you’re deficient in vitamin D,’ he said, ‘more hairs exit the growing phase and move to the shedding phase.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And it doesn’t matter how you cook your eggs, your hair will still reap the rewards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox health" data-version="2" id="mol-04d50460-90a8-11f0-8dbe-d3916b45d4e7" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15094913/hair-loss-expert-food-never-eat-causes-balding.html"&gt; &lt;font&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;IT'S A FACT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;September is considered the worst month for hair shedding, which maybe related to temperature changes &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 16:38:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNTnFENzkwcVZEWlBTVUNCRG56MTZfTGpOU0RGOWRtbEY3ZEFFVkZWUFNOaVpJemFycmVTT2N4aGFLX1haWHhXVG9ISmJTNlowcG5kLVJNME45UERvZXlfbmhDdEJqVlZta2I3VXpmMlM5TFhEdGJxM2QyXzJOeFJ0YWFGZDRKT0hxbmVwbExUU1FaeXpOTkxubW11WU16R293aTJUSEp3</guid></item><item><title>由营养师制定的7天地中海饮食计划，促进肠道健康- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/7-day-mediterranean-diet-meal-plan-healthy-gut-11808952</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table"&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th colspan="3" class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__title"&gt;Meal Plan at a Glance&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;BREAKFAST/ A.M. SNACK&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;LUNCH/ P.M. SNACK&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;DINNER&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody data-check="0"&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Smoothie/ Blueberries &amp;amp; cashews&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tomato &amp;amp; cheese sandwich/ Hummus, cucumbers &amp;amp; walnuts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Shrimp quinoa bowls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Muffins &amp;amp; orange/ Yogurt&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Shrimp quinoa bowls/ Pear&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Salmon, sweet potatoes &amp;amp; broccoli&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Muffins, kefir &amp;amp; oranges/ Raspberries, cheese &amp;amp; nuts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Green goddess wrap/ Edamame&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Spaghetti squash casserole &amp;amp; broccoli&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Overnight oats/ Apple &amp;amp; walnuts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Power salad jar/ Muffin&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Lentil salad &amp;amp; chicken&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Overnight oats/ Banana &amp;amp; nut butter&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Lentil salad &amp;amp; tuna/ Almonds&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;BBQ shrimp, kale and couscous&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Omelet &amp;amp; English muffin/ Pear &amp;amp; almonds&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tempeh &amp;amp; rice bowls/ Crispy chickpeas&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Shakshuka &amp;amp; pita&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Egg scramble &amp;amp; raspberries/ Kefir, honey &amp;amp; chia&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Tofu wraps/ Crispy chickpeas&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Chicken ramen&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 1 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Charred Shrimp, Pesto &amp;amp; Quinoa Bowls.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (249 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (211 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;¾ cup blueberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 tablespoons unsalted roasted cashews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (439 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (163 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons hummus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 cup sliced cucumbers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons walnut halves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (429 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Meal-Prep Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Save a serving of the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/274095/charred-shrimp-pesto-quinoa-bowls/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Charred Shrimp, Pesto &amp;amp; Quinoa Bowls&lt;/a&gt; for lunch tomorrow.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,491 calories, 67 g protein, 168 g carbohydrates, 29 g fiber, 70 g fat, 1,397 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 2 hard-boiled eggs to breakfast, increase to 1 cup blueberries and ⅓ cup cashews at A.M. snack, increase to ¼ cup hummus and ¼ cup walnuts at P.M. snack and add 2 servings &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7917202/creamy-yogurt-dill-sauce/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Creamy Dill Yogurt Sauce&lt;/a&gt; to dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 2 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Banana Protein Muffins.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographer: Morgan Hunt Glaze, Prop Stylist: Priscilla Montiel, Food Stylist: Emily Nabors Hall&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (254 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (208 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (429 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (101 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (504 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,496 calories, 81 g protein, 177 g carbohydrates, 27 g fiber, 58 g fat, 1,533 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 2 hard-boiled eggs to breakfast, add ¼ cup slivered almonds to A.M. snack and add 2 ounces low-fat Cheddar cheese to P.M. snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 3 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Cucumber-Chicken Green Goddess Wrap.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Brie Passano&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (373 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (173 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 cup raspberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 ounce low-fat Cheddar cheese&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;3 tablespoons shelled pistachios&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (353 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (200 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (408 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,506 calories, 84 g protein, 164 g carbohydrates, 41 g fiber, 64 g fat, 1,916 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 2 scrambled eggs to breakfast, increase to 1½ cups raspberries at A.M. snack, add 2 servings &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7917202/creamy-yogurt-dill-sauce/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Creamy Dill Yogurt Sauce&lt;/a&gt; to lunch, increase to 2 cups edamame at P.M. snack and increase to 2 slices baguette at dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 4 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Lentil Salad with Feta, Tomatoes, Cucumbers &amp;amp; Olives.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Jennifer Causey&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (291 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (176 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 medium apple&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons walnut halves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (430 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_84-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (193 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_86-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_87-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (411 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_89-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_90-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Meal-Prep Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; Save a serving of the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7899362/lentil-salad-with-feta-tomatoes-cucumbers-olives/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lentil Salad with Feta, Tomatoes, Cucumbers &amp;amp; Olives&lt;/a&gt; for lunch tomorrow.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_91-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_92-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,501 calories, 80 g protein, 162 g carbohydrates, 26 g fiber, 63 g fat, 1,394 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_94-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 2 tablespoons peanut butter to breakfast, increase to ¼ cup walnuts at A.M. snack, add 1 ounce dark chocolate to P.M. snack and increase to 4 ounces chicken at dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_95-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_96-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 5 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_97-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;BBQ Shrimp with Garlicky Kale &amp;amp; Parmesan-Herb Couscous.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_98-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (291 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_100-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_101-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (210 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_102-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 medium banana&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 tablespoon peanut butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_103-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_104-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (368 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_106-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_107-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (206 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_108-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;¼ cup unsalted roasted almonds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_109-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_110-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (414 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_112-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_113-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,489 calories, 86 g protein, 147 g carbohydrates, 24 g fiber, 67 g fat, 1,580 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_114-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_115-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 2 tablespoons peanut butter to breakfast, add ½ whole-wheat pita to lunch, increase to 5 tablespoons almonds at P.M. snack and add 1 ounce dark chocolate to dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_116-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_117-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 6 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_118-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_6-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Green Shakshuka with Spinach, Chard &amp;amp; Feta.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_119-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (311 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_121-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_122-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (301 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_123-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;1 large pear&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;22 unsalted roasted almonds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_124-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_125-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (333 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_127-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_128-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (220 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_130-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_131-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (330 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_133-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_134-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,494 calories, 63 g protein, 168 g carbohydrates, 24 g fiber, 68 g fat, 2,384 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_135-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_136-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Increase to 1 whole English muffin at breakfast, add ½ cup kimchi and 2 tablespoons chopped peanuts to lunch, increase to 2 servings chickpeas at P.M. snack and increase to 1 whole pita at dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_137-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_138-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Day 7 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_139-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-square figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_7-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-text"&gt;Spinach &amp;amp; Egg Scramble with Raspberries.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;Jen Causey&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_140-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Breakfast (296 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_142-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_143-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Morning Snack (121 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_144-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;¾ cup low-fat plain kefir&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon chia seeds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon honey &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_145-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_146-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Lunch (488 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_147-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; 1 serving &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7886977/crispy-smoked-tofu-coleslaw-wraps/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Crispy Smoked Tofu &amp;amp; Coleslaw Wraps&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_148-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_149-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Afternoon Snack (220 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_151-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_152-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dinner (383 calories) &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_154-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_155-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Totals: &lt;/strong&gt;1,508 calories, 77 g protein, 141 g carbohydrates, 25 g fiber,  66 g fat, 2,473 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_156-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_157-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories: &lt;/strong&gt;Add 1 large banana to breakfast, increase to 1 cup kefir, 2 teaspoons chia seeds and 2 teaspoons honey at A.M. snack, increase to 2 servings chickpeas at P.M. snack and add 1 hard-boiled egg to dinner.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_158-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_160-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-dad3d770-b8f8-4a55-97cb-7e95810491d0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Is it OK to mix and match meals if there's one I don't like?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes! This meal plan is meant to serve as inspiration. It doesn’t need to be followed exactly to reap the benefits. When choosing recipes, we made sure to check the calories, fiber, protein and sodium to align with the parameters of this plan and be within our sodium limits. If you’re making a recipe swap, it may be helpful to choose a recipe with similar calories, fiber, protein and sodium levels. For more inspiration, check out these delicious &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/7965961/anti-inflammatory-mediterranean-diet-dinner-recipes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;anti-inflammatory Mediterranean meal recipes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can I eat the same breakfast or lunch every day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definitely, it’s fine to eat the same breakfast or lunch every day. The breakfasts range from 249 to 373 calories while the lunches span 333 to 488 calories. These ranges are fairly close, though if you’re closely monitoring your calories or other nutrients, like protein, you may want to adjust a snack or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Why is there not a modification for 1,200 calories?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We no longer provide modifications for 1,200-calorie days in our meal plans. The 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans suggests that limiting calories to 1,200 per day is too low for most people to meet their nutritional needs, plus it’s unsustainable for long-term health and well-being.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_161-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-health-benefits-of-a-gut-friendly-mediterranean-diet"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_162-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Health Benefits of a Gut-Friendly Mediterranean Diet &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_163-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The Mediterranean style of eating is marked by a diet that is high in fruits, vegetables, beans, lean proteins, nuts, seeds, with low to moderate intakes of dairy. It is typically low in saturated fat and added sugars and higher in fiber, antioxidants and omega-3 fatty acids. Years of research has concluded that following a Mediterranean-style eating pattern reduces the risk of obesity, heart disease, cancer, cognitive decline, metabolic syndrome and type 2 diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_164-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_165-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Having a healthy gut microbiome also has many of these same benefits. Data has shown that in addition to helping with constipation and digestion, good gut bacteria may help improve mood, sleep and heart health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Probiotics—fermented dairy, kimchi, sauerkraut—are foods that contain healthy gut bacteria, while prebiotics—onions, garlic, banana, lentils—are foods that feed good gut bacteria. Furthermore, both a healthy microbiome and the Mediterranean diet are associated with helping maintain a healthy weight.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_166-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_167-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;How We Create Meal Plans&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Registered dietitians thoughtfully create EatingWell’s meal plans to be easy-to-follow and delicious. Each meal plan meets specific parameters depending on the health condition and/or lifestyle goal it is targeting and is analyzed for accuracy using the nutrition database, ESHA Food Processor. As nutritional needs differ from person to person, we encourage you to use these plans as inspiration and adjust as you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNOU94RlVhTEwycjRiMHRPNXpzRlR5RkhUWFdnRjJtWTdSWmlBb0dGdkdyTHhjWUVHbDF0V3pYWS0yS1VmSXdwTjhlMVoweXNGRmdxMnpSam9pdHAtcGJvbzlabkE4Smc5ZHk0QzV0MGkwa0JQTHFJM0NYdGZhUGY3M0E3LU5NMmNuVGc</guid></item><item><title>地图显示世界上最致命的疾病在美国蔓延-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15082229/maps-reveal-deadliest-disease-tuberculosis-concerning-rise.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For thousands of years it was the biggest health threat in the world - killing actors, poets, kings and emperors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Previously called phthisis, consumption and even the White Plague, this deadly lung infection is today known as tuberculosis (TB).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Despite sweeping advances in medical care, the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/world-health-organization/index.html" id="mol-2962a5c0-8f28-11f0-9c9d-bbdf1d2c9bde" class=""&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; (WHO) still considers it the deadliest infectious disease on the planet, killing 1.25 million people in 2023 alone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;TB remains a relatively rare threat in the US, infecting several thousand of people annually and killing around 500 - far fewer than heart disease, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-686a67c0-8e7f-11f0-a059-89b046193d55"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; and dementia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, cases are on the rise in 80 percent of US states, and health officials nationwide are now sounding the alarm. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In September, three people i&lt;span&gt;n &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/maine/index.html" id="mol-250722d0-8e83-11f0-a059-89b046193d55" class=""&gt;Maine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;tested positive for active TB, which means the bacteria responsible for the disease, Mycobacterium tuberculosis, is building up in their lungs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Officials reported that there was no connection between the patients, suggesting they were all infected from different sources. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just days later, &lt;span&gt;Leesville Road High School in Raleigh, North Carolina, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15077125/Worlds-deadliest-disease-detected-Maine-spreading-reported-second-state.html"&gt;reported a TB case&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. It is unclear if the individual is a student or employee. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The lung infection tuberculosis is on the rise in the US, prompting urgent warnings from public health experts (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Meanwhile, Kansas health officials warned in January that the state was experiencing the &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14332367/Tuberculosis-outbreak-Kansas.html"&gt;'the largest documented outbreak in US history&lt;/a&gt;,' with 67 people infected with active TB since the start of 2024, according to the latest figures. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Raj Dasgupta, internal medicine physician and Chief Medical Advisor for Sleepopolis, told the Daily Mail: 'Without strong public-health action, we’ll probably continue to see elevated numbers.' &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Children, older adults and those with weaker immune systems are more vulnerable to the infection. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While the lung infection doesn't always cause symptoms (then called inactive TB), about half of people with untreated active infections will die.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the early stages, symptoms include a persistent and unexplained cough, sometimes coughing up blood or chest pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients may also suffer from unexplained weight loss, loss of appetite, fever and night sweats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In later stages, patients may have severe breathing difficulties and extensive lung damage, and the infection may spread to other organs or the back, causing pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Deaths are most often due to respiratory failure caused by bacterial damage to the lungs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Medical advancements like antibiotics have helped dramatically curb deaths.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Once killing as many as 20,000 Americans each year in the 1950s, according to data collected by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), deaths have declined to about 560 per year as of 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;TB was on a steady decline from 1993 until 2020, when the overall number of cases hit an all-time low of 7,170. But in 2021, that number jumped to 7,866.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prevalence has gone up every year since. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The latest CDC data shows the US provisionally recorded 10,347 TB cases in 2024 - up eight percent from the year before and the highest tally since 2011, when there were 10,471 cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured above are public health posters from the Work Projects Administration in the 1930s and '40s on getting tested for tuberculosis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Compared to 2014, cases nationwide are up 10 percent, CDC data shows.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And experts have warned it is not just one area responsible for the increase. According to the data, TB infections are on the rise in 40 US states and have only declined in 10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The District of Columbia is the only jurisdiction to report no change compared to 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Maine has reported 28 cases so far this year compared to 39 during all of 2024, which showed a 179 percent increase from the 14 cases in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;TB cases have risen the most - 187 percent - in Kansas compared to a decade ago. Maine has seen a rise of 179 percent from 2014 to 2024 (14 compared to 39, respectively), while North Carolina reported 250 cases last year compared to 195 in 2014 - a 22 percent increase. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;California reported the most cases in both 2014 (2,145) and 2024 (2,100), and Texas had the second most with 1,269 in 2014 and 1,238 in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In New York, the state with the third-highest prevalence, cases have surged 73 percent over the last decade. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Across Idaho, Vermont and Wyoming, cases are up 100 percent compared to 2014. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors and public health experts told the Daily Mail that the Covid pandemic is likely a main driver in TB's surge, especially considering cases started going up in 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In my opinion, early in the pandemic, a lot of clinics focused almost entirely on Covid, which meant TB testing and treatment often got pushed aside,' Dasgupta said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'At the same time, masks and social distancing probably helped slow TB spread for a while. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Now that most people aren’t masking, and with those earlier delays in diagnosis, we’re seeing cases rise again.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Mycobacterium tuberculosis bacteria, which cause tuberculosis, are pictured above (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The pandemic also forged a growing distrust of doctors and the medical establishment, which Dr Sharon Nachman, chief of pediatric infectious diseases at Stony Brook Children's Hospital, said has likely contributed to the rise of TB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One JAMA study found the public's general trust in physicians and hospitals dropped from 71.5 percent in April 2020 to 40 percent in January 2024. Experts have suggested the change is likely due to concerns over vaccine mandates and Big Pharma's financial gains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nachman told the Daily Mail: 'I believe the erosion of public health funding and the publicity around "medical myths" being true has led to people not seeing their medical providers and not following standard guidelines or even going back for follow-up care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This translates into poor care for our population and delays in preventing TB infection from progressing to TB disease (meaning intrathoracic or lung disease).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This delay then translates into a person having an easily treatable infection to having a disease that transmits to their family and friends, leading to more cases of TB.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The demographics of TB began to shift in 2001. That was the first year the CDC reported more non-US born citizen patients than US-born, meaning immigrants and travelers were the driving force behind infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dasgupta said international travel and migration play a role as many of those cases were linked to folks who had recently come from places where TB is more common. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured above is a chest X-ray showing signs of tuberculosis. Doctors told the Daily Mail that paying attention to early symptoms is key for preventing spread (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;International travel further surged starting around 2021, after the height of the Covid pandemic, which Nachman said could have further driven the increase as Americans ventured abroad and foreign relatives made Stateside visits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The longer you stay and come into contact with an infected adult, the more likely you are to get infected yourself,' Nachman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Still, infections are linked to significant, long-term exposure over months or years, so one international trip abroad likely is not enough to bring TB back to the states, she added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tuberculosis can be prevented with the Bacillus Calmette-Guerin (BCG) vaccine. Though, due to the generally low risk, it is not routinely offered in the US - except for to children regularly exposed to people with active TB or healthcare workers in areas with increased spread. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It’s not recommended here because of its variable effectiveness against adult pulmonary TB and because it can interfere with TB skin test results,' Dasgupta said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In developing countries, the vaccine is administered to children younger than 16. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As cases rise, Dasgupta urged Americans to 'pay attention to symptoms' before they progress so antibiotics can be administered and potential spread can slow.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If you’ve had a cough for more than a couple weeks, or unexplained weight loss, fevers, or night sweats, get checked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'And if you are diagnosed, stick with treatment until the end. Stopping early can lead to drug resistance.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 14:47:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxPNGdiVExUdHdINk1hdXNJdnlkelYybDZtU3h2b0JqZ29vMDd5Vk01aFg3ZGZaV0JKUEpoaGVsMVcwWFlHbkRqZmxEV2JldWx0dXhPVFBaWkFrNkpObjNjclJHRElIVUhwMDZMbEVLcERDbDc5YVZyR2EzWl9Da0lxZ0I5aTJnZzhzWkI2MHl6NE5MdGZTQ2ZnRm5hcm9CWDdDNmpoZ1p0ZFlWeDR4R1R3TUFFZzZUZw</guid></item><item><title>7岁时的单个数据点可以预测您的寿命- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/a-single-data-point-at-age-7-could-predict-how-long-youll-live</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Researchers have found that one key health reading taken at the age of 7 could have a significant impact on the risk of dying of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-heart-is-vulnerable-these-4-things-will-help-you-protect-it"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt; (CVD) decades later: blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a new study carried out by researchers from institutions across the US, children with elevated blood pressure (in the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Percentile"&gt;90 to 94th percentile&lt;/a&gt;) or hypertension (in the 95th percentile or above) were some 40 to 50 percent more likely to meet an early death because of CVD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We were surprised to find that high blood pressure in childhood was linked to serious health conditions many years later," &lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/higher-blood-pressure-in-childhood-linked-to-earlier-death-from-heart-disease-in-adulthood"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; epidemiologist Alexa Freedman, from Northwestern University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-simple-daily-habit-could-help-lower-your-blood-pressure"&gt;A Simple Daily Habit Could Help Lower Your Blood Pressure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's a big jump in risk, but it's helpful to put these figures into some context. The researchers analyzed medical data collected on 37,081 children born in the US between 1959 and 1965, including a reading of their &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-how-much-exercise-you-need-weekly-to-control-your-blood-pressure"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; at age 7. A follow-up survey was conducted decades later, in their early fifties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out of the tens of thousands of individuals in the sample, nearly 500 died of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-gram-of-salt-is-the-difference-for-millions-of-heart-attacks"&gt;cardiovascular diseases&lt;/a&gt;, including a number without high blood pressure, so we're not talking about huge numbers overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood pressure was only measured once at age 7 rather than being monitored throughout the lives of the participants, further limiting the reliability of any conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_173638" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-173638" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/HeartChart.jpg" alt="Heart health chart" class="wp-image-173638 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/HeartChart.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/HeartChart-582x415.jpg 582w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/HeartChart-600x428.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-173638" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers charted heart-related deaths against blood pressure. The blue line represents typical blood pressure, the orange line represents elevated blood pressure, and the black line represents hypertension. (Freedman et al., &lt;em&gt;JAMA&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the increase in mortality risk is notable enough to make the findings worthy of future investigation, highlighting the importance of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-common-heart-drug-taken-by-millions-may-often-be-useless-or-even-risky"&gt;cardiovascular health&lt;/a&gt; even at a very young age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"High blood pressure in children can have serious consequences throughout their lives," &lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/higher-blood-pressure-in-childhood-linked-to-earlier-death-from-heart-disease-in-adulthood"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Freedman. "It is crucial to be aware of your child's blood pressure readings."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A host of factors contribute to CVD, so it's worth noting that 359 of the individuals studied were from families that had multiple children involved in the research. The results among children with the same family background were similar to the overall figures, suggesting that blood pressure is key &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/research-shows-one-easy-diet-swap-can-reduce-blood-pressure-and-heart-attacks"&gt;rather than diet&lt;/a&gt; or living environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further studies could take into account additional influences on CVD risk, such as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/poor-oral-hygiene-could-be-taking-a-toll-on-your-heart-expert-says"&gt;oral hygiene&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-depressions-genetic-link-to-heart-disease-in-women"&gt;genetic factors&lt;/a&gt;, investigating factors that might have an early impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood pressure data for this study had been gathered in the 1950s and 1960s – children today likely face different pressures in terms of their health and well-being. Studies have shown that exercise, diet, and stress &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/7-things-you-can-do-right-now-to-reduce-your-risk-of-high-blood-pressure"&gt;can all play a part&lt;/a&gt; in blood pressure readings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings are presented in a research letter, which provides a very brief summary of the study. However, it highlights another strong link between &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/chronic-conditions-in-children-have-surged-dramatically-in-20-years"&gt;childhood health&lt;/a&gt; and adult health, which gives us opportunities to get good health and habits in place early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as heightening the risk of CVD, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/us-has-new-guidelines-for-high-blood-pressure-heres-what-that-means"&gt;high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; has been linked to kidney disease, vision loss, sexual dysfunction, and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Atherosclerosis"&gt;atherosclerosis&lt;/a&gt;, where potentially harmful plaque builds up in the arteries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our results highlight the importance of screening for blood pressure in childhood and focusing on strategies to promote optimal cardiovascular health beginning in childhood," &lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/higher-blood-pressure-in-childhood-linked-to-earlier-death-from-heart-disease-in-adulthood?preview=bde4&amp;amp;preview_mode=True"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Freedman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research abstract has been published in &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1001/jama.2025.14405"&gt;&lt;em&gt;JAMA&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 13:02:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQOXM4UWlvTmNtd0JGeUZpQmx0akE1UEIyT0FhdElaekpRY0FQbElxU1R6Y1pnZFVoRUdpV2RNSThZMXFmWGd4XzBlSm5TR2tUc095dGdkVkpHVkVxOGVnemc5MmxkZWY2SUhuTmZibXQwUnZhSm80WkZjR2dSNFl5QTV3Vm92ZUoxNUVZWHZ4Q1B4TV9sV1E</guid></item><item><title>周六引用：肝衰竭的机制；观察到LIGO黑洞踢；原始黑洞爆炸- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2025-09-saturday-citations-mechanism-liver-failure.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
										
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/saturday-citations-a-m.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/saturday-citations-a-m.jpg" data-sub-html="Illustration of the merger of two black holes and the gravitational waves they generate. Credit: Galician Institute of High Energy Physics"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/saturday-citations-a-m.jpg" alt="Saturday Citations: A mechanism for liver failure; LIGO black hole kick observed; Primordial black hole explosions" title="Illustration of the merger of two black holes and the gravitational waves they generate. Credit: Galician Institute of High Energy Physics"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Illustration of the merger of two black holes and the gravitational waves they generate. Credit: Galician Institute of High Energy Physics
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week, researchers reported on a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-blood-hpv-neck-cancers-years.html" target="_blank"&gt;new biopsy tool&lt;/a&gt; that can detect HPV-associated head and neck cancer up to 10 years before symptoms appear. Researchers developed a process to transform two-dimensional paintings into &lt;a href="https://techxplore.com/news/2025-09-technology-holograms-art-life.html" target="_blank"&gt;full-color, three-dimensional holograms&lt;/a&gt;, providing a new way to experience art in a gallery setting. And Chinese scientists designed a physical cassette capable of storing massive amounts of data &lt;a href="https://techxplore.com/news/2025-09-dna-cassette-tapes-global-storage.html" target="_blank"&gt;encoded as DNA&lt;/a&gt; on a polyester-nylon tape substrate.&lt;/p&gt;


										      
																																	&lt;h2&gt;Pour one out for the liver&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey, it's the weekend, time to lounge around in comfortable trackwear and toss back a tall cold one, even though a new study by researchers at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign and collaborators found that tall cold ones can disrupt the regenerative abilities of the only human organ that regenerates—the liver. Specifically, &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-09-chronic-alcohol-halts-liver-cell.html" target="_blank"&gt;the study&lt;/a&gt; concludes that &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/excessive+alcohol+consumption/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;excessive alcohol consumption&lt;/a&gt; can trap liver cells in a state between their functional and regenerative modes, the result of inflammation that disrupts RNA splicing during the protein-making process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Auinash Kalsotra, who co-led the study, says, "We knew that the liver stops functioning and stops regenerating in patients with alcohol-related hepatitis and cirrhosis, even when a patient has discontinued consuming alcohol, but we didn't know why… The only real life-saving treatment option once a patient reaches the liver failure stage in those diseases is transplantation. But if we understood why these livers were failing, maybe we could intervene." The researchers hope to use misspliced RNAs as diagnostic markers for disease and to develop treatments that curb liver inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;

																																						&lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
    
     
&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="8188791252"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
																																			&lt;h2&gt;Phenomenon observed&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks to advanced instruments like the James Webb Space Telescope and the Laser Interferometer Gravitational-Wave Observatory, astronomy and astrophysics are enjoying a renaissance of entirely new discoveries, often upending longstanding theories about the origin and evolution of the universe. This isn't hyperbole—while Webb has revealed a proliferation of objects in the ancient universe called "little red dots," which may be weird early galaxies or could instead be a newly theorized object called a "black hole star," LIGO has been providing three-dimensional data on massive gravitational collisions with increasingly high resolution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LIGO detects &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/gravitational+waves/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;gravitational waves&lt;/a&gt;, ripples in the fabric of spacetime that encode information about their sources. Usually, these sources are black holes. Since 2015, the observatory has recorded over 300 collisions of black holes. When a black hole pair merges, the newly combined object creates a massive recoil, emitting gravitational waves unevenly, an imbalance in which a black hole remnant blob kicks away at thousands of kilometers per second.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An international research team has made the &lt;a href="https://phys.org/news/2025-08-black-hole-recoil-gravitational.html"&gt;first measurement&lt;/a&gt; of the speed and direction of a recoiling black hole that resulted from a merger detected in 2019. It kicked away at speeds more than 50 kilometers per second, escaping its globular cluster, and the researchers measured its recoil direction with respect to Earth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Koustav Chandra, a researcher at Penn State, says, "This is one of the few phenomena in astrophysics where we're not just detecting something—we're reconstructing the full 3D motion of an object that's billions of light-years away, using only ripples in spacetime. It's a remarkable demonstration of what gravitational waves can do."&lt;/p&gt;

																									&lt;div class="ads w-100 my-4 article-main__more bg-light p-3 border" aria-hidden="true"&gt;
    &lt;p class="mb-3"&gt;
        Discover the latest in science, tech, and space with over &lt;strong&gt;100,000 subscribers&lt;/strong&gt; who rely on Phys.org for daily insights.
        Sign up for our &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/newsletter/" target="_blank"&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; and get updates on breakthroughs,
        innovations, and research that matter—&lt;strong&gt;daily or weekly&lt;/strong&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;/div&gt;
																																			&lt;h2&gt;Phenomenon theorized&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There's a longstanding theory that primordial black holes explode at the end of their lives. But this would only occur about once every 100,000 years. A &lt;a href="https://phys.org/news/2025-09-black-hole-reveal-foundations-universe.html"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; by physicists at the University of Massachusetts Amherst finds that these may instead occur once every 10 years, and that there's a better than 90% probability that such an explosion could be observed within the decade. The study recommends that astronomers begin preparing now to make the observation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The detection of an exploding black hole would represent confirmation of the existence of &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/primordial+black+holes/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;primordial black holes&lt;/a&gt;, which physicists believe formed in the extraordinarily dense universe less than one second after the Big Bang. Unlike &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/black+holes/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;black holes&lt;/a&gt; in the contemporary universe, these were not formed by the collapse of a large object like a star, but by the very conditions that prevailed in the moments after the Big Bang.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The measurements of such an explosion would provide a definitive catalog of all existing subatomic particles, possibly including those that are completely unknown to science. Researcher Iguaz Juan says, "This would be the first-ever direct observation of both Hawking radiation and a PBH. We would also get a definitive record of every particle that makes up everything in the universe. It would completely revolutionize physics and help us rewrite the history of the universe."&lt;/p&gt;

																																	
																					&lt;div class="article-main__support"&gt;
												    &lt;p&gt;
    Written for you by our author &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/editorial-team/#authors" target="_blank"&gt;Chris Packham&lt;/a&gt;, edited by &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/editorial-team/" target="_blank"&gt;Lisa Lock&lt;/a&gt;, and fact-checked and reviewed by &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/editorial-team/" target="_blank"&gt;Robert Egan&lt;/a&gt;—this article is the result of careful human work. We rely on readers like you to keep independent science journalism alive.
    If this reporting matters to you,
    please consider a &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/donate/?utm_source=story&amp;amp;utm_medium=story&amp;amp;utm_campaign=story"&gt;donation&lt;/a&gt; (especially monthly).
    You'll get an &lt;b&gt;ad-free&lt;/b&gt; account as a thank-you.
    &lt;/p&gt;

											&lt;/div&gt;
																														
																					
																															 &lt;p class="article-main__note mt-4"&gt;
												  © 2025 Science X Network
											 &lt;/p&gt;
										                                        
										
										&lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
											 &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
												&lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
												Saturday Citations: A mechanism for liver failure; LIGO black hole kick observed; primordial black hole explosions (2025, September 13)
												retrieved 13 September 2025
												from https://phys.org/news/2025-09-saturday-citations-mechanism-liver-failure.html
											 &lt;/p&gt;
											 &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
											 This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
											 part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
											 &lt;/p&gt;
										&lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQLXZFbXdZRGdGZTh6Vy1wYjRsT3JoWHY5RlhCUE9ka3N2VFV4cHR6WHpyUVUzeWpfY01FQ09fdU0xNl9kWmU0X1VIQTg1SUhVT0JrdFNYdTVJN1cyS3VZc2hpV2dmemtDOW8zdmZqZjNHVkt0aGcyNjRLc0VVLS1RaHR1RQ</guid></item><item><title>我们向注册营养师询问了内脏脂肪损失的最佳茶-他们都选择了相同的- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/the-best-tea-for-visceral-fat-loss-11803907</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drinking green tea regularly may support metabolic health and reduce visceral fat.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Swap sugary drinks for green tea to help maintain a calorie deficit needed for fat loss.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To support visceral fat loss, exercise regularly, limit alcohol, manage stress and get enough sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Not all body fat is the same—and the one you really need to pay attention to is visceral fat. “Visceral fat is the fat that’s stored deep inside your abdomen, surrounding your organs like your liver, stomach and intestines,” explains &lt;a href="https://www.nutritionnowcounseling.com/about-1" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lauren Manaker, M.S., RDN, LD&lt;/a&gt;. Unlike subcutaneous fat, which lies just beneath the skin, visceral fat isn’t visible—but it poses greater health risks, including a higher likelihood of heart disease and type 2 diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The good news? Visceral fat responds well to lifestyle changes like diet and exercise.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The bad news? There’s no quick fix to magically melt it away overnight. That said, there are foods and beverages that may &lt;em&gt;support&lt;/em&gt; visceral fat loss, such as tea. When we asked dietitians which tea is best to help lose visceral fat, their answer was unanimous: green tea. Keep reading to learn the science behind green tea and how it may support visceral fat loss.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-benefits-of-green-tea"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Benefits of Green Tea &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; May Reduce Risk of Metabolic Syndrome &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Metabolic syndrome is a group of conditions that increase your &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/american-heart-association-redefined-heart-disease-risk-2023-8356291" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;risk of heart disease, diabetes and stroke&lt;/a&gt;. It’s defined as having three or more of the following conditions:&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Abdominal/central obesity (excess fat around the stomach area)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High blood pressure (hypertension)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High blood sugar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High triglycerides&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Low HDL (“good”) cholesterol&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Addressing metabolic syndrome is crucial for your health, and often involves reducing visceral fat. Fortunately, some research suggests that &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-tea-for-metabolic-syndrome-8782901" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;drinking green tea may support its management&lt;/a&gt;. Green tea contains catechins, including epigallocatechin gallate (EGCG), which may improve insulin sensitivity and reduce LDL (“bad”) cholesterol and blood pressure. As metabolic syndrome improves, the body’s ability to mobilize and burn visceral fat also increases.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although promising, not all research shows a strong link between green tea consumption and improvements in metabolic syndrome, so more studies are needed. Still, given its beneficial properties, regularly drinking it is a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/drink-to-limit-to-live-longer-11708703" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;healthier alternative to sugary beverages&lt;/a&gt; or energy drinks.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; May Support Weight Loss &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Research on &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-drink-for-weight-loss-11746010" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;green tea and weight loss&lt;/a&gt; often examines overall body fat rather than visceral fat specifically. However, some evidence suggests that components of green tea—especially catechins and caffeine—may help reduce fat around the midsection, where visceral fat is more concentrated, explains &lt;a href="https://sproutoutloud.com/about/#meet-ali" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Ali McGowan, M.S., RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Green tea contains compounds called catechins, which may help improve how your body uses energy,” she adds. It’s thought that these compounds can affect fat metabolism, contributing to weight loss. For instance, some observational research suggests people who regularly drink green tea alongside other healthy lifestyle habits tend to see greater &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-to-lose-body-fat-8619424" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;total fat loss&lt;/a&gt; compared to non-tea drinkers.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  Beyond this,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;most other&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;studies focus on green tea extract—a highly concentrated source of catechins—rather than the brewed beverage, making it difficult to know the true effects of drinking green tea on weight loss and whether these effects would be clinically meaningful.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, while it’s uncertain if green tea—particularly the brewed variety—directly promotes visceral fat loss, it may support fat loss by reducing calorie intake. If you typically drink calorie-dense, sugary drinks, swapping them for green tea can be an easy way to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/291208/7-day-sugar-detox-meal-plan-1500-calories/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;cut calories and sugar&lt;/a&gt;, which could support a calorie deficit needed for weight loss.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; May Lower Inflammation &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Multiple factors, including visceral fat and body weight, can &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-inflammation-8766645" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;drive inflammation in the body&lt;/a&gt;, which plays a role in the development of chronic diseases like type 2 diabetes and heart disease. Green tea catechins, such as EGCG, may help counter this process by boosting antioxidant levels in the body, McGowan explains.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For example, one study found that consuming 1 to 4 cups of green tea daily was linked with a decreased risk of heart disease, which the authors attributed to green tea’s anti-inflammatory properties.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Green tea’s potential role in reducing visceral fat may add to this benefit, since visceral fat is metabolically active and releases pro-inflammatory molecules. In turn, reducing visceral fat can &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/80991/10-ways-to-reduce-inflammation/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;improve inflammatory markers&lt;/a&gt; tied to metabolic syndrome and other chronic conditions.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; May Reduce Insulin Resistance &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Insulin resistance occurs when the body’s cells become less sensitive to insulin, the hormone that helps move glucose into cells for energy. Although many factors contribute, excess visceral fat plays a major role. In visceral fat tissue, insulin resistance disrupts normal glucose removal and promotes chronic, low-grade inflammation, leading to abnormal fat distribution and impaired metabolism.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Fortunately, green tea consumption may counter these effects. One meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials in individuals with type 2 diabetes found that green tea consumption improved fasting glucose, hemoglobin A1c and HOMA-IR levels—a marker of insulin resistance.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; By &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/lifestyle-tweaks-healthy-blood-sugar-levels-11792895" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;supporting blood sugar regulation&lt;/a&gt; and lowering inflammation, green tea may improve overall metabolic health, including the management of visceral fat.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-strategies-to-lose-visceral-fat"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Other Strategies to Lose Visceral Fat &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although green tea may help support visceral fat loss, the most effective approach is a balanced lifestyle rather than relying on one food, nutrient or activity. Here are some other strategies to help lose visceral fat:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strength-Train.&lt;/strong&gt; Strength training helps your body build muscle, which supports a healthy metabolism and body composition.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Having more muscle mass can slightly increase resting energy expenditure. “Over time, this makes it easier to tap into stored fat, including the deeper fat around your organs,” says McGowan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do Cardio. &lt;/strong&gt;Cardio exercise not only supports a healthy cardiovascular system, but it has also been linked to meaningful weight and fat loss. Combining this with strength training provides a well-rounded approach to fitness.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat Enough Protein.&lt;/strong&gt; Consuming enough protein promotes muscle growth and keeps you full, which can support a healthy body composition and prevent overeating. Some research has also linked high-protein diets with a reduction in visceral fat, though higher-quality studies are still needed.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get Enough Sleep.&lt;/strong&gt; “Poor sleep can increase stress hormones like cortisol, which may encourage visceral fat storage,” notes Manaker. Additionally, inadequate sleep can affect appetite, which may lead to poorer food choices and contribute to the accumulation of visceral fat over time.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot-inline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage Stress.&lt;/strong&gt; Stress-management techniques, such as journaling, movement, deep breathing, yoga and meditation, may contribute to reducing visceral fat. “Chronic stress may lead to higher cortisol levels, which are linked to visceral fat,” explains Manaker.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skip the Added Sugar.&lt;/strong&gt; Green tea is a great beverage choice, but adding excess sugar to it may negate some of its health benefits, warns Manaker. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limit or Avoid Alcohol. &lt;/strong&gt;Drinking alcohol too often or in excess is associated with greater visceral fat storage and poorer metabolic health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There’s no single magic fix to melting away visceral fat, but adding green tea to your daily routine may give you an extra edge. Thanks to its antioxidant-rich compounds, green tea shows promise in supporting metabolic health, including improving insulin resistance and reducing visceral fat—though more research is needed to confirm its exact role. The good news? Green tea is a safe, health-supporting beverage that most people can enjoy daily. When paired with a well-rounded lifestyle, this can be a great tool to help reduce visceral fat.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE1KRmxoRk1aMWJnekdyOXB1S1RJQ0FoRE84ZzVKMWxjalJNa2M2UGxPT1RCZUdHRDhqSDdTSFVCQ1JGZXpRcmdGc09rZVI4dDE5TXl0UXE0UERXV1c3NGRaZE90SUgzOTR6YkxrcGdDcDN5dkE3MHFZbVBn</guid></item><item><title>一个年轻的妈妈如何在被诊断出无法治愈的癌症后“活着，而不仅仅是活着” - CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elissa-kalver-her2-positive-metastatic-breast-cancer-memorial-sloan-kettering-ucla/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Elissa Kalver was 34 when she found a lump in her breast. She had no family history of cancer and had just welcomed her first child. She assumed the lump was a cyst. But when she went to get it checked out, doctors found another lump in her armpit. Biopsies found that both lumps were malignant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More tests found the situation was worse than she could have imagined: a PET scan found cancer in her lower spine and liver. She was diagnosed with HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer. Diseases that have spread as far as Kalver's are considered incurable, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/25213-her2-positive-breast-cancer" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was told I wasn't going to die tomorrow, but I was told that there was an 80% chance that I would die within five years," Kalver said. "The first oncologist I had, to uplift me, was like, 'Well, I have some patients who are six, seven years out.' Hearing that, as a 34-year-old, that your hope is to live till 40, was crazy." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new mom had to quickly adjust to her new reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/783f1f4b-7ddb-43d6-836d-6b1115e2d62b/thumbnail/620x620/5a7291772e9ff221a85155b53223e551/2b87d1dd-e5c0-4abd-97df-40859d4d9dd1.jpg#" alt="2b87d1dd-e5c0-4abd-97df-40859d4d9dd1.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/783f1f4b-7ddb-43d6-836d-6b1115e2d62b/thumbnail/620x620/5a7291772e9ff221a85155b53223e551/2b87d1dd-e5c0-4abd-97df-40859d4d9dd1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/783f1f4b-7ddb-43d6-836d-6b1115e2d62b/thumbnail/1240x1240/9a586d17389a37cbb29fe96c8ded8113/2b87d1dd-e5c0-4abd-97df-40859d4d9dd1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver and her daughter shortly after her diagnosis. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Elissa Kalver

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In my head, I was like, I know other people who have gone through this, I'll cut off my breasts, whatever we have to do to get rid of it," Kalver, now 38, said. "And it was after the PET scan, I understood that I didn't understand. It really shifted to trying to understand that I'm essentially a cancer patient for the rest of my life." &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What is HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer is an aggressive and fast-growing form of breast cancer that is considered incurable but treatable. Patients with HER2-positive breast cancer have high levels of human epidermal growth factor receptor 2, or HER2, a protein that manages how cells grow and divide, according to the Cleveland Clinic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prognosis and treatment of HER2-positive breast cancer vary depending on when it is diagnosed and the spread of the disease at the time. Patients who are diagnosed before the cancer spreads have a 97% five-year survival rate. For patients like Kalver, the five-year survival rate drops to 39%, according to the Cleveland Clinic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/d42fb43c-1843-4088-814d-3505b9aab742/thumbnail/620x827/10efbb5db9aab119fa41434e1fea2a6c/img-3346.jpg#" alt="img-3346.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/d42fb43c-1843-4088-814d-3505b9aab742/thumbnail/620x827/10efbb5db9aab119fa41434e1fea2a6c/img-3346.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/d42fb43c-1843-4088-814d-3505b9aab742/thumbnail/1240x1654/952bd0ffd333aeb808fa4fae3ee60590/img-3346.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver, her daughter and her husband shortly after her diagnosis.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Elissa Kalver

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medical advances are continually improving the prognosis, according to Dr. Shari Goldfarb, an oncologist at Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center who leads the hospital's Young Women with Breast Cancer center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Over the past 10 to 15 years, we've developed so many new medications that target the HER2 receptor, and that significantly improves the outcome of women diagnosed with HER2-positive disease. It used to be one of the worst and most aggressive subtypes of cancer," Goldfarb said. "Many women are living years and even decades now with metastatic HER2-positive breast cancer." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Treating HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treating the disease requires constant surveillance, Goldfarb said. A patient like Kalver gets scans every three to four months. If their cancer is stable or improving, they will continue their current treatment. If the disease is progressing, the treatment would need to be changed, Goldfarb said. Doctors also need to consider a patient's quality of life and treatment side effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Generally, the principle is to give people the best quality of life possible for as long as possible," Goldfarb said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kalver sought treatment at the UCLA Health Jonsson Comprehensive Cancer Center. Her first treatment was an aggressive course of chemotherapy. Over the past four years, she has participated in multiple clinical trials and undergone several different forms of treatment, according to her oncologist, Dr. Marla Lipsyc-Sharf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/da17038e-8e81-46c1-a46b-94d3c6fc708e/thumbnail/620x413/fde445a243debeeea8b84799c2e64e20/elissachemo-11192021-0051.jpg#" alt="Elissa Chemo " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/da17038e-8e81-46c1-a46b-94d3c6fc708e/thumbnail/620x413/fde445a243debeeea8b84799c2e64e20/elissachemo-11192021-0051.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/da17038e-8e81-46c1-a46b-94d3c6fc708e/thumbnail/1240x826/bc418237ca515bb25116cfb38f365188/elissachemo-11192021-0051.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver undergoes chemotherapy. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Billye Brenneisen

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About a year after her diagnosis, doctors found the cancer had spread to Kalver's brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I always thought tumors in your brain, like, 'That's it,'" Kalver said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a targeted chemotherapy that crossed the blood-brain barrier to attack the tumors. The masses were reduced by about 80%, Kalver said, and they have not grown in the past three years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatments have taken their toll, Kalver said. One chemotherapy made her so nauseous that "it was hard to be awake," Kalver said. Another caused her to lose her hair, which Kalver worried would alarm her then 1-year-old daughter. Sharf said other treatments caused Kalver to experience symptoms including bone pain, muscle pain and a bleeding rash. Each time the side effects have become too intense, Sharf works to recalibrate Kalver's treatment. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, Kalver is receiving chemotherapy infusions every three weeks and takes an oral medication twice a day. The treatment caused her to become "a bit anemic," which recently required a blood transfusion, but otherwise, things are going well, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"After being on chemo for four years, I've really learned that we have to prioritize living, not just surviving," Kalver said. "I feel really grateful to still be on chemo treatments that work." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/edfa1049-ea6d-46f4-a92a-88ea95710df9/thumbnail/620x411/23c7c16d182a9ca296416aee27a9b6f5/216c-02-0180-epines-elissakalver-20240919.jpg#" alt="216c-02-0180-epines-elissakalver-20240919.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/edfa1049-ea6d-46f4-a92a-88ea95710df9/thumbnail/620x411/23c7c16d182a9ca296416aee27a9b6f5/216c-02-0180-epines-elissakalver-20240919.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/edfa1049-ea6d-46f4-a92a-88ea95710df9/thumbnail/1240x822/de74815a6ae914c6169bf952704cba8a/216c-02-0180-epines-elissakalver-20240919.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver in her "We Got This" home office. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Ethan Pines

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;"Living like I'm alive"  &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kalver may spend the rest of her life on chemotherapy or other treatments. She, and many other HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer patients, may never enter a remission or see no evidence of disease on their scans. She did ring the bell after finishing her first course of chemotherapy, taking part in a ritual many cancer patients use to mark the end of their treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I thought about it a lot going into it, because I was like, 'I'm not done with treatment, but I'm done with this treatment. And this treatment was pretty hard, and I deserve to ring that bell,'" Kalver recalled. "I rang it so hard that I actually broke the bell." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then, Kalver has developed other ways to mark important milestones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every year, she celebrates what she calls a "cancerversary," honoring the day she was diagnosed. For her first "cancerversary," Kalver launched "We Got This," the first nonprofit gift registry for cancer patients. Since then, she has written a book, become a professional speaker and worked to educate other patients about the reality of participating in clinical trials. In July, Kalver will celebrate her fifth "cancerversary." She's still mulling over how to celebrate the "big milestone." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/0e1d5623-a00d-4ccc-9566-3b4640d360a0/thumbnail/620x465/3d9619b199dcce730228ad28186076c8/img-9471.jpg#" alt="img-9471.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/0e1d5623-a00d-4ccc-9566-3b4640d360a0/thumbnail/620x465/3d9619b199dcce730228ad28186076c8/img-9471.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/0e1d5623-a00d-4ccc-9566-3b4640d360a0/thumbnail/1240x930/eed57119f41188742a72a0be8dce6c70/img-9471.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver poses with her book during a chemotherapy infusion.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Elissa Kalver

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she's not busy with work and advocacy, she spends time with her daughter, now 4, and her husband. Living life to the fullest is a priority, she said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc5" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",5]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I want to live as long as I can with the best quality of life that I can, making the biggest impact that I can," Kalver said. "I do all the things, and I really make an effort at living like I'm alive." &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
                  
    

    



    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 12:00:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxPVmNhMGRya203WTF2Z1djcGJ5TDNOTDlPYUJEREFrQ3hYVDhjM3F6SFJrU3VSUmVFbG54YVVrVWtucTZuRDc5QU1tZVVGQ1ZNN3JKR0p1Q0d2X21yQjFNLVNwcDE2Y2lEejhMRWd2MHVYSjliUDRUZWVZUzdvSTktamd1SjRkS1RGWjIxR2N1OVd6Vi00NV84N01yRXhYeGRWeGNmVXgzZ2pWVURtYkhlNU930gG3AUFVX3lxTE9zbDB1b01EWFdGeHI2M21GbGdJQUZuTUFlQXg2d0dvb25GS3hESjdUb2RSVEk3MUNMMVpxOUFVLU81QnBrTTEzclVmQzRHemlXQ1ZmSjduU3hrcW9RV1hjclctSmhPUy1XSVl5ZDdaZVdSSGJJRzhHODlBcld2aU9QaERWVGFXOG9ibk9taGFLdU1vMGpnQkh1d2FsTmswMUIxOThMRUdBY2lhbGlhMXRtNlNVUUk1OA</guid></item><item><title>一个年轻的妈妈如何在被诊断出无法治愈的癌症后“活着，而不仅仅是活着” - CBS新闻</title><link>http://www.cbsnews.com/news/elissa-kalver-her2-positive-metastatic-breast-cancer-memorial-sloan-kettering-ucla/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Elissa Kalver was 34 when she found a lump in her breast. She had no family history of cancer and had just welcomed her first child. She assumed the lump was a cyst. But when she went to get it checked out, doctors found another lump in her armpit. Biopsies found that both lumps were malignant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More tests found the situation was worse than she could have imagined: a PET scan found cancer in her lower spine and liver. She was diagnosed with HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer. Diseases that have spread as far as Kalver's are considered incurable, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/25213-her2-positive-breast-cancer" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was told I wasn't going to die tomorrow, but I was told that there was an 80% chance that I would die within five years," Kalver said. "The first oncologist I had, to uplift me, was like, 'Well, I have some patients who are six, seven years out.' Hearing that, as a 34-year-old, that your hope is to live till 40, was crazy." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new mom had to quickly adjust to her new reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/783f1f4b-7ddb-43d6-836d-6b1115e2d62b/thumbnail/620x620/5a7291772e9ff221a85155b53223e551/2b87d1dd-e5c0-4abd-97df-40859d4d9dd1.jpg#" alt="2b87d1dd-e5c0-4abd-97df-40859d4d9dd1.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/783f1f4b-7ddb-43d6-836d-6b1115e2d62b/thumbnail/620x620/5a7291772e9ff221a85155b53223e551/2b87d1dd-e5c0-4abd-97df-40859d4d9dd1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/783f1f4b-7ddb-43d6-836d-6b1115e2d62b/thumbnail/1240x1240/9a586d17389a37cbb29fe96c8ded8113/2b87d1dd-e5c0-4abd-97df-40859d4d9dd1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver and her daughter shortly after her diagnosis. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Elissa Kalver

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In my head, I was like, I know other people who have gone through this, I'll cut off my breasts, whatever we have to do to get rid of it," Kalver, now 38, said. "And it was after the PET scan, I understood that I didn't understand. It really shifted to trying to understand that I'm essentially a cancer patient for the rest of my life." &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What is HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer is an aggressive and fast-growing form of breast cancer that is considered incurable but treatable. Patients with HER2-positive breast cancer have high levels of human epidermal growth factor receptor 2, or HER2, a protein that manages how cells grow and divide, according to the Cleveland Clinic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prognosis and treatment of HER2-positive breast cancer vary depending on when it is diagnosed and the spread of the disease at the time. Patients who are diagnosed before the cancer spreads have a 97% five-year survival rate. For patients like Kalver, the five-year survival rate drops to 39%, according to the Cleveland Clinic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/d42fb43c-1843-4088-814d-3505b9aab742/thumbnail/620x827/10efbb5db9aab119fa41434e1fea2a6c/img-3346.jpg#" alt="img-3346.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/d42fb43c-1843-4088-814d-3505b9aab742/thumbnail/620x827/10efbb5db9aab119fa41434e1fea2a6c/img-3346.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/d42fb43c-1843-4088-814d-3505b9aab742/thumbnail/1240x1654/952bd0ffd333aeb808fa4fae3ee60590/img-3346.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver, her daughter and her husband shortly after her diagnosis.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Elissa Kalver

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Medical advances are continually improving the prognosis, according to Dr. Shari Goldfarb, an oncologist at Memorial Sloan Kettering Cancer Center who leads the hospital's Young Women with Breast Cancer center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Over the past 10 to 15 years, we've developed so many new medications that target the HER2 receptor, and that significantly improves the outcome of women diagnosed with HER2-positive disease. It used to be one of the worst and most aggressive subtypes of cancer," Goldfarb said. "Many women are living years and even decades now with metastatic HER2-positive breast cancer." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Treating HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treating the disease requires constant surveillance, Goldfarb said. A patient like Kalver gets scans every three to four months. If their cancer is stable or improving, they will continue their current treatment. If the disease is progressing, the treatment would need to be changed, Goldfarb said. Doctors also need to consider a patient's quality of life and treatment side effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Generally, the principle is to give people the best quality of life possible for as long as possible," Goldfarb said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kalver sought treatment at the UCLA Health Jonsson Comprehensive Cancer Center. Her first treatment was an aggressive course of chemotherapy. Over the past four years, she has participated in multiple clinical trials and undergone several different forms of treatment, according to her oncologist, Dr. Marla Lipsyc-Sharf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/da17038e-8e81-46c1-a46b-94d3c6fc708e/thumbnail/620x413/fde445a243debeeea8b84799c2e64e20/elissachemo-11192021-0051.jpg#" alt="Elissa Chemo " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/da17038e-8e81-46c1-a46b-94d3c6fc708e/thumbnail/620x413/fde445a243debeeea8b84799c2e64e20/elissachemo-11192021-0051.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/da17038e-8e81-46c1-a46b-94d3c6fc708e/thumbnail/1240x826/bc418237ca515bb25116cfb38f365188/elissachemo-11192021-0051.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver undergoes chemotherapy. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Billye Brenneisen

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About a year after her diagnosis, doctors found the cancer had spread to Kalver's brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I always thought tumors in your brain, like, 'That's it,'" Kalver said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a targeted chemotherapy that crossed the blood-brain barrier to attack the tumors. The masses were reduced by about 80%, Kalver said, and they have not grown in the past three years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatments have taken their toll, Kalver said. One chemotherapy made her so nauseous that "it was hard to be awake," Kalver said. Another caused her to lose her hair, which Kalver worried would alarm her then 1-year-old daughter. Sharf said other treatments caused Kalver to experience symptoms including bone pain, muscle pain and a bleeding rash. Each time the side effects have become too intense, Sharf works to recalibrate Kalver's treatment. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, Kalver is receiving chemotherapy infusions every three weeks and takes an oral medication twice a day. The treatment caused her to become "a bit anemic," which recently required a blood transfusion, but otherwise, things are going well, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"After being on chemo for four years, I've really learned that we have to prioritize living, not just surviving," Kalver said. "I feel really grateful to still be on chemo treatments that work." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/edfa1049-ea6d-46f4-a92a-88ea95710df9/thumbnail/620x411/23c7c16d182a9ca296416aee27a9b6f5/216c-02-0180-epines-elissakalver-20240919.jpg#" alt="216c-02-0180-epines-elissakalver-20240919.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/edfa1049-ea6d-46f4-a92a-88ea95710df9/thumbnail/620x411/23c7c16d182a9ca296416aee27a9b6f5/216c-02-0180-epines-elissakalver-20240919.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/edfa1049-ea6d-46f4-a92a-88ea95710df9/thumbnail/1240x822/de74815a6ae914c6169bf952704cba8a/216c-02-0180-epines-elissakalver-20240919.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver in her "We Got This" home office. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Ethan Pines

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;"Living like I'm alive"  &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kalver may spend the rest of her life on chemotherapy or other treatments. She, and many other HER2-positive metastatic breast cancer patients, may never enter a remission or see no evidence of disease on their scans. She did ring the bell after finishing her first course of chemotherapy, taking part in a ritual many cancer patients use to mark the end of their treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I thought about it a lot going into it, because I was like, 'I'm not done with treatment, but I'm done with this treatment. And this treatment was pretty hard, and I deserve to ring that bell,'" Kalver recalled. "I rang it so hard that I actually broke the bell." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then, Kalver has developed other ways to mark important milestones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every year, she celebrates what she calls a "cancerversary," honoring the day she was diagnosed. For her first "cancerversary," Kalver launched "We Got This," the first nonprofit gift registry for cancer patients. Since then, she has written a book, become a professional speaker and worked to educate other patients about the reality of participating in clinical trials. In July, Kalver will celebrate her fifth "cancerversary." She's still mulling over how to celebrate the "big milestone." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/0e1d5623-a00d-4ccc-9566-3b4640d360a0/thumbnail/620x465/3d9619b199dcce730228ad28186076c8/img-9471.jpg#" alt="img-9471.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/0e1d5623-a00d-4ccc-9566-3b4640d360a0/thumbnail/620x465/3d9619b199dcce730228ad28186076c8/img-9471.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/09/10/0e1d5623-a00d-4ccc-9566-3b4640d360a0/thumbnail/1240x930/eed57119f41188742a72a0be8dce6c70/img-9471.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Elissa Kalver poses with her book during a chemotherapy infusion.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Elissa Kalver

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When she's not busy with work and advocacy, she spends time with her daughter, now 4, and her husband. Living life to the fullest is a priority, she said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc5" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",5]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I want to live as long as I can with the best quality of life that I can, making the biggest impact that I can," Kalver said. "I do all the things, and I really make an effort at living like I'm alive." &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
                  
    

    



    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 12:00:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxPUUJ5WUUtRWF2OGZ0aGowNFBZUndjVXVTYVU2eG1JdmVDT05TdGRXQ0tpeTBOMG05SUpBYmtLZnZxODF0dEpqbWE2TDliQ3dTSVhlaXdTd25MR1pYNVJsRms5Q1dUTnhGYlA5aE80MW8wcXpDN2kxZ0w4WUVUdkZkVUx4Z2VoX0FXLUxGNTNYX2dCWHp1Z2pjelZ2Qm5mcTFQM1F1aWF2NUFId0hQaU8wOdIBtwFBVV95cUxPc2wwdW9NRFhXRnhyNjNtRmxnSUFGbk1BZUF4NndHb29uRkt4REo3VG9kUlRJNzFDTDFacTlBVS1PNUJwa00xM3JVZkM0R3ppV0NWZko3blN4a3FvUVdYY3JXLUpoT1MtV0lZeWQ3WmVXUkhiSUc4Rzg5QXJXdmlPUGhEVlRhVzhvYm5PbWhhS3VNbzBqZ0JIdXdhbE5rMDFCMTk4TEVHQWNpYWxpYTF0bTZTVVFJNTg</guid></item><item><title>科学家说， “接吻虫”疾病应该在美国被视为地方病--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/13/kissing-bug-chagas-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In February, Luna donated blood at her high school in Miami, with the goal of helping save others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“She was very proud to come home and say, ‘I gave blood today,’” her mother, Valerie, said. (The Guardian is not using the mother or daughter’s full names to protect their privacy.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"us-news","tags":[{"id":"us-news/us-news","type":"Keyword","title":"US news"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"profile/eric-berger","type":"Contributor","title":"Eric Berger"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/us-news","type":"Tracking","title":"US News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"us-news/2025/sep/13/kissing-bug-chagas-disease","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It turned out, she was not able to save someone else’s life but potentially prevented herself from having serious health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A couple months later, she received a letter from the blood donation company informing her that she could not give blood. She had tested positive for Chagas disease, which is caused by a parasite spread by triatomine bugs, otherwise known as kissing bugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Neither Luna nor Valerie had heard about the disease, which is most common in rural parts of Mexico and Central and South America, where their family had traveled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“If you get a letter that tells you, you have blood cancer, you know what it is. But when you receive a letter and you hear, ‘Oh, your daughter has Chagas,’ … you’re like, oh, what is this?” said Valerie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Norman Beatty, who has studied the kissing bugs, said that like Valerie and Luna, most people in the US have not heard of Chagas, even though it is not just present south of the border but within the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Beatty, an associate professor of medicine at the University of Florida College of Medicine, is part of a group of scientists that authored a new report arguing that the United States should treat Chagas as an endemic disease, meaning that there is a constant or usual prevalence of a disease or infectious agent in a population within a geographic area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;They hope to increase public awareness of Chagas, which while rare, can cause serious health problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“My hope is that with more awareness of Chagas, we can build a better infrastructure around helping others understand whether or not they are at risk of this disease” and cause people to think about it similarly to other vector-borne illnesses, like from mosquitoes and ticks, said Beatty. “We need to add kissing bugs to this list.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Bugs spread the parasite through their droppings, which can infect humans if they enter the body through a cut or via the eyes or mouth, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chagas/about/index.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It can cause symptoms such as fever, fatigue and eyelid swelling in the weeks or months after infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some people, like Luna, do not develop any symptoms – at least initially – but about 20 to 30% of people infected can develop chronic issues later in life such as an enlarged heart and heart failure, or an enlarged esophagus or colon, leading to trouble eating or going to the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;About 8 million people, including 280,000 in the United States, have the disease, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It is not a recent arrival to the US. The 1,200-year-old remains of a man buried in south Texas revealed that he had Chagas and an abnormally-enlarged colon, according to a report in the &lt;a href="https://www.gastrojournal.org/article/S0016-5085(10)01160-1/fulltext" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Gastroenterology journal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;More recently, human development in new areas has brought us “closer to the kissing bugs’ natural environment”, Beatty said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;People in at least eight states have been infected with Chagas from local bugs, according to the new report, which was published in the CDC’s &lt;a href="https://wwwnc.cdc.gov/eid/article/31/9/24-1700_article" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Emerging Infectious Diseases&lt;/a&gt; journal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But the fact that it has not been declared endemic to the United States has led to “low awareness and underreporting”, the report states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2953998/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;2010 survey&lt;/a&gt; conducted of some American Medical Association providers found that 19% of infectious disease doctors had never heard of Chagas and 27% said they were “not at all confident,” in their knowledge of the disease being up to date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“If you ask physicians about Chagas, they would think that it is either something transmitted by ticks … or they would say that’s something that doesn’t exist in the US,” said Dr Bernardo Moreno Peniche, a physician and anthropologist who was one of the authors of the report with Beatty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But Beatty sees people with Chagas every week at a clinic in Florida dedicated to travel medicine and tropical diseases. (Those patients were infected with Chagas in Latin America.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Beatty said there is a misconception that tests for Chagas are not reliable or available in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We have the infrastructure to start screening people who have had exposure to these bugs and who may be in a region where we had known transmission, so we should be thinking about this as kind of routine care,” Beatty said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After Valerie received the letter about Luna’s infection, she contacted her pediatrician who quickly responded and told them to see an infectious disease doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;That physician told them it was likely a “false positive” and ordered additional tests before eventually starting treatment, Valerie said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Frustrated by the medical care, Valerie sought out a new physician and found Beatty, who prescribed a different anti-parasitic therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Even among people like Luna who are not experiencing any symptoms, such treatment is often recommended, Beatty said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The goal is to “detect early and treat early to avoid the chronic, often permanent damage that can occur”, Beatty explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The treatment took two months, during which Luna experienced side effects like hives and severe swelling in her hands and feet, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While she is finished with the treatment, there is no definitive test to determine whether such patients will develop chronic Chagas symptoms, but it’s less likely, Beatty said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“I hope the CDC takes it seriously,” Valerie said, “and that we can move forward and have good awareness, so that people want to be tested and get tested and get the treatment they need.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE9SdEFzUm12RDhGSGJKR2d5TE1KbkxGbE8wVDVGeWI4ak5rZmEwR0FlakVHT1llN3UwZmNxTndqclJtbXByZlFvUmJRTVF4ZHlMeXZWUlFsVnljcHF3c0Y1eTNCVVpVeS1oODFpdEdiQTl4R3BTckc1TjRDNE5QX2c</guid></item><item><title>正在尝试立即接种新冠肺炎疫苗？以下是须知事项-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/09/13/nx-s1-5540088/covid-vaccine-2025-cdc-fda-guidelines</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-88595" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                People seeking this year's COVID booster shot may find it more difficult than the past.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Francine Orr/Los Angeles Times/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Francine Orr/Los Angeles Times/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;If you want a COVID shot, it can be frustrating to try to get one right now.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's because the Food and Drug Administration has &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/08/27/nx-s1-5515503/fda-covid-vaccines-restricted" target="_blank"&gt;narrowed its approval&lt;/a&gt; for this year's shots to only certain groups: those 65 and older, and people at high risk for developing severe illness from the virus. It's a major departure from policy in past years, when the vaccines had been approved for anyone 6 months and older.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Trump administration health officials argue that most otherwise healthy, younger people have so much immunity that they don't necessarily need annual boosters anymore. But many &lt;a href="https://www.idsociety.org/news--publications-new/articles/2025/fdas-narrow-covid-19-vaccine-label-ignores-science-and-puts-millions-of-lives-at-risk/" target="_blank"&gt;doctors' groups&lt;/a&gt; say it's a good idea to get one to avoid serious illness or spreading it to others who may be high-risk.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;So the change means you may have to &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/09/11/nx-s1-5538105/covid-vaccine-shots-pharmacy-fda" target="_blank"&gt;work harder&lt;/a&gt; to get a shot. In the past, you could just walk into a pharmacy and ask for one. But now, you might get turned away if you don't meet those criteria.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Here's what to know about getting a shot right now.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Q. If the pharmacist says I'm not eligible, do I have any options?&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A: Yes. If you have one of the risk factors you may be able to "self-attest" that you're eligible. That means simply telling the pharmacist that you have a risk factor or indicating your risk factor when scheduling a shot. Often no documentation is required.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;At the moment, some pharmacies may say you need to get a doctor to issue you a prescription for a shot. That requirement may go away in some states after the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention issues specific recommendations for who should get vaccinated. The CDC advisory committee that makes those recommendations is scheduled to meet Sept. 18-19.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Q. How do I know if I am at risk -- what conditions might make me eligible?&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A: The CDC lists risk factors for the public &lt;a href="http://www.cdc.gov/covid/risk-factors/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and for health care providers &lt;a href="http://www.cdc.gov/covid/hcp/clinical-care/underlying-conditions.html" target="_blank"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. They include people who are 65 and older, people from a racial or ethnic minority and people who have disabilities. There's also a broad list of conditions, including:&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;ul class="edTag rte2-style-ul"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Asthma&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cancer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cerebrovascular disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chronic kidney disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chronic lung disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chronic liver disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cystic fibrosis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Diabetes (both types)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Disabilities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heart conditions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;HIV&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mental health conditions – including depression&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Neurologic conditions (Dementia and Parkinson's disease)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Obesity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Physical inactivity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Primary immunodeficiencies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Smoking (even if you quit)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Solid organ or blood stem cell transplantation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tuberculosis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Use of corticosteroids or other immunosuppressive medications&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMsb2506929" target="_blank"&gt;FDA estimates&lt;/a&gt; between 100 million and 200 million Americans would qualify.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Q. What if I'm pregnant?&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A: Pregnancy is also named as a risk factor, even though the CDC agency dropped the recommendation that pregnant women routinely get vaccinated. The discrepancy is causing some confusion about whether pharmacists can administer the shots and insurers will pay for vaccination. The American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists &lt;a href="https://www.acog.org/news/news-releases/2025/08/acog-releases-updated-maternal-immunization-guidance-covid-influenza-rsv" target="_blank"&gt;does recommend&lt;/a&gt; the shot during pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Q. What about children — can they get it?&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A: Yes, the COVID vaccine has been approved for children — but this year it's only for those with risk factors for serious complications. And for the first time, only one vaccine, Moderna's, has been approved for children as young as six months old. The Pfizer-BioNTech vaccine is approved for children 5 and older. Novavax's vaccine has been approved for children as young as age 12.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Parents may need to get a prescription if they want to vaccinate otherwise healthy children. And no vaccine has been approved for younger children, such as newborn babies, even though very young children are among those most vulnerable to getting seriously ill from COVID. That's one reason why doctors recommend pregnant women get vaccinated — to pass protective antibodies to babies in the womb.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Q. Some pharmacies don't seem to have them — where can I find the shots? &lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A: This year's vaccines have started to become available at many pharmacies, doctor's offices, clinics and hospitals, but some locations may not have received their orders yet but should soon. The vaccine manufacturers say they are producing plenty of vaccine, so supply shouldn't be an issue even with the narrower FDA approvals.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But some doctors that stocked the vaccine in the past may pass this time if they don't think there will be enough demand. That means you may need to go to a pharmacy to get a shot.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Pharmacy chains like &lt;a href="https://www.cvs.com/immunizations/covid-19-vaccine?icid=search_typeahead" target="_blank"&gt;CVS&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.walgreens.com/topic/promotion/covid-vaccine.jsp?ban=immhub_covidvax" target="_blank"&gt;Walgreens&lt;/a&gt; have websites where people can find a vaccine and schedule appointments. Pfizer and &lt;a href="https://products.modernatx.com/finder" target="_blank"&gt;Moderna &lt;/a&gt;both opened &lt;a href="https://www.vaxassist.com/schedule?cmp=188442362390&amp;amp;utm_source=GOOGLE&amp;amp;utm_medium=paidsearch&amp;amp;pid=Scheduler&amp;amp;utm_term=pfizer%20vaccine%20available%20near%20me&amp;amp;network=g&amp;amp;gclsrc=aw.ds&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=22943851190&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAABK5w6FawaR8GMs9_iPQ0cImTHd-Y&amp;amp;gclid=Cj0KCQjw5onGBhDeARIsAFK6QJYqqC3A_jZAbNDWf_hifoXY60dX6YR_LiYEEicIdMfLaYWnOJpbL7gaAruoEALw_wcB" target="_blank"&gt;vaccine-finder websites&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Q. Even if I can find a pharmacy that has the shots, will my insurance cover it? &lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A: That's unclear. Insurance companies are only required to pay for the shots if they have been recommended by the CDC. That won't happen until next week at the earliest. But some insurance companies say they are covering the shots anyway, so it's worth asking if your plan covers it.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;About half of&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the children in the U.S. are eligible for free vaccines through the federal government's Vaccines for Children Program but the COVID shots won't be included in that until after the CDC recommendations go into effect, and even then, it may depend on the child's health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For those who have to pay out of pocket, the shots cost between $150 and $200.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Q. The CDC's advisory committee is meeting soon about the COVID shots — will that make it easier or harder to get a shot?&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A: The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;vaccine advisory group&lt;/a&gt; is scheduled to meet Sept. 18-19 and is expected to issue specific recommendations for who should receive the shots, which then need to be accepted by the CDC director. The recommendations have several important effects, including allowing pharmacists in more states to administer the vaccines and making them available for free through the federal &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines-for-children/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Vaccines for Children Program&lt;/a&gt;. So the shots could become more easily available after the recommendations — or less so — depending on what the committee recommends and what the CDC director accepts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNanpGVU5YQjJoMzQ0SDZwci1BYXVRUUJldFZzRklmWmtoSHR2NXlQOXVTRGF3UHpSWEVMOEUwbVBpMVJfODNLRnpGM2ljTndCbXR5UTRVUXM1OWhrbjNYLXhXNGNHWWNHekt1ZEFpN2lnMXV5VGZ4V0Jfb0FBZ3p3S0dHUzRmMVE1Tmc</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现令人惊讶的新的痴呆症警告信号- Daily Express US</title><link>https://www.the-express.com/news/us-news/183440/Scientists-discover-new-dementia-warning-sign</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-description"&gt;&lt;p data-mce-linkchecker-status="valid"&gt;When it comes to &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" title="Dementia" href="/latest/dementia"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt; there are warning signs that are well-known &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health/171737/surprising-early-warning-signs-dementia"&gt;like memory loss&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health/163450/dementia-warning-sign-talking"&gt;trouble speaking&lt;/a&gt;, but based on a new study, &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/science/183058/neurologist-issues-warning-sleep-habit-harm-brain"&gt;sleep patterns can also be an indicator. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study used sleep trackers to monitor sleep patterns in 733 women in their 80s, and at the five-year follow-up, 164 of the women who took part in the study had developed mild cognitive impairment and 93 of the women were diagnosed with &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" title="Dementia" href="/latest/dementia"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the researchers, people who had large jumps in sleepiness, i&lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health/172196/scientist-sleep-doctor-reveals-shock"&gt;ncluding excessive napping&lt;/a&gt;, were more at risk of developing dementia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on the study, researches concluded changes in sleep patterns could be considered an “early marker” for dementia in women in “older women.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ovp-primis"&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clifford Segil, DO, a neurologist at Providence Saint John’s Health Center in Santa Monica, CA, said: “If you ask two different neurologist, you may get two different answer as we still don’t know the reason we sleep.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-ad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text-description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;And while that may be the case, Dr. Segil shred his opinion on the importance of sleep and how it is linked to memory consolidation, where short-term memories becomes long-term memories. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said: “Getting a good night’s sleep is more important to octogenarians — people in their 80s — than a good daytime nap.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Poor sleep can impact a person’s memory, especially if it’s an ongoing issues, according to the neurologist. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DON’T MISS: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mantis-recommender-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health/173700/sleep-disturbances-dementia-sign" target="_blank" data-name="Experiencing this at night makes you 'four times more likely' to get dementia"&gt;Experiencing this at night makes you 'four times more likely' to get dementia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health/173348/sleeping-pattern-dementia-risk" target="_blank" data-name="Sleeping pattern that may raise dementia risk - but only in certain people"&gt;Sleeping pattern that may raise dementia risk - but only in certain people&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health/170480/neurologist-reversible-dementia-symptoms" target="_blank" data-name="'I'm a neurologist - four health issues can cause dementia-like symptoms'"&gt;'I'm a neurologist - four health issues can cause dementia-like symptoms'&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text-description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The National Institutes of Aging has put together a list of early symptoms of dementia, listed below: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Memory loss, poor judgment, and confusion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trouble speaking, understanding and expressing thoughts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wandering and getting lost in a familiar area&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Difficulty handling money and paying bills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeating questions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using unusual words to refer to familiar objects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Taking longer to complete normal daily tasks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Losing interest in normal daily activities&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hallucinating or having delusions or paranoia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Acting impulsively&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Not caring about other people’s feelings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Losing balance and problems with movement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there’s something going on, and there are concerns about dementia, people are advised to go to a healthcare provider for a physical and to speak to the practitioner about your or your loved one’s symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Express US</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQWXVSMmM1SU8ySnAzc0VCSDFpRm83Mm5fOUZsZ2x3b1cyczc1bHNLS1FlWXZQRmxKZkZPVHdHZGVfQXNyeTk2bDhwSFpRRFllOXRoR0xoRTdETWFOWnZtMVh2SGloQVd3ZUtxYVhhdnVIVXl5Nnl3NUJVamZkTXNLN1ZIT0hkYkxiUTNQWERQRkJpeHAzRkdtRdIBngFBVV95cUxOQ2xhMUFrQmRwY2hBREs5YnlBZUVMVTFkTW96dEFlSkk5YW1scWRKb0ZKRHFmaWZnWW8yWFZ0R1A0Nm96MmU3eUNnR1hPT2UzM2laSGprU2NQbHVXUFlsNTNUSDRPVjctR3NRZE9PZ09LdjRVdHVHaHVxMTFFNUpNZ2NSeFBJWHFzenQ3aElGNnh6STFGX0xZaU9LTkM0Zw</guid></item><item><title>未扫描的疼痛—为什么癌症护理中缺少心理健康？ - Dawn</title><link>https://www.dawn.com/news/1939898</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p dir="auto" class="story__excerpt      text-4.5  text-center  font-lato      p-4  mb-4"&gt;For many women, surviving cancer means enduring not just physical pain but the unspoken emotional wounds of a system blind to mental health.
 
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div dir="auto" class="story__content  overflow-hidden    text-4.5  font-normal      story__content--normal  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;At just 40, Farhat had never imagined her world would shrink to hospital corridors, infusion drips, and the sterile hush of oncology wards. A spirited schoolteacher from Gulshan-i-Iqbal, Karachi, she was known for her laughter — loud, contagious, and always a beat ahead of the room.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But after her breast cancer diagnosis, the laughter disappeared. What followed was not just the slow unraveling of her physical health, but a silent, suffocating assault on her emotional wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sara, another breast cancer patient, endured mastectomy, chemotherapy, and the disorienting fog of fatigue and pain. But the darkest moments weren’t marked by physical suffering; they came in the long, sleepless nights filled with fear, anxiety, and an overwhelming sense of isolation. “Everyone talks about surviving cancer,” she whispered, “but no one prepares you for surviving yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like countless women in Pakistan, these women found themselves trapped in a blind spot of our healthcare system: psychological support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Farhat was recommended therapy, yes — but each session cost more than her monthly utility bills, and the nearest affordable counselling centre was two crowded bus rides and a month-long waitlist away. Her oncologist had done all he could for her body, but for her mind, there was nothing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a country where mental health is still spoken of in hushed tones and emotional pain is dismissed as weakness, her suffering went largely unseen. Even her family, loving but bewildered, urged her to pray harder, stay positive, and avoid “overthinking.” But what happens when the mind itself becomes a battlefield no prayer alone can soothe?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their stories are not rare. And it forces us to ask: are we truly treating cancer or only the parts of it we can see?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    &lt;figure class="media  w-full  w-full  media--stretch  media--embed  media--uneven"&gt;
        &lt;p class="media__item  media__item--newskitlink  "&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;
        
    &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a id="the-missing-half-of-cancer-care" href="#the-missing-half-of-cancer-care" class="heading-permalink" aria-hidden="true" title="Permalink"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;The missing half of cancer care&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Globally, the prevalence of anxiety and depression is 30 per cent and 33pc, respectively, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" class="link--external" href="https://bmcpsychiatry.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12888-025-06599-5#:~:text=The%20umbrella%20review%20found%20that,stage%20and%20poor%20sleep%20quality."&gt;according&lt;/a&gt; to an umbrella review carried out by Addisu et al. Some researches show the percentages to be even higher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A Karachi-based &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" class="link--external" href="https://www.pjia.com.pk/index.php/pjia/article/view/185?utm_source=chatgpt.com"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; of 402 breast cancer patients found 59.7pc suffered anxiety, 69.4pc depression, and 47.5pc reported suicidal ideation. That said, what are the options a cancer patient has? A handful of psychotherapy centres exist, but most operate privately, and for the average patient, the cost of care remains far beyond reach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Integrating mental health care into oncology remains one of the field’s greatest challenges. Despite the overwhelming prevalence of psychological distress, many cancer patients are left with unmet mental health needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The reasons are layered: limited time for distress screening, inadequate training of healthcare professionals, and insufficient resources to follow through when mental health concerns are identified. What is crucial to note here is that mental health support is often delivered separately from cancer treatment, leading to a disjointed and fragmented approach that leaves patients to piece together their own care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We don’t have to look far for examples. In Sri Lanka, psychotherapy is being &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" class="link--external" href="https://www.nccp.health.gov.lk/storage/post/pdfs/Palliative%20Care%20for%20Cancer%20Patients%20in%20Primary%20Health%20Care%20A%20guide%20for%20primary%20health%20care%20professionals.pdf"&gt;woven into&lt;/a&gt; cancer care, with the Ministry of Health recognising psychological support for patients and survivors as essential. Survivorship care, including counselling, has been &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" class="link--external" href="https://www.nccp.health.gov.lk/en/stratergic"&gt;formally built&lt;/a&gt; into the country’s National Strategic Plan for Cancer Prevention and Control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alongside this, Sri Lanka is &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" class="link--external" href="https://epid.gov.lk/storage/post/pdfs/vol_49_no_32-english_1.pdf"&gt;strengthening&lt;/a&gt; palliative care services that incorporate psychosocial support, while also exploring ways to integrate complementary medicine with conventional cancer treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a id="emotional-healing-has-a-price-tag" href="#emotional-healing-has-a-price-tag" class="heading-permalink" aria-hidden="true" title="Permalink"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Emotional healing has a price tag&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This vision of holistic care stands in sharp contrast to Pakistan, where the prohibitive cost of therapy alone keeps psychological support out of reach for most patients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A single session with a qualified therapist in Karachi can range from Rs3,000 to Rs8,000 — an amount far beyond what many middle income families can afford, especially when they’re already struggling to pay for diagnostic tests, medications, chemotherapy or even surgery. Unlike physical treatments, therapy is rarely a one-time intervention. It is ongoing, often requiring weekly or biweekly sessions — costs that quickly multiply into an overwhelming financial burden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, there are peer-led support groups in Pakistan that provide emotional comfort through shared stories, mutual encouragement, and a sense of community. However, they are not a substitute for professional mental health care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Psychotherapy, especially when delivered by psychologists experienced in trauma and chronic illness, offers evidence-based interventions tailored to each patient’s psychological needs. It can address clinical depression, anxiety, post-traumatic stress, and adjustment disorders, issues that often go beyond the scope of peer support.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;    &lt;figure class="media  w-full  w-full  media--stretch  media--embed  media--uneven"&gt;
        &lt;p class="media__item  media__item--newskitlink  "&gt;    &lt;/p&gt;
        
    &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;a id="treating-the-body-and-the-mind" href="#treating-the-body-and-the-mind" class="heading-permalink" aria-hidden="true" title="Permalink"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Treating the body and the mind&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is time for Pakistan’s healthcare system to recognise that cancer treatment cannot stop at surgery, chemotherapy, and radiation. Emotional wellbeing must be treated as an essential part of recovery, not an afterthought. Psychological screening and counselling need to be built into routine oncology care, particularly in public hospitals where most patients turn for treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Provincial governments must invest in training psycho-oncology professionals, subsidise mental health services for cancer patients, and expand teletherapy to bridge the urban–rural divide. At the same time, civil society and health institutions must lead awareness efforts so that emotional suffering is no longer dismissed as weakness, but understood as a valid, treatable consequence of illness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote class="blockquote-level-1"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because in the fight against cancer, emotional wellbeing is not a luxury, it is survival.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Training oncology staff to recognise depression in cancer patients is crucial for improving both care and outcomes. Simple tools like the &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" class="link--external" href="https://www.apa.org/depression-guideline/patient-health-questionnaire.pdf"&gt;Patient Health Questionnaire (PHQ-9)&lt;/a&gt; can be used in clinical settings to screen patients and ensure no one slips through unnoticed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Farhat survived the surgeries, the chemotherapy, the physical pain, but the emotional wounds lingered, unspoken and untreated. And her story is far from unique. Across Pakistan, countless patients endure the same silent suffering, their mental health sacrificed in a system that sees only the tumour, not the trauma.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until cancer is treated as a disease of both body and mind, true healing will remain out of reach. It is not enough to save lives; we must fight to save what makes them worth living.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Header Image:&lt;/strong&gt; The image is created via generative AI&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dawn</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 08:19:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiSEFVX3lxTFBjM1p0Mk03dTJxTEpCNjNGcFR0aElPRldHOFEyRXZ5OE9aT1BTMmNPaE4wUFY0YVRnQXA5LU9QS3R5VUhJbE1QZtIBTkFVX3lxTFBXNHdrVFA1STFNTU9acW1Ob255aFhHQkhFc3JNaUwyZi12dUQxOVEzREl2dkRRR3FFT2wwRDFVRnFVdmctN3RBS3BWZUxVUQ</guid></item><item><title>根据医生的说法，多发性骨髓瘤的5个令人惊讶的症状- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/5-surprising-symptoms-multiple-myeloma-172800923.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;5 Surprising Symptoms of Multiple Myeloma&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;bymuratdeniz - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple myeloma is a &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mayoclinic.org%2Fdiseases-conditions%2Fmultiple-myeloma%2Fsymptoms-causes%2Fsyc-20353378&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fhealth-conditions%2Fa66056798%2Fmultiple-myeloma-symptoms%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:form of blood cancer;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;form of blood cancer&lt;/a&gt; you may never have heard of–and that makes sense, because it’s, thankfully, pretty rare. That said, if you’re one of the unlucky few (your average lifetime risk of developing it is less than 1%), the odds of survival aren’t great. The thing is, as serious as the cancer is, multiple myeloma symptoms don’t always seem serious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2025, around 36,110 new cases will be diagnosed, and about 12,030 US adults will die of the disease, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/multiple-myeloma/about/key-statistics.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Cancer Society.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;American Cancer Society.&lt;/a&gt; Multiple myeloma affects more men than women, and most patients are 65 or older. Although researchers don’t know why, Black people are twice as likely to be diagnosed as white people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meet the experts: &lt;a href="https://www.myeloma.org/people/joseph-mikhael-md-med-frcpc-facp-fasco" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Joseph Mikhael, M.D., ME.d., F.R.C.P.C, F.A.C.P., F.A.S.C.O;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Joseph Mikhael, M.D., ME.d., F.R.C.P.C, F.A.C.P., F.A.S.C.O&lt;/a&gt;., professor of clinical genomics and therapeutics at the Translational Genomics Research Institute (TGen) at City of Hope Cancer Center in Scottsdale, AZ, and chief medical officer of the &lt;a href="https://www.myeloma.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:International Myeloma Foundation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;International Myeloma Foundation&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="https://profiles.icahn.mssm.edu/hearn-jay-cho" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Hearn Jay Cho, M.D., Ph.D;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Hearn Jay Cho, M.D., Ph.D&lt;/a&gt;., chief medical officer at the Multiple Myeloma Research Foundation and clinical professor of hematology and medical oncology and immunology &amp;amp; immunotherapy at Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai in New York City; and &lt;a href="https://einsteinmed.edu/faculty/17790/ridhi-gupta" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ridhi Gupta, M.D.,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Ridhi Gupta, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; assistant professor of medicine at Albert Einstein College of Medicine and a medical oncologist at Montefiore Einstein Comprehensive Cancer Center in Bronx, NY.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One of the reasons why the diagnosis of multiple myeloma is often missed and treatment is delayed is that there are not overt or obvious symptoms that point to the disease,” says &lt;a href="https://www.myeloma.org/people/joseph-mikhael-md-med-frcpc-facp-fasco" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Joseph Mikhael, M.D., ME.d., F.R.C.P.C, F.A.C.P., F.A.S.C.O;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Joseph Mikhael, M.D., ME.d., F.R.C.P.C, F.A.C.P., F.A.S.C.O&lt;/a&gt;., professor of clinical genomics and therapeutics at the Translational Genomics Research Institute (TGen) at City of Hope Cancer Center in Scottsdale, AZ, and chief medical officer of the &lt;a href="https://www.myeloma.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:International Myeloma Foundation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;International Myeloma Foundation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make things even more confusing, some of the signs that &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; prompt people to see a doctor can point to any number of conditions. “The most common three signs include fatigue, bone pain, and anemia, if that’s found on a blood test,” says Dr. Mikhael. “This is why the average time to diagnosis is about six months, and why the average patient sees their primary care provider with symptoms consistent with myeloma three times before the disease is suspected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What exactly is multiple myeloma?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple myeloma is a cancer that affects &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/plasma-cell" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:the plasma cells;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;the plasma cells&lt;/a&gt; in your blood. There are also plasma cells inside your&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/bone-marrow" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bone marrow;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt; bone marrow&lt;/a&gt;, which work as part of your immune system, according to &lt;a href="https://www.mdanderson.org/cancer-types/multiple-myeloma.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center&lt;/a&gt;. Once multiple myeloma turns plasma cells malignant, those cells multiply and crowd out normal cells–you end up with fewer healthy red blood cells that fight infection. Multiple myeloma produces an antibody called &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/monoclonal-protein" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a monoclonal or M-protein;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;a monoclonal or M-protein&lt;/a&gt;, which can &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mayoclinic.org%2Fdiseases-conditions%2Fmultiple-myeloma%2Fsymptoms-causes%2Fsyc-20353378&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fhealth-conditions%2Fa66056798%2Fmultiple-myeloma-symptoms%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:damage your body, including your kidneys and bones.;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;damage your body, including your kidneys and bones.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the most obvious signs of multiple myeloma?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Usually, patients present with symptoms like back pain, fatigue, shortness of breath while exercising, and heart palpitations. A symptom to suggest advanced disease is confusion for no reason,” says &lt;a href="https://einsteinmed.edu/faculty/17790/ridhi-gupta" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ridhi Gupta, M.D.,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Ridhi Gupta, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; assistant professor of medicine at Albert Einstein College of Medicine and a medical oncologist at Montefiore Einstein Comprehensive Cancer Center in Bronx, NY.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But everyone is different, says Dr. Gupta. “Multiple myeloma, depending on how advanced it is in its evolution, can have varied presentation.” The reason someone might have some symptoms over others depends on how multiple myeloma is specifically affecting your body, according to the &lt;a href="https://themmrf.org/multiple-myeloma/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Multiple Myeloma Research Foundation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Multiple Myeloma Research Foundation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, multiple myeloma may activate other bone marrow cells that damage bones, causing pain or fractures. It may also lead to &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mayoclinic.org%2Fdiseases-conditions%2Fhypercalcemia%2Fsymptoms-causes%2Fsyc-20355523&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fhealth-conditions%2Fa66056798%2Fmultiple-myeloma-symptoms%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:hypercalcemia;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;hypercalcemia&lt;/a&gt;, or too much calcium in the blood, which may cause mental confusion. &lt;a href="https://www.roswellpark.org/cancertalk/202009/why-does-multiple-myeloma-cause-kidney-failure#:~:text=They%20obstruct%20the%20passages%2C%20preventing,for%20myeloma%20kidney%20itself%2C%20Dr." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Kidney problems in multiple myeloma;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Kidney problems in multiple myeloma&lt;/a&gt; can happen when the condition produces groups of abnormal proteins called &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8627691/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:light chains;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;light chains&lt;/a&gt;. When light chains pass through the kidneys, they block fluid, leading to &lt;a href="https://www.myeloma.org/what-is-kidney-failure" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:damaging inflammation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;damaging inflammation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Surprising symptoms of multiple myeloma&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still other symptoms are more ambiguous or subtle and may mimic other health problems. They include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tingling in your fingers and toes&lt;/strong&gt;, according to &lt;a href="https://profiles.icahn.mssm.edu/hearn-jay-cho" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Hearn Jay Cho, M.D., Ph.D;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Hearn Jay Cho, M.D., Ph.D&lt;/a&gt;., chief medical officer at the Multiple Myeloma Research Foundation and clinical professor of hematology and medical oncology and immunology &amp;amp; immunotherapy at Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai in NYC. This could be a sign of &lt;a href="https://www.myeloma.org/what-is-peripheral-neuropathy" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:myeloma-related neuropathy;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;myeloma-related neuropathy&lt;/a&gt;. Although it’s not well-understood yet, this type of neuropathy may happen when M-protein damages your body’s motor nerve cells, or when a broken bone compresses the nerves in your spinal cord.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bubbles in your pee&lt;/strong&gt;, says Dr. Mikhael. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9296938/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; shows this sign can mean high levels of the cancer’s abnormal protein are impacting your kidney function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Feeling really thirsty&lt;/strong&gt;, due to &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.mayoclinic.org%2Fdiseases-conditions%2Fhypercalcemia%2Fsymptoms-causes%2Fsyc-20355523%23%3A~%3Atext%3DKidneys.%2520Excess%2520calcium%2520makes%2520the%2520kidneys%2520work%2Ccan%2520cause%2520serious%2520thirst%2520and%2520frequent%2520urination.&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.prevention.com%2Fhealth%2Fhealth-conditions%2Fa66056798%2Fmultiple-myeloma-symptoms%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:high blood calcium levels;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;high blood calcium levels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiredness and pain that doesn’t go away.&lt;/strong&gt; If resting your body doesn’t relieve a feeling of exhaustion, and if that tiredness is paired with any bone discomfort, see your doctor. “We usually qualify the fatigue and pain to be severe, consistent, and persistent,” says Dr. Mikhael.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Main risk factors for multiple myeloma&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to being assigned male at birth, age, and race, the American Cancer Society &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/multiple-myeloma/causes-risks-prevention/risk-factors.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reports;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt; that other factors raising your odds of getting multiple myeloma include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing your specific risk factors can clue your doctors in and if you have it, speed up your diagnosis for earlier treatment. “Multiple myeloma can be especially difficult to diagnose if a patient doesn’t experience a major event like a broken bone or severe infection that leads them to the right specialist,” says Dr. Cho.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why would a broken bone be a clue? Multiple myeloma can lead to &lt;a href="https://www.myeloma.org/bone-disease" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bone disease;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;bone disease&lt;/a&gt; and can deplete bones of calcium, weakening them. The result is that even minor pressure on a bone can cause a fracture. This is why it’s important to stay alert to any bone problems, particularly if you’re in an at-risk group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bottom line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have any of these symptoms, again, don’t freak out–but do get checked out. “Early diagnosis is crucial for better outcomes in multiple myeloma,” Dr. Cho says. “There are myeloma symptoms that can overlap with other conditions. Some include arthritis, osteoporosis, and peripheral neuropathy. To rule out some of these conditions or get diagnosed quicker, it’s important to discuss any of these symptoms with a provider, especially if you belong to a high-risk group.” Multiple myeloma is rare, but It’s better to be safe than sorry, and as always, listen to your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 08:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPd2dmQlotYVQ3WmRvV1NiWW5nV2h4dzdENjhZTUpOWWZZblJPU1R4Tk1NVzF2T1p1cmZDQ3NkUmk0M3J2eUJrdE9yZzJpb1kxZFgxeGFfYkdzbUhrSU9faWlYd2VxZXNLb0JpbFB2YW1IYlN6Wk5RVE4yLXV0M0ZhNDNaX2Q3VjVWbHc</guid></item><item><title>特朗普政府已停止为全球艾滋病毒/艾滋病项目提供资金。没有人知道影响有多大- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/13/africa/hiv-aids-program-cuts-trump-pepfar-intl</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cmfe7icqk002j28p2223edkql@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cmfe7icqk002m28p2abl901rs@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F13%2Fafrica%2Fhiv-aids-program-cuts-trump-pepfar-intl&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F13%2Fafrica%2Fhiv-aids-program-cuts-trump-pepfar-intl" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F09%2F13%2Fafrica%2Fhiv-aids-program-cuts-trump-pepfar-intl" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/13/africa/hiv-aids-program-cuts-trump-pepfar-intl" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfe7icqk002l28p2adv2fvtf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The United States has suspended some funding for its flagship AIDS relief program, according to international organizations and members of Congress who warn the cuts are already hurting patients and halting critical projects globally.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5w000e3b6n1usu34pp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The full extent of the budget cuts related to US-funded HIV/AIDS relief work is highly unclear, and Congress is still battling the White House’s proposed budget clawbacks and withholding of billions of dollars in funding.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5w000f3b6nx0ezk5sk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            PEPFAR, formally called the US President’s Emergency Plan for AIDS Relief, is credited with saving more than 26 million lives over the past two decades and preventing millions of HIV infections, particularly in Africa.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5w000g3b6nec8zekxz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Last year alone, government figures show that PEPFAR provided 20.6 million people with life-saving HIV medicines, called antiretroviral therapy. It also supported more than 342,000 health workers to deliver HIV treatments, prevention care and support services, bolstering healthcare systems in &lt;a href="https://www.hiv.gov/federal-response/pepfar-global-aids/pepfar" target="_blank"&gt;more than 50 countries&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5w000h3b6npti4mkmz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Funding for the landmark program – established in 2003 by the Bush administration – was primarily implemented by USAID, which US President Donald Trump dismantled earlier this year after a freeze on foreign aid. The US State Department later issued a waiver to exempt life-saving services from that freeze, including those of PEPFAR, and moved operations to the State Department’s remit.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000i3b6nfmh68hki@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But nonprofits are sounding the alarm that HIV/AIDS projects have been terminated regardless. And without USAID, implementation of many planned initiatives has also stalled. Such cuts are severely disrupting patients’ medical care across Africa, Asia and Latin America, threatening the global fight against the disease, they say.
    &lt;/p&gt;



  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000k3b6n7qdzi1as@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            UNAIDS, the United Nations’ agency working to end AIDS, has cited examples around the world of medicine stockouts, staffing cuts at HIV/AIDS clinics, suspended community outreach services and “rising levels of stigma, discrimination and mortality rates” in the wake of the &lt;a href="https://www.unaids.org/en/resources/presscentre/featurestories/2025/may/20250512_community-led-services" target="_blank"&gt;US funding cuts&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000l3b6nlskqzkv3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The suspensions have caused major disruptions to HIV responses in dozens of countries, including &lt;a href="https://www.unaids.org/en/resources/presscentre/featurestories/2025/july/20250718_uganda" target="_blank"&gt;Uganda&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.unaids.org/en/resources/presscentre/featurestories/2025/july/20250721_philippines" target="_blank"&gt;the Philippines&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.unaids.org/en/resources/presscentre/featurestories/2025/may/20250505_people-who-use-drugs" target="_blank"&gt;Tanzania,&lt;/a&gt; the UN agency said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000m3b6niqmep49e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            People living with HIV are skipping and rationing doses of antiretroviral medications, creating conditions for drug-resistant HIV strains to emerge, according to the nonprofit Physicians for Human Rights, which compiled &lt;a href="https://phr.org/news/trump-administration-disruptions-to-global-hiv-efforts-have-caused-severe-harms-but-congress-can-still-preserve-live-saving-programs-new-phr-research/" target="_blank"&gt;testimonies&lt;/a&gt; of healthcare disruptions from people in Tanzania and Uganda.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000n3b6nvih6xm03@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.doctorswithoutborders.org/latest/how-hiv-funding-cuts-are-undermining-years-progress-zimbabwe" target="_blank"&gt;Doctors Without Borders&lt;/a&gt; has warned that “PEPFAR faces an uncertain future” and that project cancellations following the dismantling of USAID have already impacted humanitarian work.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000o3b6nfk87uj9q@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “PEPFAR’s scope of work has already been dramatically reduced since January when the State Department restricted its work on key areas of HIV prevention, treatment, care, and support,” the Doctors Without Borders statement said, contradicting the US government’s repeated claims that lifesaving aid work is being preserved.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000p3b6n4r9gr3rn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Cuts are not just hitting program activities and medical stocks; they are crippling the logistical backbone of HIV care. Transport for distributing supplies has all but vanished,” said the organization’s representative in Zimbabwe, Zahra Zeggani-Bec.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000q3b6nl4pdxqzh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            World Vision, an international Christian organization focusing on poverty and development, told CNN it had a large PEPFAR program in Kenya that had been terminated.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000r3b6nj6zaq2am@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “That (program) had focused primarily on orphans and vulnerable children and prevention activities,” said Margaret Schuler, World Vision’s chief impact officer. Shuler said it was surprising that “what would have been considered ‘lifesaving programs’ were terminated,” including other World Vision programs related to health care and disease control.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000t3b6n6qumoog0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            PEPFAR reporting data has been publicly unavailable for months, meaning there’s little clarity on the program’s ongoing activities. A &lt;a href="https://data.pepfar.gov/?_gl=1*s1iv85*_gcl_au*NDcyMjk2NTA1LjE3NTY0ODEzMTM." target="_blank"&gt;message&lt;/a&gt; on the government website says it is “undergoing updates.” The release dates for 2025 PEPFAR data reports are all listed as “TBD.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000u3b6n4k1yweom@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A State Department spokesperson told CNN that “data collection is ongoing to capture recent updates to programming.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000v3b6nt6b1zv30@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            UNAIDS said in a report in April that, among 70 of its country offices, 28 (40%) had witnessed an end to community-led services due to the US funding cuts. Meanwhile, 21 (30%) reported that services by international NGOs had been stopped.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000w3b6n29uqc0ux@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some of that work may have resumed, but it’s impossible to determine how much, given the lack of data on the budget, contracted services and “what has actually been delivered,” said Charles Kenny, a senior fellow at the Center for Global Development, a think tank based in the US and UK.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000x3b6nnlzh3cpm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            He wrote in an &lt;a href="https://www.cgdev.org/blog/theres-lot-we-dont-know-about-status-us-assistance-delivery-should-worry-congress" target="_blank"&gt;analysis of the status of US aid operations&lt;/a&gt; that “right now, Congress and taxpayers have no visibility on what the foreign assistance system is trying to accomplish, let alone if that is happening.”
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000y3b6nsnvccrw5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Secretary of State Marco Rubio has stated PEPFAR is an important and life-saving program that will continue, a State Department spokesperson told CNN, adding that Rubio has “also said that PEPFAR, like all assistance programs, should be reduced over time as they are impactful in achieving their mission.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x000z3b6nf4k5jiev@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Last week, the State Department announced a joint commitment with the Global Fund to purchase the drug lenacapavir, an HIV prevention injection that only has to be taken twice a year, from the American biopharmaceutical company Gilead Sciences. PEPFAR will distribute the drug in eight to 12 high-burden HIV countries in 2026, with a focus on reducing the number of new HIV infections in pregnant and breastfeeding mothers, according to a State Department &lt;a href="https://www.state.gov/releases/the-united-states-presidents-emergency-plan-for-aids-relief/2025/09/pepfar-commits-to-distributing-breakthrough-hiv-drug-lenacapavir-demonstrating-american-excellence-in-science-and-american-leadership-in-hiv-prevention/" target="_blank"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x00113b6nft5c07lk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The White House Office of Management and Budget (OMB) has released only about half ($2.9 billion) of the $6 billion appropriated by Congress for PEPFAR’s 2025 funding, according to &lt;a href="https://openomb.org/file/11440522#tafs_11440522--019-1031-2025-2029--3--2025" target="_blank"&gt;budget documents&lt;/a&gt; on a nonprofit website that tracks the OMB.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x00123b6n97w6jv3g@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A congressional aide raised concerns that the budget document listed billions of dollars of this year’s funds as part of fiscal year 2026, which the aide described as atypical.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x00133b6nmucz1miz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A budget expert told CNN that the 2025 PEPFAR apportionment looks “weird” compared to &lt;a href="https://openomb.org/file/11396527#tafs_11396527--019-1031-2024-2028--2--2025" target="_blank"&gt;previous years’ documents&lt;/a&gt;, which typically specify how much money is going to each government department involved in PEPFAR. For this year, the released funds are listed as “unallocated” and conditional on a spending plan that has to be agreed upon by OMB and the State Department. Those spending plans are not publicly available.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x00143b6nunmmnm7l@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The source also said that placing the funds into fiscal year 2026 is at least an indication that OMB is not willing to spend the PEPFAR money now, and it could be an attempt to “slow walk” the funding.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x00153b6nze3xz453@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Another congressional aide told CNN that Congress doesn’t have a clear picture because of a lag time in the information the White House must report to the public. It’s possible that 2025 funding could still be released in the coming weeks and months.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x00163b6n29312e6p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The picture of funding flows remains fuzzy, and it comes after the Trump administration already tried to claw back $400 million for PEPFAR. That proposal was canceled after bipartisan opposition in the Senate. Yet not all of those funds had been released, top Senate appropriator Susan Collins, a Republican from Maine, told CNN in a statement last week.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x00173b6nmnkuuhxn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “OMB is blocking funding for PEPFAR, one of the most successful global health programs in history,” Collins said. “PEPFAR funds are simply not reaching those in need, as confirmed by those in the field.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x00183b6n3geqjfcr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The ranking Democrat on the Senate Appropriations Committee, Senator Patty Murray of Washington, has called out OMB Director Russell Vought directly, saying that “even after promising Republican lawmakers that the program would be protected, he’s choked off a huge chunk of funding provided by Congress for PEPFAR.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x00193b6nrf7fak55@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The law is clear as day: the full funding Congress provided must be used for the work PEPFAR does day in and out. The more these funds are obstructed and delayed, the more people will die needlessly,” Murray told CNN in a statement.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x001a3b6ndtsteon1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            CNN has reached out to OMB for comment but has not received a response.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x001c3b6ne64x9fdw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Separately, last week, Trump notified Congress he was moving to cancel $4.9 billion in foreign aid already approved for this year, drawing criticism from lawmakers from both parties who questioned the legality of the move. The US Government Accountability Office says rescissions so late in the fiscal year are illegal.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmff38e5x001d3b6no8ys9t0y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Last Wednesday, a federal judge ruled that without congressional approval, the administration can’t decide to withhold federally budgeted foreign aid money that will expire at the end of this month.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmfgvyd5o000a3b6nw5upr6uf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But the White House is mounting a multi-front effort to do so both in the courts and on Capitol Hill, with Trump &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/08/politics/supreme-court-trump-foreign-aid"&gt;asking the Supreme Court&lt;/a&gt; on Monday to step back into the fight.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 08:01:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxPYmwzbEdUeHRFU1ZuTWtxUHF1RS1VUUNFYjBQQUNjOW9DMjJCOGlNdHRBSGd1Rk9TSHdrWU1OQ1dlWTEzcncxa1lNX2NiaDNVR2dNTUN2TktHNmNjbWZwQU80Tkc0Y0dMejVFT2lDNnQ1NUVJMTJlcERsWFdLLUNzbjVwZw</guid></item><item><title>您真的需要每天步行10000步吗？ -《匹兹堡邮报》</title><link>https://www.post-gazette.com/news/health/2025/09/13/how-many-steps-a-day/stories/202509140012</link><description>&lt;body class="pgevoke bs-grid pg-hasicomoon pg-site-pg pg-user-checkingstatus pg-requesttype-story pgevoke-pageparentsection-news pg-piano" id="readabilityBody"&gt;

		
	&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
	
	

	
	
	
	

	

	
	
	
	
	&lt;p id="dfp-peelback" class="hidden-xs hidden-sm"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	

	&lt;p class="pgevoke-header-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	
	
	&lt;div class="pgevoke-pagewrapper clearfix"&gt;
			&lt;div class="pgevoke-slidemenu"&gt;
	&lt;div class="pgevoke-slidemenu-inner"&gt;
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-topborder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header pgevoke-slidemenu-header-account"&gt;ACCOUNT&lt;/p&gt;
					
			
				&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;SECTIONS&lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;OTHER&lt;/p&gt;
		
		&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;CLASSIFIEDS&lt;/p&gt;
		
				&lt;p class="pgevoke-slidemenu-header"&gt;CONTACT US / FAQ&lt;/p&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;		


&lt;p class="dfp-wallpaper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  
		
		 

					
		
	&lt;/div&gt; 

	


&lt;p id="pgevoke-apwidgetloader"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="pgtarget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


























	




			
		
		









  
  
  








  
























	











  







&lt;p id="dfpinterstitial-content" class="mfp-hide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="dfpinterstitialmobile-content" class="mfp-hide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



  
      
    
  
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>Pittsburgh Post-Gazette</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxNUzAwY1dCLURaQmUycER1SHBJZnJGNm9MQmhSSFl4TUd1X3RscWFMV21PUHp3b2lDRnNqenBtNXhMc2h4R0FPamNhSGJ1aFhDWHQxWjc1LUllMTJVRU9vbmppUWh4dE0ySjhvYU9iNTd4cWh4UUtCN2h5Y3E4S3UxSV82RmVMcTZabmJBcUxoUXNLejdyOFlLNQ</guid></item><item><title>总是有压力？高皮质醇正在悄悄地“杀死”脑细胞，甚至会损害记忆， RESEARC -印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/always-stressed-high-cortisol-is-quietly-killing-brain-cells-and-can-even-impair-memory-says-research/articleshow/123652966.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forgetfulness, brain fog, and difficulty in concentrating are all-too-familiar complaints in today's hectic life. Though these symptoms are most typically blamed on aging, lack of sleep, or distraction, there can be a less apparent, often undervalued offender: cortisol- the body's natural stress hormone. But when cortisol is elevated for hours, it has a profound impact on memory and brain function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is cortisol and its impact&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5619133/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Cortisol &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;is secreted by the adrenal glands due to physical or emotional stress. Its principal role is to assist in regulating the metabolism, blood sugar, blood pressure, and immune system. In a brief, stressful encounter, cortisol enhances concentration and gives access to additional energy. This is one of the body's most important defense mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Issues occur when stress is chronic and cortisol remains heightened for extended periods. Chronic exposure to high cortisol has been associated with numerous health issues, such as diminished cognitive function, mood swings, and even alterations in the brain's structure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Have you ever sought medical advice for symptoms related to high cortisol?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The brain on cortisol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most important impacts of cortisol is in the brain, and that is in the hippocampus. That region of the brain is at the center of learning and memory creation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research indicates that too much cortisol can reduce the size of the hippocampus, shutting out the brain from forming and remembering things properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cortisol also disrupts neurogenesis, the process whereby new brain cells are created. The fewer new brain cells there are, the less there is room for storing memories and the more delayed processing of new material. It can lead to persistent forgetfulness and inability to focus in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further, cortisol interferes with sleep. Proper sleeping is vital to memory consolidation, and chronic sleep interference by excessive cortisol continues to have an impact on cognitive functioning. Without proper rest, the brain is unable to carry out memory-based processes effectively, establishing a cycle of mental tiredness and poor mental sharpness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the research says&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientific research continues to confirm the connection between high cortisol and impaired memory. A recent study published in the&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6405479/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; journal Neurology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in 2018 observed that individuals who had high levels of cortisol during middle life had reduced brain volumes and lower memory functioning even when not showing symptoms of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still another study by researchers at the University of Iowa discovered that prolonged exposure of cortisol in animal models caused loss of memory. Surprisingly, with cortisol returning to its baseline levels, some cognitive abilities started to recover, indicating that damage can be reversible with appropriate interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research titled "&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27918271/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Stress-induced cortisol hampers memory generalisation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;" it clearly shows that participants who were exposed to stress before learning tasks, demonstrated a significant reduction in their ability to generalise learned associations to new, untrained pairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Cortisol's role&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The observed deficit in memory generalisation was closely linked to magnitude of cortisol increase following the stressor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;These results mirror clinical reports of anxious and depressed patients, two illnesses both of which are typically accompanied by dysregulated cortisol. Memory impairment is a common complaint among such patients, further attesting to the role of cortisol in memory impairment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Indications of excess cortisol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identification of indications of excessive cortisol could be a first step to reversing memory impairment. Symptoms commonly observed are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recurrent forgetfulness or mental fogginess&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Impaired concentration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Insomnia or disturbed sleep&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chronic fatigue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Increased irritability or mood swings&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Weight gain, particularly in the belly region&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although all these symptoms can be a result of many different things, their combination can indicate a cortisol imbalance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Natural methods to decrease cortisol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cortisol management starts with minor lifestyle tweaks. By means of regular exercise, proper sleep quantity and quality, minimising caffeine intake, and consuming whole foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some cases, medical testing is advised. It may be recommended for a healthcare provider to run tests of blood or saliva to measure cortisol levels and direct subsequent treatment as necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAJBVV95cUxNXzJOYnhROHBwX1YyMktCVVJ4NFVvUnhLSWh2WFJ5dExlb05BamRtTzBhdHUtdmlMUFhjSkdHMkl2TkE2bXdqbG8wQjZGOXJxM1ZDTEFpWlNYVHRSQ1VUbElwd2JTak1LdS1SdzZQX2l1TDVob0RMcDFlZHNfRWs3NHpvczRuTlhRdmxnNUJVSmNLMFU1UDB5SmNodWJXbGFOdFNuZU1jVHZFOGtKeEFGbnRTMkZDazIzdEFXMTVFdTNUMjVnQjVETXRDVG5fX2UyYmx0SVEzZ19EVk1WU0V4ME80Y3g1YnQtNXVvbllzZExCSVJXVGJkdk5wdGJCakhjdmhnbDJBRFVENUttOHJtTE9iZXlyeXFQ</guid></item><item><title>根据纽约一位顶级心脏病学家的说法，高血压症状往往被忽视-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/high-blood-pressure-symptoms-that-often-go-unnoticed-according-to-a-top-ny-cardiologist/articleshow/123864579.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly half of adults in the United States have high blood pressure (48.1%, 119.9 million). Hypertension was the primary contributor of 664,470 deaths in 2023, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/high-blood-pressure/about/index.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;). What’s worse is that about 46% are unaware that they have this &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;condition&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. If left untreated, high blood pressure or hypertension can put you at a greater risk of heart attack, stroke, kidney disease, and even early death. High blood pressure is often called a ‘silent killer’ as symptoms are largely absent, and some of the subtle signs get dismissed. Dr Evan Levine, a board-certified cardiologist with over 30 years of experience, has now explained some of the most common symptoms of hypertension. Let’s take a look. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Natural Ways to Control High Blood Pressure Effectively&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What is hypertension?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hypertension (high blood pressure) occurs when the pressure in the blood vessels is too high. Normal blood pressure is less than 120/80 mm Hg. Blood pressure that is consistently at or above 130/80 mm Hg is considered high blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though the blood pressure varies throughout the day depending on the activities, consistent blood pressure is a warning sign. Over time, this high blood pressure damages the arteries, leading to serious complications like a heart attack and stroke. Catching it early is crucial for a healthy life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Have you ever experienced any symptoms related to hypertension?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Symptoms of hypertension&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Headache:&lt;/strong&gt; “It can be across the head or in the back,” the doctor explains in a &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DOI0UFbjmwg/?igsh=ZG1zN3ZrYzZpZjM3" target="_blank"&gt;video&lt;/a&gt; shared on Instagram.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blurred vision:&lt;/strong&gt; It is a common symptom; however, it's often dismissed as other, less severe illnesses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shortness of breath:&lt;/strong&gt; If you find yourself gasping for air, usually when you're walking, it is a warning sign. “But if it gets really severe, you can get short of breath even at rest,” the cardiologist says.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chest pain:&lt;/strong&gt; According to Dr. Levine, it almost feels “like angina that we call when you're walking because the heart is working too hard.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nosebleed:&lt;/strong&gt; Some people complain of nosebleeds. “We call it epistaxis. Some people don't believe in that,” he adds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frothy urine:&lt;/strong&gt; “It's frothy because you're spilling protein when you go to the bathroom. You may notice that,” he explains. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Pulmonary Hypertension: Recognizing the critical symptoms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;#1 symptom of hypertension&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes high blood pressure especially dangerous is that it shows no symptoms in most people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The number one symptom of hypertension. The most common symptom by far, everyone should know about is nothing. That's right! That's why we call it the silent killer,” Dr. Levine explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cardiologist suggests getting blood pressure checked often to catch it early. “You need to get your blood pressure checked at least annually. Now, if you can't afford to see a physician, well, check it at home. Get an Omron blood pressure cuff at the store or Amazon. Watch a YouTube video before and share the cuff with your friends and family,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Remember, the most common symptom of hypertension is nothing. You don't want to present with heart failure, a stroke, or a heart attack because you didn't check your blood pressure,” the cardiologist stresses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This information is for educational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult your physician or a qualified healthcare provider regarding any questions you may have about high blood pressure or any medical condition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgJBVV95cUxPdmpHVnlzb1NVdXZ4eVVpU0YtVDVfaXdhU2JZeVVCWXJnRnhCem9UdjhfRFNqT28zRjdTWmpLRndSZmNhRXNtZHhxMHV4and5N3lieDRxdWJkbEVvSGtEQllyT2hFSHZJbEM4TkJQSnVhMVphU1BiUVNMZV9OeEhvZVI3aGctWnl4bmNrSjU5YlVpa3o0alJsRlRsQ3hTQ0F4eFBfRkJFdlpGTlZrcXNnenQ4SGhGd0pKY28tUldiY3N4MmRhdDJDOHdDQ0VhT3cxd0VvcGwtLUQyY01NajFKQWF5Q0pVc2JVeXNoMko0OHVKbThSenZicG1MVUtaZEMyb3hwaXZLVWh6ODFYd0xkdXhBS3B4QQ</guid></item><item><title>南美锥虫病： “接吻虫”在美国蔓延- DW</title><link>https://www.dw.com/en/chagas-disease-kissing-bug-spreads-in-the-us/a-73981994</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-tracking-name="rich-text" data-tracking-skip="true" class="c17j8gzx rc0m0op r1ebneao s198y7xq rich-text l1evdo4u blt0baw s16w0xvi rcjjkz7 w128axg5 b1fzgn0z"&gt;&lt;p&gt;US health authorities are on alert as cases of Chagas disease, originating from South America, are increasingly being detected in the &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/united-states-of-america/t-19065189"&gt;United States&lt;/a&gt;. Cases have now been reported in at least eight states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Researchers at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) are now about to &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://wwwnc.cdc.gov/eid/article/31/9/24-1700_article" title="External link — categorize the infectious disease as endemic"&gt;categorize the infectious disease as endemic&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; , meaning occurring regularly within an area or community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is not just a medical formality but a wake-up call: The disease would no longer be considered an imported tropical disease but regarded as a permanently present health risk in the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The proposed classification would have far-reaching consequences for monitoring, research and treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Disease transmitted by bug's bite&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The disease is passed on by the Trypanosoma cruzi parasite, which is found in various predatory bug species. The insect acquired the nickname "kissing bug" because it often bites sleeping humans in the face, in particular its more thin-skinned parts, such as lips or eyelids.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It's not the bite itself that is dangerous, but the feces of the bug that contain the pathogen. By scratching the wound or rubbing the eyes the parasite makes its way into the body. Less frequently, &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/infectious-diseases/t-71255642"&gt;people are infected&lt;/a&gt; via blood transfusions, organ transplants or during a pregnancy from mother to child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="placeholder-image master_landscape big"&gt;&lt;img data-format="MASTER_LANDSCAPE" data-id="66137086" data-url="https://static.dw.com/image/66137086_${formatId}.jpg" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" alt="Hand in a latex glove holds tweezers and a bed bug"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="img-caption"&gt;The Chagas disease is passed on by the Trypanosoma cruzi parasite, which is found in various predatory bugs&lt;small class="copyright"&gt;Image: DW&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;WHO warns of neglected danger&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The disease was named after Brazilian doctor Carlos Chagas, who discovered it in 1907. By now, Chagas is no longer some exotic tropical disease. Through migration, blood transfusions and global trade routes Chagas also found its way to Europe and North America. According to estimates, there are some 6,000 infected people in Spain and several hundred thousand in the US. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/world-health-organization-who/t-38396203"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt; estimates that, &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://www.who.int/campaigns/world-chagas-disease-day/2025" title="External link — worldwide, over seven million people are infected with the pathogen"&gt;worldwide, over seven million people are infected with the pathogen&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and that some 10,000 die each year as a result of the infection. The disease is particularly widespread in Latin America's poor regions, which is why the WHO classifies it as a "neglected disease." Due to new data from the US the potentially lethal "disease of the poor" is now increasingly receiving international attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span data-slot-id="Article_InContent-1" class="rich-text-ad"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What are the symptoms of Chagas disease?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The infection has two stages. Many of those affected don't notice any symptoms during the first weeks or months after the infection. Some develop unspecific symptoms such as fever, fatigue or swellings next to the wound, typically an eyelid edema, a painless, one-sided swelling of the eyelid which is often accompanied by conjunctivitis. Afterwards, those ailments usually disappear again, but the parasite remains in the body. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a lag period that can take years, the chronic phase of the infection can break out. This comes with has serious consequences. Myocarditis, permanent heart failure, or cardiac arrhythmia have been documented, as well as pathological enlargement of esophagus and colon. Up to 30% of those infected develop such complications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The WHO warns that, without treatment, the disease can be life-threatening, primarily for babies, children or people with a weakened immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c44391" data-lang-code="en" data-id="68339716" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;How can Chagas disease be treated?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the acute phase, the parasite can be detected microscopically in the blood. In later stages, antibody tests are the most important diagnostic tool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far, there is no vaccine. Treatment is based on two antiparasitic drugs, Nifurtimox and Benznidazole, which are particularly effective during the acute phase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Both medications, however, can cause severe side effects and are &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://www.ema.europa.eu/en/medicines/human/paediatric-investigation-plans/emea-003134-pip01-21" title="External link — not yet officially approved for treatment of the Chagas disease"&gt;not yet officially approved for treatment of the Chagas disease&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in the &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/european-union-eu/t-17440066"&gt;EU&lt;/a&gt;, for example. In the US, the drugs can usually be administered during inpatient treatment only. In chronic cases, the therapy just alleviates the symptoms; so far the disease can hardly be prevented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="embed yt-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Pets and wild animals can get infected too&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only humans are sought-after victims: Dogs, cats, rats, armadillos and opossums are also considered important hosts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Texas and California, in particular, are now increasingly reporting infected dogs, which indicates that circulation of the pathogen is already established in the south of the US.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;How to protect against Chagas disease?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to prevent an infection, expert recommend strict protection against insects. In affected regions, nets treated with insecticide, the sealing of house walls and specific pes control can help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For pets, veterinarians recommend medication which is also used against fleas and ticks. In many countries, blood donations are now routinely tested for the pathogen, in order to prevent an infection by blood transfusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article was originally written in German.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DW</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 05:44:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQdTFVWmliWXlkOGl6Sk5tUzFRQVlMaUw0MEl2UkRaV3hBMXVUVk8zcThNclBYdHRVbTh1bkYxc3V1QXo5VFRfYjN6Z09Lek5uS3lUb0wtTUdkYTZ6dHRkWUx0YXdheE5IM2xHWlZ5Y2NfN3lLZWNjUXJ4RnRLN0FTLUpjb9IBgwFBVV95cUxObzNkZzFYajBvSWdwY0VkeTh1Q29fS1lFWXFLRmxRckJOM05KamJOS2dHR0tBNFdhWExqaW42RG5GelhBbEt6RUVSbU5GWG1TTmw5Y3RPZDNsX0w2Z0FWbW50am1SQUpINmlMV1JZM1k0cENZLVlIZGRHU0ZwN3B4czRPTQ</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，心脏病发作可能与细菌感染有关-今日医学新闻</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/heart-attacks-may-be-linked-to-bacterial-infections-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-yhe8zq"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/botton-heart-attack-concept-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/botton-heart-attack-concept-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/botton-heart-attack-concept-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/botton-heart-attack-concept-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="concept illustration of a heart" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Fheart-attacks-may-be-linked-to-bacterial-infections-study-finds&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F09%2Fbotton-heart-attack-concept-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Could%20bacterial%20infections%20trigger%20heart%20attacks%3F" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/09/botton-heart-attack-concept-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-13b3g0x"&gt;Bacterial infections may sometimes trigger heart attacks, a new study says. Image credit: Viaframe/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In 2022, about 19.8 million people globally died from heart disease, with about 85% of these deaths attributed to stroke and heart attack. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Previous research has linked bacterial infections as a risk factor for heart disease. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Past studies have also linked bacterial infections to an increased risk of arterial plaque buildup.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new study has now identified specific bacteria typically found in the mouth and throat, which researchers believe may be a trigger for a heart attack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medically known as myocardial infarction, a heart attack occurs when blood in the &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/arteries" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;arteries&lt;/a&gt; is blocked from being able to reach the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous research has linked &lt;hl-trusted-source source="AHA/ASA Journals" rationale="Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/JAHA.118.009683" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;bacterial infections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; from bacteria that have entered the body’s bloodstream as a risk factor for heart disease. Furthermore, past studies have also linked bacterial infections to an &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9731758/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;increased risk&lt;/a&gt; of arterial plaque buildup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Pekka-Karhunen/6" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Pekka J. Karhunen&lt;/a&gt;, MD, PhD, a professor in the Faculty of Medicine and Health Technology at Tampere University in Finland, told &lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt; that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The possibility that infectious agents are involved in the chronic inflammation of coronary plaques has been considered for a long time, but this theory was abandoned about 20 years ago due to failed large long-term antibiotics trials. The interest has now been renewed due to the development of molecular microbiological methods that enable the identification of bacterial DNA even in small amounts of biological specimens.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Karhunen is the first author of a new study recently published in the &lt;hl-trusted-source source="AHA/ASA Journals" rationale="Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/JAHA.125.041521" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Journal of the American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;, which has found that bacteria typically found in the mouth and throat may be a trigger for a heart attack. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this study, researchers analyzed coronary plaque samples from 121 people who had died from &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/sudden-cardiac-arrest" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;sudden cardiac death&lt;/a&gt;, and from 96 people who had undergone surgery to have the plaque from their arteries cleaned, a procedure known as an &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/what-is-endarterectomy" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;endarterectomy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At the study’s conclusion, the scientists discovered that the bacteria &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10917554/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;viridans group Streptococci&lt;/a&gt; — an umbrella-term for types of &lt;em&gt;Streptococcus&lt;/em&gt; bacteria commonly found in the mouth, in &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/salivary-glands" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;saliva&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/plaque-vs-tartar" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;dental plaque&lt;/a&gt; — were the most common bacteria in the coronary plaque samples. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Oral viridans group Streptococci are known to act as early colonizers in the buildup of the dental biofilm known as dental plaque,” Karhunen explained. “This signals that the streptococci may not be there alone — it is possible that there is a biofilm composed of many bacteria. In fact we have unpublished results confirming this.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the bacterial biofilm, the bacteria are safe inside the jelly-like cover and they do not cause any harm to the individual,” he continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he noted, “the situation changes dramatically when the biofilm activates for [some] reason or other, and starts to produce new generation of bacteria that break out from the biofilm and infiltrate the atherosclerotic plaque, causing inflammation that can rupture the plaque ending up in the formation of a &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/318522" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;thrombus&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We aim to show that there is a biofilm consisting of many bacteria in the atherosclerotic plaques and we also study the possibility that calcification of the biofilm — which occurs in the surface of the teeth — might also be involved in the calcification of coronary arteries,” Karhunen added. “We also studied the possibility of developing a vaccine against the formation of a biofilm and bacterial-induced thrombosis.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;MNT &lt;/em&gt;spoke with &lt;a href="https://baptisthealth.net/doctors/sergiu-darabant/1597499" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Sergiu Darabant&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a cardiologist with Miami Cardiac &amp;amp; Vascular Institute, part of Baptist Health South Florida, about this study, who said he did not find the study surprising, but intriguing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“We’ve long suspected that inflammation is a key driver of cholesterol plaque formation and plaque rupture leading to heart attacks,” Darabant, who was not involved in the research, said. “This study adds another piece to the puzzle — showing how bacteria from the mouth might play a hidden role in driving coronary inflammation.” &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Even though we’ve made significant progress over the years in the advancement of medical therapies aimed at cardiovascular risk reduction and secondary prevention of cardiovascular events, our prevention toolkit is still limited,” he continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; also spoke with &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/yu-ming-ni" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Yu-Ming Ni&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a board-certified cardiologist and lipidologist at MemorialCare Heart and Vascular Institute at Orange Coast Medical Center in Fountain Valley, CA, likewise not involved in the study, about these research findings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“&lt;/strong&gt;This bacteria, strep viridans, is a very common oral bacteria, and the fact that it seems to be implicated in atherosclerosis is interesting,” Ni commented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he cautioned that “it’s important to recognize that these studies have some limitations because you’re taking a picture in the aftermath, so you don’t have a great timeline for what exactly is happening in someone’s plaque that leads them to have this vascular event.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“So I would be cautious to just go and make the assumption that these bacteria are definitely the reason for plaque disruption. I think there’s maybe more to that than just that, but it does support the idea of inflammation as a key factor in the development of clinical heart disease.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;– Yu-Ming Ni, MD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;When hearing the term “bacterial infection,” there may be worry that you could also be at risk of acquiring it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/brett-a-sealove/1319306" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Brett A. Sealove&lt;/a&gt;, MD, FACC, FAHA, RPVI, CPE, chair of cardiology at Hackensack Meridian Jersey Shore University Medical Center, and associate professor and vice chair of cardiology at Hackensack Meridian School of Medicine in New Jersey, told &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; people need not immediately worry about strep viridans, as these bacteria are typically benign, and help maintain a healthy balance in the mouth and body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“These bacteria live synergistically within the human body, most abundantly in the oral cavity as well as the respiratory and gastrointestinal tracts,” Sealove detailed.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“However,“ he explained, “problems arise when they enter the body — mostly via the mouth — and can cause other infections, most notably an infection of &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/heart-valves" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;heart valves&lt;/a&gt;, called &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/151016" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;endocarditis&lt;/a&gt;. So, they are benign and normally found in the body. It’s their displacement and travel that can potentially cause harm.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no vaccine approved for strep viridans, &lt;a href="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/edward-w-liu/1316101" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Edward Liu&lt;/a&gt;, MD, MPH, FACP, FIDSA, chief of infectious diseases at Hackensack Meridian Jersey Shore University Medical Center in New Jersey told &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Strep viridans is common and expected to be in parts of the body, especially the mouth,” Liu explained. “I would not expect other strep vaccines — for example, &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/pneumonia-vaccine-how-often" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;strep pneumonia vaccines&lt;/a&gt; like pneumovax or prevnar 13 or 20 — to protect against strep viridans.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liu recommended treating any active infections in a timely manner, as they occur:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For example, a dental infection may likely include strep viridans as well as other bacteria found in the mouth. We know that severe dental infections can lead to bacteria in the blood, so timely treatment of dental infections could be beneficial.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking of dental care, Sealove said that optimizing one’s &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/324708" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;oral hygiene&lt;/a&gt; and seeking dental treatment where necessary is a way to help people protect themselves from bacterial infections that may lead to heart attack. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8457130/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;oral-systemic link&lt;/a&gt; is backed by an abundance of growing evidence, and very much supported by this article, which focuses on the connection between oral and systemic health,” he explained. “The mouth provides function and aesthetics but also is an active ecosystem which needs to be healthy, and can impact one’s systemic health — especially the cardiovascular system.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These reduce risk of severe infections, which have been associated with cardiovascular events, especially in high-risk and post-myocardial infarction patients,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 05:29:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPT3FqWks2cVQtby1PVExVYXZ4dDhCQVJOUXVMWWN4aEdobS0zMzhTRXlZWS02cWdqRjlpbkVIQ1lVOEEyZF80RFlxRVlTT2h2ZFAxalQwRUxLMGt1N1Z1Vl9KWnIzaW1MZlkzNm5aWEg4TTlBRXFObndNWS1YSDZHZFRRV1AtUGxQQ0FqOFBqWE5IV01NalB0eU1Mai1hcGxia2F0QTF1X0I</guid></item><item><title>随着疾病预防控制中心推动大规模疫苗接种，高传染性病毒的住院率接近历史新高-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15093155/Hospitalizations-record-high-highly-contagious-virus-CDC-mass-vaccinations.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hospitalizations linked to the &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/flu/index.html" id="mol-01de0130-9008-11f0-a9b3-618ddb70db89"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt; reached the highest levels in over a decade last season, according to &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/centers-for-disease-control-and-prevention-cdc/index.html" id="mol-01dd64f0-9008-11f0-a9b3-618ddb70db89"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt; reporting that comes ahead of what could be another severe flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;During the 2024-2025 flu season, hospitals saw an unusually high number of severe flu cases. A tracking system recorded nearly 39,000 people hospitalized with the flu between October and April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This made it a much more severe season than usual. The total hospitalization rate was 127.1 per 100,000 people, more than double the average of the previous 14 flu seasons, and was the worst season on record since at least 2010. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The season hit its&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14389303/Covid-officially-deadly-seasonal-flu.html"&gt; peak in early February&lt;/a&gt;, when hospitals were admitting people for the flu at the highest weekly rate seen in over a decade. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Unvaccinated patients made up the overwhelming majority of hospitalizations, accounting for more than 70 percent of admissions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The clinical outcomes for those in the hospital were consistent with past severe seasons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 17 percent of patients required care in the intensive care unit (ICU), six percent needed a ventilator to breathe, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14673485/child-flu-deaths-highest-swine-flu-outbreak-cdc.html"&gt;and three percent died&lt;/a&gt; during their hospitalization, though researchers did not provide a single, exact number of total deaths. The most common complications were &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/pneumonia/index.html" id="mol-01df87d0-9008-11f0-a9b3-618ddb70db89"&gt;pneumonia&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/sepsis/index.html" id="mol-01dffd00-9008-11f0-a9b3-618ddb70db89" class=""&gt;sepsis&lt;/a&gt;, and kidney failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Unvaccinated patients made up the overwhelming majority of flu hospitalizations, accounting for more than 70 percent of admissions, according to new CDC data&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the vast majority, around 85 percent, of hospital patients received antiviral medication like Tamiflu, which can reduce the severity and duration of illness, treatment rates were lowest among children and adolescents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This is likely because parents are more likely to believe it is a mild illness for children and that their robust immune systems can easily fight it off. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But this is not always the case. CDC researchers did not quantify how many children died last flu season, but the American Academy of Pediatrics put the death toll last season &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://publications.aap.org/aapnews/news/32150/Pediatric-flu-deaths-hit-record-high-for-non?autologincheck=redirected"&gt;at 216&lt;/a&gt;, making it the deadliest non-pandemic flu season on record for U.S. children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists affiliated with the WHO and the CDC meet every year to determine which strains the upcoming season’s flu vaccine should prioritize. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The vaccine formula doesn’t always align perfectly with the circulating virus. However, on average, flu vaccines reduce the risk of needing to visit the doctor by 30 percent to 60 percent and drastically reduce the severity of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Protection wanes throughout the season, so October is the best time to get vaccinated. The CDC recommends annual flu shots for everyone six months and older, including young, healthy people with no underlying conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Selecting the strains for the annual flu vaccine requires health officials to predict which viruses will dominate the upcoming season. The vaccine's effectiveness hinges entirely on the accuracy of their forecast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Last season, the CDC estimated the vaccine was between 41 percent and 78 percent effective at preventing flu-related hospitalizations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;With a rate of 127.1 hospitalizations per 100,000 people, the 2024-25 flu season was significantly more severe than historical norms, surpassing the previous 14-season average of 62&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Its effectiveness at preventing less severe infections that still required a doctor's visit ranged from 32 percent to 60 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Most people with the flu recover within a few days or a week. But the flu kills about 36,000 Americans every year, and it can be more dangerous than people think, especially for seniors 75 and up, people with respiratory conditions such as asthma, people with obesity and/or heart disease and the unvaccinated.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In addition to common symptoms, including fever, muscle aches, respiratory infection, chills, and fatigue, the flu can cause life-threatening complications, such as pneumonia, a bloodstream infection called sepsis, inflammation of the heart and brain, and muscle inflammation or damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The latest data from the CDC reflect the most recent flu season recorded in the agency’s surveillance system, FluSurv-NET. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The system collects data from roughly 300 hospitals across 14 states, effectively monitoring a sample that represents about nine percent of the US population, or around 31 million people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The system focuses on laboratory-confirmed flu cases that are severe enough to require hospitalization, tracking individuals from infants to seniors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For a carefully selected subset of patients out of the thousands reported, researchers pulled detailed clinical information from medical records to determine whether patients had underlying health conditions, their vaccination status and whether they required intensive care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For children, the most significant risk factor for hospitalization was asthma. It was the most common pre-existing condition for 14 percent of hospitalized toddlers and preschoolers up to four years old and nearly 40 percent of school-aged children and teens from five to 17.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Last flu season, Influenza A was the dominant and most severe virus type. While the H1N1 strain was more common overall and posed a greater threat to seniors, this was a reversal from the last severe season, 2017-18, when the H3N2 strain was the main risk for that age group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For young adults aged 18 to 49, obesity was the dominant risk factor, present in about 44 percent of hospitalized patients in this age group. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In adults aged 50 to 64, chronic metabolic diseases, primarily diabetes, took the lead, affecting 45.6 percent of patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For seniors, cardiovascular disease was the most significant risk factor, found in 57 percent of adults aged 65 to 74 and an overwhelming 69 percent of those aged 75 and older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The flu season was historically severe, with hospitals having seen more flu patients per week than in any other season since 2010–2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;No age group was spared. Hospitalization rates were two to three times higher across all ages compared to the average of the past 14 seasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As in most flu seasons, adults 75 and older were hit hardest, with a rate of nearly 599 hospitalizations per 100,000 people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This was the second-highest rate on record for seniors, but it was the worst season ever recorded for every other age group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thirty percent of patients developed pneumonia, making it the most common complication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 18.5 percent of cases, the infection spiraled into sepsis, a catastrophic full-body inflammatory response, and caused acute kidney failure in another 18 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This severe season was primarily driven by influenza A viruses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The H1N1 strain was more prevalent overall, but, notably, it caused higher hospitalization rates among older adults compared to the H3N2 strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This marked a reversal from the last severe season, 2017-2018, when H3N2 was the dominant and more dangerous strain for seniors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The 2025–2026 flu vaccine is trivalent, meaning it protects against three strains: an influenza A(H1N1)-like virus, an influenza A(H3N2)-like virus, and an influenza B/Victoria lineage-like virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The flu shot is typically free with insurance. Almost all insurers are required to cover shots recommended by the CDC, including flu shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Without insurance, though, the price can change based on the pharmacy, ranging from $20 to $120. Public clinics also generally offer free flu shots.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 05:18:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiywFBVV95cUxNMWx2blZkYkg0bG5yazgxaUhyanl2Qzc3R180VlpxWV85Uk9HRjFpMFdGWS1QUmJPaDhyLTZEcURrNGVCRHZyWng1T3R6MEppbnVYa1ZFdERtZWhvMmhlUnpTc3o3c0tRWnhWajhvRWRzZWRUSHBxSW1aamttZWdzbnpVZUMtRC1WbjAyMFZXS1JyX3JzNkJmU0NmQjJ1NXJvTllhd1FBa0Q0QmM0Zmw3MTM5WEloMTVzOTNrZFhGYm1zMERSVVdsMkJ0d9IB0AFBVV95cUxPd3d4TDFrZlo3Wkw5bFViMUkzNDhVZFZxVmJUdzZteDdsWDlFUWNCd3NXX0dDQTdGTGR0LU1GNmhKYXlkMHRucXFrUFV5STV0ZlNpMjBCeFE1Snd6ZGpEaF9TWnBiY3l3TXJUVzFuR3lWeDIwYW00NmEzSlZPZzBjcWJMdVZRUnliVzdaTEFJUVZlQnR4NUFBRkp3eEJObGdjekRoZWk3QlJpMmt6SnRZYXVFR21MV2lxeHVlN2JhQWNjdXMwMnZrME9DMG9WWDNo</guid></item><item><title>一位营养专家说，持久的减肥需要可持续的、现实的改变--她推荐了五个--Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/weight-loss/a-nutrition-expert-says-lasting-weight-loss-requires-sustainable-realistic-changes-here-are-five-she-recommends</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="17a61402-55cf-45f5-858f-a89aeed9a57b"&gt;Weight loss is a complex and emotive process, with many factors at play that can impact results. And keeping the weight off can be even harder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Biologically, our bodies are designed to defend against losing weight,” says &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://staff.lincoln.ac.uk/5161f952-8468-4714-88f3-782a81998e49" target="_blank" data-url="https://staff.lincoln.ac.uk/5161f952-8468-4714-88f3-782a81998e49" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Dr Rachel Woods&lt;/a&gt;, a senior lecturer in physiology at the University of Lincoln in the U.K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="17a61402-55cf-45f5-858f-a89aeed9a57b-2"&gt;“When we reduce calorie intake, the body responds by slowing metabolism and increasing hunger signals, essentially trying to conserve energy,” says Woods, who has spent nearly 15 years working in and around health and nutrition research. “This makes sustaining weight loss very difficult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“On top of this, we live in an environment that poses significant challenges. Busy lives, long working hours and easy access to convenient, energy-dense foods make it hard to adhere to calorie-restricted diets consistently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Social pressures, stress and fatigue can also contribute to people choosing less nutritious foods. Together, these biological and environmental factors create a perfect storm that makes weight loss a real challenge for many people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And keeping it off can be even harder, says Woods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Many people are able to manage the challenges of calorie restriction for a limited period, which is often enough to achieve the initial weight loss they’re looking for. During this time, motivation is high and the effort feels purposeful. However, sustaining the same level of restraint over the long term is so much harder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-mBsCicXTuMVJWuSNQbHLyH" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-mBsCicXTuMVJWuSNQbHLyH slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The body continues to resist weight loss, with hunger signals remaining stronger and metabolism slightly slowed. Coupled with the mental and physical effort required to consistently eat differently from your habits or environment, maintaining that calorie deficit over months and years becomes extremely challenging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is why long-term weight maintenance is often harder than the initial weight loss phase, and why sustainable, realistic changes are essential for lasting success.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what does Woods recommend as the best approach to losing weight and keeping it off?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My advice is to focus less on weight itself and more on improving diet and lifestyle for overall health,” says Woods. “Weight loss may follow naturally as a result. If someone specifically wants to lose weight, the key is to adopt habits that are sustainable in the long term.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are the five habits that Woods recommends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-step-one-eat-more-plants" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-step-one-eat-more-plants"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step one: Eat more plants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check id="a11024f9-9b60-411d-b546-55ed9ee11df6"&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / 10'000 Hours)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="602fa057-45f7-41a2-a02e-1229929e5858"&gt;“Fruits, vegetables, beans and lentils are nutrient-dense, high in fiber and relatively low in calories. Increasing these foods in your meals helps you feel full and may naturally reduce the intake of higher-calorie snacks,” says Woods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-step-two-prioritise-whole-foods-over-heavily-processed-ones" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-step-two-prioritise-whole-foods-over-heavily-processed-ones"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step two: Prioritise whole foods over heavily processed ones&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="7ceb2272-cd88-490f-b0d9-5eb026168c50"&gt;“Whole foods are generally more filling, nutrient-rich and less likely to make you overeat. A simple way to identify processed snacks is to check the ingredient list and choose foods made from ingredients you recognise and can pronounce,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-step-three-reduce-alcohol-intake" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-step-three-reduce-alcohol-intake"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step three: Reduce alcohol intake&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="a839a916-fa8a-4e7f-8f1e-f84afaf216c5"&gt;“Alcohol adds extra calories without filling you up and has a negative impact on many areas of health. Cutting back can have a significant impact over time,” says Woods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-step-four-consider-portion-adjustments-strategically" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-step-four-consider-portion-adjustments-strategically"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step four: Consider portion adjustments strategically&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="820ed4ea-f70e-4da2-982b-4cbe9ea8231a"&gt;“Rather than simply eating smaller portions of everything, which can leave you hungry, try increasing your portions of low-calorie, nutrient-dense foods such as fruits, vegetables and salads while moderating higher-calorie items,” says Woods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-step-five-choose-sugar-free-drinks-or-water-instead-of-sodas" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-step-five-choose-sugar-free-drinks-or-water-instead-of-sodas"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Step five: Choose sugar-free drinks or water instead of sodas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="1fef162e-158e-4d97-8ea3-51610af51551"&gt;“If you drink a lot of sugary beverages, this is an easy swap that reduces calorie intake,” says Woods. “The overarching principle is sustainability. Small, consistent changes are better than drastic restrictions that are hard to maintain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-what-about-exercise" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-what-about-exercise"&gt;&lt;span&gt;What about exercise?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="3300e9c6-646d-49b1-b2f8-0f523549f363"&gt;“Diet generally has a larger impact on creating a calorie deficit, but exercise is also incredibly valuable for overall health. It supports cardiovascular fitness, strengthens muscles and bones, improves mood and sleep, and helps manage stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When combined with dietary changes, exercise can help protect against weight regain, support metabolic health and improve body composition—for example, maintaining lean muscle while losing fat. So, while it may not always be the fastest route to weight loss, it’s critical for long-term health and wellbeing.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5AFBVV95cUxPbExzM1lvUVFfV0JuYkxuR0V6ckhFZHJBdy1nU01hRVFGRWtiWEtqU1A3cnBadW9Za0hxaXM1azdZTTFhVndzanhDZVpQM1hSaTJnYXcxOTRVQW9YQlVQX1NjVlVGbmRjZVZCYk0wSXhCQzJZZWhqYnhOQ2NLaVp3WkZmZ3g0aTU2WWNIMXpaR195UUVJUE5zUUxuRW5LYkg5OFZlczBlb1BWaGlhWjFyb1JCZWRDcnNnSklTSERLTW9OaXc2SEJIZzltcHBTMTk3NUx3WkkxU2RoVDk4dzFWVlRyWEQ</guid></item></channel></rss>