<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>下一代抗癌mRNA疫苗可能已经到来- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/cancer-fighting-mrna-vaccine-may-already-rcna238197</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7c6401" class="body-graf"&gt;Covid vaccines may come with a tantalizing benefit that has nothing to do with the virus they’re designed to protect against: boosting the immune system to better fight tumors during cancer treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0fe91c" class="body-graf"&gt;That’s according to new results presented Sunday in Berlin at the European Society for Medical Oncology conference. The research is still in the earlier stages — it has yet to be tested in a Phase 3 clinical trial — but experts say it shows promise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-15bc07" class="body-graf"&gt;“I am cautiously optimistic,” said Stephanie Dougan, an associate professor of cancer immunology and virology at the Dana-Farber Cancer Institute, who was not involved with the work. “There is a scientific logic to why this could work.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f47922" class="body-graf"&gt;Researchers found that among &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/jimmy-carter-drug-immunotherapy-melanoma-rcna153166" target="_blank"&gt;cancer patients getting immunotherapy&lt;/a&gt;, those who got an mRNA Covid vaccine within 100 days before starting their treatment lived longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e80ffa" class="body-graf"&gt;Only about &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/inhealth/about-us/immunotherapy-precision-medicine-action-policy-brief" target="_blank"&gt;20% of cancer patients&lt;/a&gt; who get immunotherapy — which harnesses a person’s immune system to fight cancer cells — respond to the treatment. Finding a way to boost the effectiveness of immunotherapy drugs has been a feat researchers have been exploring for years, with little success.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-85eda2" class="body-graf"&gt;Typically, the immune-stimulating tactics employed in the past have either done too little to activate the immune system or done too much, triggering an overactive response that can damage the body. There’s a chance that mRNA Covid vaccines could exist in a Goldilocks zone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c8f6b6" class="body-graf"&gt;“Maybe we just needed something that was medium-strong, and this could potentially be it,” said Dougan, who emphasized the need for more research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9e2707" class="body-graf"&gt;That research will soon be underway: Dr. Adam Grippin, a senior resident in radiation oncology at the University of Texas MD Anderson Cancer Center who co-led the study, said his team is launching a Phase 3 clinical trial to confirm the initial results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e4ae7d" class="body-graf"&gt;In the research presented Sunday, Grippin and his co-authors looked back at survival rates among more than 1,000 people who had advanced non-small cell lung cancer and got &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/cancer-patients-immunotherapy-may-way-skip-surgery-chemo-rcna203038" target="_blank"&gt;immunotherapy&lt;/a&gt; as part of their treatment from 2019 through 2023. Of those, 180 people received an mRNA Covid vaccine within 100 days of starting treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8fa811" class="body-graf"&gt;The median survival for the group — when exactly half of those who underwent treatment are still alive — was nearly twice as long for those who were vaccinated compared to those who were not: about three years compared to just over 1.5 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0d2582" class="body-graf"&gt;The researchers also compared the survival rates in a smaller group of patients getting immunotherapy for metastatic melanoma. Forty-three got an mRNA Covid vaccine; 167 did not. For those who didn’t get vaccinated, median survival was just over two years. Those who were vaccinated prior to treatment hadn’t yet reached their median survival point more than three years into follow-up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-eaa50b" class="body-graf"&gt;In further experiments in mice, the researchers got an answer they believe matches the way the vaccines work in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1c77d9" class="body-graf"&gt;“It superdrives the immune system against tumors,” Grippin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-d9c2d1" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Creating a beacon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fed3a3" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/mrna-vaccine-melanoma-reduces-relapse-therapy-trial-shows-rcna79543" target="_blank"&gt;Vaccines that use mRNA&lt;/a&gt; are already a promising area of cancer research. Scientists have developed &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/mrna-vaccines-frontier-cancer-treatment-rcna8886" target="_blank"&gt;personalized mRNA cancer vaccines&lt;/a&gt; that are tailored to fight a person’s unique tumor, as well as ones that target genes that are commonly found in certain types of cancer, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/cancer/pancreatic-cancer-vaccine-prevents-recurrence-phase-1-clinical-trial-rcna223980" target="_blank"&gt;including pancreatic&lt;/a&gt;. (These developments come as the Trump administration has &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/rfk-jr-cuts-500-million-mrna-vaccine-contracts-dealing-major-blow-prom-rcna223281" target="_blank"&gt;canceled half a billion dollars in funding for mRNA vaccine research&lt;/a&gt; for infectious diseases.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cc9b77" class="body-graf"&gt;If Grippin’s later trial confirms the results of the early research, it could represent the next frontier for research on mRNA vaccines and cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c9091f" class="body-graf"&gt;Immunotherapy drugs work by&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;boosting the immune system’s ability to fight cancer, often by enhancing the power of immune cells called T cells that attack invaders, or by making tumors easier for T cells to find.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6283a0" class="body-graf"&gt;The mouse portion of the new research found that Covid mRNA vaccination appeared to make the immune system more attuned to recognizing tumors as a threat by stimulating dendritic cells, a type of white blood cell. When dendritic cells detect a threat, they turn on a sort of beacon that leads T cells to the perceived invader so they can attack. However, not everyone naturally has T cells that are capable of fighting tumors, which is why scientists believe immunotherapies only work in some of the cancer patients who take them. In these people, the immune system recognizes cancer cells as a threat, but their specific T cells are unable to stop the tumors from growing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bf9c14" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s just random chance whether you have those cells or you don’t,” said Jeff Coller, a professor of RNA biology and therapeutics at Johns Hopkins Medicine, who was not involved with the research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-80e7fb" class="body-graf"&gt;Getting an mRNA Covid vaccine doesn’t change whether a person has the specific T cells needed to fight their tumors, but it does appear to make it more likely that dendritic cells will detect a tumor as a problem and direct the T cells a person does have to the tumor. If those cells happen to be programmed to be able to kill tumor cells, having an mRNA vaccine that lights up the target before a person starts an immunotherapy can give their immune system a boost that helps the cancer therapy work better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1d82c7" class="body-graf"&gt;Coller said one reason mRNA technology may be the best tool to elicit this response is because every cell in the body already contains mRNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-94efe2" class="body-graf"&gt;“We are really tapping into that natural process that your body already knows how to respond to,” he said. “You are using your body’s natural system to fight tumors.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ad698f" class="body-graf"&gt;Dougan said it’s possible that other factors could have accounted for better survival among people who were vaccinated prior to immunotherapy treatment. For example, a Covid infection may have weakened an unvaccinated person’s body and hindered their ability to fight off cancer cells. In the past, early studies like this one have shown promising results that didn’t pan out in later trials. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a6e8fe" class="body-graf"&gt;“We have been misled by retrospective studies before,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c0fbff" class="body-graf"&gt;Grippin agreed the findings warrant a closer look. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5eec04" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“This data is exciting, but all of these findings need to be validated in Phase 3 clinical trials to determine whether these vaccines should be used in our patients,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 12:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQUFFPLURKSGxoQ2NTZ1dkRTIwaEEzSVA2dmZra21LcEI2QzExQU45YXVTdE9hN2k3aGpxbjRab0M2S2JaYm14cUw5bUtyRUEtWFJicVJuVlVBam9pYzRrT09YSGxYNFBMdkJYQ2NkcU04Y05jNDNQZXhhV281eWNfMW1oU3hWVlF5OEtKYVpzLWRjTjjSAVZBVV95cUxQMVV0OHNwOG9NanpFZTJpemZGV1BOeVpicHVneThCSzQ1U0UyVjk0clJUdXNIT1ZuLS1KcDU0eDkxWlE2TW9jVU1iZ1B4WHRwdVJCS3ljdw</guid></item><item><title>失去牙齿可能是一个致命的警告，研究发现- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/losing-your-teeth-could-be-a-deadly-warning-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;How fast we lose teeth in old age has been linked to a person's &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-single-data-point-at-age-7-could-predict-how-long-youll-live"&gt;risk of dying&lt;/a&gt; in a comprehensive new study, emphasizing the importance of good oral health, and suggesting tooth loss could be a key indicator of other serious health problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tooth loss has &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jpor.2017.08.003"&gt;been connected&lt;/a&gt; to mortality before – generally, fewer teeth means a greater chance of an earlier death – but until now, there hasn't been any data on how &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials-for-drug-that-replaces-missing-teeth-finally-underway"&gt;losing teeth&lt;/a&gt; more quickly might affect this association.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get that data, a team led by researchers from Sichuan University in China looked at tooth loss in 8,073 elderly people, tracking the rate at which they lost teeth against mortality, across an average of 3.5 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/something-in-your-hair-could-make-the-ultimate-toothpaste"&gt;Something in Your Hair Could Make The Ultimate Toothpaste&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Among older adults, the risk of all-cause mortality significantly increased with a more rapid progression of tooth loss, regardless of baseline tooth count," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12877-025-06419-1"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This relationship was still present even after adjusting for several other factors that can have an influence on health and disease, including sex, age, education level, drinking habits, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/giant-study-reveals-what-happens-if-you-dont-exercise-until-the-weekend"&gt;levels of regular exercise&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177345" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177345" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/ToothLoss.jpg" alt="Tooth loss and mortality graph" class="wp-image-177345 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/ToothLoss.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/ToothLoss-600x406.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177345" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Faster tooth loss was linked to higher mortality rates. (Duan et al., &lt;em&gt;BMC Geriatr.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers aren't suggesting that quickly losing your teeth can kill you. Rather, health issues leading to tooth loss may also be shortening your life. So tooth loss could be used as an indicator to assess someone's overall health and mortality risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good oral health has long been associated with better general health as well, with links to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/disturbing-new-finding-links-cognitive-decline-to-dental-hygiene"&gt;cognitive decline&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/severe-tooth-loss-linked-to-risk-of-fatal-heart-disease-study-finds"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt; previously identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exactly why there is this correlation between tooth loss rates and mortality isn't clear. The researchers point towards inflammation, diet, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/obr.12418"&gt;obesity&lt;/a&gt;, and psychological distress as some of the factors that could be influencing both tooth loss rates and disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to diet, for example, people with fewer teeth tend to have a less well-rounded diet because it's hard to chew; the body then gets &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00784-019-03072-y"&gt;less of the nutrition it needs&lt;/a&gt;, further exacerbating health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Despite these explanations suggesting an association between tooth loss and other known mortality risk factors, the exact mechanisms remain unclear and warrant further investigation," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12877-025-06419-1"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Astro" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team behind the study is keen to promote good oral health. Regular visits to the dentist, twice-daily brushing, and quitting smoking all help keep teeth in decent shape – with prior research showing these habits &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/jgs.12225"&gt;affect how long&lt;/a&gt; elderly populations live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177347" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177347" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/MortalityRates.jpg" alt="Tooth loss and mortality rates graph" class="wp-image-177347 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/MortalityRates.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/MortalityRates-600x408.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177347" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;With each additional tooth that was lost, death became more likely. (Duan et al., &lt;em&gt;BMC Geriatr.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check-ups &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/expert-warns-why-you-should-never-become-your-own-dentist"&gt;at the dentist&lt;/a&gt; also mean tooth numbers get counted, and fixes for missing teeth (such as dentures) can be applied. This could be a reliable way of keeping tabs on older people and their risk of death and disease, the study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, research into innovative ways to replace missing teeth continues to progress. In recent months, we've seen &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/lab-grown-teeth-are-another-step-closer-to-reality-scientists-reveal"&gt;synthetic lab-grown teeth&lt;/a&gt; take another step towards becoming a reality, and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="177341" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; of a drug that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials-for-drug-that-replaces-missing-teeth-finally-underway"&gt;grows back missing teeth&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings emphasize the critical importance of monitoring tooth loss progression," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12877-025-06419-1"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is reasonable to suggest that healthcare professionals and the general public should be aware of the potential adverse prognosis associated with a rapid progression of tooth loss."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12877-025-06419-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;BMC Geriatrics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 12:01:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOc3Z2SjF0RklHcjhsZThVaHpCNng5UUdnVXJOSFYzXzBMN3NGT1Q1RlA4OUI2aWR0VnBXMDc2LWxRRzVMUWV2OS1pRU1PS3hQa0FIQUI5eW1kNS1OTThIcU1UR1U5RzNpeWlFdGV5RjVqZnJBUWRwbEhXQzJfWjIwOXRvdUw0TnVsc3JUQw</guid></item><item><title>科学家刚刚发现了神经元之间的全新连接类型- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-just-discovered-a-whole-new-type-of-connection-between-neurons</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Super-resolution microscopes have revealed a whole new type of connection between neurons in mouse and human brains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span aria-label=" " class="c-mrkdwn__br" data-stringify-type="paragraph-break"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;In the lab, Johns Hopkins University neuroscientist Minhyeok Chang and colleagues identified tiny tubular bridges in the branching tips of cultured neurons. In further tests on mouse models of Alzheimer's disease, it appeared the bridges were shuttling calcium and disease-related molecules directly between cells.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"[Similar] structures can transport a vast range of materials, from small ions (10&lt;sup&gt;−10&lt;/sup&gt;m) to large mitochondria (10&lt;sup&gt;−6&lt;/sup&gt; m)," the team &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/science.adr7403"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt; in their paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In cultured neurons, we observed these nanotubes forming dynamically and confirmed that they possessed a distinct internal structure, setting them apart from other neuronal extensions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-identified-structural-brain-wide-changes-during-menstruation"&gt;Scientists Identified Structural, Brain-Wide Changes During Menstruation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176556" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176556" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/TinyTubularNeuronBridgesFoundDiagram.jpg" alt="Diagram of the tiny tubular bridges between neurons" class="wp-image-176556 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/TinyTubularNeuronBridgesFoundDiagram.jpg 800w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/TinyTubularNeuronBridgesFoundDiagram-642x290.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/TinyTubularNeuronBridgesFoundDiagram-768x347.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/TinyTubularNeuronBridgesFoundDiagram-600x271.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176556" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Dendritic nanotubes (DNTs) form direct conduits between neurons, transporting substances such as calcium and amyloid-beta (Aβ) (A). Alterations in this network are associated in pathological Aβ accumulation (B). (Chang et al., &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neurons are well known for passing rapid messages to each other using &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Synapse"&gt;synapses&lt;/a&gt; to transmit both electrical and chemical information. Yet, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.4161/cib.2.4.8289"&gt;other cell types&lt;/a&gt; are known to use physically connecting bridging tubes to exchange molecules. Chang and team have just confirmed that a similar type of tube bridge occurs in neurons too, using advanced imaging and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73092" data-postid="176555" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers observed the nanotubes transporting amyloid-beta molecules that they had injected into mouse brain cells. These molecules have been &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/fat-buildup-in-brain-cells-could-provide-new-target-for-alzheimers-treatment"&gt;implicated in neurodegenerative diseases&lt;/a&gt; like  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="176555" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, where they tend to clump together abnormally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When researchers stopped the bridges from forming, the amyloid-beta stopped spreading between cells, too, confirming that the nanotubes acted as direct conduits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our computational model supported these findings, predicting that overactivation in the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/graphene" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73048" data-postid="176555" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;nanotube&lt;/a&gt; network could accelerate the toxic accumulation of amyloid in specific neurons, thereby providing a mechanistic link between nanotube alterations and the progression of Alzheimer's pathology," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/science.adr7403"&gt;explain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Astro" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
This is very early on in the investigation process; given that the tubes are such a new discovery, we still don't know what they naturally transport or even how often they form or function within the whole human brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But these tubes malfunctioning could also contribute to other diseases, so researchers are keen to learn more about the miniature bridges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/science.adr7403"&gt;Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 11:01:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQOWJBSGVQZk0tQlBjRG9ZU09fNnFQV1JuMzdhVjJYNDk2UHBnTm95OWZNWV96Mjd2MjlPZzVmYkV1Zy1xRkc3R3Y1V3JjV0p3eUNmRlR0Z3JWcFI3ck83dlY0Z1p3REsyd2I4Vno1Q2RPM0w3RkRadmVSX3hzaEhPbmEzS3BtejhDeHJaLUdRNnU3bzNEcjhKRnA3VktpQnpseDlldg</guid></item><item><title>抓住护目镜。匹克球眼损伤呈上升趋势- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/10/19/nx-s1-5578303/pickleball-eye-injuries-protection</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-94049" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                A hand holds a paddle against a clear blue sky, preparing to hit a yellow pickleball. The scene suggests a bright and sunny day, with the pickleball clearly in motion.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Stefania Pelfini la Waziya/Moment RF/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Stefania Pelfini la Waziya/Moment RF/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Pickleball has quickly become huge in the United States, with &lt;a href="https://sfia.org/resources/sfias-topline-participation-report-shows-247-1-million-americans-were-active-in-2024/" target="_blank"&gt;nearly 20 million&lt;/a&gt; people playing the sport.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But that popularity comes with a price. With more people on the court, pickleball-related eye injuries, including lacerations around the eye, corneal abrasions and inflamed irises, have increased. A &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaophthalmology/fullarticle/2839640?guestAccessKey=f8bad07c-53b2-464e-87f4-721d7b62884f&amp;amp;utm_source=for_the_media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_content=tfl&amp;amp;utm_term=101625" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published this week in &lt;em&gt;JAMA Ophthalmology&lt;/em&gt; estimates that the incidence of these injuries has risen dramatically, going up by an estimated 405 cases each year from 2021 to 2024.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Researchers looked at data from a representative population of patients in emergency departments across the U.S. to understand which pickleball players are especially vulnerable to eye injuries and how they occurred. From there, they estimated what those trends looked like on a national scale.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Given the "alarming" increase in eye injury cases, the study authors called for developing standardized guidelines for eye protection, which has been found to reduce up to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3862938/" target="_blank"&gt;90% of sports-related&lt;/a&gt; eye injuries. Other sports such as squash have mandated such guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The study found that 70% of cases were in adults 50 years or older. Dr. Natasha Desai, the co-director for the Center for Women's Sports Medicine at NYU Langone, was surprised to see this finding because a large share of &lt;a href="https://www.stanfordchildrens.org/en/topic/default?id=sports-injuries-statistics-90-P01650" target="_blank"&gt;sports-related injuries&lt;/a&gt; occur in young players.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Desai, who wasn't involved in this study, doesn't think the sport is necessarily getting more dangerous. "More people are playing, so there's going to be more injuries at a higher volume," she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And there are a lot of ways you can get injured in pickleball, notes Dr. Corey Lacher, an ophthalmologist resident at Rutgers New Jersey Medical School and the paper's lead author, including getting hit by the ball, a paddle or by falling.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"A lot of people think that just because it's a wiffle ball that you're not going to get hurt," he says. But, it's still risky because "everything is very fast-paced in pickleball and you're playing on a very small court."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;However, getting players to wear eye protection is easier said than done, as Desai points out. It's another piece of equipment players have to purchase and bring with them. And with so many options on the market, choosing a pair can be daunting.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Players would benefit from standardized eye protection guidelines for pickleball, says Lacher. "There's $10 pickleball eye protection and there's $160. How do you know which one to buy?"&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If you're shopping for eyewear, Lacher and Desai recommend products made of shatter-resistant polycarbonate and those that meet the American Society for Testing and Materials's &lt;a href="https://store.astm.org/f3164-19.html" target="_blank"&gt;F3164 standard&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Dr. Daniel Henick, an ophthalmology resident at Yale School of Medicine and an avid pickleball player, has &lt;a href="https://www.aao.org/newsroom/news-releases/detail/those-most-likely-to-suffer-pickleball-injuries-ar#:~:text=Henick%20found%20that%20the%20professional,paced%20nature%20of%20these%20games." target="_blank"&gt;been researching&lt;/a&gt; which groups of players are wearing eye protection and why the rest aren't. He says one of the most common reasons players don't use protective eyewear is that they aren't aware of the risks.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Henick says that having standardized guidelines, posting them outside of courts for players to see, making eye-protection more user-friendly, and encouraging professional pickleball athletes to set an example for the influx of new players could help reduce injuries.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The paper points out its limitations are having a small sample size and relying on a database that only includes emergency departments that opt in to the data collection. But Lacher sees the main takeaway from the study as bringing awareness to these injuries.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Henick agrees, noting these injuries can sometimes be life-changing: "We're talking about hundreds, if not thousands, of injuries every year that could be prevented with what could be a relatively simple intervention."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;USA Pickleball did not reply to a request for comment on the study's call for eye-protection guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPMDVfUTVyOThuOHBRTzlrMHFLZEhGSDIxTzZwTVVmVElIYzRVa29TUS1hMFpIY29CamtteHJoMFEwRGF0cjFhb3MzR0ExRWVKeVpqYmF0VUtDemdjaWhRY2RMMWV5cWZDQVd2cndReXk1UFV0SHRtV0daVmJ1ajFtaFFZNlNWZw</guid></item><item><title>这两位疫苗专家说，这是你应该接种新冠疫苗和流感疫苗的时候--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/10/19/covid-vaccine-flu-shot-timing/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7WUICWJJ4FFCXJFWXHEEQUTTH4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Flu season is here. The summer wave of the coronavirus has receded, but the winter uptick is likely around the corner. Shots &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/09/19/cdc-covid-vaccine-vote-acip/" target="_blank"&gt;are available&lt;/a&gt; for both respiratory viruses, raising questions about the best time to get these shots if you haven’t gotten one already.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:04:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxOYVI2MHdsMG5zQUlZRUpFRG5LNHNMSVd6bjBvNHM3dGR4ZTVtLTVvVXV6VkhlYWNRclVkYlFIY1ljXzVSb1lpd2xSajJRTlI2ektVZ0R5d0RiU3lpLWV4WXhoVG1yYmVMUmlBM1g3c3AzWDlhcHI4RndZZmFBR2VTZmhlMmNJQQ</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，大脑训练游戏增强了与记忆和注意力相关的化学物质- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/aging/brain-game-boosts-chemical-memory-dementia-research-rcna237832</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8c2193" class="body-graf"&gt;With age comes a natural decline in cognitive function, even among otherwise healthy adults without dementia. A new study finds that a cognitive training program may boost production of a brain chemical that plays a role in memory and attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cec025" class="body-graf"&gt;Participants who completed game-like activities through &lt;a href="https://www.brainhq.com" target="_blank"&gt;BrainHQ, &lt;/a&gt;an online subscription program, showed increased production of acetylcholine, sometimes called the “pay attention” chemical. The process that produces acetylcholine in the brain is called the cholinergic system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fec78c" class="body-graf"&gt;Researchers at McGill University in Montreal led a clinical trial of 92 people ages 65 and older. All were healthy, meaning they had not been diagnosed with a cognitive disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7fdaec" class="body-graf"&gt;In the study, called &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT04149457" target="_blank"&gt;INHANCE&lt;/a&gt; (Improving Neurological Health in Aging via Neuroplasticity-based Computerized Exercise), participants were randomly split into two groups of 46. Both groups were asked to spend 30 minutes a day doing an assigned activity on a computer or mobile device for 10 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9a5c8d" class="body-graf"&gt;People in the intervention group did BrainHQ exercises, while those in the control group played games designed for entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f4eae3" class="body-graf"&gt;Researchers used PET, or positron emission tomography, scans and a radioactive tracer to measure acetylcholine production in participants’ brains at the beginning and end of the trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e018bb" class="body-graf"&gt;People in the BrainHQ group had a 2.3% increase in acetylcholine production in the anterior cingulate cortex, a part of the brain important for learning, memory, attention and executive function. Those in the control group didn’t have a significant change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6cdea6" class="body-graf"&gt;The research claims to be the first of its kind to show that brain training exercises can offset natural decline in cholinergic function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c529aa" class="body-graf"&gt;Senior author Dr. Etienne de Villers-Sidani, a neurologist at &lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/neuro/" target="_blank"&gt;The Neuro (Montreal Neurological Institute-Hospital)&lt;/a&gt;, which is affiliated with McGill, said his patients often ask how they can keep their brains sharp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-374d9e" class="body-graf"&gt;“I’ve always believed that there are things that you can do that have a positive impact on brain health,” said de Villers-Sidani, who is also an associate professor in McGill’s department of neurology and neurosurgery. “Now I’m even more sure with what we’re seeing, that [brain training] has a profound impact on the health of key brain chemical systems.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii" id="anchor-039421"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture" data-flavor="fit" data-original-height="1503" data-original-width="2400"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-double-decision-medium-13e46b.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-double-decision-medium-13e46b.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-double-decision-medium-13e46b.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-double-decision-medium-13e46b.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-double-decision-medium-13e46b.jpg" alt="A still from brainHQ’s “Double Decision”."&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;A still from brainHQ’s Double Decision, one of the games in the study.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;Courtesy brainHQ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cc3631" class="body-graf"&gt;BrainHQ training has been the subject of &lt;a href="https://www.brainhq.com/world-class-science/information-researchers/" target="_blank"&gt;more than 300 studies&lt;/a&gt;. A study published last year in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2227-9032/12/5/532" target="_blank"&gt;Healthcare&lt;/a&gt; linked select BrainHQ exercises to faster visual processing speed in older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0a2508" class="body-graf"&gt;But de Villers-Sidani wondered what biochemical changes might be involved in brain training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-38eb0f" class="body-graf"&gt;“We really wanted to see how these [exercises] were changing the brain in a more fundamental way,” he said, “looking specifically at a chemical system that’s crucial for attention, memory and learning, and that also drives plasticity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e84035" class="body-graf"&gt;San Francisco-based Posit Science, the company behind BrainHQ, sponsored the INHANCE trial, which was funded by the &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov" target="_blank"&gt;National Institute on Aging&lt;/a&gt;, part of the National Institutes of Health. Results of the trial were published Tuesday in the journal &lt;a href="https://games.jmir.org/2025/1/e75161" target="_blank"&gt;JMIR Serious Games&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-b8aa14" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How acetylcholine helps you learn, remember&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d764bf" class="body-graf"&gt;When you’re learning something new, your brain is using acetylcholine. It tells your brain to stay alert. It’s key to other bodily functions, too, including &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/heart-health/new-blood-pressure-drug-helps-people-uncontrolled-hypertension-trial-rcna198443" target="_blank"&gt;blood pressure regulation&lt;/a&gt; and skeletal muscle contraction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1d8e2f" class="body-graf"&gt;Acetylcholine is a neurotransmitter, which means it sends messages between neurons and other cells. It’s also a neuromodulator that can influence a neuron’s activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-560659" class="body-graf"&gt;“It’s a chemical that helps us learn and think and remember. It also helps with alertness,” said Dr. Jennifer Pauldurai, a neurologist at Inova Health System in northern Virginia, who wasn’t involved in the trial. “It’s not the only thing that goes wrong in &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/aging/dementia-risk-may-twice-high-americans-live-longer-study-finds-rcna187376" target="_blank"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;, but it is one thing that has been shown to be deficient in many types of dementia, Alzheimer’s included.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bc0ed3" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/cne.24541" target="_blank"&gt;Previous research&lt;/a&gt; has shown that between the ages of 20 and 80, acetylcholine production decreases by about 2.5% per decade in the anterior cingulate cortex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6929c3" class="body-graf"&gt;The INHANCE trial results are promising, Pauldurai said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-455e9c" class="body-graf"&gt;“One of the first things I always say is, ‘Keep your brain active,’” she said. “We all say it, but nobody had really been able to prove or show objective changes in the brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-f2f143" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gaming doesn’t equal brain training&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9e2857" class="body-graf"&gt;Research on the relationship between games and puzzles and the aging brain has been mixed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-136865" class="body-graf"&gt;The BrainHQ exercises used in the trial are game-like, yet they’re not games, said Joaquin Anguera, an associate professor at the Weill Institute for Neurosciences at the University of California, San Francisco. He’s also the clinical director of UCSF’s &lt;a href="https://neuroscape.ucsf.edu" target="_blank"&gt;Neuroscape&lt;/a&gt; translational science center and has designed brain exercises for use in other cognitive studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-87f9bb" class="body-graf"&gt;“Games like sudoku or crossword puzzles, those are made to entertain you; they’re designed to engage you and get you excited,” said Anguera, who wasn’t involved in the trial. “Are there benefits to playing those? It depends on the study of what you’re looking for and where you’re looking to see improvements.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8fc782" class="body-graf"&gt;BrainHQ exercises are adaptive, de Villers-Sidani said, meaning the levels get progressively harder the better you do and easier the worse you do. People doing such training should be “always pushed to their limit,” he said, noting that the trial exercises mimicked real-life stressors including time constraints and distractions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-615a82" class="body-graf"&gt;The two BrainHQ exercises studied in the trial were &lt;a href="https://www.brainhq.com/why-brainhq/about-the-brainhq-exercises/attention/double-decision" target="_blank"&gt;Double Decision&lt;/a&gt;, in which people simultaneously identified objects in the center of the screen and their peripheral vision, and &lt;a href="https://www.brainhq.com/why-brainhq/about-the-brainhq-exercises/attention/freeze-frame/" target="_blank"&gt;Freeze Frame&lt;/a&gt;, which involves the delayed distinguishing of a target image from other similar images.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f78975" class="body-graf"&gt;People in the control group played Double Klondike Solitaire and Bricks Breaking Hex, in which players match hexagonal shapes of the same color.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii" id="anchor-8c7f5f"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture" data-flavor="fit" data-original-height="1252" data-original-width="2400"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-freezeframe-medium-2-c9e799.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-freezeframe-medium-2-c9e799.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-freezeframe-medium-2-c9e799.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-freezeframe-medium-2-c9e799.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-10/251017-Brain-game-freezeframe-medium-2-c9e799.jpg" alt="A still from brainHQ’s “Freeze Frame”."&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;A still from BrainHQ’s Freeze Frame game.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;Courtesy brainHQ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-74edb3" class="body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/workout-exercise-commitment-personality-study-rcna217288" target="_blank"&gt;Regularly exercising your body&lt;/a&gt; can help keep you physically healthy, and routinely flexing your cognitive muscles can boost brain health, Pauldurai said. But just as hitting the gym differs from receiving physical therapy, playing a game on your phone isn’t the same thing as training your brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-00d5f0" class="body-graf"&gt;“A lot of times we have too much fun clicking colorful buttons, and we get a reward because we beat one level or something,” she said. “That doesn’t actually challenge our brain to learn new things, to learn complex information and to apply knowledge.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-9d1c30" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Could brain training help people with dementia?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a8450c" class="body-graf"&gt;The INHANCE trial had a number of notable limitations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-86a7ed" class="body-graf"&gt;Nearly 96% of participants were white, and most were well-educated and lived in the Montreal area. The various visuals used in the brain exercises may resonate differently with people of different cultural backgrounds, de Villers-Sidani said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-82e28e" class="body-graf"&gt;Laura Glass Umfleet, an associate professor of neurology at the Medical College of Wisconsin in Milwaukee, had other concerns. Though McGill scientists handled data collection and analysis, several Posit Science researchers were involved in the trial, hinting at a bias toward BrainHQ in a market saturated with brain training companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e8e302" class="body-graf"&gt;BrainHQ offers free exercises but also promotes paid subscriptions topping out at $96 a year, which may be unaffordable for some people. The software also requires an internet-connected device and some level of tech savviness, said Umfleet, who wasn’t involved in the trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-941d81" class="body-graf"&gt;“Cognitive training required a daily commitment for 10 weeks,” Umfleet said in an email. “There’s no way of knowing if less intense training could be just as effective, or if more intense training has diminishing returns.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-11b3b6" class="body-graf"&gt;De Villers-Sidani said an NIH-funded follow-up trial will determine how people with mild cognitive impairment react to brain training exercises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c4c4fa" class="body-graf"&gt;“You should look at your brain as a physical, medical organ,” Pauldurai said. “We still need the physical engagement.” She recommends &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/womens-health/puberty-late-period-healthy-diet-chemicals-obesity-rcna204935" target="_blank"&gt;eating well&lt;/a&gt;, getting 30 minutes of physical activity a day and &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/mental-health/sleep-profile-sheds-light-health-lifestyle-cognition-new-study-shows-rcna235901" target="_blank"&gt;sleeping&lt;/a&gt; seven to eight hours a night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9dda86" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“Take care of your medical health, take care of your mental health, make friends,” Pauldurai said. “And do fun, challenging things with your brain all the time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOY3lFdjRwNVlCcVQybndQRmVmTDYtT2RnV29aLTM0RVRUNk85NldGZVJ4RUNRX0ZSV29pWXF5RWR3cXMtU2FzcllHSEFfTDBTZ3kyVzA2eDZhUEU5MlEweUZ1SmR3VkpjeU5IQllKa0ljclltU01NTWVWam5qdzJBMGpCMEV2MTRONUNwWHlTaHpUeG5FQ3RBbGUxcmxNZVhN0gFWQVVfeXFMTm5WOXJSZHJtT05JVnp3bHFabFV3Z055LU93ekFEdlFoRXA1ZFZzWktTdUlsZ1ZlZkFQRGpDUXp4MTJXZHJtVzlOZzRLZndTYTlCcDdpd2c</guid></item><item><title>您的牙刷充满了细菌- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251017-why-you-might-want-to-clean-your-toothbrush-more</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kySSTS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But Hartmann sees this as less of a concern for people who do live together. "People who live together share a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://elifesciences.org/articles/00458" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;higher proportion of the microbes&lt;/a&gt; in their mouth &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-022-05620-1" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;than people who don't&lt;/a&gt;," she says. "I doubt this is driven by such an indirect route as storing toothbrushes close by, as opposed to the more direct route of kissing or less indirect route of sharing." (It's worth noting that dog owners will often &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://elifesciences.org/articles/00458" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;share many of the same microbes as their pets&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Indeed, some of the viruses found on toothbrushes could in fact be working in our favour – Hartmann and her team found that &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/microbiomes/articles/10.3389/frmbi.2024.1396560/full" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;toothbrushes host thriving communities&lt;/a&gt; of viruses known as bacteriophages, which infect bacteria rather than humans and can help to control their numbers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;&lt;span id="what's-the-risk?" class="sc-d16436d-0 cVoAro"&gt;&lt;b id="what's-the-risk?" class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;What's the risk?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 cVoAro"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In most cases the risk from pathogens is small, agrees Zinn, but it could be more of a concern for those whose immune systems are compromised, meaning they are more prone to infections. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-2607/8/9/1379" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;Zinn's research&lt;/a&gt;, along with other similar studies that have &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0964339721001099" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;sequenced bacterial DNA from toothbrushes&lt;/a&gt;, have found that at least some of these bacteria carry genes that make them resistant to antibiotics. This means that if they do cause infections they are harder to treat. But Zinn adds that in his study these genes were at "at relatively low levels" and so only present "a moderate concern from a public health perspective". One study of 50 toothbrushes from students in Italy, however, found all of them carried bacteria that were &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://journalmrji.com/index.php/MRJI/article/view/304" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;resistant to multiple drugs&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Some toothbrushes come infused with &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0300571206001990" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;antimicrobial treatments&lt;/a&gt; that are marketed as being a way to keep the bacteria living on your brush under control. But most studies seem to indicate that these treatments &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://aap.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1902/jop.2003.74.3.312" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;do little&lt;/a&gt; to limit the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0300571206001990" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;number of bacteria living on your brush&lt;/a&gt;, and may even lead to an &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.liebertpub.com/doi/10.1089/mdr.2006.12.83" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;increase in antimicrobial-resistant species&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In fact, allowing your toothbrush simply to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.dentalhealthcareeoe.nhs.uk/wp-content/uploads/2023/11/supervised-toothbrushing-guidelines-final-20.9.pdf" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;air dry at room temperature in an upright position&lt;/a&gt; after use can be a simple way of reducing the microbes living there. Many viruses, including &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00784-022-04530-w" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;influenza and coronaviruses&lt;/a&gt;, break down as they dry out. Bacteria such as &lt;i id="streptococcus-mutans" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;Streptococcus mutans&lt;/i&gt;, which are a major contributor to tooth decay, can remain viable on toothbrush bristles for up to eight hours but by &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ingentaconnect.com/content/aapd/jodc/2008/00000075/00000001/art00007" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;12 hours they begin to die off&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 09:00:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNbEptRFhGRk96LUs2dlc5VGVvZHBmZ3AwTFFGbzkta2M5QjVHdkU2YW9wRk4tUTdsejJsOWxFNlRnX2RCNi1JY25yOEN0M0hTcExiSHBENjhXSVFvWXI5MExWTjN1c3haaFJMdU82c3VYYWNHblJQQnhDQmxhMDhvTml0LW00cGRYekotd0liTlpQVU05Smd3</guid></item><item><title>以色列研究人员测试基于催眠的减肥“手术” ，早期效果良好- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/byv8yzm0ll</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="53ed5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="53ed5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="53ed5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;A real operating room, a surgeon in a gown, IV drip and monitors — but no scalpel. In a groundbreaking study at Hadassah Medical Center’s Mount Scopus campus, a bariatric surgery procedure is being simulated using hypnosis. The preliminary results are encouraging, but the research team says several more months remain before the full study is complete.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="8hcnf-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8hcnf-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8hcnf-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Most participants lost an average of 10 percent of their body weight within three months. “I’m no longer tempted by pastries,” says one participant. “It’s really magic."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="7cb6-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.S1eDuo11G0eg" id="image_ArticleImageData.S1eDuo11G0eg"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.S1eDuo11G0eg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/19/Hke9lnJzRex/Hke9lnJzRex_0_0_1280_1188_0_x-large.jpg" alt="היפנוזה במקום ניתוח בריאטרי" title='Bariatric surgery being simulated using hypnosis. "Feels like a real surgery"  (Photo: Tamar Haratz Barkai) ' aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.S1eDuo11G0eg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/19/Hke9lnJzRex/Hke9lnJzRex_0_0_1280_1188_0_x-large.jpg" alt="היפנוזה במקום ניתוח בריאטרי" title='Bariatric surgery being simulated using hypnosis. "Feels like a real surgery"  (Photo: Tamar Haratz Barkai) ' aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Bariatric surgery being simulated using hypnosis. "Feels like a real surgery" &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Tamar Haratz Barkai&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="fbdac-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="fbdac-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="fbdac-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;A few years ago, “Rose” (alias) from Jerusalem underwent a conventional bariatric surgery that initially helped her shed about 60 kg (132 lb). But over time, as happens with many bariatric surgery patients, her weight gradually rose again. “The 'honeymoon period' ended and the demons returned,” she says. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="dreoq-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="dreoq-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="dreoq-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;She tried weight‑loss injections but suffered severe side‑effects, and it seemed a second surgery would be unavoidable. “I felt hopeless after I couldn’t lose weight on my own; I was truly afraid I’d have to cut into my body again,” she says. Less than a year ago, she was introduced for the first time to this initial study at Hadassah that changed everything.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="8i32c-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="8i32c-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="8i32c-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;In the study currently underway at the hospital, patients suffering from extreme obesity undergo a simulated “gastric‑shortening” operation, carried out in a real operating room, but using hypnosis only. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="9okq2-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="9okq2-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="9okq2-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Importantly, unlike real bariatric surgery and unlike weight‑loss medications, hypnosis lacks a sufficiently strong research base for treating obesity. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="1upcb-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1upcb-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1upcb-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The study is led by psychologist and certified hypnotherapist Maya Mizrahi and managed by a multidisciplinary team of specialists from Hadassah and Hebrew University of Jerusalem. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="ecnc7-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="ecnc7-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="ecnc7-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;It is open to both former bariatric surgery patients and those who have never had surgery. Early results show that within just three months, most participants lost about 10 percent of their body weight, a result comparable to the efficacy of some of today’s approved weight‑loss drugs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="93coe-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="93coe-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="93coe-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;A few months ago, Rose, now 69, underwent the hypnotic “operation.” In the week following the procedure, she was instructed to follow a strict diet including liquids and soft‑texture food, just as standard post‑surgery patients are. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="68gl8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="68gl8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="68gl8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“I was worried I wouldn’t handle it, but I was surprised,” she says. “All my life I held myself back from eating. And suddenly, Maya played with my mind and things changed. Now I go to cafés and it’s not hard anymore to pass on the pastry next to my coffee; it’s no longer a problem. It’s magic. Who would’ve believed it? There’s hope in this study.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="633v6-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="633v6-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="633v6-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The innovative experience engages all the senses: patients are asked to fast on the day before the "surgery", and on the day of the “surgery” they are dressed in a gown and surgical garments, connected to an EKG, an IV (without a needle) and a monitor that tracks heart rate and blood pressure. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="3de6k-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="3de6k-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="3de6k-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Mizrahi, dressed as a surgeon, leads the patient into the cool, brightly lit operating room. There, the patient first receives a visual briefing of the surgical steps, then is placed into a hypnotic state.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="29jp7-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="29jp7-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="29jp7-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;For 50 minutes, Mizrahi walks each patient step by step through the surgical process of a sleeve gastrectomy, a procedure that reduces the size of the stomach, including the medical equipment used and where incisions would typically be made. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="2j622-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="2j622-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="2j622-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“The brain doesn’t distinguish between reality and imagination,” she explains. “By constructing a scenario in which the brain believes the body is undergoing surgery, the mind can recreate or trigger the same positive effects of an actual operation — sensations of fullness, self-control, confidence and motivation for change."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="fmjpp-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.B1ehFhbfCgx" id="image_ArticleImageData.B1ehFhbfCgx"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.B1ehFhbfCgx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/19/Hy79l2JM0ee/Hy79l2JM0ee_0_0_1280_960_0_x-large.jpg" alt='יובל וולהנדלר עבר היפנוזה במקום "ניתוח בריאטרי" בהדסה הר הצופים' title='Yuval Wollhandler underwent the hypnotic surgery. "Results are encouraging"  (Photo: Tamar Haratz Barkai) ' aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.B1ehFhbfCgx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/19/Hy79l2JM0ee/Hy79l2JM0ee_0_0_1280_960_0_x-large.jpg" alt='יובל וולהנדלר עבר היפנוזה במקום "ניתוח בריאטרי" בהדסה הר הצופים' title='Yuval Wollhandler underwent the hypnotic surgery. "Results are encouraging"  (Photo: Tamar Haratz Barkai) ' aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Yuval Wollhandler underwent the hypnotic surgery. "Results are encouraging" &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Tamar Haratz Barkai&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="7n82j-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="7n82j-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="7n82j-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;At the same time, throughout the hypnotic script, empowering and reinforcing messages are woven in, emphasizing satiety, discipline, a desire to exercise, and to plan meals. “Hypnosis isn’t magic,” Mizrahi says. “It’s a tool that helps a person tune in to the body and to both conscious and unconscious internal processes."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="1v70q-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="1v70q-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="1v70q-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Participants take part in five sessions that include guided self-hypnosis practice, follow-up conversations, phone check-ins and a printed nutritional guide. They also undergo blood tests to measure levels of ghrelin and leptin, hormones associated with hunger and fullness, to assess whether hypnosis impacts appetite regulation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="227l8-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="227l8-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="227l8-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“I felt like I was going through the same experience again — the sounds, the smell, the cold in the operating room, the IV as if it were really there,” says Rose, who lost 17 kg (about 37 lb) in three months. “I was skeptical at first, but I figured I had nothing to lose. At worst, it might actually work.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="e28us-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="e28us-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="e28us-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Yuval Wollhandler, 45, a male nurse and a combat medic in the army reserves, also took part in the study. “I didn’t want to have bariatric surgery. I know the statistics about weight regain, and it’s a serious procedure with significant risks,” he says. “When I heard about the study, I was excited — on the one hand, you get the benefits of the surgery, and on the other hand, you’re not in danger."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="fa3kh-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="fa3kh-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="fa3kh-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Wollhandler says he has struggled with his weight most of his life, at one point reaching 145 kg (about 320 lb). About five years ago, he began an intensive weight-loss program and lost 30 kg (66 lb), but over the past two years, the weight crept back and he reached 133 kg (293 lb).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="51pdc-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="51pdc-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="51pdc-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“The hypnotic surgery feels very real,” he says. “You truly feel like you’ve had surgery, so you find yourself actually sticking to the strict dietary rules that follow real surgery.” Wollhandler lost 25 kg (55 lb) in about five months. “It didn’t feel like a struggle. Even now, eight months later, some habits from the hypnosis remain, like planning all my meals for the day in advance."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="b6vao-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.BJgP006WGRxg" id="image_ArticleImageData.BJgP006WGRxg"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BJgP006WGRxg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/19/Hyf9xhJzRgx/Hyf9xhJzRgx_0_0_1280_1265_0_x-large.jpg" alt="היפנוזה במקום ניתוח בריאטרי" title="Psychologist and certified hypnotherapist Maya Mizrahi with one of the patients  (Photo: Tamar Haratz Barkai) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.BJgP006WGRxg" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/10/19/Hyf9xhJzRgx/Hyf9xhJzRgx_0_0_1280_1265_0_x-large.jpg" alt="היפנוזה במקום ניתוח בריאטרי" title="Psychologist and certified hypnotherapist Maya Mizrahi with one of the patients  (Photo: Tamar Haratz Barkai) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Psychologist and certified hypnotherapist Maya Mizrahi with one of the patients &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Tamar Haratz Barkai&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="duafr-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="duafr-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="duafr-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“One of the major challenges in treating obesity is dissociation — a disconnect between the person and their conscious experience,” Mizrahi explains. “People eat on autopilot and are then surprised to find they’ve gained weight. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="334cn-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="334cn-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="334cn-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;"That experience often stems from a disconnection between the mind and body or between emotion and logic while eating. The intervention we created helps patients reconnect with their body, and to work on the areas of choice, control and impulse."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="5e42l-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5e42l-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5e42l-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The idea for the study came from Mizrahi’s years of experience as a medical psychologist treating patients with obesity. “Patients started coming back after bariatric surgery saying, ‘I wish I could have this surgery every two years,’” she recalls. Research shows that within five years, 40% to 70% of bariatric patients regain weight.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="5n34v-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5n34v-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5n34v-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Mizrahi notes that while hypnosis is used in some countries as a tool for weight loss, the field remains unproven. Furthermore, existing methods rely solely on guided visualization, whereas this study includes a tangible, physical simulation in a real operating room — a combination that may enhance the placebo effect of the faux surgery.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="d3qgj-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="d3qgj-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d3qgj-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;So far, 41 participants have enrolled in the study: 19 who previously had bariatric surgery and 22 who had not undergone any surgical procedure. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="aroum-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="aroum-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="aroum-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Preliminary results show that after just three months, 35 participants (86%) had begun losing weight. Among those who had previous surgeries, 66% lost more than 20% of their excess weight. In the group without any prior surgery, 55% achieved similar outcomes. The study is ongoing, and final results are expected within the year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="6mjd7-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6mjd7-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6mjd7-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;“I hope that this research leads to real clinical change,” Mizrahi says, “and that it introduces a targeted intervention to help address weight regain, possibly even integrating it into surgical departments at hospitals."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="1p0dc" data-offset-key="db0t0-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="db0t0-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="db0t0-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;The study is led by a multidisciplinary team that includes Dr. Tamar Elram, director of Hadassah Mount Scopus; Prof. Haggi Mazeh, head of the surgical department; Dr. Ronit Greenbaum, senior bariatric surgeon; and Dr. Yorai Tal Ron, psychiatrist at Hadassah Ein Kerem. They are joined by Prof. Danny Ben-Zvi, head of the metabolism and diabetes research lab at the Hebrew University of Jerusalem, and Dr. Eitan Abramowitz, psychiatrist and medical hypnosis specialist at the Hypno-Campus Institute.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 08:29:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE5PcmI5UUt0UnlZaEw1QWZwSE1qWnpvUTBLampoQ1FTTFQtUGttVjZ4MExGOUhNODNtSUliN0NQdTlmTHp0Qy1lRmRtYnVFMm9fUGhYLTN6a2pVUkNha3UtOURzQjRjZFJhSlE</guid></item><item><title>AIIMS培训的胃肠病学家说，深夜进食和睡眠会影响肝功能； 9件事情要知道|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-says-eating-and-sleeping-late-at-night-affects-liver-function-9-things-to-know-101760856200547.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-says-eating-and-sleeping-late-at-night-affects-liver-function-9-things-to-know-101760856200547.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Your liver works quietly around the clock, processing everything you eat and drink throughout the day. While it has an incredible ability to regenerate, everyday habits - from poor sleep and late-night meals to exposure to toxins - can add strain over time. Taking care of this vital organ is essential for long-term health, and understanding how it functions can help you make smarter choices.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/19/550x309/liver_1760857435430_1760857435643.png" alt="Dr Saurabh Sethi shares 9 essential things to know about your liver. (Pixabay)" title="Dr Saurabh Sethi shares 9 essential things to know about your liver. (Pixabay)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/19/550x309/liver_1760857435430_1760857435643.png" alt="Dr Saurabh Sethi shares 9 essential things to know about your liver. (Pixabay)" title="Dr Saurabh Sethi shares 9 essential things to know about your liver. (Pixabay)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Saurabh Sethi shares 9 essential things to know about your liver. (Pixabay)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read |&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fortis-gastronologist-says-sweets-are-more-harmful-than-you-think-shares-the-right-way-to-eat-them-this-diwali-101760790425544.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Fortis gastroenterologist says 'sweets are more harmful than you think'; shares the right way to eat them this Diwali"&gt;Fortis gastroenterologist says 'sweets are more harmful than you think'; shares the right way to eat them this Diwali&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Saurabh Sethi, a gastroenterologist trained at &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-says-air-frying-does-not-make-your-food-automatically-healthy-debunks-7-myths-101760763411244.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="AIIMS"&gt;AIIMS&lt;/a&gt;, Harvard and Stanford Universities, is breaking down nine essential facts you need to know about your &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/sam-rivers-health-struggles-late-limp-bizkit-bassist-underwent-liver-transplant-battled-alcohol-addiction-101760837182600.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="liver"&gt;liver&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In an Instagram post shared on October 19, the gastroenterologist explains that while the liver has the incredible power to regenerate, habits like poor sleep, late-night eating, and exposure to toxins can compromise its efficiency over time.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Your liver can regenerate&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Sethi, the liver can regenerate damaged cells, but that does not make it invincible. He explains, “It’s not invincible, and it can regrow damaged cells, but chronic injury leads to scarring that can’t be reversed.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Coffee is liver medicine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sethi states that coffee isn’t just a morning pick-me-up or a fix for the afternoon slump - it can actually act as medicine for the liver. He states, “Three plus cups daily (is) linked to 40 percent lower risk of cirrhosis and liver cancer. Just skip the sugar and cream.” He also cautions that individual caffeine sensitivity varies, and excessive coffee intake may cause insomnia, palpitations, or &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/psychiatrist-shares-how-late-night-scrolling-anxiety-and-stress-are-fueling-a-sleep-crisis-among-gen-z-101759762270680.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="anxiety"&gt;anxiety&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Fatty liver&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gastroenterologist highlights that cases of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fortis-vasant-kunj-hepatologist-warns-1-in-every-3-people-suffer-from-fatty-liver-shares-best-foods-for-liver-health-101760161645355.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="fatty liver"&gt;fatty liver&lt;/a&gt; are more common than you think, even among non-drinkers. He states, “Fatty liver affects one in three adults, even non-drinkers. Nonalcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD) is skyrocketing and often remains silent until serious damage.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Liver processes everything&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sethi warns that everything you swallow is processed by the liver, including your medications. He stresses, “Over-the-counter painkillers like acetaminophen in high doses can cause deadly liver damage. Always confirm the correct dosage with your doctor.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Liver and sleep&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your sleep quality is directly linked to liver repair. The gastroenterologist explains that poor sleep can disrupt liver &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-shares-magic-drink-recipe-to-melt-belly-fat-faster-and-boost-metabolism-naturally-101760271069724.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="metabolism"&gt;metabolism&lt;/a&gt;, hampering the organ’s ability to clear toxins effectively. He recommends getting seven to nine hours of sleep every day, without compromise.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The liver clock&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Sethi, your liver has its own clock, and hence the circadian rhythm matters. He highlights, “Eating late at night stresses your liver’s natural detox cycle, increasing fat accumulation.”&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/19/original/liver_graphic_1760856762934.png" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Knowing how your liver functions is key to protecting its health.(Image generated via Google Gemini)" title="Knowing how your liver functions is key to protecting its health.(Image generated via Google Gemini)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Knowing how your liver functions is key to protecting its health.(Image generated via Google Gemini)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Hidden liver killers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Common household chemicals, including cleaning products, pesticides, and even some cosmetics contain toxins that the liver must filter, adding extra strain to the organ. The gastroenterologist recommends opting for natural alternatives instead.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Supplements&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gastroenterologist warns that &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-with-30-years-of-experience-shares-why-even-healthy-supplements-may-not-protect-your-heart-aspirin-101760324545123.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="supplements"&gt;supplements &lt;/a&gt;are not always safe for the liver. He explains, “Some herbal supplements and high-dose vitamins can cause liver inflammation or damage. Always check with your doctor.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The role of hydration&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sethi stresses that hydration supports liver detoxification. He recommends drinking at least two to three litres of water every day because drinking enough water helps the liver flush out toxins efficiently.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 07:22:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAJBVV95cUxOZ09yQTd1TUlzUDdrMnk5cG1QRWV3cGltRGVDY1hjak9UV1UyelZycTNyb3QtZXBFOGJDMTRZdnFmMTVuRHBubzdiRUJyU0F0Mk1saVNyZTBMNUdqYUdjc2pEUVRPQ1lOeVJaZ3dBMDFUZzFrQjZUS2tYalJMX0xpc0QzQzhUVUxoakhESjZ0akItUUZLcDV3NmNlSTZ0Njc2Rktpakd2d0ZnQ3ZPVEx5MTFrc1pELTlOSHBQYnVuS3lfMlJybl80VlVsNTdmZDZMQTRJOXFLX2FNQjBMMHpoSUQxSmtEV2lPQVBPdHd2cUIzV253SU9nS2wwR0dZd3JZd0RWc1JwTWcydFZ30gGSAkFVX3lxTE5NMmIzNC11OTZFTFFadjJMZ09YU2V1dEpDbnFmeHZlQnl3MVFJcUJNZnlFbnZXNTVXTlVETm5EcUJ6bjZ1Sk5jTUtBM3EtcGNxSkJCaFZXU012RHlCYUE4VDhJX1ZNT2pWaEJBOG5oNHNteGtvRkcwQzJRdzc2eXI0dUJpbVBRSm5QMjk3Y09qU3hyTm5rakhVcWhnc1RVSk1jazQ2RHpaSXJFVGJEYnE1YzdwUGx4SE84SkI3NXFWb1JuWTJ4eGdPbzN2SjFuZGFZNE1qOS1XaTJPUG5wYkRSejNiRnZ0TVR3Uk9FUlNRUy02SWhlVmxqSTdtZ1ZlaF9IWUVnOFQ2MGtUeWotb1RiYXc</guid></item><item><title>一位专业力量训练师说，衰老的秘诀不仅仅是举重，以下是他的建议- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/cardio-strength-workouts/an-expert-strength-trainer-says-the-secret-to-aging-well-isnt-just-lifting-weights-heres-what-he-recommends</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="5f62931a-2b88-4172-88cc-517d1629c629"&gt;I spend a lot of time looking at fitness trends, but one constant has been strength training, and for good reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, however, the concept of lifting weights for long-term health and longevity has featured repeatedly in my social feeds, on my favorite websites and in my daily conversations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="5f62931a-2b88-4172-88cc-517d1629c629-2"&gt;However, when I put this to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://onepeloton.pxf.io/c/221109/1493570/17622?subId1=fitandwell-gb-1440825047931391567&amp;amp;sharedId=fitandwell-gb&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.onepeloton.com%2F" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.onepeloton.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-placeholder-url="https://onepeloton.pxf.io/c/221109/1493570/17622?subId1=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;sharedId=hawk-prefix&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.onepeloton.com%2F" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="Peloton" data-merchant-id="317344" data-merchant-network="ImpactRad" data-merchant-url="onepeloton.com"&gt;Peloton&lt;/a&gt;’s expert strength training instructor, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.instagram.com/benjaminalldis/?hl=en" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.instagram.com/benjaminalldis/?hl=en" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Ben Alldis&lt;/a&gt;, he said that while strength training is important, it’s not the only&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;thing that matters if you want to age well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To live a long, healthy, happy life, adding variety to your training is where the magic happens,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-mix-strength-training-with-cardio-and-stretching" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-mix-strength-training-with-cardio-and-stretching"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mix strength training with cardio and stretching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="f21a7159-b026-417e-9df2-d85d0145b521"&gt;Alldis emphasizes that strength training should still be a big component of your weekly workouts, because it can help you maintain the muscle you need for everyday activities and support healthy aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4035379/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4035379/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; even shows that older people with higher muscle mass have a lower risk of dying from all major causes. But that doesn’t mean lifting weights is all you need to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiorespiratory fitness is also strongly linked to longevity, so it’s important to incorporate some exercises that improve your heart and lung health—like brisk walking, jogging, cycling or swimming—too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-HYovotBKuQL7ZtxD9TJHZ7" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-HYovotBKuQL7ZtxD9TJHZ7 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I would always suggest getting a good mixture of cardio, strength and stretching in your routine,” says Alldis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This well-rounded approach ticks all the boxes for a strong heart, functional muscle and mobile joints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-prioritize-consistency" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-prioritize-consistency"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Prioritize consistency &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="2d7fc781-c5f2-4bbe-b9de-3529f3d6fd09"&gt;I asked Alldis how to split your weekly workouts if you’re new to exercise and want to follow this approach. His advice was to prioritize building a consistent habit first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think a good goal is always to aim for three days a week,” he says. “I would probably recommend just sticking with cardio or strength to begin with.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once you’ve built this routine, he suggests adding 15-20 minutes of stretching to the end of your sessions to improve mobility and aid recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re on a roll with this, you can start tweaking your program to make sure it aligns with the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://odphp.health.gov/our-work/nutrition-physical-activity/physical-activity-guidelines/current-guidelines" target="_blank" data-url="https://odphp.health.gov/our-work/nutrition-physical-activity/physical-activity-guidelines/current-guidelines" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;national recommendations&lt;/a&gt;, which include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="4d8078aa-ba13-467b-bd88-e50f72c16dbd"&gt;&lt;li&gt;150 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic exercise or 75 minutes of vigorous aerobic exercise every week.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Two additional sessions of muscle-strengthening exercise that work the major muscles of the body every week.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 06:05:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_AFBVV95cUxNZWNkeGpQdTVoZFhlZnpEY1E3NVJ2VnNLdkwwM1VjODA2YmJzYkhHYUpMaFd6MjZBZ3NIWFNyVkNlQjdKcDRLaTFya0t4TEFyd3BkY0N6RXdsVm9lY3VWODBpVldfbWNtTFprU2hYbDNlNTdoWVFQZEV2cmZJV0Rwc01yTWpURmRyaHBLalNIVC0yRGZNNkpLUWluUXQxdzN2ZTFETkNuTGJWQmdOdFFHcS03V0p4bjRPSGt4NGhtZFVzVk55VGlGUHk0bXoyQldkb0QzRS05VlJYbmR5T0x1Smp3X1pza1E5WVRFTUtnZnVEUWFIRGFRUzJVRVY</guid></item><item><title>突破性癌症疗法在不损害健康细胞的情况下阻止肿瘤生长-《科学日报》</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251018102122.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Scientists at the Francis Crick Institute and Vividion Therapeutics have discovered chemical compounds that can precisely prevent the cancer-driving gene RAS from connecting with a key pathway responsible for tumor growth.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The potential treatment is now moving into its first human clinical trial. If proven safe and effective, it could become a way to treat a wide range of cancers while minimizing harm to healthy cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The RAS gene plays a central role in controlling how cells grow and divide, but mutations in this gene occur in roughly one in five cancers. When mutated, RAS becomes permanently active, continually sending signals that push cells to keep growing and multiplying.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Inside the cell, RAS sits on the membrane and acts as the starting signal in a chain of growth processes. Completely shutting down RAS or the enzymes it controls has proven difficult, because these same pathways are essential for normal cell function. One of the enzymes linked to RAS, called PI3K, also helps regulate blood sugar through insulin. Blocking PI3K entirely can lead to side effects such as hyperglycemia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In their study, published on October 9 in &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt;, the team combined chemical screening with biological testing to identify compounds that stop RAS and PI3K from interacting, while leaving normal cell activity intact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Vividion Therapeutics pinpointed a set of small molecules that permanently attach to the surface of PI3K near the spot where RAS would normally bind. Using an assay created by the Crick researchers, they confirmed that these compounds successfully blocked the RAS-PI3K interaction but still allowed PI3K to perform its other roles, including those related to insulin signaling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Crick team and their collaborators at Vividion then tested one of the compounds in mice with RAS-mutated lung tumors. The treatment stopped tumor growth, and the researchers found no signs of elevated blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, they tried combining the new compound with one or two additional drugs that target enzymes within the same pathway. Together, the treatments produced stronger and longer-lasting tumor suppression than any of the drugs used alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scientists also tested the compound in mice with tumors carrying mutations in another cancer-linked gene, HER2, which is often overactive in breast cancer and also connects with PI3K. Tumor growth was again halted, even though the effect did not rely on RAS. This finding suggests that the new compound could potentially help stop the growth of a broader range of cancers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The drug has now entered the first clinical trial in humans to test for safety and side effects in people with both RAS and HER2 mutations. The trial will also assess if the potential treatment is more effective in combination with other drugs targeting RAS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Julian Downward, Principal Group Leader of the Oncogene Biology Laboratory at the Crick, said: "Given the RAS gene is mutated across a wide range of cancers, we've been exploring how to stop it interacting with cell growth pathways for many years, but side effects have held back the development of treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our collaborative effort has overcome this challenge by targeting the PI3K and RAS interaction specifically, leaving PI3K free to bind with its other targets. It's exciting to see these clinical trials starting, highlighting the power of understanding chemistry and fundamental biology to get to something with potential to help people with cancer."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This discovery is a great example of how new discovery approaches can open up completely novel ways to tackle cancer," said Matt Patricelli, Ph.D., Chief Scientific Officer of Vividion. "By designing molecules that stop RAS and PI3K from connecting, while still allowing healthy cell processes to continue, we've found a way to selectively block a key cancer growth signal. It's incredibly rewarding to see this science now progressing in the clinic, where it has the potential to make a real difference for patients."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Science Daily</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 05:53:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE5PT2Q2NzRUQi1yNjVsbEtWMFN3eFFOeTdzZjN1R3FjSGhkNXBxbFRUYTM1RUFwVHRXVENZM3lBcGtIS1kwdUw2MUdrOEdHN2dGQ0UzQXA1RndfR1pMMVVEUUlBWkNDd0pNRDdYYmtVUQ</guid></item><item><title>根据新的研究，你只需要每周锻炼两次。以下是如何最大限度地利用这两个课程-汤姆指南</title><link>https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/you-only-need-to-work-out-twice-a-week-according-to-new-research-heres-how-to-maximize-those-two-sessions</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p id="727350bd-f634-492c-9faa-541311fb60a0"&gt;With the pressures of social media, it's easy to feel like you need to be exercising at least four or five times a week to get fit. But the reality is, any amount of exercise, no matter how small or infrequent, is good for you. And setting yourself realistic goals is key to maintaining consistency in your workout routine, which is what will help you make progress over time. "If you can exercise, that's a good thing, no matter what it is or how many days it is," says &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.instagram.com/laura.cavefit/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.instagram.com/laura.cavefit/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Laura Anderson&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, personal trainer and founder of Edinburgh-based gym &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.instagram.com/cavefit/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-url="https://www.instagram.com/cavefit/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Cave Fit&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And new research confirms that exercising just two times per week is enough to significantly improve your health. The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40690774/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40690774/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;study&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; was looking specifically at people with type two diabetes who identified as 'weekend warriors', which meant they only exercised on Saturdays and Sundays. Researchers found that doing so lowers your risk of all-cause mortality by 21%, and lowers your risk of dying from cardiovascular-related illnesses by 33%. Researchers noted that other studies have found similar findings around people who follow a "weekend warrior" schedule amongst the general population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-0eeefea9-0514-491f-ad29-a2b82a8d6b79" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="is-exercising-twice-a-week-really-enough-3"&gt;Is exercising twice a week really enough?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="0608f496-e631-4208-8f16-bd0b7480ccbe-0"&gt;Researchers found that being a "weekend warrior" lowered all-cause mortality to a similar extent as people who exercise regularly. However, what's crucial is that the people in the study who were only exercising twice per week were still doing 150 minutes of exercise per week in total. This is the amount of exercise most health bodies recommend, including the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Anderson two days per week is a good goal for people who are currently inactive. "I think [exercising] twice a week is a really good place to start," she says. "If you start with any more than that, you run the risk of potentially overdoing it — your body isn't trained for it, the recovery can be slower, and it can feel overwhelming."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However she caveats this by saying that it's important to try and remain generally active every day, even if you're not doing a dedicated workout. "We want to look at exercise as part of a healthier, more active lifestyle at the most basic level," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="07e552d5-2cea-47a9-8f8c-f864afa55b8a"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;a id="elk-d1e09399-f747-4dc3-b76d-820bf684e3ac" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="is-it-okay-to-exercise-on-two-consecutive-days-3"&gt;Is it okay to exercise on two consecutive days?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="dcbc7ce7-1333-42a5-95e3-f988a43262d4"&gt;This study specifically looked at people who exercised on two consecutive days. Anderson says that a lot of her clients only train at the weekends because of work and other responsibilities, and that works for them. "It definitely depends on what fits your lifestyle best, because that's what is going to be sustainable for you, so the consistency will be there," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, exercising two days in a row — particularly if you're not active at the moment and you're doing intense sessions — could potentially lead to injury. "I think the weekend warrior kind of pattern can sometimes potentially be risky, and lead to more musculoskeletal injuries," Anderson says, adding: "If the sessions are quite intense and you're not used to it [...] it is a long time to be exercising, which could potentially overload your body a bit too much."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-wvyMGTvXhKkNNcTUvd2pDa" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-wvyMGTvXhKkNNcTUvd2pDa slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get instant access to breaking news, the hottest reviews, great deals and helpful tips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="60168e97-bae1-4699-b97b-cab967a1bcc5"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty/Mike Harrington)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="e02964cb-9eb8-4ae0-ada3-911bc33a9738"&gt;If you are following a "weekend warrior" plan, then recovery is key. "The best thing you can do if you're training on consecutive days is have a great night's sleep," Anderson says. "Avoid screens before bed and try to get seven to nine hours of sleep."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She adds that diet is crucial to proper recovery too. "Just because we've been to the gym, it doesn't mean you should fall face first into a pack of donuts. We need to make sure we're giving our body the nutrients it needs, as well as eating the fun foods as well," Anderson says. "Priortise lots of carbohydrates to fuel those muscles, make sure you're hitting your protein intake and drink lots of water to stay hydrated as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On top of that, Anderson suggests doing some gentle stretching in between sessions and a short walk — 15 minutes is fine — to keep the blood flowing, remove lactate from the muscles and enhance your recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-ffc8b819-2b36-4a10-96e2-7114b6581f6b" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-should-you-focus-on-if-you-can-only-exercise-twice-a-week-3"&gt;What should you focus on if you can only exercise twice a week?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="078f462a-7aad-4b09-b226-0ee4ed454ca3"&gt;The type of workouts you should do depends on your goals and what you enjoy. But Anderson recommends trying to incorporate a mix of strength and fitness activities if you're exercising just twice per week. Below, she's shared a workout plan that will help you build strength, improve your fitness and work on your mobility in two sessions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They both involve a combination of strength training and cardio. "Balance what you want to do out over two days, rather than looking at them as two individual sessions," she advises. Anderson recommends splitting your strength workouts into "push" and "pull" movements, rather than workouts that target specific areas of the body. "I find "push" and "pull" a more functional way to train, and it also means you're hitting more movement patterns more frequently, essentially if you are only training twice a week," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You don't necessarily need to incorporate machines or barbells into your workouts to build strength, especially if you're trying to make the most of your time. "At a beginner level, I think the best thing to do is to grab some dumbbells and find a space in the gym where you can almost set up a circuit," Anderson advises. "So you can do four or five exercises back to back, take a couple of minutes rest, and then repeat that for maybe four or five rounds." Over time, Anderson recommends trying to decrease the amount of time you're resting between sets and increasing the weights you're using gradually too, to ensure you keep making progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below, Anderson has shared a specific workout format for each session and some exercise ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-weekend-warrior-workout-plan" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-weekend-warrior-workout-plan"&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Weekend warrior" workout plan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="dfe79173-20c4-428e-ac2d-f28dbaf89942"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session One&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="eb3669db-6dc6-499a-a1f0-3bb93e923411"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Warm-up: 10 minutes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five minutes of gentle cardio followed by five minutes of gentle stretching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;"Push" exercises circuit: 30 to 40 minutes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete 10 to 12 reps of the following exercises back-to-back, then take two to three minutes of rest, for four to five sets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="fb275e3c-b836-4a74-ac8a-6ca440600a4d"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dumbbell squats&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dumbbell shoulder press&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dumbbell lunge&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dumbbell chest press&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="b0c532f1-466f-4d3f-82ce-861be808aeb5"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Aerobic workout: 25 to 40 minutes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anderson recommends finishing your workout with 25 to 40 minutes of moderate cardio exercise, keeping your heart rate in zones one to three. "That could be running, that could be rowing — maybe you've got access to a swimming pool," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Heart rate zones one to three should mean working at a conversational pace," Anderson explains. "That's where you build your cardio base, which will enable you to then get fitter and faster over time. These should feel like quite easy sessions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="a8906bd4-9459-4190-a54e-41da251f7c3f"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty/Cavan Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="58b7cddd-da40-499e-a0da-fc7dc16c2dfc"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Session two&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Warm-up: 10 minutes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Five minutes of gentle cardio followed by five minutes of gentle stretching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;"Pull" exercises: 30 to 40 minutes &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete 10 to 12 reps of the following exercises back-to-back, then take two to three minutes of rest, for four to five sets:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="e93c23d9-e55e-46b8-8d74-01149c0874f9"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dumbbell Romanian deadlifts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Single-arm dumbbell&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dumbbell bicep curls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Renegade row&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="1e59986e-32e3-4458-a351-f7d8ed58d24c"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Cardio finisher: 15 to 25 minutes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anderson recommends a HIIT circuit to finish your second workout. "Zone four and particularly zone five, that's where you're then training your VO two Max, which is kind of your top end performance, really pushing your fitness levels at that stage," she explains. "These kind of sessions can be done in 10 to 15 minutes," Anderson adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She recommends doing intervals on a machine like a treadmill, rower or bike. Or you can do running intervals. Anderson recommends 30 seconds of sprints – either running or sprints on a particular machine — followed by two minutes of walking or cycling or rowing slowly. Alternatively, you could try one of the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/reference/best-beginner-hiit-workouts" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/reference/best-beginner-hiit-workouts"&gt;&lt;u&gt;best HIIT workouts for beginners&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, spend five to ten minutes cooling down by walking, jogging slowly or cooling down on the machine you were using.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cacaa86a-ea71-4641-9dac-f4d95c0a051e"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Follow &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE" data-url="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tom's Guide on Google News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, or &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=tomsguide.com" data-url="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=tomsguide.com" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;em&gt;add us as a preferred source&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, to get our up-to-date news, analysis, and reviews in your feeds. Make sure to click the Follow button!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-more-from-tom-s-guide" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-more-from-tom-s-guide"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More from Tom's Guide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a id="elk-6c288037-e143-4a1e-9cfe-f0e4b519af93" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;aside data-model-name="Apple Watch 11" data-widget-type="multimodelreview" data-render-type="editorial" class="hawk-root"&gt;&lt;div class="hawk-multi-model-review-container"&gt;&lt;div class="hawk-multi-model-review-retail-container"&gt;&lt;p class="hawk-title-container"&gt;Today's best Apple Watch 11 deals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tom's Guide</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 05:02:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4gFBVV95cUxOLTNRaV9md3NzdFRkdWR2RzZCQ29MaWg1QllTbkRJYWlQbXYwZUd5TmdSdXVQMkpKbWJaVzd4TjJOcFZGa3pJZjBfc0ZWQ3hXbVpyQThZTUVIeXVDS2wtVWhsQWdiSF9aMEFnTjM0RXA4ZGJLd2l1ZTNuX2pNTm5VZzdOeXFMZ0sxNTI1b1hmaDhfR2FiZ04zNGpiSl92XzdyUmRlRHJpX2hVZFgxVUE2X2hyQzk2ZjFQdnhfemUwaDEzbGZWbVV2XzIzUVZOUGh5YmUxalUzQW11V0Zia2ZWMGtn</guid></item><item><title>​4种可与胡芦巴种子结合调节血糖的食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/4-foods-to-combine-with-fenugreek-seeds-to-regulate-blood-sugar/photostory/124605188.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As per experts, curcumin in turmeric reduces inflammation and improves insulin action. According to a study titled&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3857752/"&gt; Curcumin and Diabetes: A Systematic Review&lt;/a&gt;, curcumin could favorably affect most of the leading aspects of diabetes, including insulin resistance, hyperglycemia, hyperlipidemia, and islet apoptosis and necrosis. In addition, curcumin could prevent the deleterious complications of diabetes.&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to consume: &lt;/strong&gt;It is suggested that one can combine methi seeds with turmeric and warm milk or water for added benefits. One can add them to curries as well for effective results, supporting digestion, reducing inflammation, regulating blood sugar, and enhancing overall metabolic health naturally.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Images Courtesy: istock&lt;br&gt;Disclaimer: The information provided in this article is meant for general knowledge only and should not be taken as medical advice. Always talk to your doctor before starting any new routine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 03:40:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3gFBVV95cUxPZDlhNUdwcEhDZ0E5azQ2c3J3UzFCRExTSjltQlE3eFFUN3FwZHBac2QwbzRPamx4blhpRFJJSVhQaGJCemRGcjFnMzVfZUY1MFJ1WExXQndVcFRycVRnY1NwU0htTjNrc0piLVZYYXNhNHJqNTJQSzlGTFBFOURMVTBVWWNoWWMtOHJxclJIMnVWWkk5dXliVW9nQXdWcTVENGYwLU9ab2pCQkFDOU5KMW9kSExEbF82eG9KM1ZZMGdybHMtY05BU09qdVdPZ1BvRWd2Tl9fdDVZQldOVlHSAeYBQVVfeXFMTnMxcWczeFB0V0xValBqN3p6LVBlZ2luZ0pRZE1qeVhsR3dKWjQwT2JEX3JpaGoyY3ZTV2xGV2VYT1hPMDFjVFkydHlpSlhmR2ppRkx2eTd5SDdrRDVXMno4QldSS1J5X29Sc01fdzVZM0d2MmE4RFJsQmIxVDNwWHZldGpZQlpQS0NzTzVkRUdrb1p4a2c4aFZoLWM5NjlEMENjMHk2UUhjWnU1c1pEMDFIQVR1TVlHZHFfNkgtQ01YME5WWFhNZk14bGdZVkJhcmpRdG00clJieVNldUZrVjljeHU5UlE</guid></item><item><title>​顶级胃肠病学家吃6种美味零食，促进肝脏健康-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/6-yummy-snacks-a-us-gastroenterologist-eats-to-boost-liver-health/photostory/124681235.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 100 million people (25% of the population) in the United States have fatty liver disease ( MASLD aka NAFLD), according to the American Liver Foundation. MASLD is the most common form of liver disease in children, and &lt;a href="https://liverfoundation.org/liver-diseases/fatty-liver-disease/nonalcoholic-fatty-liver-disease-nafld/"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; suggest that it has doubled over the past 20 years. The cause? “This surge is largely driven by poor dietary habits, excessive calories that include excessive consumption of processed foods, sugar, and unhealthy fats,” Dr. Joseph Salhab, a Florida-based gastroenterologist, says. “However, proper nutrition plays a key role in supporting liver function and reducing fat accumulation. Making informed dietary choices and following essential health tips can help combat fatty liver disease and promote long-term wellness,” he adds. The gastroenterologist has shared a list of snacks he eats to improve his liver health. Yes, you can snack your way to good health! What are those snacks? Let’s take a look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9wFBVV95cUxPUmdHS1ZySnJaRkwyQmFGcy1PbVRraUJfTHVyeWphMVVpMld2TXRib3ZQUlV0Z1BEZjBuRDlGVExsNHZpaUFrUXNlYmVlRjVGcXc1a2p4N1NMVTlfYVFmSjc3MFZUbXZqZTF5QVBvakpwb3Ffc0pfblgzZGQ1QjREU29XbzlyejFuNkVpRXRZZXNVQUZXSGpDNFpubzd6bExRa0FpX1BYNzJweElWSTh6QXVWTlRyRTRkV3hhWGRDSktLT2V6T05MOWR4REFubUhzUW4zWnU3MnNEWlNiLVlJR1pyRnFIbXUtZDJMMlEzVFk5bXh4QVlJ0gH_AUFVX3lxTE9TYkRGZjQ0ZUU3Rnc1dU5tcE9BeHJ3dzVseWswaFJ4T2tGYUdBUHp6VmViZXFzejlzQW1uM0RPM1hpTkJNOTRhVmlkS2NabTFBczNOUVVxRGtFdzVGdVFKaXVKUnl0X3IxY25RcEJfMk1wRC1DNHdBY2JycFdmV1Zvb1ZKRWN6cmRsUTN6emtQUmFxRTlUVEZuV2RKdFlhMmJHVHVxMnQyZUFNUGl5T1Fhc2RWUVU1S2RIV2c2dF9QNEVsOV8wYVp0X0tCamFuTFF4X19IRGl6dUpHUlhIcnFjR0k1SXNJc1owOXZvOU9TYjk0dXo0cTF3bEhmSGQ2OA</guid></item><item><title>新的血液检测实际上可以检测到我/CFS吗？以下是我们所知道的- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/can-a-new-blood-test-actually-detect-me-cfs-heres-what-we-know</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Scientists in the United Kingdom &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/oct/08/scientists-say-they-have-first-blood-test-to-diagnose-chronic-fatigue-syndrome-me"&gt;say they have developed&lt;/a&gt; a blood test that can diagnose  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/chronic-fatigue-syndrome" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73056" data-postid="177505" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;myalgic encephalomyelitis&lt;/a&gt;/ &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/chronic-fatigue-syndrome" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73056" data-postid="177505" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;chronic fatigue syndrome&lt;/a&gt; (ME/CFS) &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12967-025-07203-w"&gt;with 96 percent accuracy&lt;/a&gt; – the first of its kind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many who live with the debilitating condition, this will be exciting news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite affecting &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12967-020-02269-0"&gt;millions of people worldwide&lt;/a&gt;, this condition remains poorly understood. It is characterized by unrelenting fatigue that doesn't improve with rest, and post-exertional malaise – &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/j.1365-2796.2011.02428.x"&gt;a worsening of symptoms&lt;/a&gt; after even minor physical or mental activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/massive-study-links-8-genetic-signals-to-chronic-fatigue-syndrome"&gt;Massive Study Links 8 Genetic Signals to Chronic Fatigue Syndrome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet with no reliable test, many people wait years for a diagnosis. This usually depends on symptoms meeting certain clinical criteria. But &lt;a href="https://emerge.org.au/diagnosis/"&gt;diagnostic criteria can be controversial as they vary worldwide&lt;/a&gt;, and many are outdated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An accurate blood test could be a game-changer for diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, how excited should we get? Here's what we know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How diagnosis works without a test&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently, you can only receive a diagnosis if you experience disabling fatigue – one of the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1300/J092v11n01_02"&gt;key symptoms&lt;/a&gt; according to most clinical criteria – for at least six months, accompanied by post-exertional malaise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But people with the condition often experience &lt;a href="https://www.healthdirect.gov.au/chronic-fatigue-syndrome-cfs-me"&gt;a wide range of other symptoms&lt;/a&gt;, including headaches, muscle or joint pain, sleep disturbances, dizziness, a racing heart, and problems with memory, thinking, and decision making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, clinicians must also rule out other conditions with overlapping symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means diagnosis relies heavily on clinicians' knowledge of ME/CFS and their willingness to listen to the patient's complex symptom history. This process can &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK284892/#:%7E:text=Diagnosing%20ME/CFS%20in%20the,2014;%20ProHealth%2C%202008"&gt;take years&lt;/a&gt; – and the delay in diagnosis has real consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evidence suggests early intervention is key to recovery. Rest during the early stages of the illness likely results in better long-term outcomes, as has been suggested for the clinically similar disease &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0264331"&gt;long COVID&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One study showed a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/diagnostics12102540"&gt;delayed ME/CFS diagnosis&lt;/a&gt; was linked to poorer outcomes, meaning recovery was less likely and the chance of developing more severe symptoms increased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without a definitive diagnosis, patients regularly face disbelief about their illness and have limited access to information, health-care services, and medical benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frequent delays in diagnosis may contribute to the condition's low recovery rate, which is &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/diagnostics12102540"&gt;estimated at just 1–10 percent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the new study looked at&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To develop a diagnostic test, the new study identified biomarkers that may be specific to people with this condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this case, the biomarkers relate to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/epigenetic-changes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73027" data-postid="177505" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;epigenetics&lt;/a&gt; – changes in the structure of a person's chromosomes, influencing which genes can be turned on or off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These changes occur due to environmental influences such as stress, infection, and exercise. So, when someone develops ME/CFS, the illness may change the structure of their chromosomes – but until now researchers hadn't identified what this would look like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Astro" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers examined blood samples from people they knew had ME/CFS and identified around 200 such biomarkers. These changes formed a distinct biological "signature" that was not present in the blood of healthy participants in the comparison group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This signature was very accurate in correctly identifying which samples were from people with the condition and which were from the comparison group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the researchers, the test's sensitivity was 92 percent – this is the probability a positive result will show when someone has the condition. It had a specificity of 98 percent, meaning the probability it can rule out negative cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This combined to an overall diagnostic accuracy of 96 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;So, is this a breakthrough?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research is promising, but it's still very early days. It was a proof-of-concept study, meaning small-scale research to initially test whether an idea might work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this case, researchers explored the idea that structural changes in chromosomes could be used as biomarkers of ME/CFS. Their results suggest they can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, there were several limitations. The study involved a relatively small number of people: 47 participants with severe ME/CFS and 61 in the healthy "control" group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ME/CFS group had more females, and its participants were so severely affected they were housebound. So they presumably had lower activity levels than the control group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know a person's &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.tig.2020.06.016"&gt;sex&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/biomedicines10010126"&gt;activity levels&lt;/a&gt; can influence these chromosomal changes, so this may have affected the results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To develop a diagnostic test that can be used widely, several crucial steps remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How much a person's sex and exercise levels influence these biomarkers needs to be determined. The biomarkers will also need to be validated in larger, more diverse groups, which include people with less and more severe symptoms than in this study and those from different backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To confirm these biomarkers are truly specific to ME/CFS, they need to be compared with other conditions that share similar symptoms, such as multiple sclerosis and fibromyalgia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, it's also important that a test, if developed, should be affordable and accessible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ME/CFS remains a severely underdiagnosed condition, and the lack of a reliable test continues to delay care and worsen outcomes. Identifying biomarkers, as this study aimed to do, is a promising first step.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/267099/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/sarah-annesley-1397560"&gt;Sarah Annesley&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Postdoctoral Research Fellow in Cell and Molecular Biology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/la-trobe-university-842"&gt;La Trobe University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/can-a-new-blood-test-really-detect-me-cfs-an-expert-unpacks-new-research-267099"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:01:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPTUNOYmo1R0c1QmxKQkx2NHpnLWZQMXc0NnZkWFk4ajNxeVhSV0lmcUVmNWxsWFpUdmhtTG1GcjlWdzVNTDdfY3B1Z2NhcmkyRVZaWVBuWXM1SE5BS2VkMTNmcllzZXhuZGpQNUpDX2toTm1RUXBzQmpqWE0zMnFza0JrUTlQY3NROFdxNTNTMjAwTXhHVGc</guid></item><item><title>“姑娘，吃你的疯狂药丸吧！ ’抗抑郁药重塑为热门生活方式配饰- wsj.com</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/health/wellness/anti-depressants-lifestyle-accessory-3b66027d</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>wsj.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNSGNIandtTG1Xd01ycC1wVnFaVmh4VGVmcHUwbnlUQVZxX1VwOHp1RFpub1JJQkFzSG5kQmtsYlpOc0hHOHlhTktRNUduclFidWJCeUcwVUdNY1VIdWpmVFp5OEd6clFkQnJSMm9fcVZFcnF5ZnFkSS15VXotT25ablQxU2xfSzY2</guid></item><item><title>让退休生活感觉像是人生最美好时光的10个爱好- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/d-t-10-hobbies-that-make-retirement-feel-like-the-best-years-of-your-life/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;Retirement isn’t an ending.&lt;br&gt;
It’s a schedule you finally get to design around energy, curiosity, and connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want it to feel like the best chapter yet, pick hobbies that compound—skills and friendships that get better with time.&lt;br&gt;
Here are ten that do exactly that, plus simple ways to start.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Walking—on purpose&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Walking sounds basic, but it’s a Swiss Army knife for retired life.&lt;br&gt;
You get movement, sunlight, and conversation—without special gear or sore joints.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turn it into a practice, not just a pastime.&lt;br&gt;
Choose a daily loop and give it a theme: birds one day, architecture the next, neighborhood history on Fridays.&lt;br&gt;
Invite one friend each week and talk phone-free.&lt;br&gt;
If you like structure, join or start a local walking club (libraries and parks departments are underrated hubs).&lt;br&gt;
Track steps if that motivates you, but don’t let metrics outrun joy. The win is consistency and company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On my side, “camera walks” changed everything. When I bring a lightweight mirrorless camera, I notice textures, colors, small street moments. The walk becomes a &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/r-research-says-these-7-activities-can-make-you-instantly-happier/"&gt;mindfulness exercise&lt;/a&gt; I actually look forward to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Community gardening&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you’ve never pulled a sun-warm tomato from a vine you tended, you’re missing a quiet kind of magic.&lt;br&gt;
Community plots give you fresh produce, real conversations, and a rhythm to the year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Start simple: salad greens, herbs, cherry tomatoes, and one “just-for-fun” plant like shishito or lemon cucumbers.&lt;br&gt;
If you’re plant-based or plant-curious, the garden also nudges your menu in that direction without forcing it—basil practically begs to become pesto, and mint turns water into something you actually crave.&lt;br&gt;
Bonus dividends: dirt therapy, vitamin D, and neighbors you’ll know by first name by August.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not into bending and kneeling? Build two standing-height beds and use lightweight fabric pots. Your back will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Playing music again&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Did you abandon the piano in 8th grade? Guitar in your 20s?&lt;br&gt;
Retirement is the perfect time to pick it up with zero performance anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find a teacher who gets adults. They’ll prioritize songs you love over drills you hate.&lt;br&gt;
Set a tiny commitment—ten minutes a day, five days a week.&lt;br&gt;
Join a low-pressure jam circle, ukulele club, or community choir. (Choirs are secret wellness machines: breathing, posture, focus, new friends.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A neat trick: keep the instrument out, not in a case. Visibility beats &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/gen-12-signs-youre-more-disciplined-than-90-of-people-even-if-you-dont-feel-like-it/"&gt;discipline&lt;/a&gt;. When my guitar leans by the couch, I end up strumming during ad breaks and call that a win.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Volunteering with a clear role&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Volunteering adds purpose, but it’s easy to overcommit.&lt;br&gt;
The sweet spot is a specific task on a predictable cadence: food bank packing on Thursday mornings, trail maintenance the first Saturday, literacy tutoring every other week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think of it like a part-time job you actually want.&lt;br&gt;
Ask for a role description, a point person, and an end date you can renew.&lt;br&gt;
You’ll show up more, feel useful, and &lt;a href="http://www.webmd.com/mental-health/signs-resentment#:~:text=Use%20self%2Dcompassion,pain%20with%20mindfulness%20and%20kindness." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;avoid resentment&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If food is your thing, soup kitchens and community fridges always need steady help. There’s something grounding about chopping onions next to someone you wouldn’t have met otherwise and leaving with tired hands and a full heart.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Photography—story first, gear second&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need a pro setup to capture the &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/8-signs-youre-living-according-to-your-values-instead-of-societys-expectations/"&gt;life you’re living&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Smartphone cameras are incredible, and the best camera is the one you carry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Give yourself projects that force you to look closer: “One doorway a day,” “Faces of the farmers market,” “Morning light for 30 days.”&lt;br&gt;
Learn just three controls—exposure, focus, and composition (rule of thirds and leading lines carry you far).&lt;br&gt;
Share small: a private album with family, a monthly photo email to friends, prints on your fridge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This hobby also pairs perfectly with travel and walking. You’ll remember the texture of the trip—the way steam rose from ramen in a rainy alley—long after the itinerary fades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Cooking clubs (with a theme)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-60994" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/flourish-after-retirement-840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cooking hits the retirement trifecta: creativity, community, and health.&lt;br&gt;
Starting a monthly cooking club is an easy way to turn eating into a social ritual.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pick a theme structure so it doesn’t fizzle:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Country of the Month” (Lebanon, Mexico City street food, Korean temple cuisine)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“One Ingredient, Five Ways” (cauliflower steaks, aloo gobi, roasted florets, soup, tacos)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“Plant-Forward Classics” (bolognese with lentils and mushrooms, jackfruit tacos, tofu katsu)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rotate homes, cap prep at 60 minutes, and keep recipes in a shared folder.&lt;br&gt;
If you’re exploring more &lt;a href="https://www.ncoa.org/article/cooking-with-plant-based-protein-5-tasty-options-to-try/#:~:text=Swap%20cooked%20lentils%20for%20meat,and%20heartier%20with%20cooked%20lentils." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;plant-based meals&lt;/a&gt;, clubs make it fun; skepticism drops when the food is genuinely good and there’s laughter around the table.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One pragmatic trick from restaurant life: mise en place. Prep and portion ingredients before you turn on the heat. Stress drops, flavor goes up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Strength and mobility that you’ll actually do&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal isn’t a six-pack; it’s freedom—getting off the floor, carrying groceries, traveling without fear of stairs.&lt;br&gt;
Two to three short strength sessions a week plus daily mobility will change how your whole life feels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep it minimal: squats, push/pull, hinge, carry.&lt;br&gt;
A kettlebell, resistance bands, and a bath towel for shoulder mobility can handle most of it.&lt;br&gt;
If classes keep you accountable, try Pilates, tai chi, gentle yoga, or water aerobics.&lt;br&gt;
Measure what matters: “Can I get up from the floor without using my hands?” “Can I balance on one foot while I brush my teeth?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I track “streaks” for &lt;a href="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/a-trainer-says-this-10-minute-full-body-mobility-routine-is-a-non-negotiable-for-people-with-tight-hips-back-and-shoulders" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;ten-minute mobility&lt;/a&gt;. When I hit seven days, my back stops complaining and my sleep improves. That feedback is addictive in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8) Mentoring and tutoring&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’ve got decades of scar tissue and wisdom. Someone out there needs it.&lt;br&gt;
Mentoring is a high-leverage hobby: your one hour can bend a young person’s trajectory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choose a lane: reading buddies in elementary schools, résumé coaching at the library, mock interviews at a community college, entrepreneurship programs for teens, or industry mentoring through your old professional network.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set boundaries up front (frequency, platforms, preferred times).&lt;br&gt;
Remember: your job isn’t to fix; it’s to ask good questions, reflect patterns, and celebrate progress.&lt;br&gt;
And yes, reverse mentoring is real—let the 20-year-old show you how they actually use the internet in 2025. You’ll trade value both ways.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;9) Micro-adventures and slow travel&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Travel doesn’t have to mean airports and time zones.&lt;br&gt;
A micro-adventure—one night somewhere new within 90 minutes of home—scratches the novelty itch with almost no logistics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pick a theme: historic inns on old highways, small-town diners with a vegan option, train day trips, mid-week coastal walks.&lt;br&gt;
For bigger trips, aim for slow travel: longer stays, fewer moves, neighborhood markets, local transit, easy mornings.&lt;br&gt;
House swaps are an underused option that make long stays affordable and interesting. Two retired couples swapping cities for a month? Everyone wins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring a simple ritual. I journal five lines a day—what I tasted, the best conversation, one small surprise. Later, that one page brings the entire place back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;10) Making things with your hands&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a specific satisfaction in finishing something tangible—pottery that holds your morning coffee, a stool you built, a quilt that keeps a grandkid warm.&lt;br&gt;
It anchors your days and gives your brain a restorative “focus mode.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Test-drive skills through beginner classes: pottery studios, community makerspaces, woodworking shops, textile labs.&lt;br&gt;
Start with small, useful projects to bank wins: a hand-thrown bowl, a cutting board, a sewn tote, a cyanotype print from leaves you gathered on a walk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The secret is to iterate. “Same project, better each time.” It lowers the learning curve and keeps momentum high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How to pick the right hobby (and stick with it)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Two questions help cut through overwhelm:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Would I enjoy the process even if I never got “good”?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Does this invite other people in?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then build a simple system:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Schedule it. Same day, same hour, treat it like a class.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep gear visible and ready. Barriers kill habits.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track streaks, not perfection. Miss a day? Start a new streak.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pair it with an anchor you already do (walk after coffee, practice guitar during the 3 p.m. slump).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share progress publicly enough to feel accountable (a monthly photo roundup, a club calendar), but not so public it becomes performative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What these hobbies have in common&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They feed competence, connection, and contribution—the three ingredients that &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/s-if-you-want-to-look-and-feel-youthful-in-your-retirement-years-stop-doing-these-8-things-immediately/"&gt;make retired life feel rich&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Competence: you’re still learning, improving, and solving.&lt;br&gt;
Connection: you regularly see people who expect you and are glad you came.&lt;br&gt;
Contribution: someone else benefits from your time—your cooking club, a student, your own future self who gets to &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/c-lc-7-quiet-behaviors-that-reveal-youre-aging-with-more-grace-than-most-people-your-age/"&gt;age with grace&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And they scale. You can walk farther or shorter, cook for two or twelve, shoot photos on your block or in Kyoto. No matter your budget or mobility, there’s a version that fits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A quick example week (steal it, tweak it)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mon&lt;/strong&gt;: 30-minute strength + garden check-in&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tue&lt;/strong&gt;: Literacy tutoring (1 hour) + camera walk home&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wed&lt;/strong&gt;: Cooking club prep (make vinaigrette, chop veg)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thu&lt;/strong&gt;: Group walk + coffee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fri&lt;/strong&gt;: Music lesson or practice (10–20 minutes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sat&lt;/strong&gt;: Micro-adventure day trip, journal five lines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sun&lt;/strong&gt;: Batch cook two easy plant-forward dishes for the week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Swap in pottery, yoga, or volunteering as needed. The shape matters more than the specifics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Final thought&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Retirement isn’t an empty calendar. It’s an invitation.&lt;br&gt;
Pick one hobby from this list and give it four weeks. If it doesn’t click, swap it out. If it does, double down.&lt;br&gt;
Either way, you’ll be living on purpose—and that’s what makes these years feel like the best ones.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sun, 19 Oct 2025 00:02:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNNVV2SzdiYXloX1ZKc0dzVjRFd2NjczMxS3ZYS0FNbXNBQUdNMFNlNDFUejVQTTZlZVJuUWJ4bW0tOEZsTlVUYmZZOExXdzBfdExFX21mSzE2QVRSdml0eXhNNEZ4eWZLd3A4MFpGbHRKb0djc3RwVE9jMVhoXzl5WTdqbnF1eHN1em1iQWdHeGgwakllUWdsWlEycnJ6ODUzU0daQnl0S0ZnNl9BaUE</guid></item><item><title>随着当局启动应急计划-无聊的熊猫，在南方州再次发现“僵尸鹿病”</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The&lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt; Florida&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission (FWC) has detected its second case of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;Chronic Wasting Disease (CWD)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;malady&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; that has a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;100 percent fatality&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt; rate among &lt;/span&gt;&lt;b&gt;deer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The first case (for 2025) of the illness was detected by the Sunshine State’s neighboring Georgia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The University of Minnesota reported at the time that it was the 36th US state to report what the academic institution dubbed a “fatal prion disease.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="post-highlights"&gt;&lt;span class="h2"&gt;Highlights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="bullet-wrapper"&gt;&lt;i class="bullet"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission confirmed its second case of Chronic Wasting Disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="bullet-wrapper"&gt;&lt;i class="bullet"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The infected deer was found in Holmes County near the Georgia border.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="bullet-wrapper"&gt;&lt;i class="bullet"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;CWD is 100 percent fatal in deer and has no known treatment or vaccine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Florida has put in place a “disease response plan”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer resting on grass in natural habitat, relevant to zombie deer disease and wildlife health concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/pedro-lastra-F0dmGPe2KG0-unsplash-68f4143d2858f__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer resting on grass in natural habitat, relevant to zombie deer disease and wildlife health concerns." title="Deer resting on grass in natural habitat, relevant to zombie deer disease and wildlife health concerns." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-tablet-ad-within-content post-ads"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad" data-source="primis"&gt;&lt;span id="desktop-widget-loaded"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/selective-focus-of-brown-deer-lying-on-green-grass-during-daytime-F0dmGPe2KG0" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Pedro Lastra/Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Florida conservation services noted that the most recent instance was detected in Holmes County near the state’s border with Georgia—close to where the latter discovered their first case.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The recent case was a road-[fatality] 1.5 year old doe sampled less than a mile south of Florida’s 2023 detection,” the agency &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://myfwc.com/research/wildlife/health/white-tail-deer/cwd/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;announced&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; on its website.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Said 2023 case involved a white-tailed deer that was hit by a vehicle on a highway. The discovery prompted a “disease response plan.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Florida’s conservation agency says it is taking the diagnosis seriously &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer showing severe symptoms of zombie deer disease in a wooded area as authorities respond to the outbreak in southern state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/7-68a6c946c822b__700-68f41447b20e1__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer showing severe symptoms of zombie deer disease in a wooded area as authorities respond to the outbreak in southern state." title="Deer showing severe symptoms of zombie deer disease in a wooded area as authorities respond to the outbreak in southern state." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/deer/comments/1ahgy2y/what_is_wrong_with_this_deer/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Difficult_Cat1110&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Like the pledge accompanying its announcement two years ago, the recent confirmation stated: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The FWC and its agency partners take CWD very seriously and are continuing with their comprehensive response plan with the goal of containing the disease within the area it was detected.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Because the second case is close to the original case, there will be no changes to the Management or Enhanced Surveillance Zones,” the website declared.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Florida has since tested 2500 deer for the illness&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer showing symptoms of zombie deer disease with visible growths on face and neck in a natural outdoor setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/6-68a6c944c115c__700-68f41449475a0__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer showing symptoms of zombie deer disease with visible growths on face and neck in a natural outdoor setting." title="Deer showing symptoms of zombie deer disease with visible growths on face and neck in a natural outdoor setting." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://x.com/PetnurseSue/status/1955790002052345865/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;PetnurseSue&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The government website shows that the state has since checked a total of 2406 deer, and confirmed that 2 tested positive for CWD.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The FWC breakdown also shows that 90 evaluations are pending.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;Experts advise against eating affected animals’ meat for fear of it leading to illnesses like mad cow disease&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer with large tumors on body, showing signs of zombie deer disease detected in southern state emergency response area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/2-68a6c93bc1dd2__700-68f4144a81412__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer with large tumors on body, showing signs of zombie deer disease detected in southern state emergency response area." title="Deer with large tumors on body, showing signs of zombie deer disease detected in southern state emergency response area." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://x.com/povertybayhunt" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;povertybayhunt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_2" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;blockquote class="tiktok-embed" cite="https://www.tiktok.com/@ericaachristinee/video/7520785539415526670" data-video-id="7520785539415526670"&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The University of Minnesota &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/chronic-wasting-disease/georgia-confirms-cwd-case-becoming-36th-us-state-report-fatal-prion-disease#:~:text=.-,Georgia%20confirms%20CWD%20case%2C%20becoming%2036th%20US%20state%20to%20report,'%20in%20the%20immediate%20area.%22" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;describes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; the illness as a “fatal neurodegenerative disease,” caused by “infectious misfolded proteins” or prions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The academic institution’s online platform notes that it can be contracted by other members of the Cervidae family, like elk and moose, through “environmental contamination.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While not known to affect humans, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/body-language-expert-breaks-down-king-charles-subtle-signs-of-impatience-towards-trump/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;experts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; advise against eating affected animals for the fear that it could trigger bovine spongiform encephalopathy, better known as mad cow disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It must be noted that aside from the loss of weight and bodily functions in the late stages of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/cancer-stricken-ex-victorias-secret-model-rejected-after-offering-to-walk-this-years/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;illness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, there are &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;no&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt; visual symptoms in affected animals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;CWD is not to be confused with the wart-like cutaneous fibromas found on deer, wild rabbits, and squirrels&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deer standing near a residential area, highlighting concerns about Zombie Deer Disease detected in a southern state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/4-68a6c94008a71__700-68f4144bb27f4__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Deer standing near a residential area, highlighting concerns about Zombie Deer Disease detected in a southern state." title="Deer standing near a residential area, highlighting concerns about Zombie Deer Disease detected in a southern state." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Jakeymakeme/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Jakeymakeme&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Social media has since caught wind of the outbreak, and one netizen observed, “Eating a zombie deer is 100% safer than anything you buy in your local grocery stores.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Said “zombie deer” is the moniker given to cervids that have been seen with large warts on their skin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These unsightly growths are known as cutaneous fibromas, which can be passed from deer, rabbits, and squirrels but are relatively harmless to their hosts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unlike the fatal CWD, the only time cutaneous fibromas can lead to their hosts passing away is when they affect their ability to forage and eat or evade predators.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;The term “zombie deer” has been pinned on animals with cutaneous fibromas and, more recently, those with CWD&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young deer standing on grass with signs of zombie deer disease, highlighting wildlife health concerns in a southern state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/3-68a6c93d77c55__700-68f4144d4323c__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Young deer standing on grass with signs of zombie deer disease, highlighting wildlife health concerns in a southern state." title="Young deer standing on grass with signs of zombie deer disease, highlighting wildlife health concerns in a southern state." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Jakeymakeme/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Jakeymakeme&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“What in the world is a zombie deer?” asked another &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/doctor-suggests-taylor-swift-pregnant-visible-changes-viral-video/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;netizen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, unfamiliar with the term connected to the warty animals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_3" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It’s CWD (Chronic Wasting Disease),” responded another mistakenly, “similar to mad cow but only transmitted through deer and moose and like animals.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;b&gt;CWD has since been addressed at a federal level, with Congress shelling out $35 million on it every year&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="video-container"&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/V-CPTdyP90o?si=50w4qr32i_5_u4lJ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young deer standing in a grassy field, highlighting concerns about zombie deer disease in southern state emergency response efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?image_id=divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“Zombie Deer Disease” Detected Again In Southern State As Authorities Launch Emergency Response Plan" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/zombie-deer-disease-hits-southern-state-as-second-case-recorded/?media_id=divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/divide-by-zero-FGkNt8tO04I-unsplash-68f4144124ce2__700.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Young deer standing in a grassy field, highlighting concerns about zombie deer disease in southern state emergency response efforts." title="Young deer standing in a grassy field, highlighting concerns about zombie deer disease in southern state emergency response efforts." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-content-media-source"&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/brown-deer-standing-on-green-grass-field-FGkNt8tO04I" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt; Divide By Zero/Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It’s coined the term zombie deer because of what happens.. ‘weight loss, poor coordination, drooling, and a vacant stare, as their brains deteriorate into a spongy consistency’,” attempted another.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It doesn’t mean it’s walking around [deceased], it’s in the process of [expiring].”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;CWD has since been addressed at a federal level, with the Chronic Wasting Disease Research and Management Act being &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.trcp.org/2022/12/23/house-senate-send-important-chronic-wasting-disease-legislation-presidents-desk/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;approved&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by Congress in December 2022.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The bill earmarked $35 million per year for research on the animal illness, which was slated to focus on detection in live animals, prevention, and understanding what caused the spread of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/facepalm-worthy-cringe-silly-posts/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;disease&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;One netizen, in the wake of COVID, wonders which lab CWD was generated in&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment mentioning zombie deer disease in Florida, highlighting concerns and local reactions to the outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_4" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment about zombie deer disease safety compared to grocery store food, emphasizing the topic of zombie deer disease detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment on social media post with text about zombie deer disease, highlighting concerns about its detection and emergency response plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook comment by Sharon Moyer asking about any connection to GMO mosquitoes, relevant to zombie deer disease concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment from Rita Vicky Berger DuBois asking what a zombie deer is, referencing zombie deer disease concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_0" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment asking which lab the zombie deer disease sample came from in an online discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment by user Anthony Saviano expressing a view on deer consumption amid concerns about zombie deer disease detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment text on light blue background about deer, referencing the Simpsons, related to zombie deer disease detected in southern state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment by Timothy Brown reading wait until the frozen gators show up on a social media platform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_1" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment warning about eating affected meat related to zombie deer disease concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social media comment mentioning walking dead zombies, related to concerns about zombie deer disease detected again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment from Peter Winberg stating not transmitted to humans yet about zombie deer disease concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a comment saying Good thing I don’t eat deer referencing zombie deer disease detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_2" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div id="postPoll-9524016" class="post-poll poll-wrapper single-post" data-poll-viewed="false" data-post-id="9524016" data-main-post-id="" data-poll-id="17888"&gt; &lt;input class="post-9524016-poll-value" type="hidden" value="eyJwb2xsSWQiOjE3ODg4LCJwb3N0SWQiOjk1MjQwMTYsImhpZGVDb21tZW50cyI6ZmFsc2UsInF1ZXN0aW9ucyI6W3siaWQiOjE3ODg4LCJwb2xsSWQiOjE3ODg4LCJ0ZXh0IjoiRG9lcyB0aGUgdGVybSBcdTIwMWN6b21iaWUgZGVlclx1MjAxZCBtYWtlIHlvdSBtb3JlIGNvbmNlcm5lZCBhYm91dCBDV0Q/Iiwib3JkZXIiOm51bGwsImFuc3dlcnMiOlt7ImlkIjo2ODIwMiwicXVlc3Rpb25JZCI6MTc4ODgsInRleHQiOiJZZXMsIGl0IHNvdW5kcyBzZXJpb3VzLiIsInZvdGVzIjoyMX0seyJpZCI6NjgyMDMsInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE3ODg4LCJ0ZXh0IjoiTm8sIGl0XHUyMDE5cyBtZWRpYSBoeXBlLiIsInZvdGVzIjoxMn0seyJpZCI6NjgyMDQsInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE3ODg4LCJ0ZXh0IjoiQSBsaXR0bGUsIEkgd2FudCBtb3JlIGluZm8uIiwidm90ZXMiOjh9LHsiaWQiOjY4MjA1LCJxdWVzdGlvbklkIjoxNzg4OCwidGV4dCI6Ik5vdCBjb25jZXJuZWQgYXQgYWxsLiIsInZvdGVzIjoyfV19XSwicG9zdFRpdGxlIjpudWxsLCJwb3N0VXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6XC9cL3d3dy5ib3JlZHBhbmRhLmNvbVwvem9tYmllLWRlZXItZGlzZWFzZS1oaXRzLXNvdXRoZXJuLXN0YXRlLWFzLXNlY29uZC1jYXNlLXJlY29yZGVkXC8ifQ=="&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: isInitialised()"&gt;    &lt;div data-bind="if: !isLoading() &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults"&gt; &lt;div class="poll-content"&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-title"&gt;Thanks! Check out the results:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-question" data-bind="text: currentQuestionText()"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;  &lt;p class="total-votes" data-bind="visible: totalVotes() &amp;gt; 10 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults &amp;amp;&amp;amp; totalVotesDisplayMode !== 0"&gt; &lt;span class="text"&gt;Total votes · &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-bind="text: totalVotesFormatted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block-wrapper"&gt; &lt;p class="badge"&gt;Newsletter&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block"&gt; &lt;p class="left"&gt; &lt;h3 class="title"&gt;Subscribe to Access &lt;br&gt; Exclusive Polls&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="disclaimer"&gt; &lt;p&gt;By entering your email and clicking Subscribe, you're agreeing to let us send you customized marketing messages about us and our advertising partners. You are also agreeing to our &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/privacy-policy/"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: newsletterSubscribed" class="thank-you"&gt; &lt;div class="wrapper"&gt;  &lt;p class="right"&gt;Thank you! You've successfully subscribed to newsletters!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bored Panda</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 23:04:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxOV2tHT0hOaUhSVEp1aDM4dGNhOHV3U1BhZTRZaTQ4SFFFVUxKMldaYlN4THhvcWNxUlphRkdZNEpqaVJtS3JLQng2WEZCRmRIVzNFNE1vTVpHZFVzYjA1cXpmRXl2Y3NVYTQxSVBDbjZUZUpoaEtuRGh0aThuWEc5eDRzU2YyU3lod1dhSUtkSzlaR2E0YUE</guid></item><item><title>老年男性的精子携带更多突变，它们可能会变得有害- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/older-mens-sperm-carry-more-mutations-and-they-may-turn-harmful</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Potentially harmful &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mutation"&gt;DNA mutations&lt;/a&gt; can amass in men's sperm as they age, new research has found, which may in turn impact the number of mutations passed on to children – and the risks of disease in the next generation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mutations occur in DNA when cells replicate, and arise either by random chance or because of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/air-pollution-strongly-associated-with-dna-mutations-tied-to-lung-cancer"&gt;environmental stresses&lt;/a&gt;. They can impact how well the body works, or have no observable effect at all. Mutations accumulate as time goes by, just like wear and tear on a car – but it hasn't been clear how much these genetic mishaps affect sperm in older men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers from the Wellcome Sanger Institute and King's College London in the UK used a new high-resolution analysis technique called NanoSeq to look in detail at mutations in the sperm of men aged 24-75 years, and the genes those mutations affected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/it-s-not-just-women-faulty-sperm-can-contribute-to-repeated-miscarriages"&gt;Sperm Could Be a Bigger Factor in Miscarriages Than We've Been Led to Believe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only do mutations occur at higher rates in older men, the data showed, but some are '&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nrurol.2016.37"&gt;selfish&lt;/a&gt;' – giving the cells that carry them a growth advantage, so they &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/j.2047-2927.2013.00175.x"&gt;replicate faster than or outlast&lt;/a&gt; other cells in the testes and gradually take over. Many of these mutations have previously &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ajhg.2011.12.017"&gt;been linked&lt;/a&gt; to developmental disorders and cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We expected to find some evidence of selection shaping mutations in sperm," &lt;a href="https://www.sanger.ac.uk/news_item/hidden-evolution-in-sperm-raises-disease-risk-for-children-as-men-age/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; geneticist Matthew Neville, from the Wellcome Sanger Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What surprised us was just how much it drives up the number of sperm carrying mutations linked to serious diseases."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed 81 sperm samples from 57 healthy men, some of whom &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pair-of-twins-raised-in-different-countries-reveal-significantly-different-cognitive-abilities"&gt;were twins&lt;/a&gt; – a factor which helps separate the effects of age on sperm DNA mutations from inherited genetics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 2 percent of sperm from men in their 30s were found to be carrying disease-causing mutations, which jumped up to 3-5 percent for middle-aged and older men (over the age of 43). By age 70, an average of 4.5 percent of sperm had potentially &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/reversible-molecular-changes-can-cause-cancer-study-shows"&gt;harmful mutations&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team was also able to identify 40 genes affected by the 'selfish' mutant cells winning out in the positive selection competition in the testes. That will help in future research linking specific mutations to specific &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-risk-of-cancer-could-fluctuate-even-born-youre-born"&gt;disease risks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177234" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177234" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SpermChart.jpg" alt="Sperm chart" class="wp-image-177234 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SpermChart.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SpermChart-600x276.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177234" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Sperm cells carrying potentially harmful mutations became more common as men aged. (Neville et al., &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Some changes in DNA not only survive but thrive within the testes, meaning that fathers who conceive later in life may unknowingly have a higher risk of passing on a harmful mutation to their children," &lt;a href="https://www.sanger.ac.uk/news_item/hidden-evolution-in-sperm-raises-disease-risk-for-children-as-men-age/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; geneticist Matt Hurles, from the Wellcome Sanger Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's worth bearing in mind that not all of these mutations will necessarily be passed on to the next generation. Some of them may actually reduce the chances of reproduction in some way – by interfering with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/world-first-scientists-film-the-exact-moment-a-human-embryo-implants"&gt;embryo development&lt;/a&gt;, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More work is required to figure out exactly how this steady increase in DNA mutations in men actually affects the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-reveals-alarming-rise-of-superbugs-in-newborn-babies"&gt;health of their kids&lt;/a&gt;, but for now, we have a much better idea of the processes involved.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Astro" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
These findings also give scientists a much closer look at the chain of cells that are known as the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Germline"&gt;male germline&lt;/a&gt;, cells set aside for the job of passing on genetic material to the next generation – potentially with both positive and negative consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The male germline is a dynamic environment where natural selection can favor harmful mutations, sometimes with consequences for the next generation," &lt;a href="https://www.sanger.ac.uk/news_item/hidden-evolution-in-sperm-raises-disease-risk-for-children-as-men-age/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; geneticist Raheleh Rahbari, from the Wellcome Sanger Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09448-3"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 21:01:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNSGhzSlpBeU1Sc0xuYnVLdlIySkFsT3F5dl9zWlM4RnU4b2NCSmRZeHVEb0J4UEZzMDNzTEZiUjZrTU5QRVd1TmozWktUZFNaYmYzRnVOZDAzMGxzekQxYVd1aFFVUUY2Vnp5ZkktUDRPVnZ3eFc5M2M3X01LSEJVY2pYZGJYNnhNdVJaemNLRHNjbENmakVF</guid></item><item><title>新研究揭示了膝关节骨性关节炎疼痛的最佳运动类型- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/new-study-reveals-the-best-type-of-exercise-for-knee-osteoarthritis-pain/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:44:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPZWVwSllTaTBudnFnQnNkcWliVlFKQXoyaHR6RU5xcjZsbC1HYkVLVWpPMnRmeHgybWxkZThmUmtia3pBT3pkOFg3MngtY05MSmkxRjBmbzdBa09wTGFrR2xOSEF1UDZPck9namlOSS1TTlM0QmMzSFZ0VWRnaGFnT1ZIUi1lRU00SXZxODZzWm9iRlV0aVlQV203LVJMODQ</guid></item><item><title>随着可怕的副作用飙升，医生揭露了褪黑激素的真相-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15044713/rise-melatonin-addiction-overdoses.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Health experts have issued a warning about the 'terrifying' rise of melatonin use among children, which they say could lead to fatal overdoses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melatonin is a hormone naturally produced by the pineal gland in the brain. It helps regulate the body’s sleep-wake cycle (circadian rhythm). Melatonin levels rise in the evening, promoting drowsiness, and fall in the morning, promoting wakefulness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The supplement is heavily regulated as a prescription-only medication in many parts of the world, including the UK, the EU and Australia. But in the US, the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/fda/index.html" id="mol-e06c3c60-aace-11f0-889a-21cc4e50b213"&gt;FDA&lt;/a&gt; regulates it as an over-the-counter option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;More than 67 million Americans take melatonin, and analysts predict sales of the supplement will top $588 million in 2025, up from $339 million in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But as adults turn to the hormone in droves to help kick insomnia, children are also being introduced to it, either intentionally by parents to aid fussy sleepers or by mistaking appetizing-looking melatonin gummies for a sweet treat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2023 study by the &lt;span&gt;American Academy of Sleep Medicine found that almost half (46 percent) of parents have given melatonin to a child under the age of 13 to help them fall asleep. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And in 2022, the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/centers-for-disease-control-and-prevention-cdc/index.html" id="mol-ca335fb0-9f06-11f0-a9b9-b94c99276d56"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt; revealed how, in the decade leading up to 2021, poison helplines dealt with 260,435 calls about children who had taken too much melatonin, a 530 percent increase from 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2012, melatonin was responsible for one percent of pediatric poisonings. That rose to five percent in 2021.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Health experts are warning about the 'terrifying' rise of melatonin addiction and overdoses among children in the US, with little known about the long-term consequences of taking the sleep aid (Stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of the poison reports, two children died, five were put on a ventilator to help them breathe, nearly 300 ended up in intensive care and more than 4,000 were hospitalized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melatonin &lt;span&gt;is naturally produced in the brain's pineal gland, and its release into the body is controlled by light.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;During the day, melatonin levels in the body are low and we feel awake, but when the sun sets, more melatonin circulates in the body, preparing people for sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melatonin may be suggested to adults to help them fall or stay asleep, but the substance is generally not recommended for children without medical guidance because little is known about its long-term impacts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Keith Vossel, a neurologist at the University Of California Los Angeles, told the Daily Mail he would not recommend giving children melatonin as it is a hormone and 'could have effects on the timing of puberty, metabolism and immune system.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies have shown a link between melatonin intake and delayed puberty, as well as an &lt;span&gt;affect on related hormonal pathways. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This is because melatonin interacts with the hypothalamic-pituitary-gonadal (HPG) axis - the hormonal system that controls puberty - so 'we need to be cautious and longer-term studies are needed,' Vossel said.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like Vossel, Dr Rachel Toles, a clinical psychologist in California, told the Daily Mail she is concerned about the melatonin abuse among both adults and children. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Melatonin should never be the first solution for children’s sleep,' she said. 'It’s a hormone, not a harmless vitamin, and the long-term effects on developing brains are still unknown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The big issue is that the supplements look like candy and they are often left within children’s reach. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Some parents also give melatonin to their kids too freely, and it has become a cultural quick fix for sleep, which is concerning.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Along with having a possible impact on puberty, Toles said it can negatively affect the metabolism and immune systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melatonin can negatively affect metabolism by disrupting glucose regulation and weight balance when misused, and may impair immune function by suppressing necessary inflammatory responses if overused. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taking melatonin at the wrong time can disrupt insulin release and circadian control of glucose, leading to poor blood sugar control and weight gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, excess melatonin can overly suppress pro-inflammatory signals, weakening necessary immune responses to infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Toles said that parents should also be aware that m&lt;span&gt;elatonin 'can cause grogginess, headaches and even more wakefulness at higher doses.' &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'The real danger is using it to mask bigger issues like screen time, anxiety or inconsistent routines,' she added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;There is also the possibility of children getting hooked on the supplement and their sleep getting worse in the long run. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A typical dose for melatonin ranges from one to 3mg, taken about 30 minutes before bedtime, with most people rarely needing more than 5mg (Pictured: melatonin gummies on a store shelf)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Reddit, dozens of parents have revealed horror stories involving melatonin and their children. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;One mother revealed that she gives her son, who has autism and ADHD, one milligram of melatonin when on vacation. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A typical adult dose for melatonin ranges from one milligram to 3mg, taken about 30 minutes before bedtime, with most people rarely needing more than 5mg.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The recommended dose for young children is significantly lower (for three- to five-year-olds the dose is suggested not to exceed one milligram), and this amount can lead to a range of moderate to severe symptoms such as drowsiness, dizziness, headaches, nausea and agitation. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The mother said she accidentally left the bottle of gummies in her two-year-old daughter's room, and the infant ended up taking in 26mg. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ingesting 26mg of melatonin is a serious overdose for a toddler and requires immediate medical attention. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The mother said she called poison control and they told her to monitor her daughter at home but to visit the ER if any symptoms worsened. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A CDC report released in early 2022 revealed that in the decade leading up to 2021, poison helplines dealt with 260,435 calls about children who had taken too much melatonin (Stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;On Facebook, Beth McCarty from Vancouver revealed her 11-year-old son, Ethan, took 18 melatonin gummies as he had watched his father take large doses of medication. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sharing photos of Ethan looking drowsy in the back of an ambulance, she wrote: '&lt;/span&gt;So deeply thankful for the medics [and] poison control who responded after Ethan was literally laied [sic] out and plastered to the living room rug. They were all so calm with us and our boy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Parents, WATCH your kiddos with ANY med. Ethan sure knows never to try anything like this again.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In another post, Iowa-based mental health coach Marci Hanzelka McKinnon shared how she unknowingly got her son hooked on melatonin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a warning to other parents, she wrote: 'Yep, we are guilty. We gave our son melatonin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'No one knew (or no one told us) back then the dangers of using melatonin for our child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'At that time the highest dose was 10mg; that was considered extremely high. We started him at 3mg and slowly kept moving it up because it stopped working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Iowa-based mental health coach Marci Hanzelka McKinnon (pictured) shared how she unknowingly got her son hooked on melatonin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Eventually we reached 10mg. Once that stopped working we stopped giving it to him and were no better off than we were before we started using it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Today, you can get 50mg of melatonin! That’s unbelievable! And so dangerous!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;All of the doctors the Daily Mail spoke to agreed that sleep has become harder for children in the modern world with increased exposure to technology and busier schedules. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Still, they all advised against melatonin as a solution. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Los Angeles-based Dr Raj Dasgupta, the chief medical advisor for Sleepopolis, said the best thing to do before turning to sleep aids is to figure out why the child isn't sleeping first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'S&lt;span&gt;ometimes it’s as simple as bedtime habits or anxiety,' he told the Daily Mail. 'I usually tell parents to exhaust all behavioral approaches before reaching for medication or supplements.'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;And Dr David Sinclair, a professor at Harvard Medical School, said that '&lt;/span&gt;Natural alternatives are best' for addressing sleep issues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'[Try] consistent bedtime routines, dimming lights in the evening and keeping screens out of the bedroom, and making sure kids get enough daylight and physical activity during the day,' he told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I have seen cases where children were put on melatonin for sleep and it helped in the short term. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But in most situations, once children get exercise, nighttime lights are dimmed and devices are taken away before bedtime, they didn’t need the supplement anymore.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:27:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxObzI3dnQ4cUVfZ0tOUWhxSDdqYnNxV0loVzdIbnFUYjZxVHV3WWg1TUpEMmZSUGJFdm81amc2OFQyNGNXWmttVGozdlI5R2RfOTlsQmNrbnJYOE1QWWRQS0MtTzBkVnRkOWhhUmlpUzZqVTd1d1VheWdRRFlUVld4V2JxMjduNVNVRTNIWkR4RndDN1dKbVE</guid></item><item><title>世界更年期日：支持女性，加强系统-财富</title><link>https://fortune.com/2025/10/18/world-menopause-day-world-economic-forum-womens-health-support-women-october-18/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Menopause has long been treated as a quiet, private ordeal. That silence carries a cost. On World Menopause Day, bringing menopause out of the shadows is not a niche concern but a public priority with tangible dividends for health, equity, and economic growth. The conversation must move from scattered efforts to a coordinated plan that is practical to implement in clinics, workplaces, and national policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="paywall"&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Perimenopause and menopause can span more than a decade. At any given moment, more than 450 million women worldwide are navigating this transition. According to research by the World Economic Forum’s Global Alliance for Women’s Health, closing the women’s health gap on menopause alone could yield an &lt;a href="https://www.weforum.org/publications/blueprint-to-close-the-women-s-health-gap-how-to-improve-lives-and-economies-for-all/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.weforum.org/publications/blueprint-to-close-the-women-s-health-gap-how-to-improve-lives-and-economies-for-all/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;estimated 2.4 million disability adjusted life years every year and roughly 120 billion dollars in annual GDP gains.&lt;/a&gt; These figures represent fewer missed workdays, steadier household income, and less strain on health systems. They also represent lives experienced with more comfort, clarity, and confidence. Numbers summarize the stakes, but lived experience explains them.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What stands in the way is not a lack of need but a lack of preparation across the systems that touch women’s lives. Diagnosis and care are often late, inconsistent, or inaccessible. And there is evidence to back this — a Yale University &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/menopausejournal/Abstract/2015/03000/Incremental_direct_and_indirect_costs_of_untreated.5.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://journals.lww.com/menopausejournal/Abstract/2015/03000/Incremental_direct_and_indirect_costs_of_untreated.5.aspx" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; of insurance claims showed while 60% of women with significant symptoms of menopause seek treatment, almost 75% are left untreated. Training is part of the problem. &lt;a href="https://healthmatch.io/blog/why-are-there-so-many-menopause-knowledge-gaps" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://healthmatch.io/blog/why-are-there-so-many-menopause-knowledge-gaps" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;In one study&lt;/a&gt;, half of family medicine doctors reported only a single lecture on menopause during training, and one in five reported none at all. The workforce impact is visible. Research indicates that one in four women has considered leaving work during the transition, and one in ten who have worked through menopause left a job because of their symptoms. This is not only a productivity story, it is also one of opportunity cost. It is a story about experienced leaders stepping back, about teams losing anchors, and about families absorbing avoidable stress.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As an Expert Member of the one-of-its-kind multistakeholder platform, the World Economic Forum’s &lt;a href="https://initiatives.weforum.org/global-alliance-for-womens-health/home" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://initiatives.weforum.org/global-alliance-for-womens-health/home" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;Global Alliance for Women’s Health&lt;/a&gt;, as well as an expert medical advisor at acclaimed actress, director, producer, advocate, and entrepreneur, Halle Berry’s menopause care platform, &lt;a href="https://www.respin.health/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.respin.health/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;Respin Health&lt;/a&gt;, I see how quickly the conversation shifts when evidence meets execution. These organisations are helping translate science into clinical standards and employer policies, while informing policy frameworks that leaders can adopt and fund. Advocacy is meaningful when it results in actions that are easy to copy, measure, and sustain. Our work with Halle Berry, who &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7381282254116921344" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://www.linkedin.com/feed/update/urn:li:activity:7381282254116921344" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;recently joined the Global Alliance for Women’s Health as Public Ambassador&lt;/a&gt;, showcases the sheer appetite and momentum that exists to redefine menopause and empower women to be the guardians of their own health. The path is known. What remains is follow-through.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we leave women to figure menopause out alone, we pay a grave price in health, productivity, and our very own dignity. We have to normalize this conversation about menopause. We have to make guidance useable. We have to improve access to quality care, and we need to invest in research and innovation,” said Halle Berry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content-sentinel" data-index="1"&gt;



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Health care is the first place to start&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Menopause should be part of routine primary care, not a specialty service that only a few can reach. Screening can begin during routine visits for women in their forties and fifties, with clear pathways for counselling and treatment. Evidence based options include lifestyle approaches, non-hormonal treatments, and, when appropriate and safe, hormonal therapies guided by informed choice. Care should consider mental health and cardiometabolic risk, since &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4377487/" target="_blank" rel="noopener" aria-label="Go to https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4377487/" class="sc-5ad7098d-0 lcJVdL"&gt;sleep disruption, mood changes, and metabolic shifts&lt;/a&gt; often travel together. Referral pathways must connect primary care, gynaecology, mental health, and cardiometabolic services so women are not left to navigate a maze with contradictory advice. This is not about boutique clinics for the few. It is about equipping the front lines to meet a ubiquitous need.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Workplaces are the next lever. Simple adjustments can make a meaningful difference. Flexibility where feasible, paid time off for symptom flare days, and practical measures like temperature control and quiet rest areas reduce the friction that turns symptoms into lost days. Benefits should name menopause explicitly, so women know coverage exists. Manager training should normalize support without forcing disclosure. Employers who measure retention, error rates, and team performance before and after adopting these practices will find what many have already learned. Small investments stabilize teams and pay for themselves.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research and product design must close the data gap and raise the bar for solutions. Studies should reflect the diversity of real women, including race, age, and co existing conditions. Endpoints should be comparable so clinicians and consumers can tell what works and for whom. Digital tools and consumer products that target sleep, cognition, thermoregulation, and pelvic health should be evaluated against evidence standards and priced for broad access. Innovation is welcome. So is rigor. Women deserve both.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Policy and financing can turn best practice into the baseline&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Essential menopause services belong in national primary health packages and in public and private insurance coverage. Governments can accelerate employer adoption with clear standards, public recognition, and targeted incentives that reward organizations for implementing menopause supportive policies. Public information campaigns can replace stigma with practical knowledge for women, partners, managers, and clinicians. Countries should publish a small set of indicators that matter in daily life. Time to diagnosis, treatment access, and workforce participation are simple to understand and powerful to track. Accountability is easier when the yardstick is clear.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why does this matter beyond the clinic and the workplace? Because when women’s health is prioritized, families and economies function better. Earlier diagnosis and appropriate treatment reduce absenteeism. Menopause supportive workplaces keep experienced talent on the job and reduce turnover. Good care prevents avoidable complications that are costly later. These mechanisms repeat across millions of women and thousands of organizations. The cumulative effect shows up in national productivity. The more important return, however, is human. Better sleep, clearer thinking, steadier mood, and restored confidence change how women experience midlife. That is growth measured in dignity and opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content-sentinel" data-index="3"&gt;



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Effective advocacy pairs public leadership with technical depth and coordinated action. Public figures help make the issue relatable. Researchers and clinicians define what quality care looks like. Cross-sector forums align employers, health systems, and governments on practical standards and timelines. This combination turns awareness into accountable implementation. This is where platforms such as the Global Alliance for Women’s Health and the International Menopause Society bring real value to the conversation — by bringing together experts and leaders to make the shift from intention to implementation. 



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What should happen now? &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Health systems can add a brief screening and counselling step to routine primary care visits and build simple referral pathways that do not collapse under real world pressure. Medical schools and continuing education providers can strengthen training, so the next generation of clinicians starts on firmer ground. Employers can publish a menopause policy, train managers, and update benefits language so support is easy to find. Researchers can design studies that reflect the diversity of women and use shared endpoints that allow transparent comparisons. Policymakers can put menopause care in the basic benefit package and require transparent reporting on access and outcomes. None of these actions is a moonshot. Each is a choice that aligns with what we already know.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Culture change travels alongside policy change. Partners can listen without judgment. Friends can share what has helped them. Community leaders can include menopause in health talks that already reach women where they live and work. The tone matters. Precision matters. A plan matters. Together they create an environment where a woman does not have to spend years searching for a name for her symptoms or for a path to relief.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;World&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Menopause&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Day should not be a once-a-year reminder. It should be a yearly accountability moment that asks a simple question: Did we make it easier this year for women to find accurate information, timely care, and practical support? If the answer is yes, the benefits will be visible in clinics, workplaces, homes, and countries.



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The path is clear — what remains is resolve. Let us act today so more women can live, work, and thrive tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content-sentinel" data-index="5"&gt;



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The opinions expressed in Fortune.com commentary pieces are solely the views of their authors and do not necessarily reflect the opinions and beliefs of &lt;/em&gt;Fortune&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 20:16:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOZ05OdGEtOHFjX3BWSkRKTV9LOXZOMS1EbGFCUkJwR2kyUlhNenVIYXllLV9RVHR5TzdFVFdUZE1zcXYwNTZCNG9CUFZJdnNNR1pud3B3d1pDazJsRUVTQ255QXhNb3pNcmtmNXVXU3B2QlFLRmlFSFJ1V0tQM2hNWkV0WGFsYVB5QnZCRmNvY0JkMUJoeDZxSkFPOVJ0RU5SejJnS3lFQ0FJV2dLQXkwSQ</guid></item><item><title>你怀孕的地方会影响你的大脑...地图显示最好的地方-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15199237/where-born-brain-development-map.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The place where your parents conceived you could have permanently stunted your brain, a study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/spain/index.html" id="mol-d12255e0-aabb-11f0-b109-4191f609bee1"&gt;Spain&lt;/a&gt; recruited women during their first trimester of pregnancy and, later, those babies that were born, and estimated how severely they were exposed to fine particulate matter (PM2.5).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;PM2.5 are a group of microscopic particles that are emitted directly into the air from fossils fuels burned from factories and gasoline-powered stoves and cars, as well as burning wood in fireplaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These particles are so small, about &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/news/article-15170677/A-trendy-wood-burning-stove-killed-need-banned-anymore-damage.html?ico=comment-anchor"&gt;30 times thinner than a strand of human hair&lt;/a&gt;, that they undetectable by the naked eye and the nose and lungs can't filter them out, allowing them to travel to the bloodstream and induce widespread inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Using MRI scans on the newborns, the researchers found that those whose mothers were exposed to higher levels of PM2.5 during pregnancy had slower myelination, the process by which myelin is formed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Myelin is a protective sheath that coats pathways between neurons to help them better transmit information. It helps process electrical signals in the brain and allows the organ to mature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Slow myelination can lead to developmental delays, low muscle tone and seizures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The new study focused on children born in Spain, but PM2.5 is widely present in the US as well, particularly along the west coast and in the south. The US also has more air pollution than Spain, suggesting Americans could be facing a greater threat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers in Spain found exposure to fine particulate matter in the womb may slow the rate a baby's brain matures (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Gerard Martínez-Vilavella, study author and researcher at the MRI Unit of the Radiology Department at Hospital del Mar, said: 'Our study shows that the myelination process, a progressive indicator of brain maturation, occurs at a slower rate in newborns most exposed to PM2.5 during pregnancy.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the study, published last month in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0160412025005525?via%3Dihub#s0010"&gt;Environmental International&lt;/a&gt;, looked at 1,080 pregnant mothers who lived in Spain recruited between October 2018 and March 2021 during their first three months of pregnancy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The women were between 18 and 45 years old and had an average age of 34. Two-thirds were of European descent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When the participants were 32 weeks pregnant, researchers invited them to volunteer their babies for the MRI portion of the study. A total of 93 infants received the scans after they were born. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;PM2.5 exposure levels were estimated in each participant's home, during their commute and at their workplace using data from monitoring sites and questionnaires. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team found higher PM2.5 exposure early in pregnancy was associated with lower myelination in the cerebral cortex, the brain's center for thought, language, memory and sensory processing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Higher exposure later in pregnancy was associated with lower myelination throughout the brain overall. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Fetuses are more prone to lasting health effects early in gestation because their organs are rapidly developing at this time, including the brain, and early gestation is when genetic disorders tend to develop. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pollution exposure early in pregnancy has been linked to congenital heart disease and birth defects like spina bifida, as well as low birth weight and permanent brain damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And a 2024 review in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2666765724001212#sec0011"&gt;Environmental Advances&lt;/a&gt; found that PM2.5 exposure in adults as well was linked damage in the lungs and respiratory system, heart, immune system and nervous system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured above are the Mono-Inyo craters in Mono County, California, where levels of fine particulate matter are more than five times higher than the national average (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Martínez-Vilavella said: 'Air pollution, specifically PM2.5, is associated with alterations in the myelination process, a fundamental mechanism of brain maturation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Therefore, it is essential to continue controlling pollution levels and to study how this slowdown may affect the later brain development of children.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the babies have not yet been followed to see if they have lasting health impacts.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's thought that PM2.5 triggers inflammation in the brain that damages nerve cells and the myelin sheath protecting them. PM2.5 is also so small that it can cross the blood-brain barrier and enter brain tissues directly.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team noted more research is needed to see if older infants and children will suffer long-term harms from this decreased myelination.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Jesús Pujol, head of the MRI Unit of the Radiology Department at Hospital del Mar, said: 'In the early stages of life, brain changes are large and complex. Both excessive slowdown and acceleration of brain maturation can be harmful to the child. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'However, it remains to be determined whether the observed effect is necessarily detrimental. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This study opens an exciting new field of research aimed at determining the optimal speed of brain maturation during pregnancy and understanding how the mother and placenta may act as effective filters to protect and optimize this process.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the US, the most recent data collected by the National Institute on Minority Health and Health Disparities, an arm of the NIH, shows the highest concentrations of PM2.5 are along the west coast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mono County, in northern California, reported the highest levels in 2020, the latest data available, at 39.1 micrograms per cubic meter, more than five times the national average of 7.3. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The US Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) recommends being exposed to no more than nine micrograms per cubic meter of PM2.5 in a year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;With just 13,000 residents, Mono County is the least populated county in California and is home to dense rock formations and volcanic fields and craters, which spread fine ash particles and convert chemicals like sulfur dioxide into fine particulate matter like PM2.5. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Clackamas County, Oregon, and Marion County, Oregon, followed closely behind with 30.4 and 25 micrograms per cubic meter. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just outside of Portland, Oregon, Clackamas County, home to 421,000 people, has long suffered poor air quality due to wildfire smoke and seasonal wood burning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts from the American Lung Association believe Marion County, which is just below Clackamas County and has 300,000 residents, suffers high PM2.5 levels because pollution from nearby highways and farm fields gets trapped in the mountain ranges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;On the opposite end of the spectrum, Carlton County, Minnesota, reports just 1.3 micrograms per cubic meter of PM2.5, according to the latest data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just beneath Lake Superior, 36,000-resident Carlton County is heavily forested, reducing pollution exposure from highways and cities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:11:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQNE9fQmtsRlJGLVNJZFRmeUtBWUU4bFJDTjdLWVU1Zkk3N2duU3FXVzV5azU4NEpQWWR2R1V1bjJwcTM0RFlZTnZVZ0VaaXFCZDBBR0FNU2FtSzFtNUNQdUhJSXFnSEpPdlhCOGNkcWgtR1p6SkNhQTNNaU5lQ3pUaV84c2FEUDNzNWM4VWxibFFPYk0</guid></item><item><title>罕见的新型糖尿病是婴儿独有的，科学家报告- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/rare-new-form-of-diabetes-is-unique-to-babies-scientists-report</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Scientists have identified a single gene that gives rise to a rare form of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="177022" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, unique to newborn babies. Mutations of this gene can disable and ultimately kill off insulin-producing cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new discovery reveals that the pancreas's beta cells – which create the insulin hormone our bodies need to manage blood glucose – are entirely dependent on the &lt;em&gt;TMEM167A&lt;/em&gt; gene. This gene also affects neuron function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The ability to generate insulin-producing cells from  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="177022" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt; has enabled us to study what is dysfunctional in the beta cells of patients with rare forms as well as other types of diabetes," &lt;a href="https://news.exeter.ac.uk/faculty-of-health-and-life-sciences/researchers-discover-of-a-new-type-of-diabetes-in-babies/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; diabetologist Miriam Cnop, from Free University of Brussels in Belgium. "This is an extraordinary model for studying disease mechanisms and testing treatments."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-distinct-new-form-of-diabetes-is-officially-recognized"&gt;A Distinct New Form of Diabetes Is Officially Recognized&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The international team mapped the genes of six babies who had been diagnosed with neonatal diabetes and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Microcephaly"&gt;microcephaly&lt;/a&gt; before 6 months of age. Five of these babies also had epilepsy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This combination of diagnoses in infants is known as MEDS (microcephaly, epilepsy, and diabetes syndrome), and it's extremely rare, with only 11 individuals recorded so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before this study, two genes had been linked to the syndrome: &lt;em&gt;IER3IP1 &lt;/em&gt;and YIPF5. For a baby to be born with MEDS, they must have inherited two mutated copies of the gene, one from each parent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gene sequencing revealed that the same inheritance pattern applies to MEDS babies with the insulin-blocking variant of the &lt;em&gt;TMEM167A&lt;/em&gt; gene, making this the third genetic cause of MEDS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;TMEM167A &lt;/em&gt;is active across the pancreas and the brain in both adults and infants, humans and mice, which may explain why these babies experience problems with the function of both organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To better understand how the &lt;em&gt;TMEM167A&lt;/em&gt; gene variant causes diabetes, the researchers removed the gene from human pluripotent stem cells, replacing it with the variant taken from one MEDS patient's DNA. These stem cells were then encouraged to develop into beta cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177048" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177048" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001.jpg" alt="diagram of b cell issues" class="size-full wp-image-177048" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001.jpg 1000w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001-642x437.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001-609x415.jpg 609w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001-768x523.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/fgene-08-00021-g001-600x409.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1000px) 100vw, 1000px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177048" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Similar beta cell failures occur in type 2 diabetes, as shown here. (Swisa et al., &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fgene.2017.00021"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fronti. Genet.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, 2017)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gene variant didn't interfere with this development, but the beta cells produced were far from functional. Exposed to glucose, they did not release the insulin they're supposed to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These cells also didn't cope well with the resulting disruptions to their endoplasmic reticulum (the maze-like structure inside a cell that shuttles material around): it tended to kill the beta cell.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_launch"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Launch" class="alignnone wp-image-177073 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
"Finding the DNA changes that cause diabetes in babies gives us a unique way to find the genes that play key roles in making and secreting insulin," &lt;a href="https://news.exeter.ac.uk/faculty-of-health-and-life-sciences/researchers-discover-of-a-new-type-of-diabetes-in-babies/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; University of Exeter molecular geneticist Elisa de Franco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The finding of specific DNA changes causing this rare type of diabetes in six children led us to clarifying the function of a little-known gene, &lt;em&gt;TMEM167A&lt;/em&gt;, showing how it plays a key role in insulin secretion."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1172/JCI195756"&gt;The Journal of Clinical Investigation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 18:01:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNSmpKSE1vR05iNUJmWGFQeXR6cDZIQnZCek1vTVl3VDFyZ01ReHBZTGNIYks1cVY3ZTZoLW1YdEpsVmNKaFBGbU9GZFhFM3JQMFhNWk16NnJpRWNsZTMxSHkySV8tM19yeHc4ejNaazdIeE9zNG9uSmN1UmFLb0pLRFNRVVRXelU1UlhqWElwZGN2RlU0Mm5B</guid></item><item><title>奥斯卡获奖女演员黛安·基顿死于细菌性肺炎。以下是关于感染的须知事项-福布斯</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/omerawan/2025/10/18/oscar-award-winning-actress-diane-keaton-died-of-bacterial-pneumonia-heres-what-to-know-about-the-infection/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="fs-article fs-responsive-text current-article article-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-0" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA - MAY 01: Actress Diane Keaton attends the premiere of STX's "Poms" at Regal LA Live on May 01, 2019 in Los Angeles, California. (Photo by Rodin Eckenroth/WireImage)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;WireImage&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beloved Oscar winning actress Diane Keaton died of bacterial pneumonia at the age of 79, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/16/movies/diane-keaton-cause-of-death.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/16/movies/diane-keaton-cause-of-death.html" aria-label="death certificate"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/16/movies/diane-keaton-cause-of-death.html"&gt;death certificate&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; from Saint John’s Health Center in Santa Monica, CA. Every year, pneumonia leads to about 1.2 million hospitalizations in the United States and over 41,000 deaths, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/pneumonia.htm" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/pneumonia.htm" aria-label="CDC"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/pneumonia.htm"&gt;CDC&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Here is everything you need to know about pneumonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="subhead-embed"&gt;Pneumonia- Causes And Symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pneumonia is an infection of the lung that results in the air sacs within the lungs to fill with fluid and pus. This can impact the body’s ability to take in oxygen, which then results in difficulty breathing for many patients. The disease can range from mild to life-threatening, depending on a person’s age, overall health, and type of organism that is causing the illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The infection can be caused by a variety of different pathogens, including bacteria, viruses, and fungi. The most common type would be bacterial pneumonia, as was the cause in Keaton’s case. This type of pneumonia can produce more severe symptoms and is most commonly caused by the bacteria &lt;em&gt;Streptococcus Pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="vestpocket nsO6K"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Viral pneumonia is often caused by respiratory viruses such as influenza viruses, respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) and of course coronaviruses (COVID-19). Vaccines for all three of these viruses are available and can largely prevent the disease or mitigate symptoms. Fungal pneumonia is less common and typically affects people with weakened immune systems such as those with HIV or patients on chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signs and symptoms of pneumonia can appear similar to the common flu, but usually last longer, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/pneumonia/symptoms-causes/syc-20354204" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/pneumonia/symptoms-causes/syc-20354204" aria-label="Mayo Clinic"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/pneumonia/symptoms-causes/syc-20354204"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The most common symptoms for pneumonia include fever, cough, difficulty breathing, shortness of breath, chest pain and fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="subhead-embed"&gt;Conditions Associated With Pneumonia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several health conditions can increase the risk of developing pneumonia or worsen its severity. Some of these underlying medical conditions include asthma, diabetes, heart failure, chronic kidney disease and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease. Those individuals with weakened immune systems are also at risk because they are less able to fight infections effectively. These would include patients that have cancer, HIV or are on long-term steroid use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="subhead-embed"&gt;Why Pneumonia Can Be Devastating For Seniors&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older adults account for the majority of pneumonia-related deaths each year in the U.S., particularly those aged 75 and above, according to the &lt;a href="https://blogs.cdc.gov/nchs/2020/03/11/4831/#:~:text=Over%20the%20past%2020%20years,Vital%20Statistics%20System%2C%20CDC%20WONDER." target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://blogs.cdc.gov/nchs/2020/03/11/4831/#:~:text=Over%20the%20past%2020%20years,Vital%20Statistics%20System%2C%20CDC%20WONDER." aria-label="CDC"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://blogs.cdc.gov/nchs/2020/03/11/4831/#:~:text=Over%20the%20past%2020%20years,Vital%20Statistics%20System%2C%20CDC%20WONDER."&gt;CDC&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. In seniors, physical changes associated with aging such as decreased lung elasticity and a weaker cough reflex can make it more challenging to clear bacteria and different organisms from the lungs. In addition, the elderly are more likely to have underlying health conditions that can complicate a successful recovery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article_paragraph_7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An important complication known as sepsis, which is life-threatening, is also more common among the elderly. This is when the infection spreads to the bloodstream and can affect different organs in the body. In this scenario, the body’s immune system overreacts to the infection, causing damage and inflammation to multiple organs. This can ultimately lead to respiratory failure and death if left untreated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MWrh7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="subhead-embed"&gt;Preventing Pneumonia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the various causes of pneumonia can be prevented from vaccines. The most common viral pneumonias such as flu, RSV, and COVID-19 can largely be prevented through vaccination. The pneumococcal vaccine, which protects against the most common bacterial cause of pneumonia, is now recommended for children younger than the age of 5 and adults 50 years of age and older, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pneumococcal/hcp/vaccine-recommendations/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener noreferrer" data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/pneumococcal/hcp/vaccine-recommendations/index.html" aria-label="CDC"&gt;&lt;u data-ga-track="ExternalLink:https://www.cdc.gov/pneumococcal/hcp/vaccine-recommendations/index.html"&gt;CDC&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Vaccines remain the best protection against severe illness, hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition, regular handwashing, covering coughs and sneezes and avoiding close contact with sick individuals can reduce transmission of respiratory illnesses. Finally, strengthening the immune system through regular exercise, sleep and avoiding smoking can add an extra layer of protection against acquiring debilitating infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pneumonia, as exemplified through the death of beloved actress Diane Keaton, remains a serious concern for public health. Although pneumonia can affect anyone at any age, early recognition and preventive strategies can help mitigate poor outcomes from an infection that affects millions of Americans every year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Forbes</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 16:50:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7gFBVV95cUxQUGp2eGN1ak1QQmpIOTR5M1Bib0REM0otQkNBUzI0S2ZlVHAwWmR2YUlaY3Frc3NuTFlpTUhVZHFXWWV5cWdPRnVZYVNzb0lvVGVwSWF2WnZLcENkSU8ydGRmdHVOUzE1cUswMldtWS1fT2Q4enZReVZJdVNjOUtldlkwU19BOF9EWC1udUd3UEgyaFBNVWR3bWNXd1M1Rzd6RHplRUkxWllzMkk2dmJXa2FDVG1VLThQcXNxc2RlV0JROVlCQUYxVm9STWVJVEwtOFlqRWloMURFZXRCQ054Ny04RExaUTBXOG13MVVB</guid></item></channel></rss>