<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>The Longevity Business Is Booming—and Its Scientists Are Clashing - The Wall Street Journal</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxQOWEyMkJyTWJ0TkdsX1hUY1ZFMzl1Q3V2V3BRdlJIOThqMFdNNDkzRFNJZ012ZXZWUDZBeC11akF2RzZDQl8yRHJ5amlJLU84Zl84bHZ0UFQzbFNUa2N6bHRPZFhnZElQVGkxWnFWU3lCRTJTcWJZSmRMWXFmWnZmNkFKREdPdXFCamFSbm1IV1F3LWVM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 01:31:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQOWEyMkJyTWJ0TkdsX1hUY1ZFMzl1Q3V2V3BRdlJIOThqMFdNNDkzRFNJZ012ZXZWUDZBeC11akF2RzZDQl8yRHJ5amlJLU84Zl84bHZ0UFQzbFNUa2N6bHRPZFhnZElQVGkxWnFWU3lCRTJTcWJZSmRMWXFmWnZmNkFKREdPdXFCamFSbm1IV1F3LWVM</guid></item><item><title>Cruel new twist in colon cancer epidemic in young people - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwgFBVV95cUxNNW0zZ3FzN1h3OTg4ekpTRXlMZGctdHhReWRsZUozQ0RwUm04djRVelh4c05tOHlMcDctV1I5NXl1NmxqZ2lJMnVPTUZUc3Q5d2xtVE4xcEZpdHQtZ0lYbUhxSVlrYXRLR01XQ2szZnNNWHh0RXFnb1VkTlNWa3NGR0hoYmJQV3Q5VGIzdm55NnkxSExBamxrVEhRLWF4Y3RfVXVBeVlCWDN6Zi1hX2h3TGYzNDBGS04xT0hzamlLVktqZ9IBxwFBVV95cUxQQWt6dUh1cjZJb25OanEwSVhVRmRidW82b0FVRGU2eUM0LVJ5OHQ4RzVKcUpxazhwYWdHR08wRmF1S0t1TldrdmVORW5DZXM1dzZRWG9YSm1lU3QtUVNieUJPeWZOYWFIQXBXQV85STI0NEtZYlpoMzdfRWdTeTBlQVBJUUFmck9xZzBxal9aR2ZGZzV1Q3g2anJVU2lqTHdNVGt2TS1MYU5nZlI1NjRLMkFwNHNvWkxTN3lKdEpUUkxfNWVXa0U0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Young people with colon &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-32cfad30-05a1-11f0-83a7-eff5085fe898"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; are 'significantly' more likely to die from heart problems than the general population, experts warn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers found people with colorectal cancer were 16 percent more likely to die from cardiovascular disease (CVD) - a group of heart conditions like heart attack and high blood pressure - than those without colon cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In patients diagnosed with colon cancer within the last two years, their risk more than doubled.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the link was most devastating in young patients, who are &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14210777/doctor-colon-cancer-crisis-common-ingredients-responsible.html"&gt;increasingly being ravaged by colon cancer&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Colon cancer patients under the age of 50 were nearly 2.5 times more likely to die from cardiovascular disease than their peers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the researchers do not know why there is a link between colon cancer and mortality from CVD, they suggested aggressive cancer treatments like chemotherapy and radiation could damage the heart, leading to an increased risk of conditions like heart attack. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Younger people are also more likely to need more intense cancer treatments, as they are at a &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14215241/doctors-reveal-tragic-young-people-colon-cancer.html"&gt;higher risk of being diagnosed at later stages&lt;/a&gt; due to a lack of screening and attributing symptoms to more benign causes.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Based on their findings, researchers called for increased research and surveillance on cardiovascular outcomes in young patients with colon cancer, especially within the first two years after diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Rates of colorectal cancer in Americans under 50 have risen over the past two decades. This graph shows the latest year for which data is available&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Data shows that heart attack cases are on the rise in young people&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Ahsan Ayaz, study author and an internal medicine resident at Montefiore St Luke's Cornwall Hospital in New York, said: 'Based on our findings, the two-year period after a colorectal cancer diagnosis is a critical period when patients need aggressive care to improve cardiovascular outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For example, there should be an aggressive approach to control cardiovascular risk factors and comorbidities like &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-32d09790-05a1-11f0-83a7-eff5085fe898"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; and hypertension. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There is also a need for coordination between oncology teams and primary care teams, because most of those risk factors are managed by primary care providers.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Colorectal cancer is the fourth most common cancer in the US and the second-leading cause of cancer deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The American Cancer Society estimates 154,270 Americans will be diagnosed with colon cancer this year, and 52,900 will die. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the UK, 44,063 cases are diagnosed per year, and the nation experiences 16,808 deaths every year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And since the 1990s, early-onset colon cancer has increased by 50 percent, and rates are expected to double between 2010 and 2030. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The new study, which will be presented later this month at the American College of Cardiology's Annual Scientific Session, looked at data from 630,000 patients in the National Cancer Institute's Surveillance, Epidemiology, and End Results (SEER) database. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;While some warning signs are easy to spot — such as severe chest pain — others are more vague and hard to pinpoint&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;All patients were diagnosed with colorectal cancer between 2000 and 2021. The patients' exact ages are unknown. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cardiovascular mortality was defined as deaths from heart disease, high blood pressure, stroke, tears or aneurysms in the aorta, or atherosclerosis - a buildup of plaque in the arteries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers found colorectal cancer patients overall had a 16 percent increased risk of dying from cardiovascular causes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's unclear what demographic they used as a control group. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Their likelihood of dying from these conditions was highest in the first two years after their colorectal cancer diagnosis, increasing to 45 percent during this period. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Colon cancer patients under age 50 were 2.4 times more likely to die of cardiovascular issues than people in the same age group who did not have cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, researchers concluded that Black colorectal cancer patients had a 74 percent increased chance of dying from cardiovascular issues, and white men were at a 55 percent increased risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Ayaz suggested the racial disparities could be due to socioeconomic issues, location, and access to care, but added that more research on this is needed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers said the increased risk among colon cancer patients could stem from heart damage linked to cancer treatments like chemotherapy and radiation, called cardiotoxicity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Bailey Hutchins of Tennessee, pictured at left, died of colon cancer earlier this year at age 26. Monica Ackermann of Australia, pictured at right, was just 31 when she was diagnosed with colon cancer &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These treatments may lead to inflammation, scarring, and other forms of heart damage that makes it more difficult for the heart to function properly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Colon cancer also results in widespread inflammation that can spread to the heart, making it more prone to damage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, the risk of cardiovascular death may be greater in younger people because they need more aggressive treatment, which could increase their chance of cardiotoxicity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A separate study published earlier this year looking at 25,000 adults with colorectal cancer in Denmark found patients under 50 were &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14215241/doctors-reveal-tragic-young-people-colon-cancer.html"&gt;more likely to be diagnosed at later stages&lt;/a&gt;, meaning their cancer was more prone to spreading. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Later-stage cancer often requires more aggressive combinations of surgery, chemo, radiation, and immunotherapy, all of which can contribute to cardiotoxicity.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Ayaz said: 'For therapies that are newer, there is not a lot of data on the side effects and toxicities, but evidence is emerging that they cause cardiovascular toxicity.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team is planning to conduct additional research on cardiovascular mortality in colon cancer patients receiving different types of treatment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 01:26:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxNNW0zZ3FzN1h3OTg4ekpTRXlMZGctdHhReWRsZUozQ0RwUm04djRVelh4c05tOHlMcDctV1I5NXl1NmxqZ2lJMnVPTUZUc3Q5d2xtVE4xcEZpdHQtZ0lYbUhxSVlrYXRLR01XQ2szZnNNWHh0RXFnb1VkTlNWa3NGR0hoYmJQV3Q5VGIzdm55NnkxSExBamxrVEhRLWF4Y3RfVXVBeVlCWDN6Zi1hX2h3TGYzNDBGS04xT0hzamlLVktqZ9IBxwFBVV95cUxQQWt6dUh1cjZJb25OanEwSVhVRmRidW82b0FVRGU2eUM0LVJ5OHQ4RzVKcUpxazhwYWdHR08wRmF1S0t1TldrdmVORW5DZXM1dzZRWG9YSm1lU3QtUVNieUJPeWZOYWFIQXBXQV85STI0NEtZYlpoMzdfRWdTeTBlQVBJUUFmck9xZzBxal9aR2ZGZzV1Q3g2anJVU2lqTHdNVGt2TS1MYU5nZlI1NjRLMkFwNHNvWkxTN3lKdEpUUkxfNWVXa0U0</guid></item><item><title>Scientists Find Strong Link Between Drinking Sugary Soda and Getting Cancer - Futurism</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiY0FVX3lxTE5scllyM2xOcnl0Tlg0dF9wTXdHUzIwUUIxZEtEN0ppbmJVSzZKR2ptcEgtMG50RXBkTThPQUI5NGV1cHRtSVE4TDd3MmFqaF9MVjlFRl9CWi1pNElMcHVMSF9Taw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section id="incArticle" class="post-content z-50 w-full p-3 space-y-4 bg-white border lg:-mt-6 md:p-4 md:border-gray-900 lg:ml-3 lg:w-2/3 font-b text-3"&gt;&lt;div class="space-y-4 lg:space-y-0"&gt;&lt;p class="block text-xs text-gray-500 uppercase lg:hidden font-c"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image by Getty / Futurism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a new study, scientists have found an alarming link between sugary soda and oral cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.upi.com/Health_News/2025/03/13/Study-links-high-consumption-sugary-drinks-increased-risk-oral-cancer/4691741798165/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;&lt;em&gt;United Press International&lt;/em&gt; reports&lt;/a&gt;, new research out of the University of Washington found that women who drink at least one full-sugar soft drink per day appear to be about five times more likely to get oral cavity cancer (OCC) than their counterparts who avoid such beverages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Typically thought of as a cancer primarily affecting older men who smoke and drink, instances of OCC have, as &lt;em&gt;UPI &lt;/em&gt;notes, been &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35503657/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;rising steadily among women&lt;/a&gt; — including those who don't smoke or drink, or do so sparingly. The five-year survival rate for OCC, which &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28865100/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;causes painful sores&lt;/a&gt; on either the lips or the gums and can spread down the throat if left untreated, is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9437560/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;only 64.3 percent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a new paper published in the journal &lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/10.1001/jamaoto.2024.5252?utm_campaign=articlePDF%26utm_medium=articlePDFlink%26utm_source=articlePDF%26utm_content=jamaoto.2024.5252" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;JAMA Otolaryngology-Head &amp;amp; Neck Surgery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;, the University of Washington researchers looked at long-term healthcare data for more than 162,000 healthcare workers from the &lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/long-running-nurses-health-study-at-risk-of-shutting-down/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;Nurses' Health Study&lt;/a&gt; and identified 124 cases of OCC among them. Crunching the numbers, the researchers found that people who drink at least one sugary soda beverage per day were at a 4.87 times greater risk of developing OCC than their counterparts who had less than one such drink per month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who don't smoke or drink — or do so lightly — the numbers were even more stark: those who consumed one or more sugary soda per day were 5.46 more likely to develop OCC than people who drink less than one per month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper only establishes correlation, not causation, but the results are pretty striking. Brittany Barber, an assistant professor of otolaryngology head and neck surgery who led the research with her colleagues at UW, told &lt;em&gt;UPI&lt;/em&gt; that rising rates of this type of cancer among women are "alarming."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, sugary soft drinks have not been studied as one of the culprits behind that rate rise among nonsmokers — especially after rates of OCC related to smoking have seen a steady decline thanks to &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK343649/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;successful anti-smoking campaigns&lt;/a&gt; and legislature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2020, the report notes, there were 355,000 new cases of OCC and 177,000 deaths globally. Despite being far "less common than breast or colon cancer," as Barber notes, that's still a pretty grim ratio of deaths to diagnoses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than implying that the sugar from sodas themselves is causing people to get OCC, the researchers hypothesize that "diets with higher added sugar may contribute to chronic inflammation." Previous studies have connected &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41405-024-00265-w" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;excessive consumption of sugary drinks&lt;/a&gt; with gum disease — which, in turn, has been &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/news/newsroom/news-releases/2018/01/more-evidence-of-link-between-severe-gum-disease-and-cancer-risk" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;linked to oral cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will obviously need to be more research to pin down this apparent connection — but in the meantime, cutting out full-sugar sodas, or soft drinks completely, may be your best bet for avoiding mouth cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on oral health:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/rfk-fluoride-water-tooth-rot" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;&lt;em&gt;When They Took Fluoride Out of the Water Like RFK Jr. Wants to Do Everywhere, People's Teeth Started Rotting Out of Their Heads&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:41:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiY0FVX3lxTE5scllyM2xOcnl0Tlg0dF9wTXdHUzIwUUIxZEtEN0ppbmJVSzZKR2ptcEgtMG50RXBkTThPQUI5NGV1cHRtSVE4TDd3MmFqaF9MVjlFRl9CWi1pNElMcHVMSF9Taw</guid></item><item><title>Kennedy Instructs Anti-Vaccine Group to Remove Fake C.D.C. Page - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiAFBVV95cUxORWszaFhvTFpKRWQxZm5JWGp4N3NVdUxLaDNHeERJaDd4a243NFhzY3U0cU9qRE9xUTlYWDdPd0ZFYW42andpZTdkRGdNWlNkR0V4WHNrQUtZLXhqNkhBWFVDRFJ2NEpRdTgwUVJTeTI5THFGZE9zZ19WcHJ4X1ZmRW84cG93bnd4?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr., the nation’s health secretary, on Saturday instructed leaders of the nonprofit he founded to take down a web page that mimicked the design of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s site but laid out a case that vaccines cause autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The page had been published on a site apparently registered to the nonprofit, the anti-vaccine group Children’s Health Defense. Mr. Kennedy’s action came after The New York Times inquired about the page and after news of it ricocheted across social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The page was taken offline Saturday evening. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“Secretary Kennedy has instructed the Office of the General Counsel to send a formal demand to Children’s Health Defense requesting the removal of their website,” the Health and Human Services Department said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“At H.H.S. we are dedicated to restoring our agencies to their tradition of upholding gold-standard, evidence-based science,” the statement said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;It was not clear why the anti-vaccine group might have published a page mimicking the C.D.C.’s. The organization did not respond to requests for comment, and Mr. Kennedy has said he severed ties with it when he began his presidential campaign in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The fake vaccine safety page was practically indistinguishable from the one available on the C.D.C.’s own site. The layout, typefaces and logos were the same, perhaps in violation of federal copyright law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-1336jj"&gt;&lt;div class="css-121kum4"&gt;&lt;p class="css-171quhb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-asuuk5"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-7axq9l" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-1b5b8u1"&gt;&lt;path fill="currentColor" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M2.5 12a9.5 9.5 0 1 1 19 0 9.5 9.5 0 0 1-19 0Zm8.5 1.75v-7.5h2v7.5h-2Zm0 2v2h2v-2h-2Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;We are having trouble retrieving the article content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Please enable JavaScript in your browser settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dv1kvn" id="optimistic-truncator-a11y" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access. If you are in Reader mode please exit and &lt;a href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-kennedy-vaccine-disinformation.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;log into&lt;/a&gt; your Times account, or &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-kennedy-vaccine-disinformation.html"&gt;subscribe&lt;/a&gt; for all of The Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-1g71tqy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-63woee" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-spinner"&gt;&lt;g fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.28 22.8a.72.72 0 1 0 1.44 0v-6.72a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72Z" opacity=".37"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M17.766 21.16a.72.72 0 1 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.436a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.437Z" opacity=".26"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.506 14.653a.72.72 0 0 0 .445 1.37l6.391-2.078a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.369l-6.39 2.077Z" opacity=".61"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M5.07 20.314a.72.72 0 0 0 1.164.847l3.95-5.437a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165-.846l-3.95 5.436Z" opacity=".48"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.049 16.022a.72.72 0 0 0 .445-1.37l-6.391-2.076a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.39 2.076Z" opacity=".17"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.494 9.347a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.37l-6.391 2.078a.72.72 0 1 0 .445 1.369l6.39-2.077Z" opacity=".09"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M6.234 2.84a.72.72 0 0 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.436a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.437Z" opacity=".87"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.951 7.978a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.391 2.076a.72.72 0 1 0 .445-1.37l-6.39-2.076Z" opacity=".74"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M18.93 3.686a.72.72 0 0 0-1.164-.847l-3.95 5.437a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165.846l3.95-5.436Z" opacity=".02"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M12.72 1.2a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72a.72.72 0 0 0 1.44 0V1.2Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Already a subscriber? &lt;a data-testid="log-in-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-kennedy-vaccine-disinformation.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Want all of The Times? &lt;a data-testid="subscribe-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F03%2F22%2Fhealth%2Fcdc-kennedy-vaccine-disinformation.html"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Mar 2025 00:05:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxORWszaFhvTFpKRWQxZm5JWGp4N3NVdUxLaDNHeERJaDd4a243NFhzY3U0cU9qRE9xUTlYWDdPd0ZFYW42andpZTdkRGdNWlNkR0V4WHNrQUtZLXhqNkhBWFVDRFJ2NEpRdTgwUVJTeTI5THFGZE9zZ19WcHJ4X1ZmRW84cG93bnd4</guid></item><item><title>The Bird Flu Virus Is Mutating Fast – And Scientists Say Our Vaccines May Not Be Enough - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxPeWpQZjFzdnV2TFVTWGlVanBHTkdSQWpGT3RoZDNlT3M2ZTJKbW1kU0c1eDdIem5DVlhBWGdrRVFKQzdfamFqRlZycGN1NXF4MUNjSWZBQVBuM0NHV0NPMjEyWVZVOXVLN2s0M1FnMFdPRFFGR282aUs1dFl4ek56R0pYeElpSEVleEF3eWVUdzA4RHVhdXA4Y1k4eVZXMkVhT2hNeWNDUHV6WXB6WUlwRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 23:06:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxPeWpQZjFzdnV2TFVTWGlVanBHTkdSQWpGT3RoZDNlT3M2ZTJKbW1kU0c1eDdIem5DVlhBWGdrRVFKQzdfamFqRlZycGN1NXF4MUNjSWZBQVBuM0NHV0NPMjEyWVZVOXVLN2s0M1FnMFdPRFFGR282aUs1dFl4ek56R0pYeElpSEVleEF3eWVUdzA4RHVhdXA4Y1k4eVZXMkVhT2hNeWNDUHV6WXB6WUlwRQ</guid></item><item><title>Type 2 diabetes increases risk of liver and pancreatic cancers, study shows - The Guardian</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivwFBVV95cUxNbExfcVVkMW5SNXE2YXZqeWFPdnUwdUdHUWJFeEJrVXhJX2E1eTNrTWtUWFJydWE0QnBDN01iekRmU1JFTk45XzFyT0FqTHY0YkJRM0FvVXR2VjlTb3VHOVVOM25OUGZDbjdMSmFSVHhjOEdIYzJqaktQeFlVYlhLMWkxUE80d3M1N0tFM2dBaGxBcVlzUkxBT2FmN2treVNTemhlZEdHX0J2ZDRHRFV2Y2YzVC1QQ3lCenh5VjRyNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector  dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;People who develop type 2 diabetes face an increased risk of some of the most lethal cancers, including liver and pancreatic tumours, with the greatest rises in women, research suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;The analysis of health records from 95,000 people found that the risk of pancreatic cancer was nearly twice as high, and the chance of developing liver cancer almost five times as high, in women recently diagnosed with type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"society","tags":[{"id":"society/health","type":"Keyword","title":"Health"},{"id":"society/cancer","type":"Keyword","title":"Cancer"},{"id":"society/diabetes","type":"Keyword","title":"Diabetes"},{"id":"society/obesity","type":"Keyword","title":"Obesity"},{"id":"society/society","type":"Keyword","title":"Society"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"profile/iansample","type":"Contributor","title":"Ian Sample","twitterHandle":"iansample","bylineImageUrl":"https://i.guim.co.uk/img/uploads/2024/11/15/Ian_Sample.jpg?width=300&amp;amp;quality=85&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=max&amp;amp;s=8e4848b5cd47215a09f2a5d1f2d4dd9d","bylineLargeImageUrl":"https://i.guim.co.uk/img/uploads/2024/11/15/Ian_Sample,_L.png?width=300&amp;amp;quality=85&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;fit=max&amp;amp;s=9455f2ae800441cdaea2f1e216d52ea5"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/uk-home-news","type":"Tracking","title":"UK Home News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"society/2025/mar/22/type-2-diabetes-increases-risk-of-liver-and-pancreatic-cancers-study-shows","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","switches":{"lightbox":true,"personaliseSignInGateAfterCheckout":true,"abSignInGateMainVariant":true,"prebidAppnexusUkRow":true,"prebidMagnite":true,"commercialMetrics":true,"prebidTrustx":true,"scAdFreeBanner":false,"adaptiveSite":true,"prebidPermutiveAudience":true,"compareVariantDecision":false,"enableSentryReporting":true,"lazyLoadContainers":true,"ampArticleSwitch":false,"remarketing":true,"articleEndSlot":true,"keyEventsCarousel":true,"registerWithPhone":false,"darkModeWeb":true,"targeting":true,"remoteHeader":true,"slotBodyEnd":true,"ampPrebidOzone":false,"extendedMostPopularFronts":true,"emailInlineInFooter":true,"showNewPrivacyWordingOnEmailSignupEmbeds":true,"prebidAnalytics":true,"extendedMostPopular":true,"ampContentAbTesting":false,"prebidCriteo":true,"okta":true,"imrWorldwide":true,"acast":true,"twitterUwt":true,"abAuxiaSignInGate":true,"abDeferPermutiveLoad":true,"prebidAppnexusInvcode":true,"ampPrebidPubmatic":false,"a9HeaderBidding":true,"prebidAppnexus":true,"enableDiscussionSwitch":true,"prebidXaxis":true,"stickyVideos":true,"interactiveFullHeaderSwitch":true,"discussionAllPageSize":true,"prebidUserSync":true,"audioOnwardJourneySwitch":true,"brazeTaylorReport":false,"externalVideoEmbeds":true,"abTheTradeDesk":true,"callouts":true,"sentinelLogger":true,"geoMostPopular":true,"weAreHiring":false,"relatedContent":true,"thirdPartyEmbedTracking":true,"prebidOzone":true,"ampLiveblogSwitch":false,"ampAmazon":false,"prebidAdYouLike":true,"mostViewedFronts":true,"optOutAdvertising":true,"abSignInGateMainControl":true,"googleSearch":true,"brazeSwitch":true,"prebidKargo":true,"consentManagement":true,"idProfileNavigation":true,"confiantAdVerification":true,"discussionAllowAnonymousRecommendsSwitch":false,"absoluteServerTimes":false,"permutive":true,"comscore":true,"ampPrebidCriteo":false,"prebidTheTradeDesk":true,"newsletterOnwards":false,"youtubeIma":true,"webFonts":true,"liveBlogTopSponsorship":true,"ophan":true,"crosswordSvgThumbnails":true,"prebidTriplelift":true,"prebidPubmatic":true,"serverShareCounts":false,"autoRefresh":true,"enhanceTweets":true,"prebidIndexExchange":true,"prebidOpenx":true,"abPrebidBidCache":true,"prebidHeaderBidding":true,"idCookieRefresh":true,"discussionPageSize":true,"smartAppBanner":false,"historyTags":true,"brazeContentCards":true,"remoteBanner":true,"emailSignupRecaptcha":true,"prebidSmart":true,"shouldLoadGoogletag":true,"inizio":true,"europeBetaFront":true,"prebidBidCache":true},"contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;The chances of developing the cancers rose in men too, with new-onset type 2 diabetes linked to a 74% increase in pancreatic cancer and a near quadrupling in the risk of liver cancer in the five years afterwards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;A smaller effect was seen for bowel cancer, with the risk of the disease 34% higher in women and 27% higher in men with new-onset type 2 diabetes compared with people without a recent diabetes diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“Diabetes and obesity are associated with similar cancer types,” said Owen Tipping, a medical student who worked on the study with Andrew Renehan, professor of cancer studies and surgery at the University of Manchester. “Our research was detecting the effect of diabetes on cancer, after adjusting for obesity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Previous studies have linked &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2017/oct/03/cancer-obesity-weight-us-study" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;obesity with 13 types of cancer&lt;/a&gt;, many of which are also more common in people with type 2 diabetes. But researchers have struggled to work out whether diabetes itself raises the risk of some or all of the cancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;For the latest study, the Manchester group turned to the UK Biobank which holds medical and lifestyle data on half a million people. They examined the records of 23,750 people with newly diagnosed type 2 diabetes and compared them with more than 70,000 matched controls without diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;There tends to be a surge in cancer diagnoses shortly after people are found to have diabetes, simply because patients have more medical tests. The researchers accounted for this spike in cancer due to better detection by ignoring cases reported within a year of a diabetes diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;According to the study, after five years the risk of any obesity-related cancer was 48% higher for men recently diagnosed with type 2 diabetes than for those without the condition. For women, the risk was 24% higher in those with a recent diabetes diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Not all obesity-related cancers rose with diabetes, however. Women with diabetes were no more likely to develop endometrial cancer or post-menopausal breast cancer than those without, according to the study which will be presented at the European Congress on &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/obesity" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Obesity&lt;/a&gt; in Málaga, Spain, in May.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Across the population, the lifetime risks for liver and pancreatic cancer are higher for men than women. In the UK, one in 76 men and one in 130 women will develop liver cancer, while one in 55 men and one in 59 women will get pancreatic cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Tipping said it was too early to know whether people with diabetes would benefit from cancer screening, but added: “We know with pancreatic cancer that it’s important to detect it early.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;It is unclear how diabetes might drive cancer, but scientists suspect high levels of insulin, high blood glucose and chronic inflammation. The sex differences may be driven by hormone levels, how sensitive the body is to the effects of insulin or variations in body fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;Sophia Lowes at &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/cancer" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Cancer&lt;/a&gt; Research UK said: “This study helps increase our understanding of the link between diabetes and cancer. While many questions remain about how and why diabetes might cause cancer, research like this is vital in helping us better prevent, detect and diagnose the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-s3ycb2"&gt;“Overweight and obesity cause at least 13 different types of cancer. The world around us doesn’t always make it easy, but keeping a healthy weight and eating a healthy, balanced diet is one way to reduce the risk of cancer. There are other steps people can take too, such as not smoking and cutting down on alcohol.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 23:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxNbExfcVVkMW5SNXE2YXZqeWFPdnUwdUdHUWJFeEJrVXhJX2E1eTNrTWtUWFJydWE0QnBDN01iekRmU1JFTk45XzFyT0FqTHY0YkJRM0FvVXR2VjlTb3VHOVVOM25OUGZDbjdMSmFSVHhjOEdIYzJqaktQeFlVYlhLMWkxUE80d3M1N0tFM2dBaGxBcVlzUkxBT2FmN2treVNTemhlZEdHX0J2ZDRHRFV2Y2YzVC1QQ3lCenh5VjRyNA</guid></item><item><title>Prostate cancer risk increases by 45% among men who share one troubling behavior - AOL</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMid0FVX3lxTE8tTFFmYzIwMlBTVjJscmFnT0sxLWVOYm16ZEpBd1dPZlNUMjl5VmJqc1l2N0tJdmlKT1Q5VUdCQjVzVFlKOENoSEpyd3N2YTlxVmNreS1NM216QlB6cmgxeHQ3bE1KblBaRzJLUUNPZ3ZYREJUSEdj?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers are warning that men who regularly dodge prostate cancer screening appointments are 45% more likely to die from the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/cancer/prostate-cancer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Prostate cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Prostate cancer&lt;/a&gt; is the most common cancer among men and the second-leading cause of cancer deaths, according to UC San Francisco (UCSF).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if screening programs are introduced on a national scale — particularly those that measure levels of prostate-specific antigen (PSA) in the blood — they could give men earlier access to treatment, experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/prostate-cancer-cases-spike-us-state-doctors-share-likely-reason" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Prostate Cancer Cases Spike In This Us State As Doctors Share Likely Reason;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prostate Cancer Cases Spike In This Us State As Doctors Share Likely Reason&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They would thus have a better chance of being cured, according to reporting by news agency SWNS and others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screening can also prevent &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/health-care" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:costly treatments;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;costly treatments&lt;/a&gt; associated with advanced prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;A new study examined the link between the consistent decline of men's screenings and the risk of dying from prostate cancer. It reveals a "stark contrast" that emphasizes the potential consequences of screening avoidance.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's according to data from the European Randomised Study of Screening for Prostate Cancer (ERSPC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study collects information from seven European nations — Finland, the Netherlands, Italy, Sweden, Switzerland, Belgium and Spain. It is said to be the world’s largest prostate cancer screening study, said SWNS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/common-cancer-type-could-detected-new-blood-test" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Common Cancer Type Could Be Detected With New Blood Test;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Common Cancer Type Could Be Detected With New Blood Test&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-term data from this entity consistently shows that PSA screening programs can lead to a 20% reduced risk of dying from prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, an analysis of 20-year follow-up data from the ERSPC is the first to look at the link between the consistent decline of &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research/medical-tech" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:screening invitations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;screening invitations&lt;/a&gt; and men's risk of dying from this type of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It reveals a "stark contrast" that emphasizes the potential consequences of screening avoidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers from Erasmus MC Cancer Institute at the University Medical Centre in the Netherlands led the analysis, said SWNS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the 72,460 men invited to partake in the screenings, around one in six were non-attenders and skipped every single appointment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That group had a 45% higher risk of dying from &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/cancer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:prostate cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;prostate cancer&lt;/a&gt; compared with those who attended screening appointments, according to the findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Choosing not to participate in screening is a choice that may be driven by a complex collection of factors, said one expert.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;When comparing outcomes with the control group – men who were never invited to have screenings – those who attended the screening appointments had a 23% lower risk of dying from prostate cancer, while non-attenders faced a 39% higher risk, SWNS reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead study author Renée Leenen, M.D., Ph.D., said the choice not to participate in screening may be driven by a complex collection of factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Said Leenen, who is with the Erasmus CM Cancer Institute in the Netherlands, "It may be that men who opted not to attend a screening appointment are care avoiders — meaning they’re less likely to engage in &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/healthy-living" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:healthy behaviors;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;healthy behaviors&lt;/a&gt; and preventative care in general."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She added, "This is the opposite behavior of people who are perhaps more health-conscious and are more likely to attend a screening appointment … Our study identifies that men who were invited for screening, but do not attend screening appointments, are at a significantly higher risk of dying from prostate cancer compared to men who were not offered screening or accepted an invitation for screening."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Long-term data from this entity consistently shows that PSA screening programs can lead to a 20% reduced risk of dying from prostate cancer.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Leenen said that experts "need to better understand who these men are, why they choose not to attend appointments and how to motivate them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doing so, she added, "will help us design population-based prostate cancer screening programs that encourage higher rates of informed participation … Tackling attendance rates in this way could be a big factor in the long-term success of a national prostate screening program," SWNS reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:For more Health articles, visit ;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;For more Health articles, visit &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:www.foxnews.com/health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;www.foxnews.com/health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urologist Tobias Nordström, M.D., Ph.D., of the Karolinska Institute in Sweden, said, "We need to better understand why these men might actively choose not to participate in screening, despite being invited to attend, and how this behavior is linked to worse outcomes when they get a diagnosis."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings from the study are scheduled to be presented this weekend at the European Association of Urology (EAU) Congress in Madrid, Spain, said SWNS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fox News' senior medical analyst &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/person/s/marc-siegel" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Marc Siegel;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Marc Siegel&lt;/a&gt;, who was not involved in the new study on prostate cancer risks, previously called out the need for regular medical screenings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Siegel has emphasized the need to "diagnose it early for better outcomes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Angelica Stabile of Fox News Digital contributed reporting. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/prostate-cancer-risk-increases-45-among-men-share-behavior" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Prostate cancer risk increases by 45% among men who share one troubling behavior;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Prostate cancer risk increases by 45% among men who share one troubling behavior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 22:21:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE8tTFFmYzIwMlBTVjJscmFnT0sxLWVOYm16ZEpBd1dPZlNUMjl5VmJqc1l2N0tJdmlKT1Q5VUdCQjVzVFlKOENoSEpyd3N2YTlxVmNreS1NM216QlB6cmgxeHQ3bE1KblBaRzJLUUNPZ3ZYREJUSEdj</guid></item><item><title>Top plastic surgeon reveals types of people who should NEVER get plastic surgery - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxQVHkydkpVZGlCclRYV2xFV1dNZWFoRDNPOUpQOGpJaXRrb2dlSkxKN2FVLWhlaWtfS3V1N0RzVlJrX0Etekd5dTViV0dnaVE1bU9oRzR6X0d2ZmdUUEhuN0p6YVpTRm5RODNudWc3Q0VoalpnVVZmY3ZFX0tYeDRqZmxIZXpHb2ltcHlzN1hoLTNIdkw5OW5Za3ZMNUs0UdIBowFBVV95cUxPMXNoVDBKems4OExiVGhqaFN5djRBWmxCV1NOQlU4RWtJQXhDeGZvbExxZXU1S3JPc1JxVy1wX2pxbHZaMVM4X2dPNmxoUWNFemdzeWRCUmZzWmh0cG4wVTYwZ2Y5UEpfLVppSklmU1NBMHMtZVRYRFVhdC1yNVZFX2pBWGdnYkZHYXRua2MyZkpLakVoamQyVmpxS0RfM1hvZ3Q4?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hundreds of thousands of people a year go under the knife for plastic surgery - whether it's for bigger boobs, a smaller nose or even to look like their favorite celebrity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while most people are fine to &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13664679/hair-transplants-veneers-plastic-surgeries-Trump-family-bill.html"&gt;shell out thousands of dollars for the traits they desire&lt;/a&gt;, not everyone is a good candidate for cosmetic procedures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Typically, doctors advise people who are very young, suffer from health conditions such as heart disease and &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-93c0ead0-0666-11f0-97cf-e7043735ec11"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; or people who have had past surgical complications to avoid an elective operation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now, Dr Charles Lee, a board-certified plastic surgeon in Beverly Hills, has revealed why certain people shouldn't get plastic surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Below, DailyMail.com details the people Dr Lee says should avoid cosmetic procedures and why. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;People with body dysmorphia &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Nearly two percent of Americans have been diagnosed with body dysmorphic disorder as of 2024&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Body dysmorphic disorder is a mental health condition that causes you to excessively and obsessively criticize perceived defects or flaws in your appearance that are usually minor or non-existent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The person's fixation is far beyond the typical dissatisfaction people may have - like wanting to lose 5lbs - and can cause a person to constantly feel embarrassed, ashamed and anxious to the point they avoid social situations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Charles Lee, a board certified plastic surgeon explained why certain people should not get plastic surgery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nearly two percent of Americans have been diagnosed with BDD as of 2024, according to National Alliance of Eating Disorders. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a result, people suffering from body dysmorphia may seek out plastic surgery as a solution to fix their imperfections, but in one &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@drlee90210/video/7130480675517517098?lang=en"&gt;TikTok video&lt;/a&gt;, Dr Lee advises them not to do so. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The expert explained: 'So someone who looks at a perfectly normal part of their body but they see a big problem, you're not going to get that fixed with surgery that really needs to be taken care of.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead of plastic surgery, doctors suggest seeking out mental health professionals who can help evaluate the situation and suggest appropriate treatment such as therapy and medications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Control freaks and perfectionists&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Lee added that people who are extremely particular in life and cannot bear slight asymmetries should not undergo procedures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Perfectionists and control freaks tend to have a strong drive for flawlessness, which can lead to unrealistic expectations about the outcome of plastic surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, there is always a risk of complications or flaws when it comes to cosmetic procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In cases of a rhinoplasty (nose job) and eyelid surgery, it is normal to expect a bit of unevenness. However this may cause extreme disappointment among perfectionists - causing them to book more appointments and procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Lee added that people who are extremely particular in life and cannot bear slight asymmetries should not undergo procedures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Lee explained: 'Surgery is not that precise, and if you can't accept a few millimeters off here and there, you should not get plastic surgery, especially the more precise procedures, such as rhinoplasty or eyelid surgery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'A fraction of a millimeter can be seen, but a surgeon can't necessarily correct all that, plus we have some asymmetries that cannot be corrected as well.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The specialist also noted plastic surgery requires a 'lot of patience and a lot of ability to accept the unknown'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He added: 'You're going to be swollen for a while. You're going to heal a certain way. Nobody can predict exactly how the outcome is going to be. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We have a general idea, but it's in the 95 percent precision rate and that last five  percent is kind of random and you have to be willing to accept that. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'And you may not know for six months, 12 months, sometimes two years, what the final result is.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;People with delusional expectations  &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Over the last few years, social media has convinced people that plastic surgery can completely 'fix' their problems and make them look perfect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Lee highlighted that people who have a tendency to bleed easily during surgery should avoid an elective operation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Dr Lee says this is unrealistic and people shouldn't expect instant gratification. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's important to understand it is impossible for plastic surgery to completely alter facial and bodily structures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The surgeon revealed: 'I've had a lot of cosmetic surgery myself. I had rhinoplasty, chin implant, whatever. I can't go into surgery expecting to look like Tom Cruise, no matter how much surgery I get.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He also emphasized it is extremely important for patients to be grounded in reality as plastic surgery ideally cannot reverse signs of aging, improve relationships or alter any negative thought patterns about your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Easy bleeders&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Lastly, Dr Lee highlighted that people who have a tendency to bleed easily or excessively should opt out of elective surgeries.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He explained that 'one in 10 people' have a tendency to bleed during surgery and while those with milder conditions, such as vitamin K deficiency, should treat those before seeking treatment, but other 'severe bleeders' need to be careful. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Conditions such as hemophilia - a condition where blood does not clot - and Von Willebrand disease - a genetic bleeding disorder caused by low levels of a clotting protein - may lead to prolonged and difficult-to-control bleeding. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;An accumulation of cigarette smoke in the chest can also cause issues during the healing process&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Frequent cigarette smoking and excessive alcohol consumption can also cause issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol can cause blood to thin and an accumulation of cigarette smoke in the chest can lead to complications during the healing process. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Lee explained: 'The big thing that we worry about related to bleeding during surgery is substance abuse, including cigarettes.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'That's a huge one, because cigarette smoke and other smoke, but cigarette in particular has nicotine and carbon monoxide, tar, things that really clog up the oxygen flow to the healing areas and that can cause necrosis, meaning tissue death, poor scarring and a bad outcome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So you really should not smoke for almost any of these elective procedures. Alcohol, there's another one. Red wine causes bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Other types of alcohol can prolong the swelling phase, and sometimes, if it's swollen for too long of a period, you're not going to get a good result.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 20:12:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQVHkydkpVZGlCclRYV2xFV1dNZWFoRDNPOUpQOGpJaXRrb2dlSkxKN2FVLWhlaWtfS3V1N0RzVlJrX0Etekd5dTViV0dnaVE1bU9oRzR6X0d2ZmdUUEhuN0p6YVpTRm5RODNudWc3Q0VoalpnVVZmY3ZFX0tYeDRqZmxIZXpHb2ltcHlzN1hoLTNIdkw5OW5Za3ZMNUs0UdIBowFBVV95cUxPMXNoVDBKems4OExiVGhqaFN5djRBWmxCV1NOQlU4RWtJQXhDeGZvbExxZXU1S3JPc1JxVy1wX2pxbHZaMVM4X2dPNmxoUWNFemdzeWRCUmZzWmh0cG4wVTYwZ2Y5UEpfLVppSklmU1NBMHMtZVRYRFVhdC1yNVZFX2pBWGdnYkZHYXRua2MyZkpLakVoamQyVmpxS0RfM1hvZ3Q4</guid></item><item><title>Prostate cancer risk increases by 45% among men who share one troubling behavior - Yahoo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAFBVV95cUxPR2RXcGg2aTdVbmg3MjFkNlN5eTRoUzRTSWdTYm9YNE15THFScV9kNVA5VkFySElObGJJZ01mZWowMnNqSWE0VFR4bUNLNS1ObmJNN3JxdjZNanFMMUpHRnp6QUdNS1JlT0QtRGg4RnNURE01ejV0TXpQNmszbzZtaw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers are warning that men who regularly dodge prostate cancer screening appointments are 45% more likely to die from the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/cancer/prostate-cancer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Prostate cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Prostate cancer&lt;/a&gt; is the most common cancer among men and the second-leading cause of cancer deaths, according to UC San Francisco (UCSF).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But if screening programs are introduced on a national scale — particularly those that measure levels of prostate-specific antigen (PSA) in the blood — they could give men earlier access to treatment, experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/prostate-cancer-cases-spike-us-state-doctors-share-likely-reason" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Prostate Cancer Cases Spike In This Us State As Doctors Share Likely Reason;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prostate Cancer Cases Spike In This Us State As Doctors Share Likely Reason&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;They would thus have a better chance of being cured, according to reporting by news agency SWNS and others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Screening can also prevent &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/health-care" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:costly treatments;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;costly treatments&lt;/a&gt; associated with advanced prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study examined the link between the consistent decline of men's screenings and the risk of dying from prostate cancer. It reveals a "stark contrast" that emphasizes the potential consequences of screening avoidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;That's according to data from the European Randomised Study of Screening for Prostate Cancer (ERSPC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study collects information from seven European nations — Finland, the Netherlands, Italy, Sweden, Switzerland, Belgium and Spain. It is said to be the world’s largest prostate cancer screening study, said SWNS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/common-cancer-type-could-detected-new-blood-test" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Common Cancer Type Could Be Detected With New Blood Test;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Common Cancer Type Could Be Detected With New Blood Test&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Long-term data from this entity consistently shows that PSA screening programs can lead to a 20% reduced risk of dying from prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Now, an analysis of 20-year follow-up data from the ERSPC is the first to look at the link between the consistent decline of &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research/medical-tech" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:screening invitations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;screening invitations&lt;/a&gt; and men's risk of dying from this type of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It reveals a "stark contrast" that emphasizes the potential consequences of screening avoidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers from Erasmus MC Cancer Institute at the University Medical Centre in the Netherlands led the analysis, said SWNS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Of the 72,460 men invited to partake in the screenings, around one in six were non-attenders and skipped every single appointment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;That group had a 45% higher risk of dying from &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/cancer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:prostate cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;prostate cancer&lt;/a&gt; compared with those who attended screening appointments, according to the findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Choosing not to participate in screening is a choice that may be driven by a complex collection of factors, said one expert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When comparing outcomes with the control group – men who were never invited to have screenings – those who attended the screening appointments had a 23% lower risk of dying from prostate cancer, while non-attenders faced a 39% higher risk, SWNS reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Lead study author Renée Leenen, M.D., Ph.D., said the choice not to participate in screening may be driven by a complex collection of factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Health Newsletter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Said Leenen, who is with the Erasmus CM Cancer Institute in the Netherlands, "It may be that men who opted not to attend a screening appointment are care avoiders — meaning they’re less likely to engage in &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/healthy-living" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:healthy behaviors;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;healthy behaviors&lt;/a&gt; and preventative care in general."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She added, "This is the opposite behavior of people who are perhaps more health-conscious and are more likely to attend a screening appointment … Our study identifies that men who were invited for screening, but do not attend screening appointments, are at a significantly higher risk of dying from prostate cancer compared to men who were not offered screening or accepted an invitation for screening."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-term data from this entity consistently shows that PSA screening programs can lead to a 20% reduced risk of dying from prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Dr. Leenen said that experts "need to better understand who these men are, why they choose not to attend appointments and how to motivate them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Doing so, she added, "will help us design population-based prostate cancer screening programs that encourage higher rates of informed participation … Tackling attendance rates in this way could be a big factor in the long-term success of a national prostate screening program," SWNS reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:For more Health articles, visit ;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;For more Health articles, visit &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:www.foxnews.com/health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;www.foxnews.com/health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Urologist Tobias Nordström, M.D., Ph.D., of the Karolinska Institute in Sweden, said, "We need to better understand why these men might actively choose not to participate in screening, despite being invited to attend, and how this behavior is linked to worse outcomes when they get a diagnosis."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The findings from the study are scheduled to be presented this weekend at the European Association of Urology (EAU) Congress in Madrid, Spain, said SWNS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Fox News' senior medical analyst &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/person/s/marc-siegel" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Marc Siegel;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Marc Siegel&lt;/a&gt;, who was not involved in the new study on prostate cancer risks, previously called out the need for regular medical screenings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Siegel has emphasized the need to "diagnose it early for better outcomes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Angelica Stabile of Fox News Digital contributed reporting. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/prostate-cancer-risk-increases-45-among-men-share-behavior" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Prostate cancer risk increases by 45% among men who share one troubling behavior;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Prostate cancer risk increases by 45% among men who share one troubling behavior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 19:53:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPR2RXcGg2aTdVbmg3MjFkNlN5eTRoUzRTSWdTYm9YNE15THFScV9kNVA5VkFySElObGJJZ01mZWowMnNqSWE0VFR4bUNLNS1ObmJNN3JxdjZNanFMMUpHRnp6QUdNS1JlT0QtRGg4RnNURE01ejV0TXpQNmszbzZtaw</guid></item><item><title>Dendritic spines: The key to understanding how memories are linked in time - Phys.org</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMie0FVX3lxTE80Nlg4YmtVYXV5U2Nya3FNUVpVLXEwRW9ZdmtpcWRhOWRuT2JmbV9mWS1GUkc0ZDhlazVKU1BKN1hhbGFkX1dTWm1fdms1djJKTmMtSzcydGVHbGpXX1RfVDVYbmJtSXNpRXhhZHZZYVFVWXFxbmlnUkZTUdIBekFVX3lxTE1rVkdXeDhsN2RpcUR2QVpGeWlMWjk5aERoemhydmpqNVlQa0kxVWNVTW1lVVBBS1AxTmtrTUdDNUQ0ZEY5LWZESDRtanFqTERlSkNBd0tEOUszdlRyYkt2aDhKT185X2I5RmlyNHlvN0hhUHkxUHlYaXl3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
										
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/how-the-brain-links-re.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/how-the-brain-links-re.jpg" data-sub-html="Overlapping dendritic segments encode memories of two contexts explored close in time. Credit: &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;Nature Neuroscience&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41593-025-01876-8"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/how-the-brain-links-re.jpg" alt="How the brain links related memories formed close in time" title="Overlapping dendritic segments encode memories of two contexts explored close in time. Credit: Nature Neuroscience (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41593-025-01876-8"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Overlapping dendritic segments encode memories of two contexts explored close in time. Credit: &lt;i&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/i&gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1038/s41593-025-01876-8
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you've ever noticed how memories from the same day seem connected while events from weeks apart feel separate, a new study reveals the reason: Our brains physically link memories that occur close in time not in the cell bodies of neurons, but rather in their spiny extensions called dendrites.&lt;/p&gt;


										      
																																	&lt;p&gt;This discovery stems from studies in &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/mice/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;mice&lt;/a&gt;, in which researchers observed memory formation using advanced imaging techniques, including miniature microscopes that captured single-cell resolution in &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/live+animals/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;live animals&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study shows that memories are stored in dendritic compartments: When one memory forms, the affected dendrites are primed to capture new information arriving within the next few hours, linking memories formed close in time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If you think of a neuron as a computer, dendrites are like tiny computers inside it, each performing its own calculations," said lead author Megha Sehgal, assistant professor of psychology at The Ohio State University. "This discovery shows that our brains can link information arriving close in time to the same dendritic location, expanding our understanding of how memories are organized."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research was &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-01876-8" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; recently in the journal &lt;i&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Though most learning and memory studies have focused on how a single memory is formed in the brain, Sehgal's lab aims to determine how we organize multiple memories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The idea is that we don't form memories in isolation. You don't form a single memory. You use that memory, make a framework of memories, and then pull from that framework when you need to make adaptive decisions," she said.&lt;/p&gt;

																																						&lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
    
     
&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="8188791252"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
																																			&lt;p&gt;Neurons, the principal brain cells, are known to encode and relay information. Dendrites—the branch-like projections extending from neurons—serve a critical role in how information is processed, receiving incoming information and passing it to the neuronal cell body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But dendrites are not just passive conduits—each dendritic branch can act as an independent computational unit. While dendrites have been thought to play an important role in the brain's function, how they shape learning and memory has been unclear until now, Sehgal said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When mice were exposed in experiments to two different environments within a short period of time, the team found that memories of these spaces became linked. If mice received a mild shock in one of these spaces, the animals ended up freezing out of fear in both environments, associating the shock from one room with the other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study focused on the &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/retrosplenial+cortex/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;retrosplenial cortex&lt;/a&gt; (RSC), a brain region crucial for spatial and contextual memory. The researchers observed that linked memories consistently engaged the same groups of RSC neurons and their dendritic branches.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team tracked these changes at the dendritic level by visualizing &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/dendritic+spines/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;dendritic spines&lt;/a&gt;, tiny protrusions on dendrites where neurons communicate. The formation of new memories triggered the addition of clustered dendritic spines, a process critical for strengthening communication between neurons and facilitating learning.&lt;/p&gt;

																									&lt;div class="ads w-100 my-4 article-main__more bg-light p-3 border" aria-hidden="true"&gt;
    &lt;p class="mb-3"&gt;
        Discover the latest in science, tech, and space with over &lt;strong&gt;100,000 subscribers&lt;/strong&gt; who rely on Phys.org for daily insights.
        Sign up for our &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/newsletter/" target="_blank"&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; and get updates on breakthroughs,
        innovations, and research that matter—&lt;strong&gt;daily or weekly&lt;/strong&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;/div&gt;
																																			&lt;p&gt;Dendritic spine clusters formed after the first memory were more likely to attract new spines during a second closely timed memory, physically linking those experiences in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To confirm the role of dendrites in linking memories, the team used optogenetics, a technique that allows researchers to control neurons with light. By reactivating specific dendritic segments that had been active during &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/memory+formation/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;memory formation&lt;/a&gt;, they were able to link otherwise unrelated memories, further demonstrating the importance of dendritic changes in shaping memory networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to illuminating a previously unknown role for dendrites in linking memories, the findings open new avenues for understanding memory-related disorders, Sehgal said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our work not only expands our understanding of how memories are formed but also suggests exciting new possibilities for manipulating higher order memory processes," she said. "This could have implications for developing therapies for memory-related conditions such as Alzheimer's disease."&lt;/p&gt;

																																																					
																				&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
																						&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
												Megha Sehgal et al, Compartmentalized dendritic plasticity in the mouse retrosplenial cortex links contextual memories formed close in time, &lt;i&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41593-025-01876-8" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1038/s41593-025-01876-8&lt;/a&gt;
																						
																						&lt;/p&gt;
																					&lt;/div&gt;
                               											
																					
                              										                                        
										
										&lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
											 &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
												&lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
												Dendritic spines: The key to understanding how memories are linked in time (2025, March 22)
												retrieved 22 March 2025
												from https://phys.org/news/2025-03-dendritic-spines-key-memories-linked.html
											 &lt;/p&gt;
											 &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
											 This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
											 part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
											 &lt;/p&gt;
										&lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 17:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE80Nlg4YmtVYXV5U2Nya3FNUVpVLXEwRW9ZdmtpcWRhOWRuT2JmbV9mWS1GUkc0ZDhlazVKU1BKN1hhbGFkX1dTWm1fdms1djJKTmMtSzcydGVHbGpXX1RfVDVYbmJtSXNpRXhhZHZZYVFVWXFxbmlnUkZTUdIBekFVX3lxTE1rVkdXeDhsN2RpcUR2QVpGeWlMWjk5aERoemhydmpqNVlQa0kxVWNVTW1lVVBBS1AxTmtrTUdDNUQ0ZEY5LWZESDRtanFqTERlSkNBd0tEOUszdlRyYkt2aDhKT185X2I5RmlyNHlvN0hhUHkxUHlYaXl3</guid></item><item><title>A Massive New Study About Seed Oils May Change How You Eat - AOL</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMib0FVX3lxTE8zTm5DQU1uemtMckxhN2JvTmdwRmpROWxhZ3gzUnhsbWl6SnljZ1Zrclk1NkxWRUF0VE1KVHEzMGdxcVpYSFdOVHlzUXFTLVg3OUVlMHlwVFg0Ym1rVndVblFFVzdKUEk3bFBvZ08zbw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;What the Science Says on Dietary Fat&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;Lisovskaya&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ONE OF THE&lt;/strong&gt; most divisive nutrition topics right now—and &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a63448441/red-dye-number-three-ban/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:there;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;there&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a64161967/artificial-dyes-ban-rfk/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:are;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;are&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;a &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a63603209/is-beef-tallow-actually-good-for-you/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lot;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;lot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; of &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a45997622/is-raw-milk-good-for-you/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:them;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;them&lt;/a&gt;—is fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the recent arguments have centered on the supposed dangers of &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a63240441/are-seed-oils-actually-bad-for-you/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:seed oils;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;seed oils&lt;/a&gt;. Now, &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/nutrition/a35103720/saturated-fat-good-or-bad/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:saturated fats;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;saturated fats&lt;/a&gt; like butter and even beef tallow have entered the chat. The two topics are linked: The anti-seed-oils faction has turned to saturated fats as a replacement, based on the belief that these fats are more “natural.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which brings us to a new study &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamainternalmedicine/article-abstract/2831265" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:in JAMA Internal Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;in &lt;em&gt;JAMA Internal Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which looked at the association between varying consumption levels of either butter or plant-based oils (aka seed oils), and mortality levels, &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/health/a63096101/signs-of-heart-disease-in-men/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:heart disease;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/health/a43774213/good-news-about-cancer/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; incidence over the long term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using data from the &lt;a href="https://nurseshealthstudy.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Nurse’s Health Study;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Nurse’s Health Study&lt;/a&gt;, a large-scale study started in 1976, researchers analyzed the dietary habits of more than 220,000 adults. They collected the data through participants’ food frequency recalls to determine the amount of butter and/or plant-based oils in the participants’ diets over the course of roughly 30 years. (Researchers included safflower, soybean, corn, canola, and olive oils in the “plant-based” oils group.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results were consistent with what previous research has already shown: People who ate the most butter had a 12% higher risk of developing cancer, and a 15% higher risk for all-cause mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, the subjects who ate the most plant-based oils had a 16% lower risk for all-cause mortality, a 6% lower risk of death from heart disease, and 11% lower risk for cancer, which compounded the more plant-based oils were consumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers also found that substituting just 10 grams of butter a day—which is less than a tablespoon—for plant-based oil, &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/dietary-habits-study-suggests-more-plant-oils-less-butter-lead-to-better-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:led to a 17% reduction in cancer deaths and all-cause mortality;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;led to a 17% reduction in cancer deaths and all-cause mortality&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These conclusions seem aligned with what other studies have found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However—and this is a big HOWEVER—there are some caveats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, it’s virtually impossible to draw a definitive link between specific diets—&lt;em&gt;especially&lt;/em&gt; in a population—and health outcomes over time. Scientists just can’t keep people in a controlled lab environment for years of their lives. For long-term research like this, we have to rely on self-reported food intake, and at least some of that data may be inaccurate: People can forget, omit, or even lie about what they’ve been eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, other factors may muddle the link. People who eat more butter, for instance, may also do more of &lt;em&gt;other&lt;/em&gt; things that increase their risk for disease. They may eat a more processed diet, be more sedentary, or be more likely &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/health/a35213467/quitting-cigarettes-how-i-did-it/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:to smoke;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;to smoke&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, people's diets tend to change over time. (While researchers had participants fill out food frequency forms every four years, is this enough data to show the true nature of each person’s intake? Maybe or maybe not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Good Food, Bad Diet&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/1982137509?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C2141.a.64255411%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$12.05 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$12.05 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fourth, all of the participants in the study were nurses. Do they represent the general population? Also maybe or maybe not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the potential flaws in nutrition research as a whole, dietitians like myself look for reproducible effects and patterns. If we keep getting the same results over a series of similar studies, it’s likely that there is a true effect happening. In this case, it’s highly likely that a diet high in saturated fats is associated with a greater risk for disease and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn’t mean we all need to avoid saturated fat; it simply means that a diet containing a mix of fats is probably the best for health (with the exception of trans fats, which are definitely harmful).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means favoring unsaturated fats (including seed oils like canola and soybean) &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; adding in some saturated fats like butter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It might not be the next hot food trend, but it’s the most effective and sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 15:35:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE8zTm5DQU1uemtMckxhN2JvTmdwRmpROWxhZ3gzUnhsbWl6SnljZ1Zrclk1NkxWRUF0VE1KVHEzMGdxcVpYSFdOVHlzUXFTLVg3OUVlMHlwVFg0Ym1rVndVblFFVzdKUEk3bFBvZ08zbw</guid></item><item><title>An Uncertain Future for the County’s STI Clinic Stirs Outcry - Willamette Week</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQU1NXOHFUcFd0a2xjVFAtdzZuZkEwWE9ka1NZREUwdHFqQnlRRG1jZTZ1WklBTTdLaDNjS3NvVXRHU3d5YnZIZXo5TWxmV3ZrTWstMXd2NTRGeU1adHcwdzJma2EwNklzVjcwY1ltNkhGXzVMZ2NkU3YwQnV0dk5wSmZvdHdnMUdlVXRxd29yRG0tWm1UM0tXSy1YeDlEVzJ5V2lCLUtNaWY?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="b-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Health care advocates are raising alarms over the possible shutdown of Multnomah County’s sexually transmitted infections clinic in Old Town. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Last month, the county health department listed the STI clinic’s $1.4 million annual budget among $9 million in cuts needed to reduce the department’s budget by 12%, as part of a budgeting exercise ordered by County Chair Jessica Vega Pederson. She asked departments to list what they’d cut to bridge the county’s $21 million budget shortfall. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“In response to this significant budget challenge, the Health Department was asked to think strategically and concentrate on providing core services,” a Multnomah County spokesperson said in a statement to &lt;i&gt;WW&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:html-block-f0fFsJJApdG78II" data-fusion-component="html-block-f0fFsJJApdG78II"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;broadstreet-zone zone-id="169550"&gt;&lt;/broadstreet-zone&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:html-block-f0fFsJJApdG78II" data-fusion-component="html-block-f0fFsJJApdG78II"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The health department raised the possibility of eliminating the STI clinic altogether, closing its doors in June. The health department’s other clinics would be expected to pick up the STI clinic’s services, which include testing and treatment for illnesses such as HIV, syphilis and gonorrhea. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Since then, the budget outlook has grown sunnier: The county only needs to trim $15 million, and the STI clinic is listed by the health department as its first priority to be saved. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Still, those close to the program have in recent weeks expressed concern about its future, given that the county is in delicate negotiations with other governments over its homeless services budget, and its budgeting woes for that office could have a domino effect. Social media posts began circulating across platforms in February, urging voters to contact Vega Pederson and county commissioners about the clinic’s survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:html-block-f0f4sSS60cJYa3P" data-fusion-component="html-block-f0f4sSS60cJYa3P"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:html-block-f0f4sSS60cJYa3P" data-fusion-component="html-block-f0f4sSS60cJYa3P"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“Eliminating this clinic is not just going to inconvenience or something like that—it’s going to cost lives in the long run,” says Jeanne Krinsley, who worked there for nearly 25 years. “We’ve spent decades building trust with people, especially with the LGBTQ+ community and immigrants. They’re not comfortable going to someone they don’t trust.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The STI clinic has operated around Old Town since the 1960s and is currently housed in the Gladys McCoy Building on Northwest 6th Avenue. Last year, the clinic’s staff treated nearly 3,000 patients, and is on track to treat a similar caseload this year. Krinsley, who retired in 2023, not only treated and educated patients who contracted STIs through consensual encounters, but she also treated sexual assault victims, many of whom hadn’t told anyone else what happened to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“When someone says, ‘I’ve never told anyone that,’ that’s a real honor when someone confides in you like that,” Krinsley says. “Our patients—we’re supposed to call them ‘clients,’ but I don’t see what’s wrong with ‘patients’—just loved us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The medical specialty requires sensitivity toward patients of all backgrounds, including houseless people, people who don’t speak English fluently, and people navigating the complexities of American health care. Krinsley says she remembers the STI clinic leading treatment during the mpox outbreak of 2022 and staying open in 2020 for in-person care when primary care doctors pivoted to telehealth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“People trusted us, so they came in,” she says. “If we’re so unimportant, why were we still coming in?” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Multnomah County’s STI clinic workers attempt to lower the barriers patients face when seeking treatment for STIs. Some clinicians visit sites like camps of houseless people to offer testing and treatment, a service that would be cut if the clinic had to close its doors. This keeps treatment accessible for people who might not be able to afford care without insurance, or who fear the stigma associated with STI testing. A familiar staff of expert providers also means patients have access to culturally competent clinicians who can help reassure them when their care leaves them physically or emotionally vulnerable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:html-block-f0fHBQDiWeXl5zS" data-fusion-component="html-block-f0fHBQDiWeXl5zS"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;broadstreet-zone zone-id="169550"&gt;&lt;/broadstreet-zone&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:html-block-f0fHBQDiWeXl5zS" data-fusion-component="html-block-f0fHBQDiWeXl5zS"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“We had a guy who did not speak English who we spent a year trying to get into HIV treatment because he did not trust the medical system,” Krinsley says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Though new STI cases fell in Multnomah County in 2023 from their immediate post-pandemic spikes in 2020–22, the rates still remain around pre-pandemic highs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Vega Pederson said in a statement to &lt;i&gt;WW&lt;/i&gt; that she has not yet reached a final decision on the STI clinic’s future. She’ll propose a budget April 24, with the final budget to be approved in early June. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“Any cuts proposed by the department are provisional and meant to give myself and our board a range of options to consider,” she said. “We appreciate the patients, community members, and partner organizations who have contacted our office and testified to share their support for the services provided by the STI clinic. I share their passion for impactful public health initiatives and prevention efforts, especially as we see these services eroded at the federal level.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Krinsley says in her experience that primary care providers can miss an STI’s early symptoms before they’re so obvious they require urgent care, which comes with a higher co-pay when patients have insurance. Symptoms can also go away without the infection resolving, leaving unsuspecting patients unaccounted for to risk spreading infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:html-block-f0fWUJt8KR3m5Ob" data-fusion-component="html-block-f0fWUJt8KR3m5Ob"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;broadstreet-zone zone-id="169550"&gt;&lt;/broadstreet-zone&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:html-block-f0fWUJt8KR3m5Ob" data-fusion-component="html-block-f0fWUJt8KR3m5Ob"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“HIV and syphilis can kill you down the line,” Krinsley says. Closing the clinic “is just not going to work very well. It’s just going to lead to a lot more disability and death, and it’s just so short-sighted because it’s going to lead to an increase in costs.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Willamette Week</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 15:12:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQU1NXOHFUcFd0a2xjVFAtdzZuZkEwWE9ka1NZREUwdHFqQnlRRG1jZTZ1WklBTTdLaDNjS3NvVXRHU3d5YnZIZXo5TWxmV3ZrTWstMXd2NTRGeU1adHcwdzJma2EwNklzVjcwY1ltNkhGXzVMZ2NkU3YwQnV0dk5wSmZvdHdnMUdlVXRxd29yRG0tWm1UM0tXSy1YeDlEVzJ5V2lCLUtNaWY</guid></item><item><title>Oregon Man Sues Pet Food Company for Allegedly Killing His Cats With Bird Flu - Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirAFBVV95cUxQQjlkR0wzVjk4cVJWblJTNlhfUmgwRFlOYUUycTh1bzFlZHltZndzbi1XeVd4YUJyZkVrenNWaGU0eXJYVzFmUHhMUFREd1hJM01RUFpjMDFjOXBvYXFVMDczYTlqOXg1OHlkTHZPX25iLXhSX21KaGVsdUVtV3BORXFSd3Q2ek5NbjFSaXEwMFdzQU1pYWlucUQwNkNEd0Qtd000Wkt0R251ZEVY?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none"&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;A man in Oregon filed a lawsuit against Wild Coast Pet Food this week after his cat died from bird flu. The suit alleges the company misled consumers when it sold raw chicken cat food as healthy, failing to acknowledge potential risks, such as potential death from the consumption of H5N1-infected food.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The lawsuit, filed by Tim Hanson, seeks just under $8,000 in damages which covers compensation for veterinarian bills and legal fees, according to &lt;a href="https://www.ktvb.com/article/news/regional/portland-man-sues-wild-coast-pet-food-cat-dies-bird-flu/283-983181c4-2d7f-4549-8239-6e72d29d4386"&gt;KTVB 7&lt;/a&gt; in Oregon. Hanson adopted his cat Kira in 2021 and told the news outlet he typically feeds his cats raw food like the chicken that killed his cat because “I believe in the health benefits of it.” It’s not entirely clear what health benefits Hanson believes can come from raw chicken.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hanson told KTVB 7 he bought the Wild Coast Pet Foods brand cat food in January but one day in early February Kira stopped eating. Hanson told the news outlet he brought her to the vet on Feb. 5 and a few days later tests confirmed Kira had bird flu.  Kira was so sick she had to be euthanized on Feb. 9.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Wild Coast, which is based in Washington, issued a recall on March 1 for its 16 oz and 24 oz frozen Boneless Free Range Chicken Formula raw pet food for cats. The food was sold in Washington and Oregon.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The warning from the recall, which was posted on the FDA’s website:&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who fed pets the recalled products should watch for symptoms of bird flu in their pets, including fever, lethargy, low appetite, reddened or inflamed eyes, discharge from the eyes and nose, difficulty breathing, and neurological signs like tremors, stiff body movements, seizure, lack of coordination, or blindness. People with pets exhibiting these signs after feeding this product should contact their veterinarian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The spread of bird flu has been devastating for many cat owners, as they seem to be the most susceptible among domestic animals outside birds to H5N1. Many cats from New York to Oregon have been documented to have died from the disease and there are likely many more deaths that are going undetected.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;No humans in the U.S. have contracted bird flu from eating food, at least as far as health authorities can tell. But it does appear that cats are getting it from the consumption of raw food. U.S. health agencies have tested both milk and beef and it appears both are safe for human consumption even with the presence of bird flu as long as the milk is pasteurized and the beef is cooked to at least medium.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;There’s also no evidence of human-to-human spread of the bird flu in the U.S. but there is concern a mutation could allow that to happen. There have been 70 cases of H5N1 documented in Americans with one death. Forty-one of those cases have been tied to dairy cattle, 24 have been traced to poultry farms, two cases are from backyard flocks and wild birds, and three cases are still unknown sources.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Wild Coast didn’t respond to questions emailed Friday. Gizmodo will update this post if we hear back.&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 14:43:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxQQjlkR0wzVjk4cVJWblJTNlhfUmgwRFlOYUUycTh1bzFlZHltZndzbi1XeVd4YUJyZkVrenNWaGU0eXJYVzFmUHhMUFREd1hJM01RUFpjMDFjOXBvYXFVMDczYTlqOXg1OHlkTHZPX25iLXhSX21KaGVsdUVtV3BORXFSd3Q2ek5NbjFSaXEwMFdzQU1pYWlucUQwNkNEd0Qtd000Wkt0R251ZEVY</guid></item><item><title>Parkinson's Gut Bacteria Link Suggests an Unexpected, Simple Treatment - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxNb0J5Zms2anJFakFMLXFITllyc3BxUk8xT3VyZk5YZFJ1ZWExTnlqVmxhSDdfdU9jNnpjS1RtbnZncmxJQnI0VFc5LTI0MFJoTTJnSzQxdGd3d1JLVnE0S3BRXzJhMFNHd01fYTVXVEFTMzF1YTVTT1JLQnJNcFN1LTE5TUg5ZnNwMnpBRUdtSFZGTDdpdnA4Q1VtbnQ3UQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Researchers have suspected for&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-evidence-suggests-parkinson-s-might-start-in-the-gut-before-spreading-to-the-brain"&gt; some time&lt;/a&gt; that the link between our gut and brain plays a role in the development of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IYl" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73029" data-postid="155632" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt; disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study identified gut microbes likely to be involved and linked them with decreased &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Riboflavin"&gt;riboflavin&lt;/a&gt; ( &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="155632" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamin&lt;/a&gt; B2) and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Biotin"&gt;biotin&lt;/a&gt; (vitamin B7), pointing the way to an unexpectedly &lt;a href="https://youtu.be/9wuwZbPf0Vs"&gt;simple treatment that may help&lt;/a&gt;: B  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="155632" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamins&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Supplementation of riboflavin and/or biotin is likely to be beneficial in a subset of Parkinson's disease patients, in which gut dysbiosis plays pivotal roles," Nagoya University medical researcher Hiroshi Nishiwaki and colleagues &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41531-024-00724-z"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; in their paper published in May 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="aspect-w-16 aspect-h-9 youtube-iframe relative"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/9wuwZbPf0Vs?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The neurodegenerative disease impacts &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/parkinson-disease"&gt;almost 10 million people globally&lt;/a&gt;, who at best can hope for &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-is-the-first-time-drug-shows-signs-of-slowing-parkinsons-disease"&gt;therapies that slow and alleviate symptoms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Symptoms typically begin with constipation and sleep problems, up to 20 years before progressing into dementia and the debilitating loss of muscle control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/changes-in-gut-bacteria-are-present-long-before-signs-of-parkinsons-appear"&gt;Previous research&lt;/a&gt; found people with Parkinson's disease also experience changes in their microbiome long before other signs appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_131231" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-131231" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/SHakingHandPIckingUpGlass-1.jpg" alt="Hands picking up a glass" class="size-full wp-image-131231" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/SHakingHandPIckingUpGlass-1.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/SHakingHandPIckingUpGlass-1-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/SHakingHandPIckingUpGlass-1-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-131231" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Parkinson's disease impacts almost 10 million people globally. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEGCRiWJIk/"&gt;pixelshot/Canva Pro&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyzing fecal samples from 94 patients with Parkinson's disease and 73 relatively healthy controls in Japan, Nishiwaki and team compared their results with data from China, Taiwan, Germany, and the US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While different groups of bacteria were involved in the different countries examined, they all influenced pathways that synthesize B vitamins in the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers found the changes in gut bacteria communities were associated with a decrease in &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Riboflavin"&gt;riboflavin&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Biotin"&gt;biotin&lt;/a&gt; in people with Parkinson's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_145467" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-145467" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParkinsonsGutBVitamins642.jpg" alt="Graphic of human gut-brain connection and B vitamins" class="size-full wp-image-145467" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParkinsonsGutBVitamins642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParkinsonsGutBVitamins642-603x415.jpg 603w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/ParkinsonsGutBVitamins642-600x413.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-145467" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;In Parkinson's disease, a reduction in the gut bacteria of genes responsible for synthesizing the essential B vitamins B2 and B7 was found. (&lt;a href="https://www.nagoya-u.ac.jp/researchinfo/result-en/2024/06/20240618-01.html"&gt;Reiko Matsushita&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nishiwaki and colleagues then showed the lack of B vitamins was linked to a decrease in &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Short-chain_fatty_acid"&gt;short-chain fatty acids&lt;/a&gt; (SCFAs) and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Polyamine"&gt;polyamines&lt;/a&gt;: molecules that help create a healthy mucus layer in the intestines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Deficiencies in polyamines and SCFAs could lead to thinning of the intestinal mucus layer, increasing intestinal permeability, both of which have been observed in Parkinson's disease," Nishiwaki &lt;a href="https://www.nagoya-u.ac.jp/researchinfo/result-en/2024/06/20240618-01.html"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_131227" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-131227" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/GraphicOfParkinsonsVitaminBConnection642.jpg" alt="A graphic depicting the process of gut bacteria depleting B vitamins and leading to symptoms of Parkinson's disease" class="wp-image-131227 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/GraphicOfParkinsonsVitaminBConnection642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/GraphicOfParkinsonsVitaminBConnection642-280x415.jpg 280w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/GraphicOfParkinsonsVitaminBConnection642-600x888.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-131227" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Summary of findings from the study and speculations from previous research. (Nishiwaki et al., &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41531-024-00724-z"&gt;&lt;em&gt;npj Parkinson's Disease&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, 2024)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;They suspect the weakened protective layer exposes the intestinal nervous system to more of the toxins we now encounter more regularly. These include &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dry-cleaning-chemical-could-be-major-cause-of-parkinsons-scientists-warn"&gt;cleaning chemicals,&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/two-pathways-to-parkinsons-could-point-to-a-single-way-to-prevent-it"&gt;pesticides&lt;/a&gt;, and herbicides.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Such toxins lead to the overproduction of α-synuclein fibrils – molecules &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.nbd.2024.106411"&gt;known to amass&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-test-detects-parkinsons-7-years-before-most-symptoms-show"&gt;dopamine-producing cells&lt;/a&gt; in the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-pinpoint-exactly-which-brain-cells-die-in-parkinson-s-disease"&gt;substantia nigra&lt;/a&gt; part of our brains, and increased nervous system inflammation, eventually leading to the more debilitating motor and dementia symptoms of Parkinson's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.scielo.br/j/bjmbr/a/BM4WLJBtjxF8Cx3wFsjFhKb/?lang=en"&gt;2003 study&lt;/a&gt; found high doses of riboflavin can assist in recovering some motor functions in patients who also eliminated red meat from their diets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So it's possible that high doses of vitamin B may prevent some of the damage, Nishiwaki and team propose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_131228" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-131228" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/VitaminBInBlood642.jpg" alt="Illustration of a vitamin B2 molecule in the blood. " class="size-medium wp-image-131228" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/VitaminBInBlood642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/VitaminBInBlood642-628x415.jpg 628w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/06/VitaminBInBlood642-600x396.jpg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-131228" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustration of a riboflavin (B2) molecule in the blood. (Nemes Laszlo/Science Photo Library/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This all suggests ensuring patients have healthy gut microbiomes may also prove protective, as would &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/parkinsons-disease/can-environmental-toxins-cause-parkinson-disease"&gt;reducing the toxic pollutants&lt;/a&gt; in our environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Of course, with such a complicated chain of events involved in Parkinson's disease, not all patients likely experience the same causes, so each individual would need to be assessed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We could perform gut microbiota analysis on patients or conduct fecal metabolite analysis," &lt;a href="https://www.nagoya-u.ac.jp/researchinfo/result-en/2024/06/20240618-01.html"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt; Nishiwak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Using these findings, we could identify individuals with specific deficiencies and administer oral riboflavin and biotin supplements to those with decreased levels, potentially creating an effective treatment."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41531-024-00724-z"&gt;&lt;em&gt;npj Parkinson's Disease&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in June 2024.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 13:02:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNb0J5Zms2anJFakFMLXFITllyc3BxUk8xT3VyZk5YZFJ1ZWExTnlqVmxhSDdfdU9jNnpjS1RtbnZncmxJQnI0VFc5LTI0MFJoTTJnSzQxdGd3d1JLVnE0S3BRXzJhMFNHd01fYTVXVEFTMzF1YTVTT1JLQnJNcFN1LTE5TUg5ZnNwMnpBRUdtSFZGTDdpdnA4Q1VtbnQ3UQ</guid></item><item><title>Researchers pioneer groundbreaking light-driven method to create key drug compounds - Phys.org</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTFBqS2tQYzBLZUJiSm1MSHh4Y1ZPNjJWdGNpR3A0NGYtWnBham15ZUJIb1hvQzdRTF9BYzZPcDJpNmI3aEdIanExNTdBYmpkRE1qM2E3UnluMUtsNFNFeDBPbWYtOFZvX2lMcG0yd2ZRSzlsMElUQ1o2V1ZJVEnSAXtBVV95cUxQTm1tcnlVZ25oOWdVeWh4cC1VWHpjNU1qQUlYaWJpWlBfZEQyZUZuR19ZcjhEVVFTbG9RQm1pb2hPYnRZU2o5ZEdTRVZjVzI5YTV0MlYtTXBMY09QSFVjaVNuWW4yclZpamJSblE0c0J1RVJoVXlYY3ZzYkU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
										
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/researchers-pioneer-gr.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/2025/researchers-pioneer-gr.jpg" data-sub-html="Credit: &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;Chem&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1016/j.chempr.2025.102488"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/researchers-pioneer-gr.jpg" alt="Researchers pioneer groundbreaking light-driven method to create key drug compounds" title="Credit: Chem (2025). DOI: 10.1016/j.chempr.2025.102488"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Credit: &lt;i&gt;Chem&lt;/i&gt; (2025). DOI: 10.1016/j.chempr.2025.102488
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Indiana University and Wuhan University in China have unveiled a groundbreaking chemical process that could streamline the development of pharmaceutical compounds, chemical building blocks that influence how drugs interact with the body. Their &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/chem/abstract/S2451-9294(25)00078-6" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;, published in &lt;i&gt;Chem&lt;/i&gt;, describes a novel light-driven reaction that efficiently produces tetrahydroisoquinolines, a group of chemicals that play a crucial role in medicinal chemistry.&lt;/p&gt;


										      
																																	&lt;p&gt;Tetrahydroisoquinolines serve as the foundation for treatments targeting Parkinson's disease, cancer, and cardiovascular disorders. These compounds are commonly found in medications such as painkillers and drugs for &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/high+blood+pressure/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, as well as in natural sources like certain plants and marine organisms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, chemists have relied on well-established but limiting methods to synthesize these &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/molecules/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;molecules&lt;/a&gt;. The new research, co-authored by Kevin Brown, the James F. Jackson Professor of Chemistry in the College of Arts and Sciences at Indiana University Bloomington, and Professors Xiaotian Qi, Wang Wang, and Bodi Zhao of Wuhan University, presents a fundamentally different approach.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How it works: Light as a chemical tool&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead of using traditional chemical reactions, scientists harness light to trigger a process called photoinduced energy transfer, wherein light initiates a controlled reaction between sulfonylimines (a type of chemical compound) and alkenes (another type of compound), leading to the creation of tetrahydroisoquinolines—a type of complex molecule. This method allows for the development of new structural patterns in the molecules, which were previously difficult or impossible to create using other methods, offering a more efficient way to make complex molecules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The key innovation in this study is the use of a light-activated catalyst, a special molecule that speeds up the reaction without being used up itself," said Professor Brown. "Traditional methods require high temperatures or strong acids—like trying to cook food with a blowtorch instead of a stove. These harsh conditions can sometimes create unwanted side reactions, or make the process less useful for certain chemicals. The new process, however, uses molecules that respond to light, and can bypass heating by access new energy states. This makes the reaction cleaner, more efficient, and less likely to create unwanted byproducts."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brown and colleagues also found that tiny changes in the location of electrons within the starting materials had a huge impact on how the reaction played out—akin to if these electrons were puzzle pieces that needed to fit together just right. By tweaking the shapes of these pieces, the scientists made sure that only the desired product was formed, making the process highly selective. This is crucial for making medicines, where even a small mistake in a molecule's structure can turn a helpful drug into something useless or even harmful.&lt;/p&gt;

																																						&lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
    
     
&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="8188791252"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
																																			&lt;h2&gt;Implications for medicine and other industries&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The ability to create a wider range of tetrahydroisoquinoline-based molecules means that medicinal chemists can now explore new drug candidates for treating diseases like Parkinson's, certain types of cancer, and heart conditions," noted Professor Qi. "Right now, some diseases have very few effective treatment options, and this method could help scientists discover new and better drugs more quickly."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond pharmaceuticals, this research could also impact other industries that rely on fine chemicals. In agriculture, for example, similar chemical reactions could be used to develop more effective pesticides or fertilizers. In &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/materials+science/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;materials science&lt;/a&gt;, it could help create new synthetic materials with specific properties, such as better durability and longevity and greater resistance to heat for the aerospace, automotive, electronics, and medical industries.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers plan to fine-tune the reaction conditions, meaning, they will experiment with different ingredients and settings to make the improve the process further. They also aim to find out if this method can work on even more types of molecules, expanding its usefulness. In addition, they hope to partner with &lt;a href="https://phys.org/tags/pharmaceutical+companies/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;pharmaceutical companies&lt;/a&gt; to test whether this technique can be used to produce medicines, potentially leading to new drug discoveries that could make a difference in people's lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This approach gives chemists a powerful new tool," said Professor Brown. "We hope especially it will open the door to the development of new and improved therapies for patients around the world."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the field of photochemistry continues to expand, innovations like this may redefine how medicines and essential chemicals are made, paving the way for faster, cleaner, and more efficient production methods.&lt;/p&gt;

																																																					
																				&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
																						&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
												Wang Wang et al, An unconventional photochemical tetrahydroisoquinoline synthesis from sulfonylimines and alkenes, &lt;i&gt;Chem&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.chempr.2025.102488" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1016/j.chempr.2025.102488&lt;/a&gt;
																						
																						&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mt-3"&gt;
												&lt;p&gt;
													&lt;strong&gt;Journal information:&lt;/strong&gt;
																											&lt;a href="https://phys.org/journals/chem/"&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Chem&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
														&lt;a class="icon_open" href="http://www.cell.com/chem/home" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;
															&lt;svg&gt;
																&lt;use href="https://phys.b-cdn.net/tmpl/v6/img/svg/sprite.svg#icon_open" x="0" y="0"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
															&lt;/svg&gt;
														&lt;/a&gt; 
																									&lt;/p&gt;
											&lt;/div&gt;
																					&lt;/div&gt;
                               											
																					
                              										                                        
										
										&lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
											 &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
												&lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
												Researchers pioneer groundbreaking light-driven method to create key drug compounds (2025, March 22)
												retrieved 22 March 2025
												from https://phys.org/news/2025-03-groundbreaking-driven-method-key-drug.html
											 &lt;/p&gt;
											 &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
											 This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
											 part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
											 &lt;/p&gt;
										&lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:22:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFBqS2tQYzBLZUJiSm1MSHh4Y1ZPNjJWdGNpR3A0NGYtWnBham15ZUJIb1hvQzdRTF9BYzZPcDJpNmI3aEdIanExNTdBYmpkRE1qM2E3UnluMUtsNFNFeDBPbWYtOFZvX2lMcG0yd2ZRSzlsMElUQ1o2V1ZJVEnSAXtBVV95cUxQTm1tcnlVZ25oOWdVeWh4cC1VWHpjNU1qQUlYaWJpWlBfZEQyZUZuR19ZcjhEVVFTbG9RQm1pb2hPYnRZU2o5ZEdTRVZjVzI5YTV0MlYtTXBMY09QSFVjaVNuWW4yclZpamJSblE0c0J1RVJoVXlYY3ZzYkU</guid></item><item><title>Flu activity still high as COVID-19 causes nearly 40 deaths a week - Dayton Daily News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizAFBVV95cUxNM2l0T3JmS2dva19tYzlRcHNmYks0emJzWHg5TzMtMy16Slh3UkpPLW9nb3drbEhwM1AwZlNROURUMEgtUGc3UG1zMllTQnRJOUM1Y0F5b0Q4WHRkcHoydVJwYnc0OEVGRVVRYzBtTzVSY29aNjVWM0R6dzdXMFVSUk5WU3JGTGwyQ1F6WUs2dldOMWdlanJscVdsVzM5bnljcnFQU3FPLThjVWtSMFZFcVR5SkJtVUtiX2t2UG50QkJmMVM5MW9iVFFzRDI?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-contentElements" data-start-index="0"&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="1"&gt;In late January, Ohio was seeing about 5,500 flu cases a week, Vanderhoff said, but now the state is down to fewer than 3,000 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="2"&gt;There were 1,024 flu-related hospitalizations reported in the most recent week of data in Ohio, which is about a 25.7% decline over the previous week, according to ODH. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="4"&gt;Over the past two weeks, the state has sharp declines in hospitalizations, Vanderhoff said. Hospitalizations, outpatient visits and trips to the emergency for flu-like illnesses still remain above the five-year average, but they continue to decline. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="5"&gt;The flu season will continue until the middle of May, so experts say people should still take precautions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-subscription__placeholder subscription-promo b-margin-bottom-d40-m20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="7"&gt;“Typically the flu season runs from October to May, so we’re still in the midst of the traditional season,” Dan Suffoletto, public information manager for Public Health - Dayton &amp;amp; Montgomery County, said earlier this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-nativo_placeholder--moap b-clear-both is-deferred"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="9"&gt;“It’s still very important if people are having signs and symptoms of the flu to stay home if they’re sick to help reduce the spread,” Suffoletto said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="10"&gt;Flu-like symptoms also accounted for 5.37% of outpatient visits last week, according to ODH, which was down by 19%. Emergency department visits for flu-like illnesses were just under 2% of all hospital visits, while emergency department visits for general, none specific symptoms that could be flu or cold-like illnesses were at 12.9% of visits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="11"&gt;Locally, Montgomery County has had 1,033 flu-related hospitalizations this season, which is about 6.6% of all of Ohio’s flu hospitalizations, according to ODH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="12"&gt;Butler County has had 375 flu-related hospitalizations and Clark County has had 287; both are totals for this flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="13"&gt;Influenza A continues to be the most prevalent of the flu cases nationally, which is often considered to be worse than influenza B as the symptoms are more severe, according to the &lt;a href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/flu-a-vs-flu-b" target="_blank"&gt;Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="is-deferred MP03 arc_ad b-margin-bottom-d30-m20 "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="is-deferred RP09 arc_ad b-margin-bottom-d30-m20 "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="17"&gt;COVID-19 is also still a threat that needs to be taken seriously, Vanderhoff said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="18"&gt;“It continues to claim too many lives,” Vanderhoff said. “Over the past three weeks, we have averaged about 40 deaths in Ohio per week.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="19"&gt;There were 24 COVID-related deaths reported in the most recent week of data, which is down from 34 deaths the week before and 44 before then, according to ODH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="20"&gt;The three-week average for COVID-related hospitalizations is 135 hospitalizations statewide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="21"&gt;Nationwide, 0.9% of the deaths in the U.S. are related to COVID-19, according to the Centers for Disease Control, which also says the rate of COVID-related hospitalizations is 2.1 hospitalizations per 100,000 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="23"&gt;If people have not yet received the updated COVID-19 shot, Vanderhoff said they should consider getting the updated vaccine, especially those who are 65 or older.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="24"&gt;“It offers the best chance for protection,” Vanderhoff said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="25"&gt;Respiratory syncytial virus, or RSV, is another common respiratory virus active this season that infects the nose, throat and lungs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="26"&gt;“RSV was another concern earlier in the winter, but thankfully, we have seen a sharp decline in cases and hospitalizations in recent weeks,” Vanderhoff said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="27"&gt;COVID-19 and flu shots are available at most doctor’s offices and pharmacies. For more information or to find a location, visit &lt;a href="https://www.vaccines.gov/en/" target="_blank"&gt;vaccines.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="is-deferred HP03 arc_ad b-margin-bottom-d30-m20 "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="story-text " data-index="31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dayton Daily News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:17:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxNM2l0T3JmS2dva19tYzlRcHNmYks0emJzWHg5TzMtMy16Slh3UkpPLW9nb3drbEhwM1AwZlNROURUMEgtUGc3UG1zMllTQnRJOUM1Y0F5b0Q4WHRkcHoydVJwYnc0OEVGRVVRYzBtTzVSY29aNjVWM0R6dzdXMFVSUk5WU3JGTGwyQ1F6WUs2dldOMWdlanJscVdsVzM5bnljcnFQU3FPLThjVWtSMFZFcVR5SkJtVUtiX2t2UG50QkJmMVM5MW9iVFFzRDI</guid></item><item><title>These Supplements Promise To Lower Blood Sugar And Help You Lose Weight—But Do They Work? - AOL</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTE1PelVyaDVaQ1FkeVl4UzdFVWVreUhvdTNFX1lnNFoxbXBJbUhiYUtVVUpNMW5SdWp1bFFPT19ISU9yN0xpLUV3ZVhHQjFuR2FFdWdMMlFUcVJiS01TVkZXV3p5STNBZDNLRmNBZVI4aG5CMUNxOVREZF9Bd3Y?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Are Insulin Resistance Supplements Legit?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;Kseniya Ovchinnikova - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just like &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/a46052847/taylor-swift-eras-tour-training-workouts/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Taylor Swift during her Eras Tour;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Taylor Swift during her Eras Tour&lt;/a&gt;, it seems like &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a62230472/natural-glp-supplement/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:weight loss supplements;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;weight loss supplements&lt;/a&gt; are everywhere right now—and that includes insulin resistance supps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supplement companies market insulin resistance supplements to help &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a64245012/walking-blood-sugar-management-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lower your blood sugar;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;lower your blood sugar&lt;/a&gt;, curb glucose spikes, support consistent energy levels, combat sugar cravings, and help you maintain a healthy weight. These supplements also claim to help lower the risk of developing &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/diabetes/overview/what-is-diabetes/prediabetes-insulin-resistance" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:insulin resistance;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;insulin resistance&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a condition where your body doesn’t respond the way it should to insulin. If left unchecked, insulin resistance can lead to weight gain, prediabetes, and type 2 diabetes, per the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/diabetes/about/insulin-resistance-type-2-diabetes.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (CDC). And managing your blood glucose levels—and making sure they’re not too high—is also key for preventing any future diabetic issues, per the &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/diabetes/overview/managing-diabetes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institutes of Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (NIH).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meet the experts:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://doctors.nyp.org/rekha-b-kumar-md-ms/iris-cantor-womens-health-center" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Rekha Kumar;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Rekha Kumar&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is an endocrinologist at NewYork-Presbyterian Hospital Weill-Cornell School of Medicine. &lt;a href="https://rwjms.rutgers.edu/people/christoph-buettner" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Christoph Buettner;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Christoph Buettner&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, PhD, is the chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers University's Robert Wood Johnson Medical School. &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/mir-b-ali" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mir Ali;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mir Ali&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is the medical director of MemorialCare Surgical Weight Loss Center at Orange Coast Medical Center in Fountain Valley, CA. &lt;a href="https://case.edu/medicine/nutrition/node/1286" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lindsay Malone;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Lindsay Malone&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, RD, is an integrative and functional medicine dietitian and an instructor in the Department of Nutrition at the Case Western Reserve School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s the thing: The &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/consumers/consumer-updates/fda-101-dietary-supplements" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:FDA;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;FDA&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; doesn’t approve dietary supplements or set categories within them, so it’s unclear what it even means to be an insulin resistance supplement. But brands are creating all sorts of supps within the category—Apothekary sells &lt;a href="https://www.apothekary.com/products/sugar-kick" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Sugar Kick drops;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Sugar Kick drops&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Nourished has &lt;a href="https://nourishednaturalhealth.com/products/pcos-blood-sugar-balance?variant=40466492588212" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PCOS Blood Sugar Balance;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;PCOS Blood Sugar Balance&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; supps, and Walmart has an entire online &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fc%2Fkp%2Finsulin-resistance-supplement&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.womenshealthmag.com%2Fweight-loss%2Fa64254355%2Fsupplements-for-insulin-resistance%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:selection;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;selection&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, are insulin resistance supplements legit—and safe—for lowering your blood sugar and losing weight? And what’s even in them? Ahead, experts break down how these supps work, and whether you should take them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do insulin resistance supplements work?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In theory, an insulin resistance supplement would help support insulin sensitivity. “Insulin sensitivity can be looked at as the amount of insulin required to push sugar/carbs into cells to make energy,” explains endocrinologist Rekha Kumar, MD. “More sensitivity means it requires less insulin, and insulin resistance means it takes more insulin to turn carbs to energy.” This balance is vital for keeping healthy blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, these supplements are designed to help combat a range of health issues. “Poor insulin sensitivity—insulin resistance—can lead to high blood sugar and lipids, which increases the risk of &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a60525665/type-2-diabetes-food-list/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:type 2 diabetes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, obesity, cardiovascular disease, and fatty liver disease,” says Christoph Buettner, MD, PhD, chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insulin resistance supplements are a pretty broad category, so they all work in different ways. Most of them have a range of ingredients that don’t tend to overlap, although there are a few that show up repeatedly:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitter Melon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few small studies suggest that the fruit extract bitter melon may help with lowering blood sugar levels. One randomized controlled trial of 90 people with type 2 diabetes found that levels of HbA1c (which measures average blood sugar levels over two to three months) didn’t change between the bitter melon and placebo groups after 12 weeks, per 2020 research in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0965229920302491" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Complementary Therapies in Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Complementary Therapies in Medicine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. However, the average fasting glucose level of people in the bitter melon group went down during the trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another small trial on 76 people with prediabetes also found that bitter melon helped to lower glucose levels by suppressing levels of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK537082/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:glucagon;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;glucagon&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a hormone that stimulates the liver to release stores of glucose, according to 2022 research in &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10050654/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Food Science and Biotechnology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Food Science and Biotechnology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;White Mulberry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leaves from this tree are used in traditional Chinese medicine to treat diabetes, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/white-mulberry-leaf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:NIH;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;u&gt;NIH&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. There’s some research that suggests white mulberry may lower blood glucose levels, according to a 2020 study in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0965229919317315" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Complementary Therapies in Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Complementary Therapies in Medicine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. However, most of this research is preliminary and not conducted on humans, per the NIH, so it’s hard to draw a definitive conclusion from them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready for resul&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ts? &lt;a href="https://membership.womenshealthmag.com/womens-health-premium-membership-single.html?cds_tracking_code=whl_edit_inline_strength_transformation_prep_amy_williams_a64218691" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Sign up for WH+ today;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Sign up for WH+ today&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;for exclusive meal and strength training plans only available to subscribers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cinnamon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon or cinnamon bark pops up in a few supplements, too, and there is some (also limited) research to back this up. One 2023 meta-analysis in &lt;a href="https://dmsjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13098-023-01057-2" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Diabetology &amp;amp; Metabolic Syndrome;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Diabetology &amp;amp; Metabolic Syndrome&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of existing research concluded that cinnamon could be an “add-on treatment” to control blood sugar levels in people with type 2 diabetes or &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a62224378/the-impossibility-of-getting-a-pcos-diagnosis/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS);elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another four-week randomized controlled trial of 18 people with prediabetes and obesity found that blood sugar levels were “significantly lower” when people had cinnamon beforehand, according to 2024 research in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S000291652400008X" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The researchers concluded that cinnamon may improve blood glucose control for those with obesity-related prediabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But none of the research on these ingredients is robust, making it tough to say for sure that the supplements do what they claim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So, can insulin resistance supps actually improve your blood sugar and help you lose weight?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those are some pretty hefty promises, and experts are wary of them, especially because they haven’t been evaluated by the FDA. “There are no good studies or scientific evidence to show they make any dramatic difference,” in your blood sugar and weight, says Mir Ali, MD, medical director of MemorialCare Surgical Weight Loss Center at Orange Coast Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus, insulin sensitivity is a complicated process, and taking a supplement alone is unlikely to make a huge difference in your blood sugar and weight, adds integrative and functional medicine dietitian Lindsay Malone, RD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sure-fire way to improve your blood sugar and maintain your weight? Lifestyle changes: “No supplement will work unless you do,” Malone says. “Switching to a &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a39628652/80-20-diet-low-glycemic-intermittent-fasting-weight-loss-success-story/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:low-glycemic diet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;low-glycemic diet&lt;/a&gt;, eating whole, minimally processed foods, moving your body throughout the day, and getting &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a63941290/blue-light-sleep-health-benefits-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:adequate sleep;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;adequate sleep&lt;/a&gt; will address and fix the root cause of insulin resistance.” Reducing &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a27378711/weight-loss-success-story-simple-carbs/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:simple carbs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;simple carbs&lt;/a&gt; like baked goods, soda, and cereal, for instance, can also help to keep your blood sugar levels stable, since your body breaks them down into glucose which could cause blood sugar spikes, Kumar says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which supplements are best for insulin resistance?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts aren’t really on board with taking these new, buzzy, multi-ingredient supplements that claim to help with insulin resistance. However, a few vitamin and mineral supplements &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; have some inherent benefits for insulin resistance and even weight loss, especially in people with endocrine or hormonal disorders like &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11668966/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PCOS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PCOS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, experts stress that these supplements are not magic pills. “Supplements alone are not a cure and often they do not do much,” Buettner says. But, again, with lifestyle changes like a healthy diet and regular movement, they may help support your efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how they work, according to Malone:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carnitine. &lt;/strong&gt;Commonly sold as l-carnitine, this &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a60956813/amino-acid-supplements/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:amino acid;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;amino acid&lt;/a&gt; helps your body use fat for energy, which can support weight loss efforts and may improve insulin sensitivity, according to Malone. In a 2020 meta-analysis in &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32359762/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Clinical Nutrition ESPEN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clinical Nutrition ESPEN&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of 37 randomized controlled clinical trials, l-carnitine supplementation significantly decreased body weight, but there were no major effects on waist circumference or body fat percentage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a44638878/fish-oil-health-benefits/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Omega-3;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Omega-3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. These healthy fats can reduce inflammation and “may also improve insulin sensitivity and assist with fat loss, especially belly fat,” Malone says. One small 2022 study in &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35815739/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Nutrición Hospitalaria;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Nutrición Hospitalaria&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; found that omega-3 supplements “augmented” belly fat loss in overweight or obese people who were also on a weight loss diet, but more research is needed to determine whether omega-3 supplementation is effective for weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a40120300/vitamin-d-benefits/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Vitamin D;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Vitamin D&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. “Low vitamin D levels are linked to insulin resistance, so supplementing with vitamin D can help improve sensitivity and potentially support weight loss,” Malone says. There’s a link between taking vitamin D and weight loss, as part of a larger treatment plan like a changed diet, per a 2018 study in &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30246883/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Clinical Endocrinology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Clinical Endocrinology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and 2021 study in the &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/07315724.2021.1902879" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Journal of the American Nutrition Association;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;Journal of the American Nutrition Association&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Acetyl-L-Carnitine&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Courtesy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B005P0UYGA?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C2140.a.64254355%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$27.00 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$27.00 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Omega-3&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Courtesy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001GCU6KA?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C2140.a.64254355%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$12.29 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$12.29 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Vitamin D3&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Courtesy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004U3Y8OM?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C2140.a.64254355%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$10.22 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$10.22 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re concerned about insulin resistance, it’s best to talk to a healthcare provider. (And if you have severe insulin resistance, like you’re prediabetic or you have type 2 diabetes, Kumar says you may benefit from prescription medication like metformin or a &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a63788221/glp1-alcohol-use-disorder-clinical-trial-results/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:GLP-1 receptor;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;GLP-1 receptor&lt;/a&gt; agonist like &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/a62777117/running-while-on-ozempic/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ozempic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your doc can do an evaluation to see where things stand with your blood sugar levels, including testing to see if you have prediabetes or diabetes. From there, you can come up with a care plan together. So, while the idea of taking an insulin resistance supplement and hoping things will turn around is easy and appealing, it’s always best to rope in a medical professional for extra help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:09:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE1PelVyaDVaQ1FkeVl4UzdFVWVreUhvdTNFX1lnNFoxbXBJbUhiYUtVVUpNMW5SdWp1bFFPT19ISU9yN0xpLUV3ZVhHQjFuR2FFdWdMMlFUcVJiS01TVkZXV3p5STNBZDNLRmNBZVI4aG5CMUNxOVREZF9Bd3Y</guid></item><item><title>Environmental features linked to dementia risk and cognitive decline - PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxQUjlJRDk0cjZ4YnNaN28xbUVaRXQzdVNXQmF2cTd2VjRTdFdwQXBsSU9oQW9SUzM2TEVfQ0pUOHJrTzF4RkNtbU9zM0M1VU82V2JWempuUmxqSFBPNmxjbWRTbFU4Z2pBUGQ2RVRlWDZBZnc0b0szSXZLT3dfN2hsdFhOTXJBZ2dGdW9FaVcxZ1AteEdYRFNhMQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;People living in greener, more walkable neighborhoods may face a lower risk of developing dementia, while those exposed to more air pollution might face a higher risk, according to a large review of existing studies. The findings, published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.arr.2024.102630" target="_blank"&gt;Ageing Research Reviews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, highlight connections between environmental factors and brain health as people age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dementia is a growing global concern, affecting nearly 50 million people worldwide. It encompasses a range of disorders that impair memory, thinking, and daily functioning, including Alzheimer’s disease. With an aging population and no available cure, finding ways to prevent or delay dementia has become a pressing goal in public health. While many studies have examined genetic and lifestyle factors, researchers are now turning their attention to environmental influences. Previous studies have hinted that elements such as air quality, traffic noise, and neighborhood design may affect brain health, but results have been inconsistent and often based on subjective reports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To address this gap, a team of researchers conducted a systematic review and meta-analysis. This means the researchers carefully examined and combined data from many previously published studies. A systematic review aims to gather all relevant evidence on a topic, while a meta-analysis uses statistical techniques to combine the results of those studies and provide a clearer picture of how strong the observed effects are. Only studies that used objective measures—such as satellite data, geographic information systems, and pollution monitoring—were included to ensure the most reliable results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My interest in this research topic is because of the urgent global challenge posed by dementia. As dementia affects millions of people and effective treatments remain limited, I was driven to explore modifiable risk factors that could help delay or even prevent cognitive decline,” said study author Linlin Da, a PhD student at the University of Georgia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I became particularly interested in investigating the role of the built environment, and how factors such as air pollution, urban design, and the availability of green spaces might influence cognitive health. By utilizing objective measures to assess these environmental exposures, I aimed to address inconsistencies in previous studies and contribute to a clearer understanding of how urban planning and environmental policies could support dementia prevention.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers searched five major scientific databases and initially identified over 1,800 studies. After a thorough screening process, they selected 54 high-quality studies for their systematic review, 21 of which were also suitable for meta-analysis. The included studies came from around the world, with sample sizes ranging from under 200 to over 63 million individuals, most of whom were aged 60 and older. These studies measured environmental exposures like fine particulate matter in the air (known as PM2.5), nitrogen dioxide, proximity to green spaces, and access to local services. Outcomes included diagnosed dementia or measures of cognitive decline over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that people exposed to higher levels of air pollution were more likely to develop dementia. Specifically, exposure to fine particulate matter—tiny particles that can be inhaled into the lungs and bloodstream—was associated with a 9% higher risk. Nitrogen dioxide exposure was linked to a 10% higher risk. Living near major roads, often a source of both air pollution and noise, was also tied to a 10% increase in dementia risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, people living in neighborhoods with more green and blue spaces—such as parks, forests, rivers, or lakes—had a 6% lower risk of developing dementia. These areas were also associated with slower cognitive decline. Neighborhoods with more connected street layouts and better walkability also supported cognitive health, possibly by encouraging physical activity and social engagement. Access to food stores, community centers, and healthcare services was similarly beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While these associations don’t prove direct cause and effect, they are consistent with what scientists already know about how the environment can affect the brain. Air pollution is known to cause inflammation and oxidative stress in the body, which can harm brain tissue and potentially contribute to dementia. On the other hand, green spaces may help protect the brain by reducing stress, encouraging exercise, and improving sleep—all of which are known to support cognitive health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study did have some limitations. The researchers found considerable variation across the studies they analyzed. This so-called heterogeneity reflects differences in study designs, populations, and how environmental factors were measured. Some factors, like indoor air quality or socioeconomic status, were not always taken into account, and the methods used to estimate environmental exposure may not perfectly reflect individuals’ real-life experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, the authors emphasize that their findings provide strong evidence that environmental features play a meaningful role in brain health. By focusing on studies that used objective measurements and following participants over time, the researchers were able to offer a more reliable picture than many past efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Song hopes the findings will help shape future research and public health efforts. “These numbers show that living in a dementia-friendly environment is important to delay or prevent cognitive decline and the onset of dementia,” said Suhang Song, an assistant professor at the University of Georgia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urban planning decisions—like adding parks, improving air quality, and making neighborhoods more walkable—may offer a promising path toward protecting cognitive health at the population level. Future research may focus on how to better measure these environmental exposures over time, and how they interact with genetics, lifestyle, and other personal risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1568163724004483" target="_blank"&gt;Objectively measured environmental features and their association with cognition and dementia: A systematic review and meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Linlin Da, Xia Song, Zimu Jia, Nicholas Gary Lamont Myers, Jin Sun, Jingkai Wei, Daniel Jung, Feiyang Li, and Suhang Song.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 12:02:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQUjlJRDk0cjZ4YnNaN28xbUVaRXQzdVNXQmF2cTd2VjRTdFdwQXBsSU9oQW9SUzM2TEVfQ0pUOHJrTzF4RkNtbU9zM0M1VU82V2JWempuUmxqSFBPNmxjbWRTbFU4Z2pBUGQ2RVRlWDZBZnc0b0szSXZLT3dfN2hsdFhOTXJBZ2dGdW9FaVcxZ1AteEdYRFNhMQ</guid></item><item><title>Kennedy praises cell phone bans in schools, for science-backed and tenuous reasons - NBC News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxQSElwekJlQW93eFBoZDNFNW11c01wZVJkS3VHZVVFeEl1d29jQ25iYWFmTlZnWTZkUEItRmRnazlucUljdTBWclRfZTBHMzFneTNhX2YtN1JLNnBQSDdJMWRqbXN6bWllWlpIZ3NKLS00T3ZERFAtT0lqSXJyMkdNVGFOa21EcjB5cEF2Y1B30gFWQVVfeXFMUGpjLXhJVkFyZWVJckcxWVp1VkY2WGp3OVRVWXhYQVRnSmdSN2tSNWNfV1ZlaWNuYWRPWkpFU3EzUFdwcTRDNG9VVnV6NE1zVHRTaEJQM3c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Health and Human Services secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. took aim at a new target this week as part of his “Make America Healthy Again” agenda: cell phones in schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/video/6370269070112" target="_blank"&gt;an interview with “Fox &amp;amp; Friends”&lt;/a&gt; on Thursday, Kennedy praised &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/politics/politics-news/state-lawmakers-bills-ban-cellphones-schools-rcna187309" target="_blank"&gt;cell phone restrictions in schools&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/rfk-jr-health-stances-vaccines-fluoride-raw-milk-rcna180244" target="_blank"&gt;listed health hazards&lt;/a&gt; that he said were linked to phone use among children and teens  — some backed by scientific research, others less so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy cited established links between social media use and depression and poor school performance. But he also suggested that cell phones “produce electromagnetic radiation, which has been shown to do neurological damage to kids when it’s around them all day, and to cause cellular damage and even cancer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Studies have found that excessive use of social media via smartphones can &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamapsychiatry/fullarticle/2749480" target="_blank"&gt;negatively impact teens’ mental health&lt;/a&gt;, elevating their risk of depression and anxiety. Scientists have also long understood that cell phone use in school &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11894741/" target="_blank"&gt;can lead to poor academic performance&lt;/a&gt;, including &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0747563213003993" target="_blank"&gt;lower grades&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;However, the bulk of research so far has found no association between cell phone use and cancer, nor evidence that cell phones damage DNA. Cell phones emit radio frequency radiation, which has far less energy than ionizing radiation, such as that released by medical X-rays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy’s statements follow a pattern of his, in which he mixes misinformation with scientific fact. Some of the issues he has highlighted &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/kennedy-first-month-health-secretary-vaccines-food-additives-rcna196042" target="_blank"&gt;during his first five-plus weeks in office&lt;/a&gt;, such as reducing chronic disease in children and warning of the dangers of ultraprocessed food, have broad support among the public and many scientists. But certain factors Kennedy blames for those problems and some of his proposed solutions — such as substituting &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/influencers-claim-beef-tallow-health-beauty-benefits-not-necessarily-e-rcna195206" target="_blank"&gt;beef tallow&lt;/a&gt; for seed oils in fast food — are not backed by research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;So, too, for cell phones in schools. Restricting their use is an issue leaders have embraced on both sides of the aisle. Vivek Murthy, while he was surgeon general under the Biden Administration last year, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/06/17/opinion/social-media-health-warning.html" target="_blank"&gt;called on schools to get rid of phones in the classroom&lt;/a&gt;. Nine states have already enacted such &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/mental-health/issue-brief/a-look-at-state-efforts-to-ban-cellphones-in-schools-and-implications-for-youth-mental-health/" target="_blank"&gt;bans or restrictions&lt;/a&gt;, and 15 states and Washington, D.C. have introduced legislation to do so, according to KFF, a nonprofit health think tank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“Both in red states and blue states, there’s a lot of concern about kids and cell phones, so I do think that there is bipartisan support on this,” said Annette Campbell Anderson, deputy director of the Johns Hopkins Center for Safe and Healthy Schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;However, there’s no reason to fear a cancer risk from using your cell phone at this time, said Jerrold Bushberg, a clinical professor of radiation oncology at the University of California, Davis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“There’s a lot of low-quality research in the literature that, if you wanted to collect all that and put it together, it would look very damning,” he said. “There are many activist groups out there that promote those studies and say that that’s the truth.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;An HHS spokesperson did not respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;What Kennedy says, and what studies say&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy has made repeated, unsubstantiated claims about the physical harms of cell phone use in the past, including &lt;a href="https://open.spotify.com/episode/3DQfcTY4viyXsIXQ89NXvg" target="_blank"&gt;on Joe Rogan’s podcast&lt;/a&gt; last year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;At his confirmation hearing in January, Kennedy also told Sen. Andy Kim, D-N.J., that he stood by his past statements that WiFi radiation causes cancer, saying that he had “won a case in front of the Court of Appeals against the FCC on that very issue.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The anti-vaccine group that Kennedy founded, Children’s Health Defense, challenged the Federal Communications Commission’s decision not to review its 1996 health and safety guidelines for wireless-based technologies. An appeals court &lt;a href="https://www.fcc.gov/ecfs/search/search-filings/filing/1041748778173" target="_blank"&gt;ruled in favor of the plaintiffs&lt;/a&gt; and ordered the FCC to explain how its guidelines protect against potentially harmful health effects. However, that case was about health issues unrelated to cancer, and the court did not take a position on the potential health effects of cell phone radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Research thus far has been “very reassuring” about cell phone safety, Bushberg said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Most studies have examined whether exposure to radiation from cell phones could increase the risk of brain tumors, given that people often hold their phone by their head while talking. But overall brain cancer rates haven’t risen as cell phones have become more widely used. And &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34974237/" target="_blank"&gt;a large study&lt;/a&gt; among children found no association between wireless phone use and brain tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/causes-prevention/risk/radiation/cell-phones-fact-sheet" target="_blank"&gt;National Cancer Institute&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/radiation-emitting-products/cell-phones/do-cell-phones-pose-health-hazard" target="_blank"&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/radtown/non-ionizing-radiation-wireless-technology" target="_blank"&gt;Environmental Protection Agency&lt;/a&gt; — agencies that Kennedy now oversees — have all said there’s not enough scientific evidence to associate cell phone use with cancer. However, the International Agency for Research on Cancer has classified radio frequency radiation as possibly carcinogenic, meaning it cannot rule out a causal link. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Several questions remain, said David McCormick, a biology professor at Illinois Institute of Technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“I think it’s fairly clear that Mr. Kennedy doesn’t necessarily pay much attention to the bulk of the scientific data that is out there. That said, it’s not impossible that there are health effects from people using cell phones,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29217849/" target="_blank"&gt;2017 study&lt;/a&gt;, McCormick and his fellow researchers exposed rodents to &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29217848/" target="_blank"&gt;radio frequency radiation&lt;/a&gt; and found a possible increased rate of certain tumors — however, findings in lab animals don’t necessarily apply to humans, given the many biological differences, and the studies contained limitations that prevented the researchers from drawing conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;A decade earlier, a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17636416/" target="_blank"&gt;study looked at cell phone use&lt;/a&gt; among more than 5,000 people with brain tumors and found a possible increased risk of tumors in the 10% who used their phones the most. But the research relied on people’s memories about past phone use, which aren’t always reliable, so its results (like those of similar studies) are hard to interpret.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Cell phone use has also changed in recent years, McCormick said, which could affect exposure. Whereas studies thus far have mainly looked at the effects of 2G or 3G mobile signals, higher-frequency 5G networks are common today. And people now text as much if not more than they call, so there’s potentially less radiation near the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="body-heading"&gt;The pros and cons of cell phone bans&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Despite bipartisan support for cell phone restrictions in schools, plenty of disagreement persists as to precisely what those rules should look like. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Phones can have life-saving benefits — for instance, by allowing children to call 911 — so some parents worry that outright bans could jeopardize their child’s safety. Anderson said policymakers have to weigh those concerns against risks to kids’ mental health and their ability to focus in the classroom. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“Part of what schools are trying to do is figure out how to wrest back control over what happened in their school climates because of the phone — everything from using the phone to tape fights and incidents that happen in schools to kids using them to make TikToks,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The right approach likely differs from school to school, she added — for instance, in schools where cell phones are the only internet-connected device, a ban may make less sense. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;In his interview on Thursday, Kennedy applauded Virginia Gov. Glenn Youngkin, who last year issued an executive order directing the state’s education department to &lt;a href="https://www.governor.virginia.gov/newsroom/news-releases/2024/july/name-1030522-en.html" target="_blank"&gt;draft guidance for public schools to restrict or eliminate phone use&lt;/a&gt; and set aside $500,000 to fund those efforts. Kennedy visited a Virginia high school on Monday that adopted the change, which he said students and teachers there have welcomed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“The states that are doing this have found that it is a much healthier environment when kids are not using cell phones in schools,” Kennedy said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;However, prior to becoming HHS secretary, Kennedy suggested that although he personally supports getting phones out of schools, parents and teachers should make their own decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“Do we really want the government to decide when, where, and how we communicate?” he &lt;a href="https://x.com/RobertKennedyJr/status/1710023376360632465" target="_blank"&gt;wrote on X&lt;/a&gt; in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQSElwekJlQW93eFBoZDNFNW11c01wZVJkS3VHZVVFeEl1d29jQ25iYWFmTlZnWTZkUEItRmRnazlucUljdTBWclRfZTBHMzFneTNhX2YtN1JLNnBQSDdJMWRqbXN6bWllWlpIZ3NKLS00T3ZERFAtT0lqSXJyMkdNVGFOa21EcjB5cEF2Y1B30gFWQVVfeXFMUGpjLXhJVkFyZWVJckcxWVp1VkY2WGp3OVRVWXhYQVRnSmdSN2tSNWNfV1ZlaWNuYWRPWkpFU3EzUFdwcTRDNG9VVnV6NE1zVHRTaEJQM3c</guid></item><item><title>Allergy sufferers expected to have worse season than usual: See pollen maps - USA TODAY</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxNSEIxVkh4SzRuWncxNlBBd3BieGhGUW5jTVJVbmJJUzlubTlOb0IyTjZXelktVDJlVVI4LVB4OHBKaTA3WWNWLTk1eGYzc1FZZm1FQkd6UjJNMk9CY1V6TTVRa240cl9zNzFkanNqbnplNTctNzhjY3RzSzR2MXR2SVduaURVTExzcWR6RlVuNkZuMTdFWnFsbWZfa28tdERXTEgw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;For trees and flowers, early spring might be wonderful, but for allergy sufferers, it can be awful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Springtime has arrived two weeks earlier than usual in several Midwest states this year, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.usanpn.org/data/maps/spring" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;USA National Phenology Network&lt;/a&gt; at the University of Arizona. In the mid-Atlantic and northeast regions, it arrived just over a week ahead of schedule. For those in the western U.S., depending on where you live, spring can arrive anywhere from two weeks earlier to a week later in California, Arizona, and Nevada.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://www.climate.gov/news-features/understanding-climate/us-climate-outlook-march-2025#:~:text=On%20February%2028%2C%20CPC%20released,exception%20of%20in%20the%20Northeast." data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Climate Prediction Center&lt;/a&gt;, much of the country's southern and eastern regions are expected to experience temperatures far above average, which means an increase in pollen levels due to blossoming trees. That’s bad news for people with seasonal allergies ‒ about &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db460.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;1 in 4 adults&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db459.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;1 in 5 children&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;States where spring sprang earlier than usual&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The USA National Phenology Network's map below shows the springtime leaf activity earlier than average (in red tones) and later than average (blue tones) this year:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unable to view our graphics? &lt;a href="/story/graphics/2025/03/22/allergy-season-spring-pollen-symptoms/82568198007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Click here to see them.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;According to a recent &lt;a href="https://aafa.org/asthma-allergy-research/allergy-capitals/" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; by the &lt;a href="https://aafa.org/" data-t-l=":b|z|k|${u}" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Asthma and Allergy Foundation of America&lt;/a&gt;, eight cities in California saw large increases in their allergy rankings as a result of a "grass and weed pollen explosion," which the foundation says was intensified by heavy rains that year that spurred plant growth. New Orleans also jumped considerably, going from 34th place the previous year to second in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Where are pollen counts at their highest?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;As warm spring temperatures expand throughout the United States, pollen levels are rising. Pollen counts forecasted on March 20, the first official day of spring:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Why does pollen cause allergies?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Plants, trees and grass release pollen in the springtime to fertilize other plants of the same species. The powdery particles drift in the air and are easily inhaled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In some people, inhaling pollen causes their immune systems to overreact. The immune system sees the pollen as a danger and releases antibodies that attack the allergens. This leads to the release of histamines into the blood. Histamines trigger runny noses, itchy eyes and other allergy symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;How pollen affects your body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;How to help stop the allergy symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Reducing your exposure to pollen allergens and identifying seasonal triggers might help ease your symptoms. You can do the following to decrease your reaction:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story was updated to add new information.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA TODAY</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 10:53:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNSEIxVkh4SzRuWncxNlBBd3BieGhGUW5jTVJVbmJJUzlubTlOb0IyTjZXelktVDJlVVI4LVB4OHBKaTA3WWNWLTk1eGYzc1FZZm1FQkd6UjJNMk9CY1V6TTVRa240cl9zNzFkanNqbnplNTctNzhjY3RzSzR2MXR2SVduaURVTExzcWR6RlVuNkZuMTdFWnFsbWZfa28tdERXTEgw</guid></item><item><title>Sperm may carry effects of childhood maltreatment to future generations - PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxOVlNhMG9mM0tWUDhIWFY3c19XYmt4bDRTYWtoaWZVY1lQeVhacWhfOHo3bHVVanJFYy11Smxxa0pvUzJVV0IwOFZ3LXdQcVRVemNmWmRDRDg1MnoyU0JndWNRMkNEY3ViczdIWHJial8zMkNGdXUyOWN3VWpaRU5sN2dhNFQyVkcyNEhfYjExdnJDeGM1aXFKVHViRV8?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men who experienced abuse or neglect in childhood show distinct changes in the molecular makeup of their sperm, according to new research published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41380-024-02872-3" target="_blank"&gt;Molecular Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. The study found that men with high levels of childhood maltreatment had altered patterns in small RNA molecules and DNA methylation within their sperm. These biological markers are thought to play an important role in gene regulation and development. The findings offer new clues into how early life stress may impact not only individuals themselves, but potentially their future children through a process known as epigenetic inheritance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Epigenetic inheritance refers to the passing of biological information from one generation to the next that does not involve changes to the DNA sequence itself. Instead, it involves chemical modifications—such as DNA methylation or changes in small RNA molecules—that can affect how genes are turned on or off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study was launched to explore whether childhood stress might leave a lasting biological imprint that goes beyond the person directly affected. While previous animal studies had shown that stress experienced by males early in life could change sperm and affect the behavior or health of their offspring, similar evidence in humans was still very limited. The idea that a father’s childhood experiences could be biologically encoded in his sperm and potentially passed on through epigenetic mechanisms intrigued the researchers, especially since sperm contributes half of the genetic and regulatory material at conception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their motivation was further strengthened by earlier work showing associations between paternal childhood adversity and structural changes in the brains of newborns. This finding was surprising, as it suggested a link between a father’s early life and the development of a child’s brain. That observation raised a critical question: how could a father’s early psychological stress affect a child he hasn’t yet conceived? The team hypothesized that sperm could be a potential pathway through which early experiences are transmitted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We have published a prior study that found associations between paternal childhood maltreatment exposure and neonatal brain white matter. This is striking as the fathers do not have direct influence on the developing fetus during pregnancy. This sparked my interest towards this line of research,” said study author &lt;a href="https://users.utu.fi/jjtuul/" target="_blank"&gt;Jetro J. Tuulari&lt;/a&gt;, the director of Turku Brain and Mind Center at the University of Turku.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To carry out the study, the researchers used data from the long-running &lt;a href="https://sites.utu.fi/finnbrain/en/" target="_blank"&gt;FinnBrain Birth Cohort Study&lt;/a&gt;. They focused on a group of 55 Finnish men, selecting participants based on how much childhood adversity they reported using a standardized questionnaire called the Trauma and Distress Scale. The researchers then compared two groups: one made up of men with high scores—meaning more childhood maltreatment—and one with low scores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed sperm samples from these men to investigate two key molecular features: small non-coding RNAs and DNA methylation. Small non-coding RNAs, including microRNAs and tRNA-derived fragments, help regulate gene activity and are thought to play a role in early embryonic development. DNA methylation is a chemical tag that can silence or activate genes and is also considered an important regulator during development. The team used advanced sequencing techniques to map these features across the sperm cells, ensuring high-quality data while controlling for variables such as age, smoking, alcohol use, and mental health symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They found notable differences between the two groups. Specifically, 68 small RNAs—including 29 microRNAs and 21 tRNA fragments—were expressed at different levels in the sperm of men with high childhood trauma. One of the strongest findings involved a molecule called miR-34c-5p, which was consistently lower in men with higher adversity scores. This result matched earlier studies that also found reduced levels of this RNA in men who experienced childhood stress. Notably, miR-34c-5p is involved in brain development and is passed from sperm to the embryo during fertilization, potentially influencing how the brain forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The biggest, and positive surprise was that we were able to replicate findings from a prior human study regarding one of the micro-RNA molecules. This is encouraging for future research efforts.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to small RNAs, the researchers also identified three regions of the genome that showed lower levels of DNA methylation in men who had experienced more childhood adversity. These regions were located near genes that are known to play important roles in the developing brain. One such gene, CRTC1, has been linked to mood disorders and memory. Another, GBX2, is involved in forming the neural plate and other early brain structures. The third gene, WFIKKN1, is primarily involved in muscle development, but its potential effects on offspring remain uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes these findings particularly compelling is that the epigenetic signatures remained significant even after adjusting for a range of lifestyle and health variables. This suggests that the patterns are not simply the result of poor health or lifestyle choices in adulthood, but may instead reflect long-term biological changes stemming from early life experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Different exposures like environmental toxins and stress exposure can affect the sperm epigenome. Our study found statistically robust associations between childhood maltreatment exposure and sperm epigenome, which implies that early life stress can have lasting impacts on gametes. While inheritance was not assessed in this study, our results provide basis for testing a very important question: can the epigenetic modifications cause heritable changes in humans?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the study also has limitations. Although it includes the largest human sample to date for this kind of sperm analysis, the number of participants is still relatively small. The researchers relied on self-reported data to assess childhood maltreatment, which could be affected by memory or bias. They also examined sperm samples at a single time point, so it’s unclear how stable these epigenetic markers are over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research will be needed to follow children conceived by men with and without these epigenetic markers to see if differences emerge in development. The research team hopes to expand their work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Looking into to the future, we plan to continue with the data from FinnBrain Birth Cohort study to carry similar analyses in larger sample sizes and see if we find associations to offspring outcomes. I also have high hopes to be able to establish a new cohort study building on this research.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41380-024-02872-3" target="_blank"&gt;Exposure to childhood maltreatment is associated with specific epigenetic patterns in sperm&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Jetro J. Tuulari, Matthieu Bourgery, Jo Iversen, Thomas Gade Koefoed, Annukka Ahonen, Ammar Ahmedani, Eeva-Leena Kataja, Linnea Karlsson, Romain Barrès, Hasse Karlsson, and Noora Kotaja.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 10:02:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOVlNhMG9mM0tWUDhIWFY3c19XYmt4bDRTYWtoaWZVY1lQeVhacWhfOHo3bHVVanJFYy11Smxxa0pvUzJVV0IwOFZ3LXdQcVRVemNmWmRDRDg1MnoyU0JndWNRMkNEY3ViczdIWHJial8zMkNGdXUyOWN3VWpaRU5sN2dhNFQyVkcyNEhfYjExdnJDeGM1aXFKVHViRV8</guid></item><item><title>Stoners Vastly More Likely to Have Heart Attacks At a Young Age - Futurism</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiakFVX3lxTE9BdU95ajFoWnhwNXpQOTg4QkxiQmpfUjE5R0FZWlVSTHZFQVRCYy0xdEFOcjBHZVJzTF9SSkY1STdlX1hXVFl6T1JiWWIwd2Zpc1RMa3RVcWZ5ZC1sSDJaVDN1SFRDMXNTTGc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section id="incArticle" class="post-content z-50 w-full p-3 space-y-4 bg-white border lg:-mt-6 md:p-4 md:border-gray-900 lg:ml-3 lg:w-2/3 font-b text-3"&gt;&lt;div class="space-y-4 lg:space-y-0"&gt;&lt;p class="block text-xs text-gray-500 uppercase lg:hidden font-c"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Image by Getty / Futurism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannabis use appears to be linked to a significant increase in heart attack and stroke risk for folks under 50, a new study has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the American College of Cardiology (ACC) explained in a &lt;a href="https://www.acc.org/About-ACC/Press-Releases/2025/03/17/15/35/Cannabis-Users-Face-Substantially-Higher-Risk" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;, Boston University researchers found by analyzing healthcare records for more than 4.6 million patients that those who used cannabis under 50 had a sixfold increase in heart attack risk than their non-stoner counterparts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, those who dabbled in the devil's lettuce had a four times greater risk of stroke, double the risk of heart failure, and triple the risk of dying from heart attacks or strokes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://www.jacc.org/doi/epdf/10.1016/j.jacadv.2025.101698" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; due to be published in the journal &lt;em&gt;JACC: Advances&lt;/em&gt;, Boston University clinical instructor Ibrahim Kamel and his team used data from the TriNetX health research network, a tool that allows researchers to access non-identified healthcare records from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at people under the age of 50 between the years 2010 and 2018, the team identified more than 4.6 million "relatively healthy adults" to see how their healthcare outcomes fared over the years. After narrowing it down to about 90,000 cannabis users and an equivalently sized group of non-users, the researchers found that the risks for heart attacks, stroke, and related deaths were substantially higher among the using group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the ACC's statement, Kamel suggested cannabis legalization around the United States should lead doctors to ask their patients more questions about their pot use — especially given the &lt;a href="https://masscannabiscontrol.com/health-effects/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;growing body of evidence&lt;/a&gt; that it's &lt;a href="https://www.rstreet.org/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/Final-Study-No.-253.pdf" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;not as risk-free&lt;/a&gt; as some advocates would have you think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Asking about cannabis use should be part of clinicians' workup to understand patients' overall cardiovascular risk, similar to asking about smoking cigarettes," he said. "At a policy level, a fair warning should be made so that the people who are consuming cannabis know that there are risks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, there are other factors to consider when it comes to weed, which is still &lt;a href="https://www.mpp.org/policy/federal/" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;illegal on the federal level&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We should have some caution in interpreting the findings in that cannabis consumption is usually associated with other substances such as cocaine or other illicit drugs that are not accounted for," Kamel said. "Patients should be forthcoming with their doctors and remember that we are their number one advocate and having the full story matters."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notably, the records Kamel and his team looked at also didn't differentiate between smoking pot and ingesting it in other forms, like edibles. They also didn't look at levels of cannabis use or doses — and anyone who has known true stoners can attest that there's a big difference between a &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i6Hmd7zFG9M" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;bong-ripper's choked coughing fits&lt;/a&gt; and the chilled-out bliss of those who occasionally pop indica gummies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, this link is pretty alarming — and a good reminder that weed, unfortunately, doesn't seem to be consequence-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on weed:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/scientists-weed-cognitive-decline" class="underline hover:text-neoscope hover:no-underline transition-all duration-200 ease-in-out"&gt;&lt;em&gt;If You Blazed Massive Amounts of Weed as a Youth, Scientists Have Interesting News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 10:00:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE9BdU95ajFoWnhwNXpQOTg4QkxiQmpfUjE5R0FZWlVSTHZFQVRCYy0xdEFOcjBHZVJzTF9SSkY1STdlX1hXVFl6T1JiWWIwd2Zpc1RMa3RVcWZ5ZC1sSDJaVDN1SFRDMXNTTGc</guid></item><item><title>The truth about ‘condoms for Gaza’: DOGE canceled $33 million USAID contract treating 350,000 HIV patients - Fortune</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxQeWVGYTJyOVVFOFhkSFNFQWg3T1RZcVhQdlR3bk1leFJrU200UDloWGtOMDVjaDdPZGVHbWFkMzdTVTdhNDlfSmZmYkh2dnc3bWhubXhFREJVd0E5bnhzTWxzQXBnWDNqUThjSU9CZ05OZ0FMUk15QnpYd0FuY001R0pYbloySEV3b0I0TFFjS3lkNGRPV2tucFBqempsdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fortune</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxQeWVGYTJyOVVFOFhkSFNFQWg3T1RZcVhQdlR3bk1leFJrU200UDloWGtOMDVjaDdPZGVHbWFkMzdTVTdhNDlfSmZmYkh2dnc3bWhubXhFREJVd0E5bnhzTWxzQXBnWDNqUThjSU9CZ05OZ0FMUk15QnpYd0FuY001R0pYbloySEV3b0I0TFFjS3lkNGRPV2tucFBqempsdw</guid></item><item><title>These Supplements Promise To Lower Blood Sugar And Help You Lose Weight—But Do They Work? - Women's Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwFBVV95cUxQQnZQQzJCS3BTSThNbkswZE42ZzZIREVXTE1fSkxXcnVNeU5faTVfS0xhVDhNYjl2VDhvbGZCOGRYdFJMc1V5ZWk1eUVZaHBxcE1qaDl3blMwVGZ1ZjJhMzJIeUxXZFNBaFdPblg5clBTeTRvRUthbHRjNGlLSVc4MFlSN1ZwcHV0a2NpOU94OFZFc2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-j4k1z9 et2g3wt6"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="0" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Just like &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/a46052847/taylor-swift-eras-tour-training-workouts/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/a46052847/taylor-swift-eras-tour-training-workouts/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Taylor Swift during her Eras Tour" data-node-id="0.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Taylor Swift during her Eras Tour&lt;/a&gt;, it seems like &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a62230472/natural-glp-supplement/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a62230472/natural-glp-supplement/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="weight loss supplements" data-node-id="0.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;weight loss supplements&lt;/a&gt; are everywhere right now—and that includes insulin resistance supps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="1" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Supplement companies market insulin resistance supplements to help &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a64245012/walking-blood-sugar-management-study/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a64245012/walking-blood-sugar-management-study/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="lower your blood sugar" data-node-id="1.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;lower your blood sugar&lt;/a&gt;, curb glucose spikes, support consistent energy levels, combat sugar cravings, and help you maintain a healthy weight. These supplements also claim to help lower the risk of developing &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/diabetes/overview/what-is-diabetes/prediabetes-insulin-resistance" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/diabetes/overview/what-is-diabetes/prediabetes-insulin-resistance" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="insulin resistance" data-node-id="1.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="1.3.0"&gt;insulin resistance&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a condition where your body doesn’t respond the way it should to insulin. If left unchecked, insulin resistance can lead to weight gain, prediabetes, and type 2 diabetes, per the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/diabetes/about/insulin-resistance-type-2-diabetes.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/diabetes/about/insulin-resistance-type-2-diabetes.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Centers for Disease Control and Prevention" data-node-id="1.5" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="1.5.0"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (CDC). And managing your blood glucose levels—and making sure they’re not too high—is also key for preventing any future diabetic issues, per the &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/diabetes/overview/managing-diabetes" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/diabetes/overview/managing-diabetes" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="National Institutes of Health" data-node-id="1.7" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="1.7.0"&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (NIH). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="body-tip css-13fzjfi emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="2.0"&gt;Meet the experts:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://doctors.nyp.org/rekha-b-kumar-md-ms/iris-cantor-womens-health-center" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://doctors.nyp.org/rekha-b-kumar-md-ms/iris-cantor-womens-health-center" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Rekha Kumar" data-node-id="2.2" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="2.2.0"&gt;Rekha Kumar&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is an endocrinologist at NewYork-Presbyterian Hospital Weill-Cornell School of Medicine. &lt;a href="https://rwjms.rutgers.edu/people/christoph-buettner" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://rwjms.rutgers.edu/people/christoph-buettner" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Christoph Buettner" data-node-id="2.4" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="2.4.0"&gt;Christoph Buettner&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, PhD, is the chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers University's Robert Wood Johnson Medical School. &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/mir-b-ali" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/mir-b-ali" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Mir Ali" data-node-id="2.6" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="2.6.0"&gt;Mir Ali&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, MD, is the medical director of MemorialCare Surgical Weight Loss Center at Orange Coast Medical Center in Fountain Valley, CA. &lt;a href="https://case.edu/medicine/nutrition/node/1286" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://case.edu/medicine/nutrition/node/1286" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Lindsay Malone" data-node-id="2.8" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="2.8.0"&gt;Lindsay Malone&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, RD, is an integrative and functional medicine dietitian and an instructor in the Department of Nutrition at the Case Western Reserve School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Here’s the thing: The &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/consumers/consumer-updates/fda-101-dietary-supplements" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.fda.gov/consumers/consumer-updates/fda-101-dietary-supplements" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="FDA" data-node-id="4.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="4.1.0"&gt;FDA&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; doesn’t approve dietary supplements or set categories within them, so it’s unclear what it even means to be an insulin resistance supplement. But brands are creating all sorts of supps within the category—Apothekary sells &lt;a href="https://www.apothekary.com/products/sugar-kick" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.apothekary.com/products/sugar-kick" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Sugar Kick drops" data-node-id="4.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="4.3.0"&gt;Sugar Kick drops&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Nourished has &lt;a href="https://nourishednaturalhealth.com/products/pcos-blood-sugar-balance?variant=40466492588212" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://nourishednaturalhealth.com/products/pcos-blood-sugar-balance?variant=40466492588212" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="PCOS Blood Sugar Balance" data-node-id="4.5" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="4.5.0"&gt;PCOS Blood Sugar Balance&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; supps, and Walmart has an entire online &lt;a href="https://goto.walmart.com/c/3006986/565706/9383?veh=aff&amp;amp;sourceid=imp_000011112222333344&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fc%2Fkp%2Finsulin-resistance-supplement&amp;amp;subId1=wmh&amp;amp;subId3=xid:{xid}" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.walmart.com/c/kp/insulin-resistance-supplement" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="selection" data-vars-ga-product-id="fff09b49-d3d8-4cb7-a8ef-285589af5f12" data-node-id="4.7" data-href="https://www.walmart.com/c/kp/insulin-resistance-supplement" data-product-url="https://www.walmart.com/c/kp/insulin-resistance-supplement" data-affiliate="true" data-affiliate-url="https://goto.walmart.com/c/3006986/565706/9383?veh=aff&amp;amp;sourceid=imp_000011112222333344&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fc%2Fkp%2Finsulin-resistance-supplement&amp;amp;subId1=wmh&amp;amp;subId3=xid:{xid}" data-affiliate-network='{"afflink_redirect":"/_p/afflink/syFq/walmart-robot-or-human","site_id":"6b499c58-dc46-4f93-80b3-25265395e77a","network":{"name":"Trackonomics"},"metadata":{"trackonomics":{"network_name":"ir"}},"product_metadata":{"6b499c58-dc46-4f93-80b3-25265395e77a":{"network_name":"ir","link":"https://goto.walmart.com/c/3006986/565706/9383?veh=aff&amp;amp;sourceid=imp_000011112222333344&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.walmart.com%2Fc%2Fkp%2Finsulin-resistance-supplement&amp;amp;subId1={subid}"}}}' data-vars-ga-product-price="$0.00" data-vars-ga-product-retailer-id="2ba0f0ba-e82a-4dc9-948f-22202e471b29" data-vars-ga-link-treatment="(not set) | (not set)" class="body-link product-links css-7bauu1 e1aq0z090"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="4.7.0"&gt;selection&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="5" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;So, are insulin resistance supplements legit—and safe—for lowering your blood sugar and losing weight? And what’s even in them? Ahead, experts break down how these supps work, and whether you should take them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="how-do-insulin-resistance-supplements-work" data-node-id="6" class="body-h2 css-1coetfg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="6.0"&gt;How do insulin resistance supplements work?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="7" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;In theory, an insulin resistance supplement would help support insulin sensitivity. “Insulin sensitivity can be looked at as the amount of insulin required to push sugar/carbs into cells to make energy,” explains endocrinologist Rekha Kumar, MD. “More sensitivity means it requires less insulin, and insulin resistance means it takes more insulin to turn carbs to energy.” This balance is vital for keeping healthy blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;As a result, these supplements are designed to help combat a range of health issues. “Poor insulin sensitivity—insulin resistance—can lead to high blood sugar and lipids, which increases the risk of &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a60525665/type-2-diabetes-food-list/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a60525665/type-2-diabetes-food-list/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="type 2 diabetes" data-node-id="9.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, obesity, cardiovascular disease, and fatty liver disease,” says Christoph Buettner, MD, PhD, chief of the division of endocrinology at Rutgers University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="10" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Insulin resistance supplements are a pretty broad category, so they all work in different ways. Most of them have a range of ingredients that don’t tend to overlap, although there are a few that show up repeatedly:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 data-node-id="11" class="body-h3 css-s6zph9 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="11.0"&gt;Bitter Melon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="12" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;A few small studies suggest that the fruit extract bitter melon may help with lowering blood sugar levels. One randomized controlled trial of 90 people with type 2 diabetes found that levels of HbA1c (which measures average blood sugar levels over two to three months) didn’t change between the bitter melon and placebo groups after 12 weeks, per 2020 research in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0965229920302491" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0965229920302491" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Complementary Therapies in Medicine" data-node-id="12.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="12.1.0"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="12.1.0.0"&gt;Complementary Therapies in Medicine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. However, the average fasting glucose level of people in the bitter melon group went down during the trial. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Another small trial on 76 people with prediabetes also found that bitter melon helped to lower glucose levels by suppressing levels of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK537082/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK537082/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="glucagon" data-node-id="15.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="15.1.0"&gt;glucagon&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a hormone that stimulates the liver to release stores of glucose, according to 2022 research in &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10050654/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10050654/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Food Science and Biotechnology" data-node-id="15.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="15.3.0"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="15.3.0.0"&gt;Food Science and Biotechnology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 data-node-id="16" class="body-h3 css-s6zph9 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="16.0"&gt;White Mulberry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="17" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Leaves from this tree are used in traditional Chinese medicine to treat diabetes, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/white-mulberry-leaf" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/white-mulberry-leaf" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="NIH" data-node-id="17.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="17.1.0"&gt;NIH&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. There’s some research that suggests white mulberry may lower blood glucose levels, according to a 2020 study in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0965229919317315" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0965229919317315" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Complementary Therapies in Medicine" data-node-id="17.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="17.3.0"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="17.3.0.0"&gt;Complementary Therapies in Medicine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. However, most of this research is preliminary and not conducted on humans, per the NIH, so it’s hard to draw a definitive conclusion from them.&lt;br data-node-id="17.5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="18" class="body-tip css-13fzjfi emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="18.0"&gt;Ready for resul&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="18.1"&gt;ts? &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://membership.womenshealthmag.com/womens-health-premium-membership-single.html?cds_tracking_code=whl_edit_inline_strength_transformation_prep_amy_williams_a64218691" data-sk="tooltip_parent" href="https://membership.womenshealthmag.com/womens-health-premium-membership-single.html?cds_tracking_code=whl_edit_inline_strength_transformation_prep_amy_williams_a64218691" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://membership.womenshealthmag.com/womens-health-premium-membership-single.html?cds_tracking_code=whl_edit_inline_strength_transformation_prep_amy_williams_a64218691" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Sign up for WH+ today" data-node-id="18.1.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Sign up for WH+ today&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;for exclusive meal and strength training plans only available to subscribers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 data-node-id="19" class="body-h3 css-s6zph9 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="19.0"&gt;Cinnamon&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="20" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Cinnamon or cinnamon bark pops up in a few supplements, too, and there is some (also limited) research to back this up. One 2023 meta-analysis in &lt;a href="https://dmsjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13098-023-01057-2" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://dmsjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13098-023-01057-2" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Diabetology &amp;amp; Metabolic Syndrome" data-node-id="20.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="20.1.0"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="20.1.0.0"&gt;Diabetology &amp;amp; Metabolic Syndrome&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of existing research concluded that cinnamon could be an “add-on treatment” to control blood sugar levels in people with type 2 diabetes or &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a62224378/the-impossibility-of-getting-a-pcos-diagnosis/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a62224378/the-impossibility-of-getting-a-pcos-diagnosis/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS)" data-node-id="20.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS)&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="21" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Another four-week randomized controlled trial of 18 people with prediabetes and obesity found that blood sugar levels were “significantly lower” when people had cinnamon beforehand, according to 2024 research in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S000291652400008X" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S000291652400008X" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition" data-node-id="21.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="21.1.0"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="21.1.0.0"&gt;The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The researchers concluded that cinnamon may improve blood glucose control for those with obesity-related prediabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="23" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;But none of the research on these ingredients is robust, making it tough to say for sure that the supplements do what they claim. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="so-can-insulin-resistance-supps-actually-improve-your-blood-sugar-and-help-you-lose-weight" data-node-id="24" class="body-h2 css-1coetfg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="24.0"&gt;So, can insulin resistance supps actually improve your blood sugar and help you lose weight?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="25" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Those are some pretty hefty promises, and experts are wary of them, especially because they haven’t been evaluated by the FDA. “There are no good studies or scientific evidence to show they make any dramatic difference,” in your blood sugar and weight, says Mir Ali, MD, medical director of MemorialCare Surgical Weight Loss Center at Orange Coast Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="26" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Plus, insulin sensitivity is a complicated process, and taking a supplement alone is unlikely to make a huge difference in your blood sugar and weight, adds integrative and functional medicine dietitian Lindsay Malone, RD. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="28" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;The sure-fire way to improve your blood sugar and maintain your weight? Lifestyle changes: “No supplement will work unless you do,” Malone says. “Switching to a &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a39628652/80-20-diet-low-glycemic-intermittent-fasting-weight-loss-success-story/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a39628652/80-20-diet-low-glycemic-intermittent-fasting-weight-loss-success-story/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="low-glycemic diet" data-node-id="28.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;low-glycemic diet&lt;/a&gt;, eating whole, minimally processed foods, moving your body throughout the day, and getting &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a63941290/blue-light-sleep-health-benefits-study/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a63941290/blue-light-sleep-health-benefits-study/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="adequate sleep" data-node-id="28.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;adequate sleep&lt;/a&gt; will address and fix the root cause of insulin resistance.” Reducing &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a27378711/weight-loss-success-story-simple-carbs/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/weight-loss/a27378711/weight-loss-success-story-simple-carbs/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="simple carbs" data-node-id="28.5" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;simple carbs&lt;/a&gt; like baked goods, soda, and cereal, for instance, can also help to keep your blood sugar levels stable, since your body breaks them down into glucose which could cause blood sugar spikes, Kumar says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="which-supplements-are-best-for-insulin-resistance" data-node-id="29" class="body-h2 css-1coetfg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="29.0"&gt;Which supplements are best for insulin resistance?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="30" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Experts aren’t really on board with taking these new, buzzy, multi-ingredient supplements that claim to help with insulin resistance. However, a few vitamin and mineral supplements &lt;em data-node-id="30.1"&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; have some inherent benefits for insulin resistance and even weight loss, especially in people with endocrine or hormonal disorders like &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11668966/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11668966/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="PCOS" data-node-id="30.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;PCOS&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="31" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Still, experts stress that these supplements are not magic pills. “Supplements alone are not a cure and often they do not do much,” Buettner says. But, again, with lifestyle changes like a healthy diet and regular movement, they may help support your efforts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="33" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Here’s how they work, according to Malone: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="34" class="css-9b1pbo emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="34.0"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="34.0.0"&gt;Carnitine. &lt;/strong&gt;Commonly sold as l-carnitine, this &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a60956813/amino-acid-supplements/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a60956813/amino-acid-supplements/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="amino acid" data-node-id="34.0.2" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;amino acid&lt;/a&gt; helps your body use fat for energy, which can support weight loss efforts and may improve insulin sensitivity, according to Malone. In a 2020 meta-analysis in &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32359762/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/32359762/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Clinical Nutrition ESPEN" data-node-id="34.0.4" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="34.0.4.0"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="34.0.4.0.0"&gt;Clinical Nutrition ESPEN&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of 37 randomized controlled clinical trials, l-carnitine supplementation significantly decreased body weight, but there were no major effects on waist circumference or body fat percentage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="34.1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="34.1.0"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a44638878/fish-oil-health-benefits/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a44638878/fish-oil-health-benefits/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Omega-3" data-node-id="34.1.0.0" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Omega-3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. These healthy fats can reduce inflammation and “may also improve insulin sensitivity and assist with fat loss, especially belly fat,” Malone says. One small 2022 study in &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35815739/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35815739/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Nutrición Hospitalaria" data-node-id="34.1.2" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="34.1.2.0"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="34.1.2.0.0"&gt;Nutrición Hospitalaria&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; found that omega-3 supplements “augmented” belly fat loss in overweight or obese people who were also on a weight loss diet, but more research is needed to determine whether omega-3 supplementation is effective for weight loss. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="34.2"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="34.2.0"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a40120300/vitamin-d-benefits/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a40120300/vitamin-d-benefits/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Vitamin D" data-node-id="34.2.0.0" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Vitamin D&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. “Low vitamin D levels are linked to insulin resistance, so supplementing with vitamin D can help improve sensitivity and potentially support weight loss,” Malone says. There’s a link between taking vitamin D and weight loss, as part of a larger treatment plan like a changed diet, per a 2018 study in &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30246883/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30246883/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Clinical Endocrinology" data-node-id="34.2.2" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="34.2.2.0"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="34.2.2.0.0"&gt;Clinical Endocrinology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and 2021 study in the &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/07315724.2021.1902879" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/07315724.2021.1902879" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Journal of the American Nutrition Association" data-node-id="34.2.4" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="34.2.4.0"&gt;&lt;u data-node-id="34.2.4.0.0"&gt;Journal of the American Nutrition Association&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div data-embed="embed-gallery" data-lazy-id="P0-19" data-node-id="35" class="embed css-0 e1ghppmw15"&gt;&lt;div class="css-vniqbw e1ghppmw12"&gt;&lt;div class="css-tiqbpf e1ghppmw14"&gt;&lt;div class="css-1bdrxq9 e1ghppmw10"&gt;&lt;div data-ad-exclude="(min-width: 90rem)" data-embed="embed-product" size="large" class="size-large align-center embed css-me9690 e1ydkxnk0"&gt;&lt;p id="product-c1001804-6205-4189-ae3c-f515120baa5e" data-anchor-id="product-c1001804-6205-4189-ae3c-f515120baa5e" class="css-17pp2fn e1ydkxnk1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div size="large" class="align-center css-0 ebgq4gw4"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-theme-key="base-link" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B005P0UYGA?tag=womenshealth-auto-20" aria-label="$27 at Amazon for Acetyl-L-Carnitine" data-href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B005P0UYGA" data-product-url="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B005P0UYGA" data-affiliate="true" data-affiliate-url="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B005P0UYGA?tag=womenshealth-auto-20" data-affiliate-network='{"site_id":"6b499c58-dc46-4f93-80b3-25265395e77a","metadata":{"links":{"default":"https://www.amazon.com/dp/B005P0UYGA?tag=womenshealth-auto-20","sem":"https://www.amazon.com/dp/B005P0UYGA?tag=wh-lift-20","social":"https://www.amazon.com/dp/B005P0UYGA?tag=wh-soc-lift-20"}},"network":{"name":"Amazon"},"product_metadata":null,"afflink_redirect":"/_p/afflink/syJb/amazon-thorne-acetyl-l-carnitine-mg"}' data-vars-ga-call-to-action="$27 at Amazon" data-vars-ga-media-role="1" data-vars-ga-media-type="Embedded Gallery List" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B005P0UYGA" data-vars-ga-product-brand="THORNE" data-vars-ga-product-id="c1001804-6205-4189-ae3c-f515120baa5e" data-vars-ga-product-price="$27.00" data-vars-ga-product-retailer-id="afd5c634-bca7-45d8-8605-b21cb8ab7804" data-vars-ga-product-sem3-brand="THORNE" data-vars-ga-product-sem3-category="Acetyl-L-Carnitine Nutritional Supplements" data-vars-ga-link-treatment="sale | (not set)" data-vars-ga-sku="B005P0UYGA" data-vars-ga-magento-tracking="1" class="product-image-link ebgq4gw0 e1b8bpvs0 css-g6od0w e1c1bym14"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div class="css-1kpik7c ebgq4gw3"&gt;&lt;div size="large" class="css-19is6rd ebgq4gw1"&gt;&lt;h6 class="css-wziefo e1bddzxd0"&gt;THORNE Acetyl-L-Carnitine&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;p class="css-12k1hqd e1uq555e0"&gt;Now 10% Off&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption data-theme-key="photo-credit-figcaption-embedded-gallery" class="css-1am3yn9 e1g9hcy40"&gt;&lt;span data-theme-key="photo-credit-creditor" class="css-1xs3or1 e1geg53v2"&gt;Credit: Courtesy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-tiqbpf e1ghppmw14"&gt;&lt;div class="css-1bdrxq9 e1ghppmw10"&gt;&lt;div data-ad-exclude="(min-width: 90rem)" data-embed="embed-product" size="large" class="size-large align-center embed css-me9690 e1ydkxnk0"&gt;&lt;p id="product-c491063a-076f-46d7-b755-bc2edff33241" data-anchor-id="product-c491063a-076f-46d7-b755-bc2edff33241" class="css-17pp2fn e1ydkxnk1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div size="large" class="align-center css-0 ebgq4gw4"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-theme-key="base-link" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001GCU6KA?tag=womenshealth-auto-20" aria-label="$12 at Amazon for Omega-3" data-href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001GCU6KA" data-product-url="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001GCU6KA" data-affiliate="true" data-affiliate-url="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001GCU6KA?tag=womenshealth-auto-20" data-affiliate-network='{"site_id":"6b499c58-dc46-4f93-80b3-25265395e77a","metadata":{"links":{"default":"https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001GCU6KA?tag=womenshealth-auto-20","sem":"https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001GCU6KA?tag=wh-lift-20","social":"https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001GCU6KA?tag=wh-soc-lift-20"}},"network":{"name":"Amazon"},"product_metadata":null,"afflink_redirect":"/_p/afflink/syJW/amazon-now-supplements-omega-3-180-epa"}' data-vars-ga-call-to-action="$12 at Amazon" data-vars-ga-media-role="1" data-vars-ga-media-type="Embedded Gallery List" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B001GCU6KA" data-vars-ga-product-brand="NOW" data-vars-ga-product-id="c491063a-076f-46d7-b755-bc2edff33241" data-vars-ga-product-price="$12.29" data-vars-ga-product-retailer-id="fad0dfaa-c01e-44ef-adc6-32bebbf22da4" data-vars-ga-product-sem3-brand="NOW" data-vars-ga-link-treatment="sale | On Sale" data-vars-ga-sku="B001GCU6KA" data-vars-ga-magento-tracking="1" class="product-image-link ebgq4gw0 e1b8bpvs0 css-g6od0w e1c1bym14"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div class="css-1kpik7c ebgq4gw3"&gt;&lt;div size="large" class="css-19is6rd ebgq4gw1"&gt;&lt;h6 class="css-wziefo e1bddzxd0"&gt;NOW Omega-3&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;p class="css-12k1hqd e1uq555e0"&gt;Now 39% Off&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption data-theme-key="photo-credit-figcaption-embedded-gallery" class="css-1am3yn9 e1g9hcy40"&gt;&lt;span data-theme-key="photo-credit-creditor" class="css-1xs3or1 e1geg53v2"&gt;Credit: Courtesy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-tiqbpf e1ghppmw14"&gt;&lt;div class="css-1bdrxq9 e1ghppmw10"&gt;&lt;div data-ad-exclude="(min-width: 90rem)" data-embed="embed-product" size="large" class="size-large align-center embed css-me9690 e1ydkxnk0"&gt;&lt;p id="product-1d71407a-d94d-4c0b-af59-2f40ea9888e5" data-anchor-id="product-1d71407a-d94d-4c0b-af59-2f40ea9888e5" class="css-17pp2fn e1ydkxnk1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div size="large" class="align-center css-0 ebgq4gw4"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener" data-theme-key="base-link" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004U3Y8OM?tag=womenshealth-auto-20" aria-label="$10 at Amazon for Vitamin D3" data-href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004U3Y8OM" data-product-url="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004U3Y8OM" data-affiliate="true" data-affiliate-url="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004U3Y8OM?tag=womenshealth-auto-20" data-affiliate-network='{"site_id":"6b499c58-dc46-4f93-80b3-25265395e77a","metadata":{"links":{"default":"https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004U3Y8OM?tag=womenshealth-auto-20","sem":"https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004U3Y8OM?tag=wh-lift-20","social":"https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004U3Y8OM?tag=wh-soc-lift-20"}},"network":{"name":"Amazon"},"product_metadata":null,"afflink_redirect":"/_p/afflink/syIN/amazon-nature-made-vitamin-d3-0"}' data-vars-ga-call-to-action="$10 at Amazon" data-vars-ga-media-role="1" data-vars-ga-media-type="Embedded Gallery List" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B004U3Y8OM" data-vars-ga-product-brand="Nature Made" data-vars-ga-product-id="1d71407a-d94d-4c0b-af59-2f40ea9888e5" data-vars-ga-product-price="$10.22" data-vars-ga-product-retailer-id="339ecd52-fe7a-4daf-9d35-dce323272f04" data-vars-ga-product-sem3-brand="Nature Made" data-vars-ga-link-treatment="sale | On Sale" data-vars-ga-sku="B004U3Y8OM" data-vars-ga-magento-tracking="1" class="product-image-link ebgq4gw0 e1b8bpvs0 css-g6od0w e1c1bym14"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div class="css-1kpik7c ebgq4gw3"&gt;&lt;div size="large" class="css-19is6rd ebgq4gw1"&gt;&lt;h6 class="css-wziefo e1bddzxd0"&gt;Nature Made Vitamin D3&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;p class="css-12k1hqd e1uq555e0"&gt;Now 47% Off&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figcaption data-theme-key="photo-credit-figcaption-embedded-gallery" class="css-1am3yn9 e1g9hcy40"&gt;&lt;span data-theme-key="photo-credit-creditor" class="css-1xs3or1 e1geg53v2"&gt;Credit: Courtesy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="36" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;If you’re concerned about insulin resistance, it’s best to talk to a healthcare provider. (And if you have severe insulin resistance, like you’re prediabetic or you have type 2 diabetes, Kumar says you may benefit from prescription medication like metformin or a &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a63788221/glp1-alcohol-use-disorder-clinical-trial-results/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a63788221/glp1-alcohol-use-disorder-clinical-trial-results/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="GLP-1 receptor" data-node-id="36.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;GLP-1 receptor&lt;/a&gt; agonist like &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/a62777117/running-while-on-ozempic/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/fitness/a62777117/running-while-on-ozempic/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Ozempic" data-node-id="36.3" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="37" class="css-auya5i emevuu60"&gt;Your doc can do an evaluation to see where things stand with your blood sugar levels, including testing to see if you have prediabetes or diabetes. From there, you can come up with a care plan together. So, while the idea of taking an insulin resistance supplement and hoping things will turn around is easy and appealing, it’s always best to rope in a medical professional for extra help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-journey-blur="partial" data-ad-exclude="true" class="css-19m4yzp e1jy25xv0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-sfzxfp ev8dhu59"&gt;&lt;span class="css-3mrz81 ev8dhu51"&gt;&lt;img src="https://hips.hearstapps.com/rover/profile_photos/ea27d1a6-ecd9-4da8-b2a7-049a03b4ab93_1528214135.file?fill=1:1&amp;amp;resize=120:*" alt="Headshot of Korin Miller" title="Headshot of Korin Miller" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="css-o0wq4v ev8dhu53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dsojn8 ev8dhu55"&gt;&lt;p class="css-19s3ilq ev8dhu54"&gt;Korin Miller is a freelance writer specializing in general wellness, sexual health and relationships, and lifestyle trends, with work appearing in Men’s Health, Women’s Health, Self, Glamour, and more. She has a master’s degree from American University, lives by the beach, and hopes to own a teacup pig and taco truck one day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Women's Health</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQQnZQQzJCS3BTSThNbkswZE42ZzZIREVXTE1fSkxXcnVNeU5faTVfS0xhVDhNYjl2VDhvbGZCOGRYdFJMc1V5ZWk1eUVZaHBxcE1qaDl3blMwVGZ1ZjJhMzJIeUxXZFNBaFdPblg5clBTeTRvRUthbHRjNGlLSVc4MFlSN1ZwcHV0a2NpOU94OFZFc2c</guid></item></channel></rss>