<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>完美的早晨例行公事：如何建立一个快乐、健康的一天开始--从淋浴到阳光明媚--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/26/perfect-morning-routine-happy-healthy-start-showers-sunshine</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;he first thing to say about the ideal morning routine is that it probably doesn’t exist. Yes, endless influencers promise that they have tweaked, tested and fine-tuned the process of revving up for the day, but how history’s most productive people &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; get things done is so varied that it’s hard to draw definitive conclusions. Beethoven, reportedly, used to count out exactly 60 beans for his morning cup of coffee, while Victor Hugo downed two raw eggs after reading a daily missive from his mistress. Mark Wahlberg, on the other hand, wakes at &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/Ej-o9ooFqcQ" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;3am&lt;/a&gt; for pre-workout prayer, chasing up his gym time with a few holes of golf and a jolt in the cryo chamber before he even thinks about doing any work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It is clear, though, that having some sort of routine is key: a set of automatic actions that you do every day, to ease you into your responsibilities with a bit of momentum and a fresh frame of mind. And there is some stuff that seems beneficial enough that everyone should be doing a version of it, even if individual methods differ: one person’s meditative bean arithmetic, after all, is another’s mindfulness. But if you want to finesse your routine, the key is to add one change at a time. &lt;strong&gt;“&lt;/strong&gt;When you focus on a single behaviour,” says the behaviour change specialist Dr Heather McKee, “you build confidence through quick wins, and give your brain the clarity and dopamine hit it needs to automate that action. Once that habit feels natural, you free up mental space to layer in the next change.” But what habits should you be building?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="5b7d789a-a77e-4871-acb8-11ba2837fc53" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Dogs are the perfect excuse to get a dose of morning light.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; Olga Rolenko/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="get-up-get-out" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get up, get out&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;First things first: there’s no single best time to get up. If you have the luxury of picking your own window, it’s probably best to start by roughly working out your chronotype, which boils down to if you feel and perform best earlier in the day, you can probably get away with getting up a bit earlier (if you do your best work at night, of course, it would be ideal to sleep in).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Most adults need between seven and nine hours’ sleep to feel fully functional, and you probably have a good idea of where you fall in that range. In an ideal world, you shouldn’t need an alarm to wake up: if that means going to bed at 10 so you’re feeling fresh by 6am, that’s the way forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ellie Hambly, a clinical psychologist specialising in helping families deal with stress, advises getting outside in the morning light. “This is getting harder with daylight hours reducing, but trying to manage your diary around getting some daylight can make a huge difference in your mood.” Morning exposure to natural sunlight plays a key role in keeping our body clock working properly. It suppresses melatonin, boosts serotonin, gets you ready for the day – and &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39077837/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;seems to help people sleep better&lt;/a&gt; at night. If you have a dog or a running habit, great – but it’s even worth poking your head out of the door while you enjoy your morning coffee. “If you can make the time for a short walk without your phone in the morning, the combination of movement and lack of stimulation can help to activate your brain’s default mode network – the set of brain regions engaged in introspection and daydreaming,” says Hambly. “That can help with creative problem-solving and coming up with new ideas. If you don’t have time for a walk, even taking a shower without a podcast can work.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="efb00c4b-f635-4ec5-836e-3364af22114f" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Getting outside in the morning light can make a huge difference.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; Brook Pifer/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="put-the-kettle-on" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Put the kettle on&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Recently, it’s become fashionable among self-optimisers to claim that you should wait 60-90 minutes to drink your first coffee to avoid an afternoon crash. This sounds plausible, but a &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/10.1080/15502783.2024.2323919?url_ver=Z39.88-2003&amp;amp;rfr_id=ori:rid:crossref.org&amp;amp;rfr_dat=cr_pub%20%200pubmed" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;review of studies&lt;/a&gt; published in 2024 concluded that there’s no evidence this happens – and caffeine has also been shown to increase exercise performance in a variety of ways, so it’s definitely worth having a coffee if you’re going to work out (giving it 20-30 minutes to let the effects kick in). Otherwise, just do what’s most comfortable for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="08c288e0-01f8-4543-a6b5-913030a24ad4" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Go with your natural flow.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by models; Thomas Barwick/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Should you exercise first thing? If you can face it, yes: at least a bit. The best time of day to hit the gym seems to vary depending on your chronotype, specific goals and preferred workout style: morning exercise, for instance, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26844280/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;can help with burning fat&lt;/a&gt;, and strength-building sessions are also &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27863207/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;probably slightly better&lt;/a&gt; if your aim is muscle. But it’s possible that you can “retrain” your body to work out more effectively at different times of day by doing it consistently (&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25631930/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;one study on swimmers&lt;/a&gt; found that both chronotype and habitual training time are important). However, morning workouts seem to have a host of benefits all of their own, from &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40419564/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;reducing body fat to improving sleep&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;On a more basic note, it’s also just easier to ensure you get your workouts done if you schedule them first thing, with no chance of a random pub invite or work demand getting in the way. If you can’t face a full-on run or dragging the dumbbells out from under the bed, it helps to have a pre-set, full-body routine that’s simple enough to do in your living room while everyone else dashes around eating toast and doing last-minute homework. The “slow” burpee is a winner here: squat down low, put your hands on the floor (between your feet if you can), then step one foot back at a time until you’re in a plank position. Do a press-up if you’ve got it in you, then reverse the whole process to come back to your feet: a handful of these will hit your arms, legs and core while also helping you stretch out stiff joints. Start with five, and work your way up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Read a line of poetry, sip your tea, write a quick reflection, or get through a couple of pages of a book&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;h2 id="cold-comforts" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Cold comforts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;How cold should your morning shower be? Again, this depends on what you’re going for. There is some evidence that hosing yourself down with frosty water in the morning can offer physiological benefits: cold exposure can trigger the release of endorphins and help your parasympathetic nervous system (the restful one) kick in, so even if it doesn’t feel like it in the moment, it’s probably cheering you up. On the flipside, a cold shock is potentially going to jolt you out of any default mode network thinking that’s helping you to solve problems or think creatively. But there’s a best-of-both-worlds approach. “I recommend to my coaching clients that they introduce hot and cold cycling as part of their morning routine for both the physical and mental benefits,” says the wellness expert Tana Hoffman Cook. “For people who are just starting out, even ending your shower with a cold blast can offer health benefits – cold exposure has been linked to increased dopamine levels, making it a powerful addition to anyone’s morning routine when they want to start their day feeling alert, clear-headed and with a mood-boost.”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:16,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:6060,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;how-to-have-a-better-day&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Sign up to our 16-part series and get expert advice on how to improve your life - from morning to night&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;How to have a better day&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Twice weekly, for eight weeks&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;You're signed up to How to have a better day.&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;features&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="b6aa2ace-6a53-45b2-b357-9a1d8b1dd80f" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Judgment-free scribbles can boost physical and psychological health.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; Luis Alvarez/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="scribble-it-out" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Scribble it out&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;What about journalling, which is frequently recommended? A 2018 &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/advances-in-psychiatric-treatment/article/emotional-and-physical-health-benefits-of-expressive-writing/ED2976A61F5DE56B46F07A1CE9EA9F9F" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;review of studies&lt;/a&gt; found that writing about stressful or emotional events for a few minutes resulted in improvements in physical and psychological health in non-clinical and clinical populations. “Morning pages”, as they’re sometimes known, can work as a sort of lower-stakes version of that: aiming to fill a page or two with judgment-free scribble (that you’re definitely allowed to throw away afterwards) might help you reorganise your thoughts before you go about your day, or at least get your biggest worries down on paper. If you’re struggling to get anything out, use a prompt as an easy starting point: “What’s the biggest thing I’m worried about?” or “What’s one thing I want to focus on today?” Or you could be more specific with something like: “How am I actually going to get this project done on time?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="mindfulness-on-the-go" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;Mindfulness on the go&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure id="b6ea70a8-6560-4841-8ee3-bcf0f350683e" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Meditation can be alternated with breathing techniques.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Posed by model; pixdeluxe/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As for meditation, the benefits are &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10355843/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;well established&lt;/a&gt; – they range from reduced anxiety to a boosted immune system – but if your mornings are too chaotic to sit in a quiet space (or plug into an app for 10 minutes), it might be worth starting with something a bit simpler. “I use something called the Ease morning routine to start the day with nervous system regulation rather than jumping straight into hustle mode,” says the wellbeing coach and yoga teacher Chloe Markham. “We begin with an Exhale, or stillness. If I don’t have time to meditate, I’ll use the 4-7-8 breathing technique: breathe in gently through your nose for a count of four, hold for seven, and breathe out through your mouth for eight. Next, we Anchor – this is where we clock in with the way our body feels and maybe set a soft intention for the day.” Spend a second listening to your body, she suggests, and maybe change your goals accordingly. “If you’re feeling energised, great! If not, maybe scale things back a bit. The next step is movement, or Shift – this is about moving our bodies in ways that feel good – and the final step is to Engage in something nourishing: read a line of poetry, sip your tea, write a quick reflection or get through a couple of pages of a book.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;You could try to sneak in a bit of mindfulness while you do the washing-up&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Whether it takes five minutes or 95, she says, “this sort of routine cannot only prepare us for a calmer day, but also can strengthen our nervous system’s ability to self-regulate more quickly. The magic comes from consistency rather than perfection.” And if all that takes too much time, you could try to sneak in a bit of mindfulness while you do the washing-up: in &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s12671-014-0360-9" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;one paper from Florida State University&lt;/a&gt;, a group of volunteers who read a text that encouraged them to focus their thoughts on the sensations evoked by the activity they were doing reported increases in elements of “positive affect” (such as inspiration) and decreased nervousness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“You don’t need a 5am wake-up call or a one-hour ritual to have a ‘good’ morning,” says the yoga teacher Maysun Hassanaly. “What matters is consistency. Think small daily doses of feelgood moments to lift your mood, that are useful and doable. Think of your mornings in three layers: must-do, nice-to-have and optional. On busy days, stick to your must-dos: the simple actions that ground you or energise you. On slower mornings, add a nice-to-have or two. It could be something as small as putting on your favourite song and having a quick dance, walking one extra bus stop, or taking a moment to notice the morning light. Tiny rituals like these help you feel calmer and in control of your day, without sacrificing sleep or overloading your to-do list.” You can’t micromanage everything that’s going to happen for the rest of the day, or everything that’s going on in the world – so for 10 minutes after you wake up, why not just be a bit nicer to yourself?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQc1BuYWVYc29TaEM1RWQtLW5BSHJOMEZnVjhPNjlMTjFIU1lnYVBHTjhoYV9mWHhiLUt6MVVIQ3ZXMks4R2lVZnh1Vmx5aV9DeWlCdUtqYlJ3eG14dTkyU0pZSy1RQ3hvOWZESkhLaHNqZjBfSTVJWEVxVWdKZmRLWXFvRjhVZ3dsV01tRnhVdXd3RUMxeEduUnoybm15b01DUmVxQU1kRGVkSzJnN3E1elphdw</guid></item><item><title>Ozempic时代的婚姻和性：更新-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/26/podcasts/the-daily/sex-ozempic-update.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:52:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNNFpPWkVZQWZZVWpCYk9OMWZMYkpwWFh2UXNEVlBmMHNadVQ1Z3ZUcnFkOFRsZDZDM096a1BFWkFob3djbWhnT3pZQmlXMVdQZW4yUGltR2VLWmdyMDRKb2w1NHdya3hkbnNYR21Tc1N4Zmxlbi1Oc3BRQVYzTDhTMUZ3MA</guid></item><item><title>骑自行车会导致勃起功能障碍吗？一位泌尿科医生解释说- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/26/health/cycling-prostate-erectile-dysfunction-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmj3h9jsn000e3b6povrpcc29@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Dr. Jamin Brahmbhatt is a urologist and robotic surgeon with Orlando Health and an assistant professor at the University of Central Florida’s College of Medicine.
&lt;/p&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmj3h58vf001z29oyhrfcbbw0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            During the pandemic, I did what many other people did: I bought a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2020/08/17/health/biking-workout-exercise-routine-benefits-wellness"&gt;stationary bike&lt;/a&gt;. I joined the group rides, pushed through the resistance and pedaled my way to better health. A few weeks in, I started noticing something I didn’t expect — a subtle, intermittent pressure near my prostate that lingered throughout the day.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00023b6p8fpa1smu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As a urologist, knowing what those sensations can sometimes signal only made me more anxious.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00033b6pni52f9yl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Was the bike irritating something important? Was this the start of chronic prostate pain or even trouble in the bedroom? The worry built up enough that I stopped riding and eventually sold the bike. That fear is something I hear from patients all the time: Is biking causing my prostate issues or erection problems? The science-based answer is that it probably does not.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00043b6pugzn6mc9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In my case — and in many others — the problem wasn’t &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2Fcnn-underscored%2Fhealth-fitness%2Fcycling-essentials-for-beginners%3Futm_source%3Dinternal%26utm_medium%3Dmainsite%26utm_id%3Dfeatures&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CLee.Smith1%40wbdcontractor.com%7C2e857a36a8ae4a64130808de3cea8f07%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639015175304342729%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=4l4VcSXKk%2FRssVnOkxYJA4%2FjRB5K0vncvjOJBNiCwxw%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;the bike or the exercise&lt;/a&gt;. It was my form and my mind.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00053b6ph6iw5t94@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The prostate sits just below the bladder and wraps around the urethra. It is located deep in the pelvis, directly above the perineum (the soft area between the scrotum and anus). Anything that irritates that region, including pressure, tight muscles or prolonged sitting, can create sensations that men interpret as “prostate pain.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00063b6pk3wkh40z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Cycling concentrates your body weight on the perineum, where the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/22000-pudendal-nerve" target="_blank"&gt;pudendal nerve&lt;/a&gt;, key blood vessels and the pelvic floor muscles all travel. The major nerves that support erections also run along the outer surface of the prostate, which is why irritation in the surrounding tissues can feel like a prostate or sexual function problem, even when the gland itself is normal.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00073b6p8epdpqic@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A narrow or traditional bike saddle can press on these sensitive areas for long periods, creating burning, pressure or a bruised feeling. That discomfort is real, but it isn’t the prostate or surrounding nerves themselves being damaged. Cycling affects the tissues around the gland — not the gland itself. This mirrors what the latest &lt;a href="https://www.auanet.org/guidelines-and-quality/guidelines/male-chronic-pelvic-pain" target="_blank"&gt;American Urological Association guidelines&lt;/a&gt; note: Perineal pressure and prolonged sitting are known triggers for pelvic and scrotal pain, not true prostate injury.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00083b6paw4uyvss@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/prostatitis/symptoms-causes/syc-20355766" target="_blank"&gt;Prostatitis&lt;/a&gt; is one of the most commonly misunderstood diagnoses in my field. The severe bacterial form — the one that causes fever, chills and intense urinary symptoms — is rare. Much more often, men are told they have prostatitis, even though there is no infection. Their symptoms come from irritated or tight pelvic floor muscles, nerve hypersensitivity, stress or prolonged sitting — problems that don’t show up on urine tests or cultures. Tenderness in these muscles is found in a significant number of men with pelvic pain, which helps explain why the symptoms can feel so similar to prostate inflammation.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos00093b6pmcktud1t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Cycling can aggravate these muscles for some riders, especially if they stay seated the entire ride or are new to the activity. The discomfort that follows can feel identical to true prostate inflammation, even though the prostate itself is normal.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000a3b6p2vfq0key@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The fear of erectile dysfunction often appears the moment men feel pressure or numbness in the pelvic region after a ride. Older research studies raised concerns that cycling might reduce blood flow to the penis. Those early studies made headlines, and many men still assume there is a direct link between biking and erectile dysfunction — but that’s not necessarily true.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000b3b6pojc8o0lc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29031767/" target="_blank"&gt;More recent research&lt;/a&gt; shows that regular cycling does not increase the long-term risk of erectile dysfunction. In fact, many cyclists report better sexual function than those who don’t ride, mainly because cycling or any exercise can improve heart and vascular health. Temporary numbness or tingling after a long or intense ride can happen, but it typically resolves quickly once pressure is relieved.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000c3b6pvo7hmjpl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Erections depend on healthy blood vessels, well-functioning nerves and balanced hormones working together with psychological factors such as stress and arousal. Chronic conditions such as diabetes, high blood pressure, high cholesterol and heart disease are among the most common contributors to erectile dysfunction because they reduce blood flow to the penis. Smoking, inactivity, obesity, stress and certain medications also play major roles in the quality of erections.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000d3b6pv2fewvdk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Testosterone affects libido and energy but is rarely the sole cause of erectile dysfunction. The latter is usually a whole-body issue, not a cycling problem. And as mentioned earlier, the cardiovascular benefits of cycling often help erectile function rather than harm it.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000e3b6p8yw7c1n6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Even if cycling doesn’t cause permanent harm, it can still leave riders with temporary sensations during or after a ride. These feelings come from how your body meets the saddle — the amount of time you stay seated, your posture and how conditioned your pelvic muscles are for supporting pressure in that position.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000f3b6piph5xxxk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            How you ride also matters. Stationary bikes often keep you in one position for extended periods, especially during high-resistance climbs, which can increase pelvic pressure. That’s different than outdoor cycling, which naturally shifts your weight — you stand to pedal, adjust during climbs and descents, and move more freely — giving the pelvic muscles brief breaks. Electric bikes assist during harder efforts and may limit how far forward you lean, but they still depend on proper saddle fit and posture.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000g3b6phztuwa67@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Factors such as saddle shape, handlebar height and uninterrupted time in the seat determine how much pressure the pelvis absorbs. New riders tend to notice these sensations more simply because their bodies haven’t yet adapted to longer periods in the saddle.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000h3b6pljpk88ya@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some men may notice pelvic symptoms more than others. Riders with a history of lower back problems, hip tightness, chronic stress, anxiety or previous pelvic pain often have more sensitive pelvic floor muscles to begin with. Men with desk jobs who sit for long hours may also feel saddle pressure more intensely when they first start cycling. These symptoms don’t mean harm is being done — but they do mean your body may need more attention to bike fit, posture and gradual mileage.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000i3b6pbcs7ggp3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Most cycling-related discomfort improves with adjustments rather than stopping the activity. Saddles with center cutouts or split designs reduce pressure on sensitive areas, and small changes in seat height, tilt or handlebar position can shift weight away from the perineum.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjjblzeg00043b6p3ymick11@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Briefly standing every 10 to 15 minutes, wearing padded shorts and building mileage gradually can also help.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000j3b6pr48su20c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            If symptoms persist, pelvic floor physical therapy is one of the strongest evidence-backed treatments available. The goal isn’t to stop cycling — it’s to ride in a way that supports comfort, protects the surrounding tissues and allows your body to adapt safely over time.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000k3b6p4uqnp7ij@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Persistent numbness, discomfort lasting hours or days after cycling, painful erections or new urinary changes should be evaluated. These symptoms are usually treatable and do not imply permanent injury.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjjbmb1200063b6pfe8n1mq0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Equipment adjustments, a short break from riding or targeted therapy often resolve the issue.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjjbmjis00083b6ptv8ylt8r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Persistent symptoms shouldn’t be ignored, but they also shouldn’t trigger panic. Most riders improve with straightforward changes.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000l3b6pyj842rfi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Cycling did not damage my prostate or affect my sexual health — but the sensations I felt were real, and the fear is something I hear from men every week. Understanding how saddle pressure interacts with the pelvic floor and nerves can help you ride more comfortably and interpret new sensations without assuming the worst.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000m3b6pkmrdev2h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Looking back, I probably didn’t need to sell my bike. What I needed was a better seat, a few adjustments and a reminder not to panic the moment something in my pelvis felt different.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000n3b6ptxfoopda@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            I know many men react the same way I did — with fear first, facts later. You don’t have to. With the right setup and a little awareness, cycling can stay part of your routine without putting your prostate or sexual health at risk.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmja53tos000o3b6pok17pib2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And this isn’t just about cycling. Any new exercise will come with an adjustment period, and it’s normal to feel unfamiliar aches as your body adapts. A little preparation, good form and asking for help when you need it can keep you moving safely.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmj3hq4sq00173b6p3s4u3cmn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Get inspired by a weekly roundup on living well, made simple. Sign up for &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/newsletters/life-but-better?source=nl-acq_article"&gt;CNN’s Life, But Better newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for information and tools designed to improve your well-being.
&lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:00:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQOWFXTUI0ek9waThYUGcwMzlxQjNkNU43bExCRXJHcnN0TVJYMDBfeERIYnBZTnZKMFpWbDhEdHh6LTdtLXNDQ1IydEU3b2JHTGpzb1RReWx5bVF2aXNIcmNBV2Y2Q0YtYlNPR2FKS1p3eS1PcmpBWjhzQV9wd3lUUjdHVnV5S1AzeWVncg</guid></item><item><title>昨晚吃了太多糖？以下是营养师今天建议您做的事情- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/what-to-do-if-you-ate-too-much-sugar-last-night-11863856</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Don’t restrict or cleanse—just return to your usual balanced meals and routine.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Start the next day with a protein- and fiber-rich breakfast to steady blood sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hydrate, move your body and practice self-kindness to break the binge-restrict cycle.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So you ate an entire pint of ice cream while streaming Netflix. Or maybe you ate more dessert than felt comfortable at a family gathering. We’ve all been there. But then the inevitable happens. You wake up the next morning feeling not so great and maybe a little anxious and guilty. And you’re wondering what to do next.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While you may have the overwhelming urge to restrict calories, cut out carbs or resort to an expensive cleanse, dietitians recommend you let it go and get back into your regular routine. There is no need to take any extreme measures.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-first-thing-you-should-do"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; The First Thing You Should Do &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You might think the best way to recover from a sugar-filled night is to double down on rigid food rules. But with that approach, you can really get caught in a vicious cycle. Instead, let it go and get back to your regularly scheduled programming!
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Resist the urge to “undo” the sugar with more restriction, says &lt;a href="https://revvhealth.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Marissa Beck, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. “Get back into a routine with ample self-care, tune into hunger and fullness cues, and aim for regular meals and snacks that include all macronutrients,” she says.&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;If you focus on balance and nourishing your body, you can get on with the show in a way that supports your physical and mental health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What’s the first step you should take? Start your day with a nourishing protein- and fiber-rich breakfast to set the tone. While you might think &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-skip-breakfast-8417958" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;skipping breakfast&lt;/a&gt; is a good way to make up for the sugar you ate the night before, the opposite is true. Eating a nutrient-dense breakfast that’s rich in protein and fiber supports &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/simple-ways-to-keep-blood-sugar-in-check-11791785" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;balanced blood sugar&lt;/a&gt; and will keep you feeling energized and ready to take on the day. It can also prevent cravings and overeating later in the day so you don’t repeat the same cycle. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Then, aim to eat balanced meals and snacks for the rest of the day. Skipping meals in an attempt to compensate for overeating can backfire. When you deprive your body of the nutrition it needs, it may respond by ramping up hunger hormones, which may lead to eating more later in the day. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To stay consistent, Beck suggests a midmorning snack of strained strained (Greek-style) yogurt with berries, nuts and chia seeds. Lunch could be a fiber-filled grain bowl like this 10-minute &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/263359/buffalo-chicken-grain-bowl/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Buffalo Chicken Grain Bowl&lt;/a&gt;. If you’re hungry between lunch and dinner, have an afternoon snack like our satisfying &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7913705/chickpea-snack-salad/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Chickpea Snack Salad&lt;/a&gt;. Dinner could be our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7946192/creamy-spinach-artichoke-salmon/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Creamy Spinach-Artichoke Salmon&lt;/a&gt;, a side of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7965900/air-fryer-baby-potatoes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;Air-Fryer Baby Potatoes&lt;/a&gt; and a fresh salad.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-getting-back-to-your-routine-is-key"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Why Getting Back to Your Routine Is Key &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; No diets, cleanses or &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7898359/why-i-dont-believe-in-calorie-counting-according-to-a-dietitian/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;restricting calories&lt;/a&gt; here! Restriction leads to bingeing, and bingeing leads to restricting. Give yourself some grace, eat a balanced meal and put a stop to the binge-restrict cycle before it starts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “I often tie this back into the broader picture of developing a healthy relationship with food,” says &lt;a href="https://www.lextalknutrition.com/philosophy" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alexis Silver, M.P.H., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. “At some points in your life, you’re going to eat more sugar, sodium or fat. But your overall habits and lifestyle choices are what really determine your health. We’re all human!”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-tips--strategies"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Tips &amp;amp; Strategies &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition to nourishing your body and eating regular meals and snacks, there are other things you can do to alleviate any unpleasant physical or emotional symptoms. These strategies can help you get back on track and move on.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Go for a walk.&lt;/strong&gt; “It will help lower your blood sugar and clear your head,” says &lt;a href="https://www.soundbitesnutrition.com/about-lisa" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lisa Andrews, M.Ed., RD, LD&lt;/a&gt;. “One night of overindulgence won't destroy your health, but moving your body may improve your mood if you feel crappy after too much sugar.” &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay hydrated. &lt;/strong&gt;While there’s nothing magical about drinking water, and it doesn’t negate sugar, it is important for digestion and overall health. You might be feeling &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7921422/why-bloating-can-be-normal-healthy-according-to-a-dietitian/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;bloated&lt;/a&gt; or sluggish. “Oftentimes this sluggish feeling is due to dehydration and less an effect of the sugar consumption,” says &lt;a href="https://www.arugalyssa.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="nofollow"&gt;Alyssa Smolen, M.S., RDN, CDN&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be kind to yourself and get curious. &lt;/strong&gt;It's important to remember that no foods are good or bad, and that you don't need to feel shame about what or how much you eat. Eating isn't a moral or shameful act. This will help you learn from your experience. What was going on that caused you to eat that much sugar? Were you having a rough day? Were you bored? Was the ice cream just tasting too good? Answering these questions creates self-awareness and prepares you to make a different choice the next time you’re in a similar situation. It may be helpful to talk to a healthcare provider if you consistently have binge-eating episodes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Eating too much sugar happens to all of us. But there’s no need to panic or punish yourself the next day. Skip the restrictive diets and cleanses. Instead, focus on getting back to your regular routine with balanced meals, staying hydrated and moving your body. Acknowledge the moment with kindness, reflect on what happened and let it go. Your health is determined by your overall habits, not one sugary night.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNYk02ZkRVNzJnRURRZHJiZjZXY1dPS1JOSDlRLXhZUW5GeGtSaWNER0FHZXhhWU51QUk3QWhxQXNPTTdrZUVuWVR2M2ZFOUZCRE1KMkhUazNsSGEwV3JUNDRINXp5d0M1RlFjWVplcmI4VjExcHVvX1ptWTRtTnh2YzVuYWlRdFZCUVU0</guid></item><item><title>科学家确定了可能改变游戏规则的阿尔茨海默病治疗方法，可以像高胆固醇一样控制它-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/northwestern-university-possible-alzheimers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;Scientists at Northwestern University used a novel compound to arrest early stages of Alzheimer’s disease in mice — setting the stage, if all goes well, for a groundbreaking treatment in which the debilitating condition can be controlled like high cholesterol. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The researchers discovered an unknown subtype of a protein in the brain which can lead to Alzheimer’s disease, according to a &lt;a href="https://alz-journals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/alz.70968" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;new paper&lt;/a&gt; the team published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia: The Journal of the Alzheimer’s Association&lt;/em&gt;, and they demonstrated that their new novel compound, dubbed NU-9, can attack this brain protein and stop the disease from taking hold — in mice, at least.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Most people are used to monitoring their cholesterol levels,” said Richard Silverman, a chemistry professor at Northwestern who coauthored the paper and invented NU-9, in a &lt;a href="https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2025/12/nu-9-halts-alzheimers-disease-in-animal-model-before-symptoms-begin" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;university statement&lt;/a&gt;. “If you have high cholesterol, it doesn’t mean that you will have a heart attack soon. But it’s time to take drugs to lower your cholesterol levels to prevent that heart attack from happening down the road. NU-9 could play a similar role. If someone has a biomarker signaling Alzheimer’s disease, then they could start taking NU-9 before symptoms appear.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;For this particular experiment, the team took lab mice that were predisposed to develop Alzheimer’s disease but hadn’t developed the condition yet, and started giving them an oral dose of NU-9 for 60 days. They were especially curious about how NU-9 would impact the protein amyloid beta oligomers, which accumulate in the brain hand in hand with signs of Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;After closely examining the mice brains, scientists observed that NU-9 essentially decreased the presence of a previously unknown subtype of amyloid beta oligomers that they dubbed ACU193+ AβOs. This specific type of protein was associated with brain inflammation that shows up before people are diagnosed with Alzheimer’s. When the team introduced NU-9 into these mice brains, they found that NU-9 tamped down the presence of this toxic protein and hence decreased inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“These results are stunning,” William Klein, a Northwestern neuroscience professor and the paper’s principal investigator, summed up in the university statement.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“There are a couple early diagnostic blood tests for Alzheimer’s disease in development,” he said. “The promise of better early diagnostics — combined with a drug that could stop the disease in its tracks — is the goal.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The next step now is to experiment and analyze the effectiveness of NU-9 in the later stages of Alzheimer’s disease, according to the scientists.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Silverman originally invented NU-9, a synthetic compound with the technical name of cyclohexane-1,3-dione, in an effort to identify chemicals that can tackle neurological diseases. Besides Alzheimer’s disease, the NU-9 has proved &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2021/02/210223110414.htm" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;effective against Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS)&lt;/a&gt; and possibly &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/frontotemporal-dementia/symptoms-causes/syc-20354737" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;frontotemporal degeneration&lt;/a&gt;, all &lt;a href="https://lesturnerals.org/national-institute-on-aging-invests-an-additional-7-3-million-into-nu-9/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;three of which involve&lt;/a&gt; the appearance of toxic protein in brains.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on Alzheimer’s disease:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/scientists-intrigued-alzheimers-drug-mice"&gt;Scientists Intrigued by Old Drug That Reverses Signs of Alzheimer’s in Mice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNQmNIQ2t4YmNDMjhjZ0d5dFhtLWF0Ny1CRVF0ZWpleW1lQ3dZeXNDM05Zc0lOSHhTT0x4MzZvVndBb1gtRUptdVhFWDFTaU9jd0c5UVdfblV2NC1IVlh3RTRxTU8tWnNGdnBDazE1Wng3NVB4aUsxRGo0UGNWN2lKWnFxRDZfUGc</guid></item><item><title>手术中扁平化后，我被从身体弹射到天堂。当我回来时，没有癌症的痕迹-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15378465/near-death-experience-heaven-cancer-cured.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rosemary Thornton had been praying for a miracle after the tragic death of her husband.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, instead, she was dealt with the devastating health blow of her own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2018, two years after her husband died by suicide, the Midwestern author noticed unusual vaginal bleeding, which prompted her to rush to a gynecologist. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A biopsy in the following days revealed Thornton, 59 at the time, had stage two &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15321767/Vaccine-prevent-STDs-effective-preventing-cervical-cancer-new-breakthrough-research-shows.html"&gt;cervical cancer&lt;/a&gt;, which affects about 13,000 American women every year and kills 4,000. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Soon after diagnosis, Thornton underwent emergency surgery to assess the cancer and remove the tumor from her cervix. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While this operation is generally considered safe, Thornton began to bleed out on the operating table and her blood pressure plummeted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As the monitors measuring her vital signs displayed an 'error' message, Thornton claims, she raised her arms toward the ceiling, with her fingers reaching up as though she was about to hold somebody’s hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When she flatlined seconds later, she was considered clinically dead and said she was 'catapulted out of her body.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Rosemary Thornton, pictured here, suffered a near-death experience while undergoing surgery to remove cervical cancer &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton, now 66, said: 'It was the most extraordinary moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It wasn’t gentle. I was catapulted out of my body like a ping. The first thing I declared was that my heart had stopped beating. I then told the universe I was no longer dying, I had died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I didn’t feel any terror, though, only release. All the anxiety, regret and sadness was gone. What was left was me – every part of my personality, even my giggle - went with me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I realized we carry everything that really matters when we leave this world.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton claimed she was floating through a 'velvety blackness' that was filled with peace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rather than the afterlife being an empty void, it was calm. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For someone who’s always struggled with anxiety, this place was surely Heaven itself,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton is one of the one in 10 Americans who have had a near-death experience (NDE), a transformative event that occurs during a severe medical crisis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some feel themselves being propelled down into a black hole, blinded by a bright light or &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-15223139/near-death-experience-visions-revealed.html"&gt;wandering a Matrix-like grid&lt;/a&gt;. Many are met by an angel and taken to heaven for a visit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But not all NDEs are pleasant. A &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15191705/Scientists-reveal-really-happens-near-death-experience.html"&gt;recent study&lt;/a&gt; out of the University of Virginia found  that ‘a small percentage of NDEs experienced [are] distressing.' The team also suggested between 10 and 22 percent of these experiences are negative. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Thornton is pictured here two days after her near-death experience. She claims the experience was so peaceful that she begged angels not to end her back&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton claims that as she floated through the darkness, she felt a 'presence' behind her that said: 'You are the image and the likeness. I am the Original.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She then entered a white room filled with 'radiant light and a swirling mist' that she compared to a 'spiritual car wash.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I was told I had been restored to wholeness and that it was time for me to push through,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She was then shown a vision of a nurse who had been caring for her sitting in a supply room sobbing uncontrollably, convinced she had failed her patient. Thornton absorbed the grief as if it were her own and claims she made the decision then to return to her body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said: 'I lowered my hand from death’s door and next thing I knew, I was in the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I felt disappointed. I even argued with the angels not to send me back.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tests concluded Thornton had suffered a heart attack, which caused her to cross over to the other side. But she was more surprised that four days later, she had no evidence of cancer and that her blood work was 'textbook perfect.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The surgeon said my tissue was so pink and perfect she would have never believed I’d had cancer,' Thornton said. 'The cancer was gone, but more than that, my soul was made whole again.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Thornton (pictured here) said the experience strengthened her faith in God and taught her how to enjoy the small aspects of life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's unclear if the surgery she had was considered successful from a medical standpoint.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Thornton now claims she is visited by angels dressed in light who surround her and sing during moments of sadness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The experience also helped her strengthen her faith in God and has shown her how to appreciate the small aspects of her life, prompting her to move to the countryside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She said: 'In the afterlife, I discovered God not only loves us, but really likes us, just as we are. It’s changed everything for me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'To anyone facing the end, I can promise you don’t need to be afraid. What’s waiting is peace, joy and more life than we can imagine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Death really is like waking up from a very intense dream. And this whole time on Earth is reduced to this tiny little grain of salt. It’s not a big deal.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:33:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNbllQakNzS0swRDNnOE42cFVhdkNaYXV5ZFlpS25jQ1RuRUo1azNMVzd4eHdRWnF0Z3lkTzBoZFVOa0w5V2xzR3BhckdiY3ZGd1dZVVN0TGJLV3lJWVBEQ1YwTTRRSnJJTHVfaXA2Ry1uUzRMcHlqVmJENzlqcEVPRDN1WTBzRHFmYXNTOEtLUGdYb0FxbUpKUEFSS1VwOFnSAaQBQVVfeXFMTUpKeTJGRGVEM0FnV2dzNnJkYlRXaHpSNDdidVpqMnRESktyemlSX1c4UFZ6QkdDc1ZiN3lHUEx1LTk3eEdraVZPTHJMbUNkUTNtek1zaFI1NmJvVUp1aVJGMWdwazVMZWhpQjFPWDBBb1NHR3BSeFhianZSeTVXYlNMMzRHQkNYQTljemZWZkxKSGQwRzVfUnY5TXRyX3BNVE53Tjk</guid></item><item><title>新的研究揭示了咖啡和巧克力中发现的一种有益化合物--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/26/dark-chocolate-health-benefits/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4XQRGIXIIRHPRPKB3UKDBPUBH4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If you enjoy dark chocolate or coffee, or both, you may be benefiting from a substance found in these products that is linked to a reduction in cellular aging&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3N7DIRITIRCTHF44BU2L4KNNJQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.aging-us.com/article/206344" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published this month in the journal Aging found that people with higher blood levels of an alkaloid called theobromine seemed to have slower cellular aging as measured by “epigenetic clocks,” models that estimate aging based on molecular biomarkers. Most abundant in cocoa, theobromine is also found in smaller amounts in coffee and tea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:31:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOektQdkU4eVoxTDZzTUZZNGNtWVhCWUxnQ0g5LTV4aDJFby1yWGtZSkpKckxKRXlQYjhTZ0VjNXZoVEVVc3JMc3RvQUQ4eWdxUXlCMk5DeHBNNUhycW9CNFVUOGwwZ1hSSXo5Y1MtUFpsUlMzOWNjUUdWN2tyU3g0VnhGS0d5Rnpaenc</guid></item><item><title>达菲并不是美国唯一推荐的流感治疗方法。这些是其他人。-CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/26/health/flu-treatment-tamiflu-xofluza-relenza-rapivab</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmhi9y00f526ozdpz4gv6s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When the flu strikes, it can feel relentless: rising fever, hacking cough, stuffy nose and sore throat. For many people, relief can come in the form of Tamiflu, a prescription antiviral medication used to treat and even prevent the illness.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt700063b6pzfkdgx2t@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But some people may not realize that Tamiflu isn’t the only option.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt800073b6pms06fbrs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Other flu treatments are available in the United States. These alternatives sometimes fly under the radar, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/treatment/antiviral-drugs.html" target="_blank"&gt;in part because some are targeted for specific populations&lt;/a&gt;. But Xofluza, a one-dose pill, is approved for people 5 years and older – and can be a strong alternative for some people who may otherwise be prescribed Tamiflu.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000a3b6p9w6ekwly@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Antiviral medications tend to work best when started within two days after symptoms begin, so having easy access to treatment options is key for treating the flu most effectively.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000c3b6pykhjmbku@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            To treat flu this season, there are &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/treatment/antiviral-drugs.html" target="_blank"&gt;four antiviral drugs recommended&lt;/a&gt; by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention: Tamiflu or oseltamivir, Xofluza or baloxavir, Relenza or zanamivir, and Rapivab or peramivir.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000d3b6pxarl68sy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Tamiflu is used to treat flu in people ages 2 weeks and older, and to &lt;a href="https://www.tamiflu.com/" target="_blank"&gt;reduce the chance of getting the flu&lt;/a&gt; in people 1 year and older. The medicine is administered in liquid form or capsules, and typically must be taken twice daily for five days when used for flu treatment. When used for prevention after exposure, it is typically taken once daily for 10 days. Available as a generic or under the trade name Tamiflu, it &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/tamiflu?c" target="_blank"&gt;may cost about $50 or less&lt;/a&gt; without insurance. The most common side effects include nausea and vomiting.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000e3b6pzjm5v4l6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As another option, Xofluza is administered as a single-dose tablet and approved for ages 5 and older. It can be used to &lt;a href="https://www.xofluza.com/about-xofluza.html?c" target="_blank"&gt;treat or prevent&lt;/a&gt; the flu, and it &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/xofluza?srsltid=AfmBOorpfTCHg0ZxUo26czQwzVfqtltq-qeYhS72mql5MTa4BrGHdob4" target="_blank"&gt;may cost nearly $200&lt;/a&gt; without insurance, but eligible patients can use &lt;a href="https://www.xofluza.com/save-on-xofluza/coupon.html" target="_blank"&gt;coupons&lt;/a&gt; to lessen costs. The most common side effects include diarrhea and vomiting.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000f3b6pfjqp9n2c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The most common complaint I hear about is vomiting from Tamiflu,” Dr. Ari Brown, a pediatrician based in Texas and author of the &lt;a href="https://www.draribrown.com/books/" target="_blank"&gt;Baby 411&lt;/a&gt; book series, said in an email. She referenced a &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fpmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov%2Farticles%2FPMC10569673%2F&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Cjacqueline.howard%40cnn.com%7C49eceb51e5a94e5640df08de42fe93ba%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C639021858353662466%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=Nwf8pYiivUtl9SoH6lp8euGgW0v%2B8JQlw%2BIBC0XsbfI%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; that showed about 18% of people experience vomiting with Tamiflu versus 5% with Xofluza.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlpj8iz00073b6pwv8icuej@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study also found that about 5% of people get diarrhea with Xofluza compared with none taking Tamiflu. “I’ve also had a few pediatric patients experience moodiness with Tamiflu, which is reported in the literature,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000i3b6p52br2qf3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The “biggest difference” between Tamiflu and Xofluza is that Xofluza can stop viral shedding in one day while Tamiflu may take about three days, Brown said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000j3b6p5gghm7l4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That means the rest of the household may have less exposure to the flu and fewer people may come down with it, but “both antivirals will help reduce the duration of the misery by a couple of days,” Brown said. For instance, with treatment, some people may experience five days of flu symptoms instead of seven.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000k3b6p9oq2wzg2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Rapivab is one of the other prescription medications approved to treat flu. The drug is approved for ages 6 months and older, &lt;a href="https://rapivab.com/" target="_blank"&gt;given once as an intravenous infusion&lt;/a&gt; by a health care provider. It &lt;a href="https://www.singlecare.com/prescription/rapivab" target="_blank"&gt;may cost up to about $1,000&lt;/a&gt; without insurance, and the most common adverse reaction in adults tends to be diarrhea.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000l3b6pox0s4b96@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lastly, Relenza is the other recommended flu medication. It is &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/drugs/postmarket-drug-safety-information-patients-and-providers/relenza-zanamivir-information" target="_blank"&gt;inhaled in powder form&lt;/a&gt;, and typically administered using an inhaler device twice a day for five days. The prescription drug is approved to treat flu in ages 7 and older, and for preventive use in ages 5 and older. It &lt;a href="https://www.goodrx.com/relenza?c" target="_blank"&gt;may cost up to about $90&lt;/a&gt; without insurance. &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a699021.html#side-effects" target="_blank"&gt;Side effects&lt;/a&gt; include allergic reaction, dizziness or irritation of the nose, and it is not recommended for people with breathing problems, such as asthma.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000n3b6pphv57pbn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Among the recommended flu treatments, Tamiflu tends to be the go-to flu medication for most patients. But Xofluza is becoming more widely used, Brown said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlp0r6b00023b6p2nebd1uo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, it may not always be available in pharmacies, recommended by providers or covered by insurance.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlp15kw00053b6pqjlsbgfx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I suspect it is region-dependent,” Brown said about access to treatment.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlp2wip000b3b6ph4rqkaxy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “When one part of the country has surging flu cases, there is higher demand. We have not encountered this issue in Austin,” she said. For instance, this flu season, she has only had one Xofluza prescription that she needed to send to a different pharmacy because the first pharmacy was out of stock.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000o3b6pveuc4qm3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But overall, “Xofluza is rising in popularity over Tamiflu,” Brown said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjlpp3y700093b6pi69u022v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “One dose. Fewer side effects. More insurances are covering the cost of it now and manufacturer coupon makes it less expensive than in previous years,” she said, adding that she prefers it for her patients. “But all of the factors above–cost, ability to swallow a pill, availability can impact that decision.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000q3b6pohxzb491@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Another factor that may impact decisions: There is a growing concern about the influenza virus developing resistance to Xofluza.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000r3b6pkphitr6b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This is more in the minds of the practitioner – and I think it has been one of the reasons it hasn’t been used more frequently – the influenza virus can develop resistance to baloxavir, to Xofluza, during the course of treatment,” said Dr. William Schaffner, an infectious disease expert at Vanderbilt University Medical Center.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000s3b6pxk0oevts@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “That happens sometimes around 10% of the time, so it’s not trivial. And that’s why I think the longer-term Tamiflu continues to be favored – that and the side effect of diarrhea,” he said. “So, Tamiflu tends to be recommended more frequently, despite the fact that you do have to take it for five days.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000t3b6pbo5taj5e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Xofluza resistance has appeared to occur even more frequently in younger children, Dr. Tim Uyeki, chief medical officer of the influenza division at the CDC’s National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases, said during a call earlier this month of the CDC’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/coca/hcp/trainings/seasonal_influenza_2025-2026.html" target="_blank"&gt;Clinician Outreach and Communication Activity&lt;/a&gt; (COCA).
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000u3b6ph8a4jrje@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This emergence of baloxavir resistance is associated with a longer duration of symptoms,” Uyeki &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wN-6nVGBBc0" target="_blank"&gt;said during the call&lt;/a&gt;. “Fortunately, transmission of a baloxavir-resistant virus from person to person has been very, very limited. It’s been reported, but it appears to be very uncommon and there’s no circulation of baloxavir-resistant viruses or oseltamivir-resistant viruses in the general population.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000w3b6pj1aunv3c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            National influenza experts discussed on the COCA call that Tamiflu or oseltamivir is preferred for treating hospitalized patients and people with progressive illness.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000x3b6pqp8sfr94@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Xofluza is not recommended during pregnancy, while breastfeeding, for outpatients with complicated or progressive illness, severely immunosuppressed people or hospitalized patients, because of the lack of information on its use for these groups.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000y3b6pvmtinmow@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But there are situations for which Xofluza may be preferred.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt8000z3b6pacacjyik@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For a patient with known or suspected influenza B, baloxavir has much greater efficacy against influenza B compared to oseltamivir,” Uyeki said during the call, adding that the medication is “generally well tolerated.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt800103b6p1gm4vlbs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “A single dose of baloxavir is not associated with many side effects and fewer side effects compared to oseltamivir,” he said. “For patients, I think every patient would prefer a single oral dose of baloxavir versus five days, twice-daily of oseltamivir treatment.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt800113b6p1kmgcbh6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            At the end of the call, Uyeki added that researchers should continue studying the potential benefits of treating flu patients with a combination of antiviral medications, especially those with severe disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjkmkyt800123b6pcl5c15qe@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I think we need more data for treatment of influenza in hospitalized influenza patients, so severe influenza,” he said. “And for that we need more data for a combination antiviral treatment, for example oseltamivir-plus-baloxavir.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:10:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQWWdHdDFCOUF1MnBDVlV4aGEwaXlpdEdVOXVUSU51MnJQcDluR3hPWXhoQzc2ZUhTQmh2WElBdXRwa3FFY0gtZV90OXlwU3FHWWxNeVpRV0h3eWthTS10RjNKV1NYbVRvam83SWZpVndIaE54LUx0VkQtRlpNZnlPaU5OdXQ4V0MxN2lB</guid></item><item><title>这种常见血压药物可延长动物寿命并减缓衰老- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/this-common-blood-pressure-drug-boosts-lifespan-and-slows-aging-in-animals</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The hypertension drug &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rilmenidine"&gt;rilmenidine&lt;/a&gt; has been found to slow aging in worms – an effect that, if it translates to humans, could one day help us live longer and stay healthier in old age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rilmenidine appears to mimic the effects of caloric restriction on a cellular level, and reducing available energy while maintaining nutrition has been shown to extend lifespans &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-018-24146-z"&gt;in several animal models&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether this translates to human biology, or is a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/skipping-meals-could-be-much-worse-for-you-than-we-realized"&gt;potential risk to our health&lt;/a&gt;, is a topic of &lt;a href="https://sitn.hms.harvard.edu/flash/2020/can-calorie-restriction-extend-your-lifespan/"&gt;ongoing debate&lt;/a&gt;. Finding ways to achieve the same benefits without the costs of extreme calorie cutting could lead to new ways to improve health in old age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dick-van-dyke-credits-his-longevity-to-one-habit-and-its-backed-by-science"&gt;Dick Van Dyke Credits His Longevity to One Habit, And It's Backed by Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a study published in 2023, young and old &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Caenorhabditis_elegans"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Caenorhabditis elegans&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; worms treated with the drug – which is normally used to treat &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/us-has-new-guidelines-for-high-blood-pressure-heres-what-that-means"&gt;high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; – lived longer and presented higher measures in a variety of health markers in the same way as restricting calories, as the scientists had hoped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below for a summary of the research:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For the first time, we have been able to show in animals that rilmenidine can increase lifespan," &lt;a href="https://news.liverpool.ac.uk/2023/01/23/hypertension-drug-could-be-repurposed-to-delay-ageing-study-finds/"&gt;said molecular biogerontologist João Pedro Magalhães&lt;/a&gt;, from the University of Birmingham in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are now keen to explore if rilmenidine may have other clinical applications."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;C. elegans&lt;/em&gt; worm is a favorite for studies, because many of its genes have similarities to counterparts in our genome. Yet in spite of these similarities, it is still a rather distant relation to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further tests showed that gene activity associated with caloric restriction could be seen in the kidney and liver tissues of mice treated with rilmenidine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, some of the changes that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mice-that-eat-less-live-longer-and-we-may-finally-know-why"&gt;caloric restriction gives in animals&lt;/a&gt; and thought to confer certain health benefits also appear with a hypertension drug that many people already take.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144581" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144581" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/08/SizeAndMorphologyCElegansCellsComparedToHumanCells642.jpg" alt="Various cell types illustrated in shades of pink" class="size-full wp-image-144581" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/08/SizeAndMorphologyCElegansCellsComparedToHumanCells642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/08/SizeAndMorphologyCElegansCellsComparedToHumanCells642-600x334.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144581" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Some human cell types and their nuclei on the left, compared to cells from &lt;em&gt;C. elegans &lt;/em&gt;on the right. (&lt;a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:C_elegans_cell_and_nucleus_sizes.svg"&gt;J.J.Froehlich/CC BY-SA 4.0/Wikimedia Commons&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another discovery was that a biological signaling receptor called nish-1 was crucial in the effectiveness of rilmenidine. This particular chemical structure could be targeted in future attempts to improve lifespan and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/making-one-diet-change-for-8-weeks-could-turn-back-the-clock-on-aging"&gt;slow down aging&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We found that the lifespan-extending effects of rilmenidine were abolished when nish-1 was deleted," the researchers explain in their &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/acel.13774"&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Critically, rescuing the nish-1 receptor reinstated the increase in lifespan upon treatment with rilmenidine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Low-calorie diets are hard to follow and come with a variety of side effects, such as hair thinning, dizziness, and brittle bones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's early days still, but the thinking is that this hypertension drug could confer the same benefits as a low-calorie diet while being easier on the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-pressure-guidelines-mean-you-may-now-have-hypertension"&gt;New Blood Pressure Guidelines Mean You May Now Have Hypertension&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This research presents a novel case for rilmenidine to be considered a potential calorie restriction mimetic through its prolongevity and health preserving effects," the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/acel.13774"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes rilmenidine a promising candidate as an anti-aging drug is that it can be taken orally, it's already widely prescribed, and its side effects are rare and relatively mild (they include palpitations, insomnia, and drowsiness in a few cases).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_141684" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-141684" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/ManTakingBloodPressurereadingAtHome_R_U_642.jpg" alt="A man sitting on a couch taking his blood pressure" class="size-full wp-image-141684" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/ManTakingBloodPressurereadingAtHome_R_U_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/ManTakingBloodPressurereadingAtHome_R_U_642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/ManTakingBloodPressurereadingAtHome_R_U_642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-141684" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Rilmenidine is normally used to treat high blood pressure. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEwj7ICt3Y/"&gt;Prostock-studio/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-common-diabetes-drug-is-linked-to-exceptional-longevity-in-women"&gt;Recently, observational research&lt;/a&gt; hinted that the drug &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metformin"&gt;metformin&lt;/a&gt;, which is already used to manage type 2 &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="181787" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, may also give older women a better chance of living to the grand old age of 90.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists in the US and Germany analyzed data from a long-term US study of postmenopausal women. Records on 438 people were picked out – half of whom took metformin to treat  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="175539" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, and half who took a different &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-confirms-experimental-drug-breaks-record-for-weight-loss-in-clinical-trials"&gt;diabetes drug&lt;/a&gt;, called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sulfonylurea"&gt;sulfonylurea&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those in the metformin group were calculated to have a 30 percent lower risk of dying before the age of 90 than those in the sulfonylurea group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study can't demonstrate cause and effect like a randomized controlled trial (RCT), because the participants weren't randomly assigned to one treatment or the other – rather, they were following professional medical advice. What's more, there wasn't a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-a-placebo"&gt;placebo group&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key strength was the average follow-up period of 14 to 15 years, extending far beyond the length a standard RCT would be able to. That's important to understand how any intervention impacts lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-critical-factor-predicts-longevity-better-than-diet-or-exercise-study-says"&gt;One Critical Factor Predicts Longevity Better Than Diet or Exercise, Study Says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We'll need a lot more research to figure out if rilmenidine might also work as an anti-aging drug for humans, but the early signs in worms and mice are promising. Scientists now know more about what rilmenidine can do, and how it operates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"With a global aging population, the benefits of delaying aging, even if slightly, are immense," &lt;a href="https://news.liverpool.ac.uk/2023/01/23/hypertension-drug-could-be-repurposed-to-delay-ageing-study-finds/"&gt;said Magalhães&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Repurposing drugs capable of extending lifespan and healthspan has a huge untapped potential in translational geroscience."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1111/acel.13774"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Aging Cell&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in January 2023.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxOa2VMcDAycjM5dGJWbVF2Yzhfakt6VTRMcEVVeVA3S19IMk0yUWR5Y2hLc1pyUFctUjg5QXljamFNZUd6b19BSUdOdEJRN1dzaC1JZkRuQVdhZ21ycG44Q2lFZzNMUEVQa3BzNjFjaDdYMzFjdUQ2TTdJZ0Q4NmRySEJrNmc2M2EyVkxNMzV0S0hwSnZKcVRXRUQ5OGQ5UUc4VEJkckl3</guid></item><item><title>专家表示，猪器官移植有朝一日可能会优于人类器官移植</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/dec/26/pig-organ-transplants-could-one-day-be-superior-to-human-ones-says-expert</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A leading surgeon behind a clinical trial of transplanting pig kidneys into living humans has said they could one day be superior to those from human donors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Robert Montgomery, the director of NYU Langone’s Transplant Institute, said the first transplant &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT06878560?term=ukidney&amp;amp;rank=2" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;of the trial&lt;/a&gt; had already been carried out, with another expected to take place in January. Six patients are initially expected to receive the pig organs, which have been gene-edited in 10 places to reduce rejection by the human body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Should the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) give approval, the trial will be expanded to involve 44 further transplants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The approach, called xenotransplantation, is aimed at solving the shortage of human organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;According to the NHS Blood and Transplant, in the UK alone more than 12,000 people have died or been removed from the transplant waiting list over the past 10 years before receiving a new organ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Participants in the new trial are either ineligible for human kidney transplantation or on a waiting list for such an organ but thought to be more likely to die, or remain un-transplanted, within five years than receive it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The truth is that there’s just never going to be enough human organs,” Montgomery told the Guardian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He speaks from experience. He is not only a pioneering transplant surgeon and one of &lt;a href="https://time.com/collections/100-most-influential-people-2025/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Time Magazine’s most influential people of 2025&lt;/a&gt;, but he has inherited a heart condition called dilated cardiomyopathy, which killed his father and brother. After Montgomery experienced seven cardiac arrests – one of which resulted in a month-long coma – he &lt;a href="https://www.stlawu.edu/news/surgeon-survivor-humanitarian-laurentian" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;received a heart transplant himself&lt;/a&gt; in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“I think everybody really knows that we have a terrible problem in terms of rationing organs because there’s such a scarcity of supply. But unless you’ve walked in the shoes of somebody who’s waiting for a transplant, you don’t really fully understand how unlikely it is that you’re going to receive a transplant in time,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Montgomery has pioneered new approaches to increasing supply of human organs, including &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(06)69115-0/abstract" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;domino-paired kidney transplants&lt;/a&gt;. In this situation, a living donor whose kidney is incompatible with their expected recipient is matched with another patient, whose own incompatible donor is then matched to another patient and so on, creating a chain of donors and recipients that increases the availability of compatible organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Montgomery has also been a leader in the use of organs from donors with hepatitis C, treating recipients with medication to clear the resulting infection, and even accepted a hepatitis C–positive heart for his own heart transplant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But he said other approaches were needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Having spent a career trying to increase incrementally the number of human organs available, I realised that we just weren’t making that much progress, not in a meaningful way,” he said. “And any progress we made was kind of deleted by the ever-expanding number of people who are waiting for transplants. ”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While the idea of xenotransplantation has been around for decades, Montgomery said recent developments had proved pivotal – including the ability to create gene-edited pigs. “There were all these kind of jokes about xenotransplantation, like it’s just around the corner and it’s an awfully long corner,” he said. “But suddenly we’re in it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Montgomery carried out the world’s first gene-edited pig-to-human organ transplant in 2021. While the recipient of the kidney was a brain dead individual, Montgomery said it was an important step, showing the organs were not immediately rejected and providing crucial safety data that had opened the door for use in living people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Montgomery said it was even possible that pig organs could eventually become superior to human ones for transplants, with the possibility for further gene edits to make rejection less likely. “They could be superior at some point because we can constantly modify them to make them better, where you can’t do that with a human organ,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Studies by researchers &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/news/immune-reactions-found-behind-human-rejection-transplanted-pig-kidneys" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;including Montgomery&lt;/a&gt; have shown that transplanting the pig’s thymus – an organ involved in the development and selection of immune cells – along with the kidney can also improve tolerance, raising the possibility of eventually reducing or even eliminating the need for anti-rejection drugs. “We’re not there yet, but that’s why we’re doing those studies,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While the new clinical trial is a first to be carried out with xenotransplantation, pig organs have previously been transplanted into a handful of humans, most of whom were already severely ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some of these patients subsequently had to have the organs removed and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2023/nov/01/pig-heart-transplant-faucette-dies" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;others have died&lt;/a&gt;, albeit not necessarily from complications relating to the transplant. However, Montgomery said there were two living recipients of pig kidneys who still had the organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He said kidneys and hearts were promising organs for xenotransplantation, while lungs were more complicated. “[And] the liver, it’s still a mystery of whether it’s going to work,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;He said he would not be adverse to receiving a pig heart himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Next time around, if I continue to be healthy and alive, I certainly would consider it,” he said. “I’ve got kids who have the same genetic disease that I have and I certainly think about them all the time, and want them to have more options than my dad had, or my brother or I had.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxOeVJka0ZBczlVNHpFNVpqZS14aG1ocEN0M3FLYWtjekZGQXlfLVpLanY2b3NYenFLd2NrUmp2aHZuWEdjT2wxMTdfV3JqWmthQVlTbExmd1l1WmVEX1NHcGxZeURfSnR3cEFPOGhaLXhnRlVHTE5nVzNPNnpqbFFqdGxkUk8zeHV6dEpKOGdad2szR251MTZadkFfQTNBUXZSSXVxR2pmOWdHc3lnQ0hUQ1Y4RDlQZkVQU3ZsaV9n</guid></item><item><title>美国是否应该仿效丹麦的疫苗政策？专家说，我们没什么相似之处-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/26/nx-s1-5656214/childhood-vaccination-denmark-rfk-policy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-103674" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Guards march in the courtyard of Fredensborg Palace in Denmark. The northern European country of around 6 million people has been suggested as a model for U.S. childhood vaccination policy.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Scott Barbour/Getty Images Europe/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Scott Barbour/Getty Images Europe/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a long-time vaccine critic, has made it clear he thinks American children get too many vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Earlier this month, President Trump issued a &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/12/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-begins-process-to-align-u-s-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/" target="_blank"&gt;memorandum&lt;/a&gt; directing Kennedy and the acting director of the CDC to align the U.S. with best practices on childhood vaccine recommendations from peer nations, and it specifically mentioned Denmark. That could mean fewer shots against fewer diseases.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But critics say you can't simply adopt another country's vaccine schedule in the U.S., which has a very different population and different health risks.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"It's like fitting a square peg in a round hole when our goal is to prevent disease," says &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/person/josh-michaud/" target="_blank"&gt;Josh Michaud&lt;/a&gt;, associate director for global and public health policy at KFF.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Denmark recommends routinely vaccinating all children against just 10 diseases. In the U.S., the immunization schedule calls for routine universal vaccination against 16 diseases. It was 17 diseases until last week, when the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention officially dropped the recommendation to vaccinate all newborns against hepatitis B.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But Denmark has created its immunization schedule in a very different context than that of the U.S., notes &lt;a href="https://medschool.cuanschutz.edu/accords/about/accords-faculty-directory/O-Leary-Sean-UCD11631" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Sean O'Leary&lt;/a&gt;, chair of the Committee on Infectious Diseases for the American Academy of Pediatrics.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's like comparing a cruise ship to a kayak," says O'Leary, a professor of pediatrics and infectious diseases at the University of Colorado School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Different populations, different health systems&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For starters, Denmark's population is about 6 million people – roughly that of Wisconsin – compared to &lt;a href="https://www.census.gov/popclock/#:~:text=select%20date,Learn%20More%20%7C%20Download%20and%20Share" target="_blank"&gt;more than 343 million people&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. Denmark also lacks the racial and ethnic diversity and wide income disparities that are prevalent in the U.S. Denmark also has a highly unified health system, with a national health registry that basically tracks everyone from birth to death, Michaud says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"And so if there are outbreaks or if there are cases of these diseases, they can easily identify them," Michaud says. "They can treat them, get them into care, and also track down contacts, if that's needed for the particular disease we're talking about."&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;What's more, Danish families get about a year of paid parental leave — between the two parents — so they can stay home with their babies, who potentially aren't exposed to as many diseases. Plus, Denmark has free, universal health care. So for example, if an infant is hospitalized with RSV – a disease which Denmark does not routinely vaccinate against but the U.S. does – then the system will absorb the cost, so it's not a barrier to getting care.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's very different from the U.S., where many people struggle to access health care, says &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/profiles/jake-scott" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Jake Scott&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease specialist at Stanford University School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We have fragmented insurance, we've got millions uninsured, we don't have a national health registry and we've got enormous gaps in the continuity of care," Scott says. "And we use broader vaccine recommendations because our system can't reliably identify and follow up with every person at risk."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The U.S. also has higher rates of childhood obesity and asthma than Denmark, Scott notes, which puts those kids at higher risk of some diseases.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;"What diseases do they want to bring back?"&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;All of these complex differences have led the U.S. to create a different immunization schedule than Denmark's – one that puts a greater emphasis on disease prevention rather than management, says &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/497/william-john-moss" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. William Moss&lt;/a&gt;, an epidemiology professor at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health and director of the school's International Vaccine Access Center.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The reason why countries, particularly in Europe, have different vaccination schedules is not because they consider the vaccines not to be safe or that the vaccines don't work," Moss says. And I think it's very important that people understand that."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Scaling back America's vaccine schedule to model Denmark's in this very different context puts America's children at real risk, O'Leary says. "It's like, what diseases do they want to bring back to the U.S.? Which diseases do they want kids to be hospitalized for that they're not protected from? I simply don't get it."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Which country is the outlier?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In his presidential memo, Trump called the U.S. "a high outlier in the number of vaccinations recommended for all children" compared to peer countries.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But when you look at the 30 countries that are part of the European Center for Disease Prevention and Control, the U.S. is very much in line with them, says Michaud of KFF.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"In fact, it is Denmark that seems to be the outlier here in terms of recommending very few vaccines," he says. "In the case of Germany, France and Italy, we might be talking about 15 or more vaccines."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Even compared to other Nordic countries with similar health systems, Denmark is "unusually minimalist," says Scott of Stanford. "Sweden, Norway, Finland – they all cover more diseases."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It's unclear what Kennedy might do next. The Health and Human Services Department notified the press last Thursday that it was going to make "an announcement regarding children's health" with the CDC the next day. But HHS canceled the press conference hours later. &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/18/health/hhs-childhood-vaccine-changes" target="_blank"&gt;Media reports&lt;/a&gt; suggest the administration had planned to announce an overhaul of the childhood vaccination schedule. HHS spokesperson Andrew Nixon declined to discuss the matter.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In an email to media, the HHS said the announcement had been postponed until after the first of the new year.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Experts say it's legally murky whether the health secretary could overhaul vaccine policy by simply announcing it in a press conference, without going through the usual process for deliberating such changes.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Kennedy technically has broad authority in setting vaccine policy, says &lt;a href="https://www.uclawsf.edu/people/dorit-reiss/" target="_blank"&gt;Dorit Reiss&lt;/a&gt;, a law professor at the University of California, San Francisco whose research focuses on legal and policy issues related to vaccines. But simply announcing such a major change via press conference — rather than going through the CDC's Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices — could open up the Trump administration to legal challenges, she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The process makes them very vulnerable to legal challenges," Reiss says.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxPYXNhNTEySVdkeHJna3QtTXhGNjNrNzN2Mk9BSURfTkltS0FqQlFncElPZXdoWDBBd0c3ZEFXNDRSSmp2ZHd1UThkVkZkRFFWUFB0MGdFdGhVS0hwSjFJMVBrYjkwQ2pqUkhwS2NxMWZvdm9vRlFjeXk1eWdjUlR3Uk5PTUtoaDNxVDNzb2ln</guid></item><item><title>为什么女性在晚年会爱上女性-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/wellbeing/sex/why-women-fall-in-love-with-women-in-later-life/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;After putting their daughter to bed one November evening in 2022, David* fetched two glasses and uncorked a bottle of red, anticipating what had become an increasingly rare night at home with his wife. There had been tensions between the 50-year-old and his second wife Eva, 45, for several weeks. Time alone, David hoped, would get them back on track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, that night three years ago saw &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/wellbeing/sex/bring-back-intimacy-broken-marriage/"&gt;their marriage spectacularly implode&lt;/a&gt;, as civil servant Eva announced she was gay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The couple had been planning to relocate to Bristol, but that summer Eva’s mood seemed different. She’d suddenly decided against the move, which led to rows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Her swift change of heart totally confused me and things were strained at home – I hoped we’d talk and reconcile. But when I went to put my arm around her on the sofa that night she assumed I was instigating sex and angrily jumped up and blurted out ‘I’m gay and I’m in love with someone’.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I sat there in stunned silence as it all poured out. Eva had been having an affair with a married lesbian at work, and when that woman’s wife had discovered some steamy email exchanges… well, the s--- hit the fan, frankly.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bombshell left David blind-sided. “It was an incredibly dark time which left me questioning everything – my own masculinity, my abilities in bed, whether my wife’s aversion to full sex was actually psychosomatic, was she repulsed by me?” he admits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After their child, now 12, was born their sex life changed. Penetrative sex became problematic, often &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/wellbeing/sex/everything-you-need-to-know-about-urinary-track-infections/"&gt;leading to UTIs&lt;/a&gt; for Eva. “It made me sad but we just adapted the way we were intimate, and I’d definitely describe the relationship as happy – healthy even,” says David, an east London lecturer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the revelation, “I took &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/wellbeing/mental-health/what-antidepressants-do-to-your-brain-body/"&gt;antidepressants&lt;/a&gt; for a year and found a support group specifically for ‘straight spouses’ like me. I just needed to speak to someone about it as Eva didn’t want her sexuality made public, so I’d agreed to keep the details of our split secret.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What I learnt in that group was that for the person ‘coming out’, it’s a process of self-discovery over months, perhaps years, whereas for the person left – me – it wasn’t a &lt;em&gt;process&lt;/em&gt;, but an &lt;em&gt;event&lt;/em&gt; that upended my whole life,” says David.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’ve always thought I was emotionally intelligent, but the stigma and feelings of shame I felt were overwhelming.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Anecdotally, it’s likely many of us will know of couples who’ve been in this situation” says Dr Justin Lehmiller, a senior research fellow at the Kinsey Institute and host of the &lt;em&gt;Sex and Psychology&lt;/em&gt; podcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Personally I know several people, men and women, who didn’t come out until midlife and most of these individuals had previously been in long-term heterosexual relationships,” says Dr Lehmiller. “The phenomenon is real but it’s an under-researched area.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;The role of sexual fluidity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sexual attraction and behaviour don’t necessarily stay the same for everyone over the course of their lives, says Dr Lehmiller. “While most people’s sexuality remains pretty stable over time, some people experience one or more shifts in their attractions, and women are more likely to experience these than men, which may explain why there seem to be more later-in-life lesbians than gay men,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This sexual fluidity is significant and something “most women have to some degree” says Dr Ruth L. Schwartz, author of &lt;em&gt;Conscious Lesbian Dating &amp;amp; Love&lt;/em&gt;. Dr Schwartz founded the Conscious Girlfriend Academy, an online school for lesbian relationship education in 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“About 50 per cent of the women in our academy were married or in long-term partnerships with men at some point. We have women who are just coming out in their 50s, 60s and 70s, and it’s often a process fraught with self-doubt and inner turmoil,” says Dr Schwartz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Some who come out later in life realise they were never really sexually attracted to their husbands and always ‘endured’ sex. But, others felt fine about having sex with men – they just feel more drawn to being sexual with women. It’s also common for women to feel sexually bisexual, but emotionally lesbian, i.e. they fall more deeply in love with women even though sex can work well enough for them with either gender.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While your wife “coming out” is understandably a shock for any husband, there’s even more emotional turmoil for the woman herself, which can have endured for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lisa Madsen, 56, a licenced clinical social worker, only came out at the age of 50. “There wasn’t a single moment when I knew I was gay, but certainly the intimacy between my husband and I ebbed away after about eight years of marriage,” she admits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I spent the first half of my life trying to be the woman everyone else needed me to be – a good daughter, a devoted wife, a mother who held everything together.”&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQNkZkek16dXV1a0h4SjZIakM1Y0k4X2VlOEFySkx6UXVBVmMwZkZRZDFiUUtVcUp3ZWFJYk5BZkkwTGpIVkIxY3BrYVhncEhkTWlTRVNONDJaMzBjb1B4Ymd1SlZsQVhCczRlN0FGcURLbThobDVWdnR3ZjNycVFEMFNnWnBJQ2FNek5fZkdvbU9XOGdkd3BFS3hIM1pGdElxMGVFUGlXWmU</guid></item><item><title>“许多自闭症”的新科学及其对疾病起源的揭示--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/26/autism-research-diagnosis-subtypes/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="X4GBVQ4E3BBNJIJPIG7Q5NNSQI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When Marc and Cristina Easton’s son was diagnosed with autism at 20 months, the Baltimore couple left the doctor’s appointment in confusion. Their toddler — who was very social — didn’t resemble the picture of the condition they thought they knew. And the specialists could offer little clarity about why or what lay ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:23:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQdjZjWWVtMUpka3ZhTmZVRUFYVUo5aWJkWWFzS21ZQTVWZkx3RUdfdHpvcmZGVVFhb2M5aDdRc2xpYmFRcE1WV2dic3pRQVpTdzhYLV9BUnZWM2h1Q0xmVXpGR0o5RG9IbVI0blR6MTRuZ1RxeFBMc0d6SUdsNl9NeDZLRXhNdHZCTGE1UQ</guid></item><item><title>当你的妻子服用睾丸激素是什么感觉-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/26/magazine/what-its-like-when-your-wife-goes-on-testosterone.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:02:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQRS1lSmlaNkJ5QlZRSW9kbkRUeU1pTlVKdElGSnE0N3JlN0g3Uk0tTl8yXzE3QzZxVzdyT2dQMDJXMFNaV2sxeDZRU3pNSWp4NXB6OGpaTUdLM0JRTW5VYTNIbmJQb2c0eHN0NWQyX2pDV3JmT3IwY2ZZd1F6SW1OXzRnSGJvdGxlRV9wcnhvcVNRbk81Q083LUk2YXJFakE</guid></item><item><title>疫苗中的铝盐可能是卫生官员的目标- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/aluminum-salts-vaccines-kennedy-rcna248055</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-43885e" class="body-graf"&gt;With further changes to the U.S.’ recommended vaccine schedule likely in the year ahead under Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.’s leadership, his agency’s recent scrutiny of one vaccine additive in particular — aluminum salts — may offer a clue about what’s to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a1d86d" class="body-graf"&gt;Earlier this month, members of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s vaccine advisory committee — &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/rfk-jr-cdc-acip-vaccine-panel-eight-new-members-rcna212477" target="_blank"&gt;whom Kennedy selected&lt;/a&gt; after firing the previous group — suggested digging into concerns about aluminum salts, though large studies have found them to be safe. Andrew Nixon, a spokesperson for the Department of Health and Human Services, told NBC News that the committee is “reviewing the body of science related to aluminum and other possible contaminants in childhood vaccine[s].” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1bff07" class="body-graf"&gt;Similarly, a statement that &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccine-safety/about/autism.html" target="_blank"&gt;appeared on the CDC website&lt;/a&gt; last month said that HHS is investigating whether aluminum in vaccines could be linked to autism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d70731" class="body-graf"&gt;Aluminum salts are not a “contaminant” in vaccines: The compound is added as an adjuvant, an ingredient that boosts the body’s immune response to a vaccine, allowing for a smaller dose to be used. Nearly a century of evidence has found it to be safe for this purpose. Aluminum salts are naturally present in soil and water, and the amount children are exposed to from vaccines is minuscule compared with cumulative daily exposures from food. (&lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/vaccine-education-center/vaccine-safety/vaccine-ingredients/aluminum" target="_blank"&gt;Exposure from infant formula or breastmilk&lt;/a&gt; is higher than exposure from vaccines in the first six months of life, as well.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7dc770" class="body-graf"&gt;“This is not the thing that you wrap your food in at the barbecue. … The purpose of them is to just help the immune system respond a little more robustly to that vaccine,” said Dr. Michelle Fiscus, chief medical officer at the Association of Immunization Managers, a nonprofit that supports public vaccination programs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-dd8694" class="body-graf"&gt;“Aluminum adjuvants have made vaccines very, very effective and have helped us significantly reduce suffering and sickness and death,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fa2c4d" class="body-graf"&gt;Skeptical or negative statements about aluminum have cropped up repeatedly during federal health announcements and meetings in recent months. President Donald Trump in September said aluminum was being “taken out of the vaccines” during a news conference in which &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/trump-acetaminophen-fda-pregnancy-autism-cause-rcna232909" target="_blank"&gt;he and Kennedy warned that Tylenol use in pregnancy&lt;/a&gt; may be linked to autism. (The bulk of scientific research has not identified such a link.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0f08bb" class="body-graf"&gt;“Who the hell wants that pumped into a body?” Trump said of aluminum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-32d4e7" class="body-graf"&gt;Then, during the CDC’s vaccine advisory panel meeting, Dr. Tracy Beth Høeg, acting director of the Food and Drug Administration’s Center for Drug Evaluation and Research, argued for adopting the vaccine schedule that Denmark uses, which is sparser than in the U.S., in part because doing so would reduce aluminum exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii" id="anchor-29011f"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture" data-flavor="fit" data-original-height="1667" data-original-width="2500"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-cdc-vaccine-meeting-gk-85edb4.jpg" alt="Image: Advisory Committee On Immunization Practices Holds Meeting At CDC Headquarters"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;Retsef Levi listens during a meeting of the CDC Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices on Dec. 5 in Atlanta.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;Elijah Nouvelage / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-887baa" class="body-graf"&gt;“I do not feel like we have the data to show that there is an established safe amount [of aluminum] that children can receive before the age of 2, before the age of 18,” Høeg said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0eead9" class="body-graf"&gt;Some public health experts worry that the investigation into aluminum is part of a broader push to restrict access to or approval of some childhood shots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-16e24b" class="body-graf"&gt;Last week, HHS postponed a planned announcement about children’s health to the new year. The details are not yet known — &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/18/health/hhs-childhood-vaccine-changes" target="_blank"&gt;CNN reported&lt;/a&gt; that the Trump administration was considering decreasing the number of recommended childhood vaccines to align more closely with Denmark’s, citing an unnamed source “familiar with the plans.” Several other outlets subsequently reported the same, though NBC News has not confirmed that plan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3c1574" class="body-graf"&gt;Already, the CDC’s vaccine advisory committee voted to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/cdc-panel-vote-hepatitis-b-vaccine-babies-rfk-jr-rcna247482" target="_blank"&gt;stop recommending the hepatitis B vaccine&lt;/a&gt; for all newborns, and as a result, the &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-stops-recommending-hepatitis-b-vaccines-newborns-rcna248035" target="_blank"&gt;CDC now advises women&lt;/a&gt; who test negative for the virus to decide about the shot with their medical providers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-301bce" class="body-graf"&gt;Changing vaccine recommendations based on concerns about aluminum salts would be a flimsy justification, several public health experts said. Even in Denmark, many recommended vaccines contain aluminum salts, including those for human papillomavirus (HPV), pneumococcal disease, tetanus and whooping cough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e1eb1b" class="body-graf"&gt;Of the pediatric vaccines on the CDC’s schedule that are &lt;a href="https://vaccine-schedule.ecdc.europa.eu/Scheduler/ByCountry?SelectedCountryId=58&amp;amp;IncludeChildAgeGroup=true&amp;amp;IncludeChildAgeGroup=false&amp;amp;IncludeAdultAgeGroup=true&amp;amp;IncludeAdultAgeGroup=false" target="_blank"&gt;missing from Denmark’s universal recommendations&lt;/a&gt;, just three — for hepatitis A, hepatitis B and meningococcal vaccines — contain aluminum salts. The others — for respiratory syncytial virus (RSV), rotavirus, flu and chickenpox — do not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii" id="anchor-af3293"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture" data-flavor="fit" data-original-height="1667" data-original-width="2500"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251224-chickpox-vaccine-gk-94f5b2.jpg" alt="A person holds a vial for the Varivax vaccine"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;A person holds a vial of the Varivax vaccine, which protects against chickenpox, in Los Angeles on Oct. 24.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;Patrick T. Fallon  / AFP via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5e9a20" class="body-graf"&gt;The shot that anti-vaccine activists most frequently and erroneously associate with autism — the combination measles, mumps and rubella vaccine — also does not contain aluminum salts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b0f480" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-25-00997" target="_blank"&gt;study of more than 1.2 million children in Denmark&lt;/a&gt;, published in July in the journal Annals of Internal Medicine, found no link between aluminum salts from vaccines and neurodevelopmental disorders, including autism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-42985a" class="body-graf"&gt;But Kennedy — who has made unsubstantiated claims that aluminum in vaccines is linked to rising rates of allergies and autism in children — demanded the paper be retracted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cd7b67" class="body-graf"&gt;“A closer look reveals a study so deeply flawed it functions not as science but as a deceitful propaganda stunt by the pharmaceutical industry,” he &lt;a href="https://www.trialsitenews.com/a/flawed-science-bought-conclusions-the-aluminum-vaccine-study-the-media-wont-question-aaec2793" target="_blank"&gt;wrote in an editorial on the website TrialSite News&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-52e796" class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy argued that the paper excluded some children who may have been at risk and did not include a control group. However, Annals of Internal Medicine stood by the study and said there was &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/medical-journal-rejects-kennedys-call-for-retraction-vaccine-study-2025-08-11/" target="_blank"&gt;no reason to retract it&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-072ba4" class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy, a longtime critic of vaccines, had been involved in lawsuits against the pharmaceutical company Merck over allegations related to its HPV vaccine (which contains aluminum salts), but since taking office, he has said any fees earned would go to one of his sons. His focus on aluminum dates back to his time as chairman and chief litigation counsel at &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/rfk-jr-childrens-health-defense-tax-revenue-loss-rcna179934" target="_blank"&gt;the anti-vaccine group Children’s Health Defense&lt;/a&gt;. The group has claimed for years that thimerosal — a mercury-based preservative — is linked to autism, and Kennedy said in &lt;a href="https://annlouise.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/07/RFK-Interview-July-2020.pdf?utm_source=chatgpt.com" target="_blank"&gt;a podcast appearance in 2020&lt;/a&gt; that aluminum had replaced thimerosal in some vaccines, causing them to remain toxic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6cb8cc" class="body-graf"&gt;In reality, the ingredients serve different purposes and aluminum salts have been used in vaccines for nearly a century. Thimerosal, meanwhile, was largely phased out of childhood vaccines in 2001, and under Kennedy’s leadership, HHS in July &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/press-room/thimerosal-mercury-removed-from-us-flu-vaccines-acip.html" target="_blank"&gt;pulled the ingredient from the roughly 5% of flu vaccines&lt;/a&gt; that still had it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-11b6f7" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/11-12-2025-who-expert-group-s-new-analysis-reaffirms-there-is-no-link-between-vaccines-and-autism" target="_blank"&gt;recent analysis&lt;/a&gt; from the World Health Organization found no link between autism and vaccines containing thimerosal or aluminum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-bac3e2" class="body-graf"&gt;“There’s this constant movement of the goal post to try to implicate vaccines in the development of these diseases, and there’s just not science to back those claims,” Fiscus said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e823d7" class="body-graf"&gt;In 2021, Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lkKOt4SYYiY" target="_blank"&gt;told food blogger Mikhaila Peterson&lt;/a&gt; that all aluminum-containing vaccines had “negative risk profiles” and that the brains of children with autism were “loaded with aluminum.” He suggested, too, that kids develop food allergies because “we’ve been inducing allergies by pumping them full of aluminum.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9ca85f" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/21412506/" target="_blank"&gt;large German study&lt;/a&gt; in 2011, however, did not find an increased risk of allergies in vaccinated children and even identified a decrease in hay fever among the group. In 2023, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36180331/" target="_blank"&gt;a study found&lt;/a&gt; a positive association between vaccine-related aluminum exposure and persistent asthma, but the results couldn’t be replicated and scientists said the research didn’t properly control for confounding variables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5e1559" class="body-graf"&gt;In response to mounting hesitancy about aluminum salts in vaccines, Dr. Seth Ari Sim-Son Hoffman, a physician-scientist at Stanford Medicine, decided to reanalyze the existing data with some of his colleagues. The team’s findings, &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/pediatrics/article/doi/10.1542/peds.2025-074874/205757/The-Role-and-Safety-of-Aluminum-Adjuvants-in?autologincheck=redirected" target="_blank"&gt;published this month&lt;/a&gt; in the journal Pediatrics, found no major safety concerns with aluminum-containing vaccines. Side effects were mostly limited to redness and swelling at the injection site. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b1b912" class="body-graf"&gt;“When you see the same ‘no’ finding or ‘no’ association across multiple countries, multiple study designs and over a million children, that’s really, really clear and reassuring,” Hoffman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c80692" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;The current childhood vaccine schedule in the U.S., he added, “is backed by powerful evidence in terms of safety and effectiveness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQVDdjMVlYQ3NYUnYwUjhsam9raVZtVmNpQzBMZmltRW1FUkhxN3dYWEN2Vm1fNk5Rdno3X0NXUGNHSF9oYlNoNXJrVnFTZzJCRDhzZ0xMb0ZLM2FyNDJlZG9EN3U4dnEtNktJVlFlUmdFVUhrN3pleFNJaEVxM0FKQ2p6d1g4QS00c1c2MFdn0gFWQVVfeXFMTzJUVjFZNHRGY19BQklHSERiRTZMc016bm9wekR6ZEozWmNpRkpDZlMyR0xMRGlRNFJ0ZlhGVkpCRlJQZWZadmc2bjk5ZDN5blNWUl93SHc</guid></item><item><title>十年来纽约市流感病例攀升至最高水平-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/26/nyregion/nyc-flu-cases.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 08:00:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE92eGtIZzhwZ3BteUQ4bmpLeHFkd2FIY0dCdUxzcWxJYnhJMy1TSEd1NGFrTnJ4bFBsa0V1M1lEUURhWGg1WTVKdWVpNmpoQ082UVlwU1FESlJpdjlESVptYjZTcnJpbk1OQkg1bU1wQQ</guid></item><item><title>我正在看脑部手术，看看阿尔茨海默氏症是否可以治愈- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cn4dnwky48wo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;I'm watching brain surgery to see if Alzheimer's can ever be cured&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Health and science correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/12e5/live/ad18e600-df3b-11f0-a5e8-050d4171e402.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/12e5/live/ad18e600-df3b-11f0-a5e8-050d4171e402.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/12e5/live/ad18e600-df3b-11f0-a5e8-050d4171e402.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/12e5/live/ad18e600-df3b-11f0-a5e8-050d4171e402.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/12e5/live/ad18e600-df3b-11f0-a5e8-050d4171e402.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/12e5/live/ad18e600-df3b-11f0-a5e8-050d4171e402.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/12e5/live/ad18e600-df3b-11f0-a5e8-050d4171e402.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/12e5/live/ad18e600-df3b-11f0-a5e8-050d4171e402.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="James Gallagher Head and shoulder selfie of correspondent James Gallagher, in green surgical scrubs, a blue facemask and a blue surgical hat. He is wearing dark blue glasses with metal arms. He is standing in front of a row of dark green lockers" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;James Gallagher, health and science correspondent&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Is curing Alzheimer's disease an impossible challenge or can we get there?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;To find out I've been invited to watch brain surgery at the cutting edge of dementia research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;I'm wearing scrubs at the back of an operating theatre at Edinburgh Royal Infirmary. The intense focus of the dozen people in the room radiates an aura of calm despite the cacophony of medical machinery beeping and pumping away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The patient is sedated and covered up on the operating table. On the large screens above I can see the MRI scan of his brain. It is impossible to miss the large, bright white mass of a tumour. The cancer had started in his colon before spreading deep inside his brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's not on the surface of the brain so we need to make a hole in the cortex," Prof Paul Brennan, professor of neurosurgery tells me, "as small as possible, but large enough that we can get down towards the tumour".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The cortex is the outer layer of the brain involved in language, memory, and thought. The inner parts of the brain are softer, but the cortex has to be cut through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Brennan uses a surgical drill to remove a flap of skull. The exposed brain is pink, flushed with blood, and gently pulsing to the beat of the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Standing next to me is Dr Claire Durrant, an Alzheimer's researcher at the University of Edinburgh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She's holding a container of ice-cold, artificial cerebrospinal fluid, which mimics the liquid that bathes the brain and spinal cord.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In most brain surgeries the removed section of cortex is medical waste and would be binned. But Edinburgh is one of only a handful of centres around the world where it is collected, with permission, for dementia research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When the moment comes, it is quick. Prof Brennan places a section of brain - about the size of my thumb nail - into the jar to sustain it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6cf9/live/51af53a0-df39-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6cf9/live/51af53a0-df39-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6cf9/live/51af53a0-df39-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6cf9/live/51af53a0-df39-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6cf9/live/51af53a0-df39-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6cf9/live/51af53a0-df39-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6cf9/live/51af53a0-df39-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6cf9/live/51af53a0-df39-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="James Gallagher A blue-gloved hand balances a clear beaker, filled with a clear liquid, in one hand. Ice crystals are dripping off the outside of the glass. Inside is a piece of brain tissue. It looks like a small white round lump but is striped red. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;A small piece of brain tissue kept inside ice-cold artificial cerebrospinal fluid.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Then, with a quick thank you, we're getting changed and travelling across the city to the university.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In the back of the car it strikes me how, just minutes ago, this piece of brain was still a part of a man's thoughts and fears of the surgery he was about to face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I'm always aware - every time - what we're getting is a precious gift on what is probably the worst day of that person's life," Dr Durrant tells me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Her lab is one of the few to work on living adult brain tissue to try to understand dementia and other diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"By developing these techniques we hope we're going to move forward to a world free of many different, horrible neurological diseases," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Around one million people in the UK have some form of dementia, with Alzheimer's being the most common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But can it ever be cured? That was the question set by &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/m002ntz4" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;the inventor Sir James Dyson who is guest editing BBC Radio 4's Today programme on Boxing Day&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d4f4/live/68455e50-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d4f4/live/68455e50-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d4f4/live/68455e50-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d4f4/live/68455e50-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d4f4/live/68455e50-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d4f4/live/68455e50-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d4f4/live/68455e50-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d4f4/live/68455e50-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="James Gallagher On the left a scientist in a lab coat is leaning over. She holds the jar containing the brain in her left hand and with a tool in her right she is coaxing the brain out into a petri dish. Other laboratory equipment can be seen." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;The brain tissue is removed from the container...&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/765e/live/77328330-df67-11f0-876a-05947b6d6bdb.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/765e/live/77328330-df67-11f0-876a-05947b6d6bdb.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/765e/live/77328330-df67-11f0-876a-05947b6d6bdb.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/765e/live/77328330-df67-11f0-876a-05947b6d6bdb.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/765e/live/77328330-df67-11f0-876a-05947b6d6bdb.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/765e/live/77328330-df67-11f0-876a-05947b6d6bdb.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/765e/live/77328330-df67-11f0-876a-05947b6d6bdb.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/765e/live/77328330-df67-11f0-876a-05947b6d6bdb.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="James Gallagher A green A4 sized grid is the background. On it rests a round, clear petri dish. Inside is a lump of red and white brain tissue, it appears blurred because of the fluid it is still suspended in. There are two syringes to the side." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;... and will be set in agar jelly to hold it in place...&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3203/live/ab2545a0-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3203/live/ab2545a0-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3203/live/ab2545a0-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3203/live/ab2545a0-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3203/live/ab2545a0-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3203/live/ab2545a0-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3203/live/ab2545a0-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3203/live/ab2545a0-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="James Gallagher A scientist in a white lab coat and blue gloves is sat at a lab-bench. She has an implement in each hand and is looking through a magnifying glass to see the brain tissue below." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;... before being delicately cut into slices thinner than a human hair&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Durrant's laboratory team are trying to figure out the answer by understanding the fundamental biology of Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There are still crucial unknowns - there isn't a definitive explanation of why the connections between neurons, called synapses, are lost in Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The four scientists preparing the brain tissue in the lab work in synchrony like a pitstop team - which is very on brand as the research is sponsored by the Race Against Dementia charity set up by Formula 1's Jackie Stewart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;First, the brain sample is set in jelly. Next, it is cut into slices 10-20 brain cells deep, before being stored in specialised incubators to keep the tissue alive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The team are then exposing the brain slices to toxic proteins called amyloid and tau, which build up in the brains of people with Alzheimer's disease. It allows them to witness the destruction of synapses and see if there is a way of stopping it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Everything Dr Durrant is seeing so far convinces her that curing Alzheimer's is not an impossible challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/2343/live/1c8917e0-df36-11f0-9c1c-4997b886a9bb.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/2343/live/1c8917e0-df36-11f0-9c1c-4997b886a9bb.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2343/live/1c8917e0-df36-11f0-9c1c-4997b886a9bb.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/2343/live/1c8917e0-df36-11f0-9c1c-4997b886a9bb.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/2343/live/1c8917e0-df36-11f0-9c1c-4997b886a9bb.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/2343/live/1c8917e0-df36-11f0-9c1c-4997b886a9bb.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/2343/live/1c8917e0-df36-11f0-9c1c-4997b886a9bb.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2343/live/1c8917e0-df36-11f0-9c1c-4997b886a9bb.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt='James Gallagher Scientist Dr Claire Durrant smiles. She has tied back hair and looks to the camera in her laboratory. She is wearing a white lab coat with the words "Race Against" clearly written and the word dementia can be inferred. There are people at work behind her.' class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Dr Claire Durrant says there is more hope than ever in Alzheimer's research&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The evidence we have at the moment is that it is a disease, and that we know from past experiences that disease can be cured. Maybe one day we'll find evidence that Alzheimer's disease is inherently part of being human, but at the moment I don't see that," says the Race Against Dementia Dyson Fellow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I've not seen so much hope in Alzheimer's disease research than I do right now. I'm really hopeful we'll see meaningful change in my lifetime."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Glimmers of hope came from two drugs – called lecanemab and donanemab –  that slow the pace of Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;They were a scientific achievement, however their real-world impact in patients has been labelled by some as too small to be noticeable. Neither is funded by the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Prof Tara Spires-Jones, director of the Centre for Discovery Brain Science at the University of Edinburgh, thinks these two drugs have "really opened the door" for cracking Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/39e0/live/37dc2e10-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/39e0/live/37dc2e10-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/39e0/live/37dc2e10-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/39e0/live/37dc2e10-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/39e0/live/37dc2e10-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/39e0/live/37dc2e10-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/39e0/live/37dc2e10-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/39e0/live/37dc2e10-df36-11f0-b6a6-1bf5f87ee304.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="James Gallagher Scientist Prof Tara Spires-Jones stares down the black eye piece of a microscope. She is wearing a yellow hair band to keep her hair pinned back. She's wearing a blue T-shirt with a rainbow lanyard." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Prof Tara Spires-Jones predicts there could be life-changing developments in the field&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She greets me from behind a giant theatrical curtain in her lab. It is blocking out the light so she can work at a highly-sensitive confocal microscope that uses lasers to illuminate brain samples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She's studying the role of star-shaped immune cells, called astrocytes, in Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It is part of a growing acknowledgement that Alzheimer's may need to be tackled from multiple directions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Lecanemab and donanemab both target the toxic sticky protein called amyloid. Clinical trials of drugs targeting the other protein tau are under way. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And the importance of the immune system, inflammation, the health of your blood vessels and how genetics and the environment combine are all furthering understanding of Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Spires-Jones thinks there will be three key moments:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;In the short term, drugs that meaningfully slow or stop the progression of the disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;Tools for preventing dementia entirely&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;And, in the long term, a way of curing those who already have symptoms -  although she acknowledges that will be much harder.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She thinks we are five to 10 years away from a treatment that is "truly life-changing" and we will get to the point where we can "really make your life normal" by catching the disease early enough and then halting it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But while there is optimism, it will still need research and clinical trials to prove that curing Alzheimer's is possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The human brain is so phenomenally complex that we really just have to see it in people," Prof Spires-Jones says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;i id="to-listen-back-to-the-full-bbc-radio-4-today-programme-guest-edit-with-sir-james-dyson-head-to-bbc-sounds." class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;To listen back to the full BBC Radio 4 Today Programme Guest edit with Sir James Dyson head to BBC Sounds.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;i id="the-today-programme-sir-james-dyson-guest-edit-was-produced-by-laura-cooper." class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;The Today programme Sir James Dyson guest edit was produced by Laura Cooper.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 06:00:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9aUW80WDJuSVI1eWVrRzdxVkE0N19vNE9sT3VROFlZWDJfNU5HZnRJSGlEYndlTTdJb1I3N0FuQW1ub2QxMkp0Z0hFcGNaRzctZnhENlpJdVlpZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE1CUjNwWnA3OGRDQ2ZmNm5ocGpZVGwyU3BBM2ItNXo5aS1sX05xTTdmdGZUNlFJQ1o1VENfU0pCRjZzeEZRaEJLOTc0cFlHZnlfQ0NUSHVwaEhhWlcyb29z</guid></item><item><title>减肥刺拳如何改变城市生活-《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2164f23c-9602-4bcd-9c39-f310861dfd48</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMicEFVX3lxTE9jQmNBZC1yZy1CNjduLUlDWWo0ZGxkTHpmWFFveFpkQ29nN2tEaHgwTHlxLXF1WjRWRUQ0UHplX0NDZXROV25NekFhbTZtRFY4XzYtSVZpVll0ZzA3LVFBUWw4ZkdrdVFmVWNlOUlUODI?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;How weight-loss jabs are changing life in the City&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMickFVX3lxTE1FWFpUekY0U1VWZEowZDJ2UVdjYnA2bEFUQmo4M0dJTUlvWHBjZXN5NnRtV1hNN1dETGJIaXdVSTY0VEVHLXhjamptNTAzQVdXVkdGSmNrZGdUSDV5TGRidVZnbFByTmJKRUVPQ0dVMEtQUQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Searching for new weight loss treatments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;pharmaphorum&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxPRVVCdVNZdE1GOTFHcVpELTF6Rzl4OWRyTXpEZHd3MFZNb25vS0hZQzZSRHZOSFRRQm5sQ1lKY1dtRkN4UDRWRlZJeHlpeEJvZ081RUJ4TGJodEExNWpzcGcydXJVRTN4US1oQjBXRDVQMWJzUndXUjNaa0dRX3FIOUNrb05uRjg4elpRZW45X3NFUEMtWHJNVlNaMmZ2T05zemI0OEsyN294TFBodHdwLW1lNHEzQ09H?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Weight-loss jab prescriptions double as doctors tackle obesity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiY0FVX3lxTE5JdVQ0NjB0c2pSWi1YSmRuMWZmSGcxNEFrbzdOdnU2WlBBaFg5VW5oUkxsTU8zaDNPMFhRVVA3bXdHQlpNSm9sbS1uemRyVVJ6aFludHgzSHNmU0E5cTZuZ2pwZw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;A Shot at Better Health?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Enable Magazine&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxOM1gzTDZ3UVUzLW9oWGJKcU1iVTJMNWFTT05wODlUZm02bEI1QXFUOE9xSG9fNmloQllPVUxEb0JmcUFVTVZ3VzgtRUhoQ0pWa2hHdXVFeGU3VzlQbWk4UDdLQkhKQnYybGdXYUh1TE1VbnV5NndIbTZpX3ZtckVsbzRwQV9oelpQaVFnQ25SQ05IYnZ1YTZrbFBuSmhrTFo1MkxPSg?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Obese Scots prescribed weight-loss drug in record numbers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:00:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9jQmNBZC1yZy1CNjduLUlDWWo0ZGxkTHpmWFFveFpkQ29nN2tEaHgwTHlxLXF1WjRWRUQ0UHplX0NDZXROV25NekFhbTZtRFY4XzYtSVZpVll0ZzA3LVFBUWw4ZkdrdVFmVWNlOUlUODI</guid></item><item><title>我最奇怪的圣诞节：在节礼日，我在水槽里呕吐–并开始怀疑我有一个神秘的状况-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/26/my-weirdest-christmas-vomited-mysterious-condition</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Waking foggy-headed and with the room spinning on 26 December is surely not an uncommon condition. Who among us hasn’t felt the effects of overindulgence on &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/christmas" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Christmas&lt;/a&gt; Day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;These were my immediate thoughts when I rose in such a state in my parents’ house in Dublin two years ago. An hour later, the room continued its relentless swirl, nausea was building and it was becoming hard to stand. So far, so Christmas hangover. I remained in bed and waited for things to blow over. They didn’t. Gradually, family members stuck their heads into my childhood bedroom and wondered if everything was OK. I could only say that I felt quite strange.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After a couple of hours, I thought I was over the worst, so I joined my mother, sister and wife in the kitchen. Moments later, they watched on helplessly as I vomited in the kitchen sink, a silent bond created between them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This process repeated itself several times over the next day, so I visited a doctor. The GP diagnosed &lt;a href="https://www.meandve.org.uk/information-and-support/symptoms-and-conditions" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;a case of vertigo&lt;/a&gt;: not any Hitchcock-infused vision, but dizziness and nausea, usually caused by inner ear problems. Often this lasts only seconds, but there can be more prolonged incidents. I was prescribed medication to restore order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The wider oddity was that, at the time, I was working as a producer on a podcast documentary for BBC Sounds called &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p0lgrwds" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Havana Helmet Club&lt;/a&gt;, investigating &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2024/apr/01/havana-syndrome-linked-to-russian-unit-media-investigation-suggests" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Havana syndrome&lt;/a&gt; – the 2016 case of mystery brain injuries affecting CIA agents and US embassy officials in Cuba and farther afield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-19m4xhf"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;I wondered if somehow I had imagined myself into sickness&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;I had spent the previous year researching all aspects of this strange story: starting with the array of symptoms the patients had begun experiencing, seemingly out of nowhere. Most reported hearing piercing sounds in their homes in Havana, followed by overwhelming headaches, dizziness, nausea and, eventually, lasting brain trauma. There was speculation about &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jun/02/microwave-weapons-havana-syndrome-experts" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Russian microwave weapons&lt;/a&gt; and jokes about an “immaculate concussion”. Politicians, scientists, diplomats and security experts argued endlessly about it. Some claimed people had simply imagined it or overreacted to the sound of crickets – suggestions that the victims were rather hostile to. Doctors explained that even if there wasn’t a weapon, other triggers – physical and mental – could cause a dramatic reaction in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Shortly before my own incident, I had been listening to an interview a colleague had done with a neurologist. The doctor was talking about how, when you become aware of a certain part of your body, your mind can then overly focus on it. If you’re told you have a family history of heart disease, for example, you might suddenly start noticing how you feel out of breath walking up stairs. In the weeks after listening to this, I had occasionally noticed mild head rushes when I bent over or stood up quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In my vertigo-addled state, I attempted to explain all of this to the doctor. I wasn’t claiming I had been dragged into a dastardly spy plot. More, I wondered if somehow I had imagined myself into sickness. Could something a person had read about take possession of their body? When I finished this spiel, she looked at me politely, said, “Right, yes,” and explained it wasn’t an unusual affliction. The pills should do the trick after a week, she told me, and if it happened again I would need vestibular physiotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She was right, of course, and it passed relatively smoothly. But it did make me think of everyone who had been caught up in the case of Havana syndrome. As well as needing care, many were consumed by a need to know what had happened to them. My illness was minor, but I could see how easily such thinking can take over when you get struck down out of the blue. The list of causal factors for vertigo and vestibular disorders includes everything from lying down to standing up, air travel and much else in between. Most dismayingly for someone in their 40s, it &lt;a href="https://www.meandve.org.uk/information-and-support/symptoms-and-conditions/bppv" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;“becomes progressively more common with age”&lt;/a&gt;. We are where we are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Rather than go down the rabbit hole, I decided it was better just to be grateful that my bout of ill health had occurred the day &lt;em&gt;after&lt;/em&gt; my big Christmas dinner – even if the medication did mean I could only sip non-alcoholic “champagne” on New Year’s Eve. Perhaps a fate worse than vertigo itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNYTNONDhUOFBWVEFDZ2ZTUXRNNDZRam5WQXgwTjhDUFhwZnFlTHpmMnB4N3pma0NJZHRtb1VHczhFa2RneWM4RFBCVXZnNjlHbGtkY2JhUENGbkNNbDZJcmxSaW44LXA2RjQ4VTYwLTQtVFNIS3ZhVDNOeVdTUGU2T2JRc2JjeVBkRUdGQU50YjJDOGZqMm51MzV3ckpZWFZDMEpFeXhB</guid></item><item><title>滴鼻剂可能有助于对抗致命的脑癌- NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/nasal-drops-deadly-brain-cancer/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 03:05:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE5pczdSWkVSbDN1QUwtV0tXTDRJaTJIOGhJbW5BNUxKOXkzSGx3eUlVMGNJejZPQmdZMXhwaUR3OWswQlIwRjF3UE5lYmNDVGRQNDhTWUtJWWRoeHBMT3FmVnJHRkt6UG5idnBHVnJoSHluM2JuRmN5OdIBfkFVX3lxTFBaRzZUb0hDeWU5cXp0N0pjUWdUMzVhdVZOMS1mYU5IbVg5Umw1Z1FDbGtsT1Z0dnJCVVdaT25ZVUZkZjBsNDNsVW55Yy1Ua3BxRXF0eHdxOFdjSDZZWVJTOG9kaEtJNVo1MW0yMHJvRTVOUklac0U3aGRaQkdBZw</guid></item><item><title>顶级医生揭示了5种治疗焦虑和压力的最佳食物-女性世界</title><link>https://www.womansworld.com/wellness/mental-health/best-foods-to-relieve-anxiety-and-stress-naturally</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body class="post-template-default single single-post postid-597858 single-format-standard post-best-foods-to-relieve-anxiety-and-stress-naturally theme-womans-world has-custom-search article-format-posts" id="readabilityBody"&gt;
				
			&lt;noscript&gt;
				
			&lt;/noscript&gt;		
				

	
		
	

	




	
			&lt;p class="screen-reader-only"&gt;
							&lt;span id="ac-describe-top-level-help"&gt;
					Use left and right arrow keys to navigate between menu items.				&lt;/span&gt;
							
							&lt;span id="ac-describe-esc-help"&gt;
					Use escape to exit the menu.				&lt;/span&gt;
							
							
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
	
	
&lt;span id="recommended-posts-config" data-config='{"appName":"womansworld_non_commerce_oyml","ab_percentage":50,"tracking_event":"recommended-item-clicked-v2","post_type":"non_commerce","api_key":"AIzaSyARaAm8QMYecpd36kg0Jg7H1TwKE7_DofY","post_id":597858,"blacklist":""}'&gt; &lt;/span&gt;



	







&lt;p class="feedback-wrapper" id="feedback-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="login-body sso-ww" id="login-body"&gt;
	
	
	
	

&lt;div class="login-request" id="login"&gt;
			&lt;svg class="login-logo logo-ww" aria-label="Woman's World" fill="none" viewbox="0 0 148 20" focusable="false" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;g fill="#000" clip-path="url(#clip0_4486_4911)"&gt;&lt;path d="M91.889 19.333H89.86L88.64 5.973c-.111-1.195-.528-1.306-2.139-1.306l.278-.945h8.555l-.277.945c-1.556 0-2.14.194-2.14.888q.003 1.24.14 2.473l.61 6.305h.056l4.167-6.5-.222-2.5c-.056-.472-.223-.694-1.667-.694l.278-.945h8.555l-.277.945c-1.917 0-2.417.139-2.417 1.11 0 .556.111 1.25.139 1.695l.555 7.111h.056l4.639-7.277c.666-1.14 1.055-1.667 1.055-2.028 0-.445-.222-.611-2.305-.611l.278-.945h6.361l-.278.945c-1.806 0-2.111.25-2.722 1.166l-8.834 13.528H99l-.861-9.583h-.056zM4.389 19.333H2.36L1.14 5.973C1.028 4.777.61 4.666-1 4.666l.278-.945h8.555l-.277.945c-1.556 0-2.14.194-2.14.888q.002 1.24.14 2.473l.61 6.305h.056l4.167-6.5-.222-2.5c-.056-.472-.223-.694-1.667-.694l.278-.945h8.555l-.277.945c-1.917 0-2.417.139-2.417 1.11 0 .556.111 1.25.139 1.695l.555 7.111h.056l4.639-7.277c.666-1.14 1.055-1.667 1.055-2.028 0-.445-.222-.611-2.305-.611l.278-.945h6.36l-.277.945c-1.806 0-2.111.25-2.722 1.166l-8.834 13.528H11.5l-.861-9.583h-.056zM113.778 8.389a4.736 4.736 0 0 1 4.778 4.667c0 3.555-3.195 6.555-6.861 6.555a4.736 4.736 0 0 1-4.778-4.667c0-3.583 3.556-6.555 6.861-6.555m1.5 2.611c0-1.278-.444-1.778-1.444-1.778-2.195 0-3.639 5.445-3.639 7.722 0 1.278.444 1.778 1.444 1.778 2.111.028 3.639-4.889 3.639-7.722M118.473 19.333l1.944-7.833q.176-.599.195-1.222c0-.528-.334-.695-1.278-.75l.222-.806 4.5-.083-.556 2.805.056.056c.861-1.917 2.361-3.083 3.75-3.083a1.79 1.79 0 0 1 1.833 1.777 1.72 1.72 0 0 1-1.777 1.778c-.917 0-1.306-.5-1.306-1.278.001-.318.077-.632.222-.916l-.055-.056c-1.223.445-2.834 3.278-3.834 6.695l-.861 2.944h-3.055zM132.417 15.306c-.417 1.527-.695 2.5-.695 2.805 0 .195.139.306.361.306.528 0 1.278-1.084 2.056-2.334l.639.445c-.722 1.444-1.945 3.083-3.75 3.083-1.528 0-2.278-1-2.278-2.305 0-1.528.389-2.584.944-4.667l1.695-6.167q.132-.45.194-.916c0-.528-.333-.695-1.583-.75l.222-.806 5.306-.083z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m142.445 4.028 5.166-.084-3.222 12.584c-.222.944-.305 1.222-.305 1.555 0 .195.055.445.333.445.806 0 1.917-2.278 2.167-2.806l.75.472c-.695 1.64-1.806 3.417-3.806 3.417-1.222 0-2.111-.806-2.333-2.417h-.056c-.528 1.306-1.694 2.417-3.25 2.417-2.25 0-3.972-1.639-3.972-4.444 0-3.945 3.417-6.778 6.167-6.778 1.305 0 2.055.61 2.444 1.639h.056c.416-1.723 1.083-3.917 1.083-4.25 0-.556-.333-.89-1.5-.945zm-.5 7.305c0-1.444-.556-1.86-1.306-1.86-1.555 0-3.444 4.5-3.444 7.582 0 .945.472 1.445 1.139 1.445 1.472 0 3.611-3.5 3.611-7.167M26.694 8.278a4.74 4.74 0 0 1 4.778 4.694c0 3.556-3.195 6.556-6.861 6.556a4.74 4.74 0 0 1-4.778-4.695c0-3.583 3.556-6.555 6.861-6.555m1.5 2.639c0-1.278-.444-1.778-1.444-1.778-2.195 0-3.64 5.444-3.64 7.722 0 1.278.445 1.778 1.445 1.778 2.111 0 3.64-4.889 3.64-7.722M31.277 19.25l1.861-7.056c.39-1.444.445-1.86.445-2.11 0-.417-.194-.584-1.278-.64l.222-.805 4.445-.084c-.14.5-.278 1.417-.556 2.417l.056.056c1.083-1.723 2.083-2.695 3.722-2.695 1.694 0 2.361 1.084 2.389 2.723h.056c1.055-1.695 2.194-2.723 3.805-2.723 1.361 0 2.583 1.278 2.583 3.056s-1.805 4.972-1.805 6.278c0 .305.11.444.333.444.611 0 1.75-1.806 1.945-2.278l.722.445c-.806 1.5-2.028 3.278-3.945 3.278-1 0-2.083-.695-2.083-2.417 0-2.028 1.917-5.306 1.917-6.667a.728.728 0 0 0-.75-.805C44.055 9.667 42.25 13 41 17.75l-.417 1.555h-3.139l1.861-6.944q.314-1.01.472-2.056a.555.555 0 0 0-.639-.61c-1.305 0-3.277 3.194-4.805 9.638h-3.056z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m62 8.5-2 8.111q-.156.646-.222 1.306c0 .194.055.416.305.416.861 0 1.972-2.083 2.833-2.444l.75.417c-1.36 1.333-2.416 3.222-4.5 3.222-1.277 0-2.055-.861-2.277-2.417h-.056c-.917 1.417-1.805 2.417-3.444 2.417-1.945 0-4.056-1.222-4.056-4.389 0-3.472 3.222-6.833 6.417-6.833 1.416 0 2.083.75 2.444 1.805h.056l.36-1.583H62zm-5.722.972c-2.084 0-3.417 5.056-3.417 7.223 0 1.138.36 1.638 1.139 1.638 2.028 0 3.694-4.5 3.694-6.888 0-1.334-.5-1.973-1.416-1.973M74.223 8.889c.889-.472 2.027-1 2.083-2.167a1.3 1.3 0 0 1-.472.056c-.695 0-1.111-.528-1.111-1.195a1.353 1.353 0 0 1 1.36-1.389c1.056 0 1.612.778 1.612 1.778C77.695 7.75 76 8.917 74.5 9.5c-.61-.056-.277-.611-.277-.611"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M73.556 18.333c-.695.695-1.5 1.167-2.528 1.167s-2.195-.639-2.195-2.333c0-1.806 2-5.167 2-6.695a.775.775 0 0 0-.86-.861c-1.362 0-3.223 2.944-4.362 7.333l-.583 2.306h-3.222l1.889-6.861c.25-.945.61-2 .61-2.306 0-.416-.166-.583-1.305-.639l.222-.805 4.584-.084c-.14.556-.306 1.417-.5 2.223l.055.055c.972-1.305 1.972-2.5 3.722-2.5S73.89 9.75 73.89 11.39c0 1.805-1.917 5.194-1.917 6.278 0 .222.084.444.417.444-.028-.056 1.611-.917 1.167.222"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M80.11 8.278c3.279 0 4.223 1.416 4.223 2.305 0 1.028-.528 1.556-1.639 1.556-.916 0-1.555-.528-1.555-1.306 0-1.083.972-1.139.972-1.222s-.667-.417-1.833-.417c-1.167 0-2.306.695-2.306 1.667 0 2.028 5.722 1.667 5.722 5.195 0 2.11-2.305 3.86-6.25 3.86-2.166 0-4.305-.971-4.305-2.944 0-.972.694-1.61 1.833-1.61a1.51 1.51 0 0 1 1.556 1.416c0 1.278-1.167 1.444-1.167 1.528 0 .36.805.722 2.25.722 1.917 0 2.917-.89 2.917-1.583 0-2.445-5.64-1.834-5.64-5.445.028-2.222 2.39-3.722 5.223-3.722"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_4486_4911"&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="M0 0h148v20H0z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;p class="login-body__title"&gt;Sign In&lt;/p&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="login-form__wrapper"&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="social-login"&gt;
	&lt;p class="social-login__title"&gt;Sign &lt;b class="title--sign-in"&gt;In&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b class="title--sign-up"&gt;Up&lt;/b&gt; with your social account&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;button name="googleSignUpButton" class="btn google-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 256 262" preserveaspectratio="xMidYMid"&gt;
			&lt;path d="M255.878 133.451c0-10.734-.871-18.567-2.756-26.69H130.55v48.448h71.947c-1.45 12.04-9.283 30.172-26.69 42.356l-.244 1.622 38.755 30.023 2.685.268c24.659-22.774 38.875-56.282 38.875-96.027" fill="#4285F4"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 261.1c35.248 0 64.839-11.605 86.453-31.622l-41.196-31.913c-11.024 7.688-25.82 13.055-45.257 13.055-34.523 0-63.824-22.773-74.269-54.25l-1.531.13-40.298 31.187-.527 1.465C35.393 231.798 79.49 261.1 130.55 261.1" fill="#34A853"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M56.281 156.37c-2.756-8.123-4.351-16.827-4.351-25.82 0-8.994 1.595-17.697 4.206-25.82l-.073-1.73L15.26 71.312l-1.335.635C5.077 89.644 0 109.517 0 130.55s5.077 40.905 13.925 58.602l42.356-32.782" fill="#FBBC05"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 50.479c24.514 0 41.05 10.589 50.479 19.438l36.844-35.974C195.245 12.91 165.798 0 130.55 0 79.49 0 35.393 29.301 13.925 71.947l42.211 32.783c10.59-31.477 39.891-54.251 74.414-54.251" fill="#EA4335"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Google&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;














	&lt;button name="amazonSignUpButton" class="btn amazon-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 175 181" version="1.1" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;
			&lt;defs&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
			&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
				&lt;g fill="#000"&gt;
					&lt;path d="M153.507609,149.082589 C154.515676,148.678569 155.38932,148.577566 156.128569,148.779576 C156.867818,148.981586 157.237437,149.570773 157.237437,150.547154 C157.237437,151.523535 156.733411,152.651407 155.725344,153.930804 C154.851687,155.00819 153.373211,156.47274 151.289874,158.324498 C149.206536,160.176256 145.997572,162.465667 141.662886,165.192801 C137.3282,167.919936 132.590358,170.411354 127.449219,172.667132 C122.308079,174.922909 115.990957,176.875643 108.497662,178.525391 C101.004367,180.175138 93.2927738,181 85.3626502,181 C77.3653221,181 69.368114,179.956298 61.370786,177.868862 C53.3734579,175.781426 46.3506996,173.205837 40.3023002,170.14202 C34.2539008,167.078203 28.457605,163.57675 22.913239,159.637556 C17.3688729,155.698362 12.9166457,152.163241 9.5564238,149.032087 C6.19620193,145.900933 3.3736579,142.954999 1.08870702,140.194196 C0.551071524,139.588167 0.215054377,139.032648 0.0806455023,138.527623 C-0.0537633725,138.022598 -0.0201616578,137.618584 0.181451654,137.315569 C0.383064967,137.012554 0.651878684,136.77688 0.987900871,136.608538 C1.32392306,136.440196 1.71034278,136.372861 2.14717162,136.406529 C2.58400046,136.440197 2.97042018,136.591703 3.30644237,136.861049 C16.2096944,144.739437 26.2902088,150.328295 33.548288,153.62779 C59.6908142,165.47904 86.5385842,168.509144 114.092404,162.718192 C126.861247,160.024726 139.999517,155.479571 153.507609,149.082589 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M174.374483,137.467076 C175.113731,138.544462 175.197736,140.884376 174.626498,144.486886 C174.05526,148.089397 173.097611,151.540348 171.753523,154.839844 C169.468572,160.428785 166.612426,164.603595 163.185,167.364397 C162.042524,168.30711 161.16888,168.610121 160.56404,168.273437 C159.9592,167.936754 159.9592,167.128727 160.56404,165.84933 C161.975333,162.819181 163.470609,158.728541 165.049913,153.577288 C166.629218,148.426035 166.847629,145.109754 165.705153,143.628348 C165.369131,143.156992 164.848305,142.769812 164.142658,142.466797 C163.437011,142.163782 162.529765,141.961775 161.420892,141.86077 C160.312019,141.759765 159.320768,141.675596 158.44711,141.608259 C157.573453,141.540922 156.397393,141.540922 154.918895,141.608259 C153.440398,141.675596 152.381944,141.742931 151.743501,141.810268 C151.105059,141.877605 150.063406,141.978608 148.618511,142.113281 C147.173615,142.247955 146.417577,142.31529 146.350372,142.31529 C145.947146,142.382627 145.510323,142.433129 145.039892,142.466797 C144.569461,142.500465 144.199842,142.534133 143.931025,142.567801 C143.662207,142.60147 143.376592,142.635137 143.074172,142.668806 C142.771752,142.702474 142.53654,142.719308 142.368529,142.719308 L141.360468,142.719308 C141.259661,142.719308 141.158856,142.702474 141.058049,142.668806 C140.957243,142.635137 140.890039,142.584636 140.856437,142.517299 L140.705228,142.214286 C140.302001,141.136899 141.881282,139.790187 145.443117,138.174107 C149.004952,136.558028 152.465929,135.547993 155.826151,135.143973 C158.917555,134.672617 162.54654,134.638949 166.713215,135.042969 C170.87989,135.446989 173.43362,136.255016 174.374483,137.467076 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M134.656859,92.7220982 C134.656859,94.8095342 135.110482,96.9642746 136.017742,99.1863839 C136.925002,101.408493 138.000256,103.361227 139.243539,105.044643 C140.486821,106.728059 141.746885,108.276779 143.023769,109.690848 C144.300654,111.104918 145.40951,112.182288 146.350372,112.922991 L147.660852,114.03404 L124.777856,136.65904 C122.089678,134.167584 119.435143,131.625664 116.81417,129.033203 C114.193197,126.440742 112.244297,124.471175 110.967413,123.124442 L109.052096,121.104353 C108.312847,120.36365 107.472804,119.252612 106.531942,117.771205 C103.978174,121.744067 100.702006,125.195019 96.7033423,128.124163 C92.7046783,131.053307 88.4204597,133.191214 83.8505579,134.537946 C79.2806562,135.884679 74.5764161,136.659039 69.7376966,136.861049 C64.8989771,137.063059 60.2787414,136.356035 55.8768507,134.739955 C51.4749601,133.123876 47.5267586,130.918634 44.0321278,128.124163 C40.5374971,125.329692 37.7485548,121.525229 35.6652172,116.710658 C33.5818796,111.896088 32.5402265,106.425068 32.5402265,100.297433 C32.5402265,94.6411548 33.4810745,89.4563108 35.3627987,84.7427455 C37.244523,80.0291803 39.6638465,76.1068795 42.6208417,72.9757254 C45.5778369,69.8445714 49.1564196,67.0501425 53.3566969,64.5923549 C57.5569742,62.1345673 61.6731843,60.2155017 65.7054505,58.8351004 C69.7377168,57.4546992 74.1059397,56.2931595 78.8102503,55.3504464 C83.5145609,54.4077334 87.5299658,53.7848787 90.8565855,53.4818638 C94.1832051,53.1788489 97.5265758,52.9600081 100.886798,52.8253348 L100.886798,39.9977679 C100.886798,35.6208859 100.181162,32.3551075 98.7698684,30.2003348 C96.4849176,26.6314926 92.4191101,24.8470982 86.572324,24.8470982 C86.1690974,24.8470982 85.6146691,24.880766 84.9090225,24.9481027 C84.2033759,25.0154393 82.8425065,25.4194531 80.8263734,26.1601562 C78.8102402,26.9008594 76.9285442,27.89406 75.1812288,29.1397879 C73.4339135,30.3855159 71.5522174,32.3887511 69.5360843,35.1495536 C67.5199512,37.9103561 65.9070689,41.1424666 64.697389,44.8459821 L35.0603803,42.1188616 C35.0603803,38.0786628 35.799618,34.0721925 37.2781156,30.0993304 C38.7566133,26.1264682 41.0079281,22.3220048 44.0321278,18.6858259 C47.0563275,15.049647 50.6853127,11.8512043 54.9191923,9.09040179 C59.1530718,6.32959929 64.2437316,4.12435721 70.1913243,2.47460938 C76.138917,0.824861543 82.5400437,0 89.3948963,0 C96.11534,0 102.19725,0.841695452 107.64081,2.52511161 C113.084369,4.20852776 117.435791,6.27909857 120.695207,8.73688616 C123.954622,11.1946737 126.676361,13.9891026 128.860505,17.1202567 C131.044649,20.2514107 132.556726,23.1468431 133.396782,25.8066406 C134.236837,28.4664382 134.656859,30.9410228 134.656859,33.2304688 L134.656859,92.7220982 Z M66.9151244,94.843192 C66.9151244,100.634144 69.2672444,105.111963 73.971555,108.276786 C78.4070479,111.239598 83.0776862,111.98029 87.9836102,110.498884 C93.6287829,108.815468 97.4593784,104.674326 99.4755115,98.0753348 C100.416374,95.0451857 100.886798,91.6447361 100.886798,87.8738839 L100.886798,71.5111607 C96.9217358,71.645834 93.1919455,72.0498478 89.6973147,72.7232143 C86.202684,73.3965807 82.6241014,74.5244527 78.9614595,76.1068638 C75.2988177,77.689275 72.3754685,80.0796901 70.1913243,83.2781808 C68.0071801,86.4766715 66.9151244,90.3316367 66.9151244,94.843192 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
				&lt;/g&gt;
			&lt;/g&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Amazon&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;button name="appleSignUpButton" class="btn apple-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;

                &lt;span&gt;&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 170 170" version="1.1"&gt;
    &lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
        &lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;
            &lt;path d="m150.37 130.25c-2.45 5.66-5.35 10.87-8.71 15.66-4.58 6.53-8.33 11.05-11.22 13.56-4.48 4.12-9.28 6.23-14.42 6.35-3.69 0-8.14-1.05-13.32-3.18-5.197-2.12-9.973-3.17-14.34-3.17-4.58 0-9.492 1.05-14.746 3.17-5.262 2.13-9.501 3.24-12.742 3.35-4.929 0.21-9.842-1.96-14.746-6.52-3.13-2.73-7.045-7.41-11.735-14.04-5.032-7.08-9.169-15.29-12.41-24.65-3.471-10.11-5.211-19.9-5.211-29.378 0-10.857 2.346-20.221 7.045-28.068 3.693-6.303 8.606-11.275 14.755-14.925s12.793-5.51 19.948-5.629c3.915 0 9.049 1.211 15.429 3.591 6.362 2.388 10.447 3.599 12.238 3.599 1.339 0 5.877-1.416 13.57-4.239 7.275-2.618 13.415-3.702 18.445-3.275 13.63 1.1 23.87 6.473 30.68 16.153-12.19 7.386-18.22 17.731-18.1 31.002 0.11 10.337 3.86 18.939 11.23 25.769 3.34 3.17 7.07 5.62 11.22 7.36-0.9 2.61-1.85 5.11-2.86 7.51zm-31.26-123.01c0 8.1021-2.96 15.667-8.86 22.669-7.12 8.324-15.732 13.134-25.071 12.375-0.119-0.972-0.188-1.995-0.188-3.07 0-7.778 3.386-16.102 9.399-22.908 3.002-3.446 6.82-6.3113 11.45-8.597 4.62-2.2516 8.99-3.4968 13.1-3.71 0.12 1.0831 0.17 2.1663 0.17 3.2409z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
        &lt;/g&gt;
    &lt;/g&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Apple&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;p class="social-login__legal"&gt;We won't post to any of your accounts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div class="login-register" id="register"&gt;
					&lt;svg class="login-logo logo-ww" aria-label="Woman's World" fill="none" viewbox="0 0 148 20" focusable="false" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;g fill="#000" clip-path="url(#clip0_4486_4911)"&gt;&lt;path d="M91.889 19.333H89.86L88.64 5.973c-.111-1.195-.528-1.306-2.139-1.306l.278-.945h8.555l-.277.945c-1.556 0-2.14.194-2.14.888q.003 1.24.14 2.473l.61 6.305h.056l4.167-6.5-.222-2.5c-.056-.472-.223-.694-1.667-.694l.278-.945h8.555l-.277.945c-1.917 0-2.417.139-2.417 1.11 0 .556.111 1.25.139 1.695l.555 7.111h.056l4.639-7.277c.666-1.14 1.055-1.667 1.055-2.028 0-.445-.222-.611-2.305-.611l.278-.945h6.361l-.278.945c-1.806 0-2.111.25-2.722 1.166l-8.834 13.528H99l-.861-9.583h-.056zM4.389 19.333H2.36L1.14 5.973C1.028 4.777.61 4.666-1 4.666l.278-.945h8.555l-.277.945c-1.556 0-2.14.194-2.14.888q.002 1.24.14 2.473l.61 6.305h.056l4.167-6.5-.222-2.5c-.056-.472-.223-.694-1.667-.694l.278-.945h8.555l-.277.945c-1.917 0-2.417.139-2.417 1.11 0 .556.111 1.25.139 1.695l.555 7.111h.056l4.639-7.277c.666-1.14 1.055-1.667 1.055-2.028 0-.445-.222-.611-2.305-.611l.278-.945h6.36l-.277.945c-1.806 0-2.111.25-2.722 1.166l-8.834 13.528H11.5l-.861-9.583h-.056zM113.778 8.389a4.736 4.736 0 0 1 4.778 4.667c0 3.555-3.195 6.555-6.861 6.555a4.736 4.736 0 0 1-4.778-4.667c0-3.583 3.556-6.555 6.861-6.555m1.5 2.611c0-1.278-.444-1.778-1.444-1.778-2.195 0-3.639 5.445-3.639 7.722 0 1.278.444 1.778 1.444 1.778 2.111.028 3.639-4.889 3.639-7.722M118.473 19.333l1.944-7.833q.176-.599.195-1.222c0-.528-.334-.695-1.278-.75l.222-.806 4.5-.083-.556 2.805.056.056c.861-1.917 2.361-3.083 3.75-3.083a1.79 1.79 0 0 1 1.833 1.777 1.72 1.72 0 0 1-1.777 1.778c-.917 0-1.306-.5-1.306-1.278.001-.318.077-.632.222-.916l-.055-.056c-1.223.445-2.834 3.278-3.834 6.695l-.861 2.944h-3.055zM132.417 15.306c-.417 1.527-.695 2.5-.695 2.805 0 .195.139.306.361.306.528 0 1.278-1.084 2.056-2.334l.639.445c-.722 1.444-1.945 3.083-3.75 3.083-1.528 0-2.278-1-2.278-2.305 0-1.528.389-2.584.944-4.667l1.695-6.167q.132-.45.194-.916c0-.528-.333-.695-1.583-.75l.222-.806 5.306-.083z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m142.445 4.028 5.166-.084-3.222 12.584c-.222.944-.305 1.222-.305 1.555 0 .195.055.445.333.445.806 0 1.917-2.278 2.167-2.806l.75.472c-.695 1.64-1.806 3.417-3.806 3.417-1.222 0-2.111-.806-2.333-2.417h-.056c-.528 1.306-1.694 2.417-3.25 2.417-2.25 0-3.972-1.639-3.972-4.444 0-3.945 3.417-6.778 6.167-6.778 1.305 0 2.055.61 2.444 1.639h.056c.416-1.723 1.083-3.917 1.083-4.25 0-.556-.333-.89-1.5-.945zm-.5 7.305c0-1.444-.556-1.86-1.306-1.86-1.555 0-3.444 4.5-3.444 7.582 0 .945.472 1.445 1.139 1.445 1.472 0 3.611-3.5 3.611-7.167M26.694 8.278a4.74 4.74 0 0 1 4.778 4.694c0 3.556-3.195 6.556-6.861 6.556a4.74 4.74 0 0 1-4.778-4.695c0-3.583 3.556-6.555 6.861-6.555m1.5 2.639c0-1.278-.444-1.778-1.444-1.778-2.195 0-3.64 5.444-3.64 7.722 0 1.278.445 1.778 1.445 1.778 2.111 0 3.64-4.889 3.64-7.722M31.277 19.25l1.861-7.056c.39-1.444.445-1.86.445-2.11 0-.417-.194-.584-1.278-.64l.222-.805 4.445-.084c-.14.5-.278 1.417-.556 2.417l.056.056c1.083-1.723 2.083-2.695 3.722-2.695 1.694 0 2.361 1.084 2.389 2.723h.056c1.055-1.695 2.194-2.723 3.805-2.723 1.361 0 2.583 1.278 2.583 3.056s-1.805 4.972-1.805 6.278c0 .305.11.444.333.444.611 0 1.75-1.806 1.945-2.278l.722.445c-.806 1.5-2.028 3.278-3.945 3.278-1 0-2.083-.695-2.083-2.417 0-2.028 1.917-5.306 1.917-6.667a.728.728 0 0 0-.75-.805C44.055 9.667 42.25 13 41 17.75l-.417 1.555h-3.139l1.861-6.944q.314-1.01.472-2.056a.555.555 0 0 0-.639-.61c-1.305 0-3.277 3.194-4.805 9.638h-3.056z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="m62 8.5-2 8.111q-.156.646-.222 1.306c0 .194.055.416.305.416.861 0 1.972-2.083 2.833-2.444l.75.417c-1.36 1.333-2.416 3.222-4.5 3.222-1.277 0-2.055-.861-2.277-2.417h-.056c-.917 1.417-1.805 2.417-3.444 2.417-1.945 0-4.056-1.222-4.056-4.389 0-3.472 3.222-6.833 6.417-6.833 1.416 0 2.083.75 2.444 1.805h.056l.36-1.583H62zm-5.722.972c-2.084 0-3.417 5.056-3.417 7.223 0 1.138.36 1.638 1.139 1.638 2.028 0 3.694-4.5 3.694-6.888 0-1.334-.5-1.973-1.416-1.973M74.223 8.889c.889-.472 2.027-1 2.083-2.167a1.3 1.3 0 0 1-.472.056c-.695 0-1.111-.528-1.111-1.195a1.353 1.353 0 0 1 1.36-1.389c1.056 0 1.612.778 1.612 1.778C77.695 7.75 76 8.917 74.5 9.5c-.61-.056-.277-.611-.277-.611"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M73.556 18.333c-.695.695-1.5 1.167-2.528 1.167s-2.195-.639-2.195-2.333c0-1.806 2-5.167 2-6.695a.775.775 0 0 0-.86-.861c-1.362 0-3.223 2.944-4.362 7.333l-.583 2.306h-3.222l1.889-6.861c.25-.945.61-2 .61-2.306 0-.416-.166-.583-1.305-.639l.222-.805 4.584-.084c-.14.556-.306 1.417-.5 2.223l.055.055c.972-1.305 1.972-2.5 3.722-2.5S73.89 9.75 73.89 11.39c0 1.805-1.917 5.194-1.917 6.278 0 .222.084.444.417.444-.028-.056 1.611-.917 1.167.222"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M80.11 8.278c3.279 0 4.223 1.416 4.223 2.305 0 1.028-.528 1.556-1.639 1.556-.916 0-1.555-.528-1.555-1.306 0-1.083.972-1.139.972-1.222s-.667-.417-1.833-.417c-1.167 0-2.306.695-2.306 1.667 0 2.028 5.722 1.667 5.722 5.195 0 2.11-2.305 3.86-6.25 3.86-2.166 0-4.305-.971-4.305-2.944 0-.972.694-1.61 1.833-1.61a1.51 1.51 0 0 1 1.556 1.416c0 1.278-1.167 1.444-1.167 1.528 0 .36.805.722 2.25.722 1.917 0 2.917-.89 2.917-1.583 0-2.445-5.64-1.834-5.64-5.445.028-2.222 2.39-3.722 5.223-3.722"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_4486_4911"&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="M0 0h148v20H0z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
				&lt;p class="login-body__title" id="titleheader"&gt;Sign Up&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;span class="login-registration-cta"&gt;Create a free account to access exclusive content, play games, solve puzzles, test your pop-culture knowledge and receive special offers.&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span class="already-have-acc"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a id="signin-already-have-account" class="signin-already-have-account" role="button" name="Login" tabindex="0"&gt;Login&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div class="social-login"&gt;
	&lt;p class="social-login__title"&gt;Sign &lt;b class="title--sign-in"&gt;In&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b class="title--sign-up"&gt;Up&lt;/b&gt; with your social account&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;button name="googleSignUpButton" class="btn google-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 256 262" preserveaspectratio="xMidYMid"&gt;
			&lt;path d="M255.878 133.451c0-10.734-.871-18.567-2.756-26.69H130.55v48.448h71.947c-1.45 12.04-9.283 30.172-26.69 42.356l-.244 1.622 38.755 30.023 2.685.268c24.659-22.774 38.875-56.282 38.875-96.027" fill="#4285F4"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 261.1c35.248 0 64.839-11.605 86.453-31.622l-41.196-31.913c-11.024 7.688-25.82 13.055-45.257 13.055-34.523 0-63.824-22.773-74.269-54.25l-1.531.13-40.298 31.187-.527 1.465C35.393 231.798 79.49 261.1 130.55 261.1" fill="#34A853"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M56.281 156.37c-2.756-8.123-4.351-16.827-4.351-25.82 0-8.994 1.595-17.697 4.206-25.82l-.073-1.73L15.26 71.312l-1.335.635C5.077 89.644 0 109.517 0 130.55s5.077 40.905 13.925 58.602l42.356-32.782" fill="#FBBC05"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
			&lt;path d="M130.55 50.479c24.514 0 41.05 10.589 50.479 19.438l36.844-35.974C195.245 12.91 165.798 0 130.55 0 79.49 0 35.393 29.301 13.925 71.947l42.211 32.783c10.59-31.477 39.891-54.251 74.414-54.251" fill="#EA4335"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Google&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;














	&lt;button name="amazonSignUpButton" class="btn amazon-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;
		&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 175 181" version="1.1" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink"&gt;
			&lt;defs&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;
			&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
				&lt;g fill="#000"&gt;
					&lt;path d="M153.507609,149.082589 C154.515676,148.678569 155.38932,148.577566 156.128569,148.779576 C156.867818,148.981586 157.237437,149.570773 157.237437,150.547154 C157.237437,151.523535 156.733411,152.651407 155.725344,153.930804 C154.851687,155.00819 153.373211,156.47274 151.289874,158.324498 C149.206536,160.176256 145.997572,162.465667 141.662886,165.192801 C137.3282,167.919936 132.590358,170.411354 127.449219,172.667132 C122.308079,174.922909 115.990957,176.875643 108.497662,178.525391 C101.004367,180.175138 93.2927738,181 85.3626502,181 C77.3653221,181 69.368114,179.956298 61.370786,177.868862 C53.3734579,175.781426 46.3506996,173.205837 40.3023002,170.14202 C34.2539008,167.078203 28.457605,163.57675 22.913239,159.637556 C17.3688729,155.698362 12.9166457,152.163241 9.5564238,149.032087 C6.19620193,145.900933 3.3736579,142.954999 1.08870702,140.194196 C0.551071524,139.588167 0.215054377,139.032648 0.0806455023,138.527623 C-0.0537633725,138.022598 -0.0201616578,137.618584 0.181451654,137.315569 C0.383064967,137.012554 0.651878684,136.77688 0.987900871,136.608538 C1.32392306,136.440196 1.71034278,136.372861 2.14717162,136.406529 C2.58400046,136.440197 2.97042018,136.591703 3.30644237,136.861049 C16.2096944,144.739437 26.2902088,150.328295 33.548288,153.62779 C59.6908142,165.47904 86.5385842,168.509144 114.092404,162.718192 C126.861247,160.024726 139.999517,155.479571 153.507609,149.082589 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M174.374483,137.467076 C175.113731,138.544462 175.197736,140.884376 174.626498,144.486886 C174.05526,148.089397 173.097611,151.540348 171.753523,154.839844 C169.468572,160.428785 166.612426,164.603595 163.185,167.364397 C162.042524,168.30711 161.16888,168.610121 160.56404,168.273437 C159.9592,167.936754 159.9592,167.128727 160.56404,165.84933 C161.975333,162.819181 163.470609,158.728541 165.049913,153.577288 C166.629218,148.426035 166.847629,145.109754 165.705153,143.628348 C165.369131,143.156992 164.848305,142.769812 164.142658,142.466797 C163.437011,142.163782 162.529765,141.961775 161.420892,141.86077 C160.312019,141.759765 159.320768,141.675596 158.44711,141.608259 C157.573453,141.540922 156.397393,141.540922 154.918895,141.608259 C153.440398,141.675596 152.381944,141.742931 151.743501,141.810268 C151.105059,141.877605 150.063406,141.978608 148.618511,142.113281 C147.173615,142.247955 146.417577,142.31529 146.350372,142.31529 C145.947146,142.382627 145.510323,142.433129 145.039892,142.466797 C144.569461,142.500465 144.199842,142.534133 143.931025,142.567801 C143.662207,142.60147 143.376592,142.635137 143.074172,142.668806 C142.771752,142.702474 142.53654,142.719308 142.368529,142.719308 L141.360468,142.719308 C141.259661,142.719308 141.158856,142.702474 141.058049,142.668806 C140.957243,142.635137 140.890039,142.584636 140.856437,142.517299 L140.705228,142.214286 C140.302001,141.136899 141.881282,139.790187 145.443117,138.174107 C149.004952,136.558028 152.465929,135.547993 155.826151,135.143973 C158.917555,134.672617 162.54654,134.638949 166.713215,135.042969 C170.87989,135.446989 173.43362,136.255016 174.374483,137.467076 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
					&lt;path d="M134.656859,92.7220982 C134.656859,94.8095342 135.110482,96.9642746 136.017742,99.1863839 C136.925002,101.408493 138.000256,103.361227 139.243539,105.044643 C140.486821,106.728059 141.746885,108.276779 143.023769,109.690848 C144.300654,111.104918 145.40951,112.182288 146.350372,112.922991 L147.660852,114.03404 L124.777856,136.65904 C122.089678,134.167584 119.435143,131.625664 116.81417,129.033203 C114.193197,126.440742 112.244297,124.471175 110.967413,123.124442 L109.052096,121.104353 C108.312847,120.36365 107.472804,119.252612 106.531942,117.771205 C103.978174,121.744067 100.702006,125.195019 96.7033423,128.124163 C92.7046783,131.053307 88.4204597,133.191214 83.8505579,134.537946 C79.2806562,135.884679 74.5764161,136.659039 69.7376966,136.861049 C64.8989771,137.063059 60.2787414,136.356035 55.8768507,134.739955 C51.4749601,133.123876 47.5267586,130.918634 44.0321278,128.124163 C40.5374971,125.329692 37.7485548,121.525229 35.6652172,116.710658 C33.5818796,111.896088 32.5402265,106.425068 32.5402265,100.297433 C32.5402265,94.6411548 33.4810745,89.4563108 35.3627987,84.7427455 C37.244523,80.0291803 39.6638465,76.1068795 42.6208417,72.9757254 C45.5778369,69.8445714 49.1564196,67.0501425 53.3566969,64.5923549 C57.5569742,62.1345673 61.6731843,60.2155017 65.7054505,58.8351004 C69.7377168,57.4546992 74.1059397,56.2931595 78.8102503,55.3504464 C83.5145609,54.4077334 87.5299658,53.7848787 90.8565855,53.4818638 C94.1832051,53.1788489 97.5265758,52.9600081 100.886798,52.8253348 L100.886798,39.9977679 C100.886798,35.6208859 100.181162,32.3551075 98.7698684,30.2003348 C96.4849176,26.6314926 92.4191101,24.8470982 86.572324,24.8470982 C86.1690974,24.8470982 85.6146691,24.880766 84.9090225,24.9481027 C84.2033759,25.0154393 82.8425065,25.4194531 80.8263734,26.1601562 C78.8102402,26.9008594 76.9285442,27.89406 75.1812288,29.1397879 C73.4339135,30.3855159 71.5522174,32.3887511 69.5360843,35.1495536 C67.5199512,37.9103561 65.9070689,41.1424666 64.697389,44.8459821 L35.0603803,42.1188616 C35.0603803,38.0786628 35.799618,34.0721925 37.2781156,30.0993304 C38.7566133,26.1264682 41.0079281,22.3220048 44.0321278,18.6858259 C47.0563275,15.049647 50.6853127,11.8512043 54.9191923,9.09040179 C59.1530718,6.32959929 64.2437316,4.12435721 70.1913243,2.47460938 C76.138917,0.824861543 82.5400437,0 89.3948963,0 C96.11534,0 102.19725,0.841695452 107.64081,2.52511161 C113.084369,4.20852776 117.435791,6.27909857 120.695207,8.73688616 C123.954622,11.1946737 126.676361,13.9891026 128.860505,17.1202567 C131.044649,20.2514107 132.556726,23.1468431 133.396782,25.8066406 C134.236837,28.4664382 134.656859,30.9410228 134.656859,33.2304688 L134.656859,92.7220982 Z M66.9151244,94.843192 C66.9151244,100.634144 69.2672444,105.111963 73.971555,108.276786 C78.4070479,111.239598 83.0776862,111.98029 87.9836102,110.498884 C93.6287829,108.815468 97.4593784,104.674326 99.4755115,98.0753348 C100.416374,95.0451857 100.886798,91.6447361 100.886798,87.8738839 L100.886798,71.5111607 C96.9217358,71.645834 93.1919455,72.0498478 89.6973147,72.7232143 C86.202684,73.3965807 82.6241014,74.5244527 78.9614595,76.1068638 C75.2988177,77.689275 72.3754685,80.0796901 70.1913243,83.2781808 C68.0071801,86.4766715 66.9151244,90.3316367 66.9151244,94.843192 Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
				&lt;/g&gt;
			&lt;/g&gt;
		&lt;/svg&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Amazon&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;button name="appleSignUpButton" class="btn apple-button socialButton-customizable"&gt;

                &lt;span&gt;&lt;svg class="social-logo" viewbox="0 0 170 170" version="1.1"&gt;
    &lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;
        &lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;
            &lt;path d="m150.37 130.25c-2.45 5.66-5.35 10.87-8.71 15.66-4.58 6.53-8.33 11.05-11.22 13.56-4.48 4.12-9.28 6.23-14.42 6.35-3.69 0-8.14-1.05-13.32-3.18-5.197-2.12-9.973-3.17-14.34-3.17-4.58 0-9.492 1.05-14.746 3.17-5.262 2.13-9.501 3.24-12.742 3.35-4.929 0.21-9.842-1.96-14.746-6.52-3.13-2.73-7.045-7.41-11.735-14.04-5.032-7.08-9.169-15.29-12.41-24.65-3.471-10.11-5.211-19.9-5.211-29.378 0-10.857 2.346-20.221 7.045-28.068 3.693-6.303 8.606-11.275 14.755-14.925s12.793-5.51 19.948-5.629c3.915 0 9.049 1.211 15.429 3.591 6.362 2.388 10.447 3.599 12.238 3.599 1.339 0 5.877-1.416 13.57-4.239 7.275-2.618 13.415-3.702 18.445-3.275 13.63 1.1 23.87 6.473 30.68 16.153-12.19 7.386-18.22 17.731-18.1 31.002 0.11 10.337 3.86 18.939 11.23 25.769 3.34 3.17 7.07 5.62 11.22 7.36-0.9 2.61-1.85 5.11-2.86 7.51zm-31.26-123.01c0 8.1021-2.96 15.667-8.86 22.669-7.12 8.324-15.732 13.134-25.071 12.375-0.119-0.972-0.188-1.995-0.188-3.07 0-7.778 3.386-16.102 9.399-22.908 3.002-3.446 6.82-6.3113 11.45-8.597 4.62-2.2516 8.99-3.4968 13.1-3.71 0.12 1.0831 0.17 2.1663 0.17 3.2409z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
        &lt;/g&gt;
    &lt;/g&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;span&gt;Continue with Apple&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;/button&gt;

	&lt;p class="social-login__legal"&gt;We won't post to any of your accounts&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	

&lt;/div&gt;

		
			
	














		

				

		&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Woman's World</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 22:00:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNR25CTk10bFNLTHRoWF9fUDJEVWEtd3NURkRpMVBtbm10UzQzdENjTnRsMlRwbW9nMWpQSXEtLUNwZWgyUFAyem5UZFFqXzFFdU11OWw4TDVKeHhNOHBvbE1SMFZwdjNEcGxsVlN5S1R4M3Bidk9KYmJ5SUVyeWlFUzhJb1lpel9SelFBRjZhdW5HLXRkRHEtSkk3R3hrSEIxamVj</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现可以通过肠道治疗抑郁症的蛋白质- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-discover-protein-that-could-treat-depression-through-the-gut/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:53:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPR3kyR1h4MklhZWpjaFJKNmVrVTFJS3Ezal9ZMllmZlhqdkJ3RlM2dHdBb0RyR1d6QWJBZ0ZOS29pSXpRMFR3bURKZmNnVGhoTVVORmZIbjlhSFR6TFFXZjZQSzFZbTBSMlpDdHFhMVRpODZyclNUS3BOUnVRamVucGgzSTd0Y1lsaWxuQzcwZlFwTUh3Zi1xbWNCczJHUQ</guid></item><item><title>在日本树蛙体内发现强效抗癌药物- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/powerful-anti-cancer-drug-discovered-inside-japanese-tree-frog</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Scientists have discovered a promising new approach to fighting  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="186339" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; in the gut bacteria of a Japanese tree frog, with one strain completely shrinking tumors in mice, with no severe side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese tree frog (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Japanese_tree_frog"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dryophytes japonicus&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) wasn't a lucky find. We know amphibians and reptiles &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/026119290703500514"&gt;rarely develop cancer&lt;/a&gt;, and researchers from the Japan Advanced Institute of Science and Technology wanted to see whether transferring gut bacteria from frogs to mice might have any anti-cancer effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of 45 different bacterial strains from frogs, newts, and lizards were shortlisted for testing, with 9 strains showing notable tumor-fighting capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most impressive of the bunch was the frog bacteria, &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ewingella_americana"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ewingella americana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/simple-supplement-combo-could-help-fight-deadly-brain-cancer"&gt;Simple Supplement Combo Could Help Fight Deadly Brain Cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings suggest that gut microbiomes of lower vertebrates harbor numerous uncharacterized bacterial species with exceptional therapeutic potential," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2025.2599562"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186342" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186342" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CancerAction.jpg" alt="Cancer treatment diagram" class="wp-image-186342 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CancerAction.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CancerAction-600x319.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186342" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The bacteria seem to enlist the help of immune cells to fight cancer. (Iwata et al., &lt;em&gt;Gut Microbes&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;While other strains showed short-lived anti-tumor effects, a single dose of &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; didn't just shrink tumors in treated mice – their tumors disappeared completely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, when cancer cells were reintroduced 30 days later to mice treated with &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-vaccine-for-two-deadly-cancers-shows-promise-in-clinical-trial"&gt;tumors didn't develop&lt;/a&gt; in the following month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further analysis revealed that &lt;em&gt;E. americana &lt;/em&gt;works in two ways: It attacks tumor tissue while also amping up the body's immune response, enlisting extra help from T cells, B cells, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/22313-neutrophils"&gt;and neutrophils&lt;/a&gt; – key fighters in the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers think &lt;em&gt;E. americana's &lt;/em&gt;effectiveness lies in the way it has evolved to survive in low-oxygen environments (such as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/simple-supplement-combo-could-help-fight-deadly-brain-cancer"&gt;cancer tumors&lt;/a&gt;) that typically suppress immune cells and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-023-01332-8"&gt;reduce the effectiveness&lt;/a&gt; of chemotherapy drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on these preliminary animal studies, &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; seems fairly safe, too. The bacteria were cleared quickly from the bloodstream of mice, didn't cause any long-lasting toxicity, and didn't appear to affect healthy organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Injections of &lt;em&gt;E. americana &lt;/em&gt;were also more effective at shrinking tumors in mice than several current treatments, including &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doxorubicin"&gt;doxorubicin&lt;/a&gt;, a chemotherapy drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These results suggest that &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; represents a promising therapeutic candidate with an acceptable safety profile suitable for potential clinical development," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2025.2599562"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's still early days, and much more testing is needed to see whether the findings of these &lt;a href="https://www.crick.ac.uk/research/animal-research/why-and-how-we-use-animals/why-do-we-use-mice-in-research"&gt;animal studies&lt;/a&gt; could translate into humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also want to test &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; against other types of cancers in animal models, see how it works in combination with other treatments, and experiment with drug-delivery methods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safety will be paramount if bacterial treatment is to progress to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="186339" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; are bacteria after all, and can &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/antibiotics13060559"&gt;cause infections&lt;/a&gt; in humans. Figuring out if they can be used in people without any harmful effects will be a challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, scientists are exploring other ways of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-are-hacking-bacteria-to-fight-cancer-then-self-destruct"&gt;co-opting bacteria to kill cancer cells&lt;/a&gt;, with at least one bacterial therapy already used to treat some cases of bladder cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frogs and other reptiles may add to that arsenal in time by providing another source of potential cancer therapeutics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings demonstrate the vast untapped potential residing within diverse microbial ecosystems and highlight the critical importance of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-species-of-tiny-pumpkin-toadlet-discovered-in-brazils-cloud-forests"&gt;biodiversity conservation efforts&lt;/a&gt; in advancing medical science and therapeutic innovation," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2025.2599562"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2025.2599562"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gut Microbes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:02:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQVENmaTZFeURhalBUazFhOWFPMkhPMElZbzhCNHFRT3VReVY1YWJpc0pqd0NxeW9fd0F5UGQtNWNodThVSkNLVnRGSDJsbXBIZ2Q4Yi0taEZWY2FhY2YtNDlUYUdzeWhXYVZ6aUZGdEtmMjNfVEFadDM4ZlVGM2ZZS3VaQlI5WHZjMEhqUkhxSzhidXVCRGc</guid></item><item><title>实验性阿尔茨海默氏症药物可以及早预防疾病- NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/alzheimers-drug-nu-9-prevent-disease/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:33:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFB3M05hbWN1MDZIdTBURVpjQ3pCUllYNWhXOGZpUUh5NXhQUzVNaHU3bEgzX1l2UVFzdFJJYmdDb0w0dVlidmRraDB0dXpYZTktVkFEbWt1a0g1bUQxYXdrTlRVUDk2WVdOcGhpOXhlUTVOcExMdktXVWNJSHdJdjDSAYQBQVVfeXFMT3lTYXQ1RDBQYm5TQ0xNT3BNMjZBaGVDbjVNVFJRdjlqN3JCR2xqY21GdHY5T2U5VVdERlgtbk9XRml5RHo0dW1QdjJSYklMQmdSbDdKUVJUVnJXSDlVc1ZNQWpMT2I1QkEzVzJxSmJ2Y1lodENKMmpYeW9KYjNkUXRHV3N2</guid></item><item><title>根据科学家的说法，新的植物性血清显示在几周内头发再生- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/plant-based-serum-shown-in-lab-tests-to-boost-hair-growth-in-weeks/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team of scientists has created a daily scalp hair growth serum, using a tropical plant-based extract, that has proven to regrow hair and improve hair thickness in just 56 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The test enrolled 60 adults in a randomized, double-blind trial run by researchers in Taipei. Each person used one milliliter nightly across the scalp for eight weeks, and changes were tracked with standardized imaging. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Initial results showed a 25 percent increase in hair thickness, compared to the placebo group, in less than two months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-fast-signal-for-hair-growth"&gt;Fast signal for hair growth&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Male-pattern &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/how-a-natural-sweetener-improves-hair-loss-treatment/"&gt;hair loss&lt;/a&gt; is common, and some current treatments do help, but results vary and take months. This short, controlled test that moves the needle faster is drawing global attention for obvious reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead researcher Dr. Tsong Min Chang of &lt;a href="https://sbc-biotech.com/"&gt;Schweitzer Biotech Company&lt;/a&gt; (SBC) led the clinical work in Taiwan. The team set out to see if a multi-part serum could nudge more follicles into active growth within a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people try over-the-counter serums with mixed ingredients and vague claims. A tightly designed, blinded study offers cleaner signals than marketing before and after photos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-hair-growth-serum-ingredients"&gt;Hair growth serum ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The proprietary serum uses mild &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/drinking-coffee-may-reduce-frailty-in-aging-adults/"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt; and panthenol, a moisturizer many shampoos already carry. On top of that, the formula added extracellular vesicles – tiny packets released by cells that carry signals – derived from a plant species called &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Centella_asiatica" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Centella asiatica&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also included fibroblast growth factor 7, a protein cue that supports hair-producing skin cells. The mix further added insulin-like growth factor 1, a protein signal that promotes follicle growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those choices were not random. Growth factor biology links these signals to hair cycling, and careful delivery can matter for effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-the-test-was-done"&gt;How the test was done&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volunteers ages 18 to 60 were randomly assigned to five groups, including a placebo. Technicians measured density, thickness, length, and shedding at days 14, 28, 42, and 56 using standardized tools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four active arms stacked ingredients stepwise, from a simple base, to base plus growth factors, to base plus plant vesicles, to a full combination. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The design used placebo controls and blinding, a good way to reduce bias in a small study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-hair-growth-changed-by-day-56"&gt;Hair growth changed by day 56&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across most measures, results improved as more components were combined, with the full formula on top. Hair density rose by almost 25 percent in the combination group compared with a smaller shift on placebo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strands also measured thicker in that group. The study authors suggest the plant material may support scalp health around follicles. These outcomes hint at synergy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stepwise gains across the arms suggest each component added something, with the trio together giving the largest effect on density at the study’s endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143300/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1m.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143306/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1s.webp" alt="Representative photographs of the participants in Group E on Day 0 and Day 56 after treatment. Credit: medRxiv" class="wp-image-1991078" srcset="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143306/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1s.webp 300w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143306/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1s-150x150.webp 150w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143306/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1s-32x32.webp 32w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Representative photographs of the participants in Group E on Day 0 and Day 56 after treatment. Click image to enlarge. Credit: medRxiv&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-short-trial-big-questions"&gt;Short trial, big questions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study involved healthy adults rather than people with clear pattern hair loss. It lasted only eight weeks, which is short relative to a full hair growth cycle and not long enough to judge durability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company employees and consultants worked on the project and reported the outcomes, which raises routine questions about bias. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Independent replication and longer follow up are essential before any claims move beyond a small controlled test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was no head-to-head comparison with proven therapies. A direct run against minoxidil and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/daily-dose-finasteride-magic-pill-regrows-hair-heals-prostate-boosts-heart-health/"&gt;finasteride&lt;/a&gt; would show whether the new mix adds more than what is already available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-context-in-hair-growth-research"&gt;Context in hair growth research&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hair grows in cycles that include resting and growth phases. The growth phase, called &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/finally-a-cure-for-baldness-scientists-regrow-hair-using-stem-cells/"&gt;anagen&lt;/a&gt;, the several month window when hair actively lengthens, is where many therapies try to act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signals that include IGF-1 and FGF-7 influence follicle behavior in lab systems and animal models. A scholarly overview outlines how these signals extend the growth window, with supporting growth factor details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Centella asiatica&lt;/em&gt; also appears in cosmetic research. Topical preparations that deliver plant-derived vesicles have shown skin tolerance and signs of anti-inflammatory action in small human studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ingredient list also included caffeine and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Panthenol" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;panthenol&lt;/a&gt;, which are common in shampoos. Caffeine has been explored for scalp microcirculation, while panthenol primarily conditions the hair shaft rather than stimulating new growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-next-phase-of-testing"&gt;Next phase of testing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Larger trials should enroll people with diagnosed pattern hair loss and report absolute changes in hairs per square inch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They should track photographs, shedding counts, and patient-reported outcomes, and they should compare results with minoxidil and finasteride directly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safety deserves close tracking because growth cues are biologically active. Trials should monitor &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/fat-injection-therapy-offers-hope-for-reversing-baldness/"&gt;scalp&lt;/a&gt; irritation, unwanted shedding at the start of treatment, and any systemic effects even if risk is expected to be low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manufacturers will also need to show lot-to-lot consistency. If plant vesicle cargo drives benefit, batches must be standardized or variability will swamp the signal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-where-this-leaves-patients-now"&gt;Where this leaves patients now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evidence-based options still matter most in today’s world. &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/finally-a-cure-for-baldness-scientists-regrow-hair-using-stem-cells/"&gt;Minoxidil&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/daily-dose-finasteride-magic-pill-regrows-hair-heals-prostate-boosts-heart-health/"&gt;finasteride&lt;/a&gt; remain the proven standards from randomized trials and medical guidance, and they work best when started early in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Set expectations accordingly. Even with clean eight-week data, hair biology moves on the scale of months, not days, and gains usually require steady use to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, the new data from the &lt;em&gt;Centella asiatica&lt;/em&gt; serum are very intriguing, but more tests are needed. They show a measurable signal in a strict but short test and justify moving to larger studies with hard, patient-centered endpoints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2025.09.10.25335404v1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;medRxiv&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:29:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNZzlkY09RWUtPOWdRR1NFdXlINWdxYjYxUzJ5VkQ3MmFWRUNneXdBcXZRX3JzR2l2V1pKNEpDLXhzc0RucW5DMGR4N29mQkk0ZUpFLU1iZEh4S2xvelFTWGVKZHVkYnF3bGhnWWsta0ZBVFFCLUY4dVdLZ2lsaTRlaFlPdmZ0QmJGOVFObTgzQ2JFMlBCY2lrTzZB</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，流行的止痛药几乎没有缓解作用，会增加严重的健康风险- KTVU</title><link>https://www.ktvu.com/news/tramadol-offers-little-relief-raises-serious-health-risks-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body" data-v-6c8e215c&gt;&lt;div original-article-post="livenowfox.com/news/tramadol-offers-little-relief-raises-serious-health-risks-study-finds" origination_station="LNFX" class="big-top featured article-ct" data-v-7d0efd03 data-v-6c8e215c&gt;&lt;div class="m featured-img" data-v-7d0efd03&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.foxtv.com/static.livenowfox.com/www.livenowfox.com/content/uploads/2025/12/764/432/gettyimages-2180870505-scaled.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1" alt="" data-v-7d0efd03&gt; &lt;span class="overlay" data-v-7d0efd03&gt;article&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="info" data-v-7d0efd03&gt;&lt;div class="caption" data-v-7d0efd03&gt;&lt;p data-v-7d0efd03&gt;&lt;span data-v-7d0efd03&gt;FILE - Tramadol capsules (Photo by NICOLAS GUYONNET/Hans Lucas/AFP via Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;A widely prescribed &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/pain-management/painkillers" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;opioid painkiller&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; showed limited effectiveness and increased risk of negative effects in a new analysis published in BMJ Evidence-Based Medicine.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;The study examined tramadol, a common prescription opioid used to treat &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/pain-management" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;chronic pain&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails" data-v-6c8e215c&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-js" data-v-6c8e215c&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-ad-pos="inread" data-ad-size="1x1" class="ad gpt" data-v-6c8e215c&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;Tramadol has historically been perceived as a safer or less addictive opioid, which has contributed to its widespread use in chronic pain treatment, the study authors noted.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;"Often, we may use tramadol to avoid more addictive drugs like other opioids, though in fact tramadol is a synthetic opioid. It is much milder," &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/person/s/marc-siegel" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Marc Siegel&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, senior medical analyst for Fox News, told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;In the new analysis, researchers used data from 19 randomized clinical trials involving 6,506 adults with conditions including osteoarthritis, chronic low back pain, neuropathic pain and fibromyalgia. All the studies compared tramadol to a placebo treatment.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;Overall, tramadol led to a small decrease in pain, but the amount of relief was less than what is usually considered clinically meaningful, the authors reported.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;"It is notable how minimal the pain reduction was and how clearly the study highlighted the elevated risk of serious adverse events, even over relatively short &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;trial durations&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;," Alopi M. Patel, M.D., pain medicine physician at Icahn School of Medicine at Mt. Sinai in New York City, told Fox News Digital. (Patel was not involved in the study.)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/more-people-turn-acupuncture-back-pain-without-opioids-study-shows-relief" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;MORE PEOPLE TURN TO ACUPUNCTURE FOR BACK PAIN AS STUDY SHOWS RELIEF&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;Participants receiving tramadol experienced a higher risk of adverse events, both serious and non-serious, compared with those receiving a placebo. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;Serious adverse events primarily included &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/heart-health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cardiovascular events&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, such as chest pain, coronary artery disease and congestive heart failure. The authors concluded that tramadol likely increases the risk of heart-related issues.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;The authors concluded that the benefits of tramadol for chronic pain are small and that the harms likely outweigh the benefits. The findings call into question the &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/healthy-living/medications" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;use of tramadol&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for chronic pain conditions, they stated.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 data-v-6c8e215c&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study limitations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;Most of the trials included in the analysis were short, with treatment periods ranging from two to 16 weeks and follow-up periods from three to 15 weeks. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;This limited the ability to assess long-term outcomes, the researchers acknowledged.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;The authors reported that many outcomes had a high risk of bias, which may have exaggerated the apparent benefits and minimized the reported harms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;The trials involved several different types of chronic pain, but the data were not detailed enough to draw conclusions for any specific condition. This makes it "harder to generalize the findings to specific &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/health-care" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;patient populations&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;," noted Patel.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;Though the study has value, Siegel said, "looking at slight increased rates of cancer or &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/heart-health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;heart disease&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; among those on the drug is completely misleading, because it is not controlled for other factors and there is no evidence or hint of causation."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;"You would have to first look at underlying characteristics of that group who took the meds."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;The doctor also pointed out that the study "doesn’t compare [tramadol] with &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/topic/opioid-crisis" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;full-on opioids&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; like Percocet."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;Experts emphasize that patients should not stop taking tramadol abruptly, as doing so can lead to withdrawal symptoms. Those looking to change their medication should consult a doctor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;"I recommend that clinicians and patients engage in transparent, shared decision-making that considers tramadol’s modest benefits alongside its risks," Patel advised.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;Fox News Digital reached out to several manufacturers of tramadol requesting comment.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-6c8e215c&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LINK: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/widely-prescribed-opioid-shows-minimal-pain-relief-higher-heart-risk-study-finds" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get updates and more at foxnews.com.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;     &lt;p data-uid="fts-ar-17" class="vendor-unit" data-v-6c8e215c&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KTVU</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:21:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPUF8xU0NyOVRZRVhBWkszMEw4T050VGlaUzAtVU5yYWZIeVJTc3JONXNoUEtOVTl6OTVDdjJFMk9MeXp4bDllakc4LWtGbmFlSDV2Q29nRnp0RTVPZkllSi1JYnFvenhDeTgyRVRheDNfRmcza0M3Rk5pbGlVaHgwRFhGdDdaekwxYVdMeldyX0g4OEQ3NmtQNjdTa9IBoAFBVV95cUxQUVZXYS15SFdHclEzRTVHbmZnNEFjbWlRa0Y5MDl2dEpvcllmQWlCcWllaGYtNWlieUlyR1lvd01WNlcxU1RBd3VKSDhWR3N6a0ZDdm9JNmxCM283RXZPYjlSbFhmRGYyU2l1VTh3UWJZWmxHNHRWQUw1NW9Yb1dSMThfeThOaWE2eE5kTG04VV9HYUtJdF9Id1BUeVktT0o1</guid></item><item><title>研究人员发现挑鼻子与阿尔茨海默病之间存在令人费解的联系- The Mirror US</title><link>https://www.themirror.com/news/health/researchers-find-puzzling-link-between-1582076</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oops.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;Our website is temporarily delivering an degraded response in your location. We are working hard to get it back online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mirror US</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxObzJCbHQyY20yT1lpajVldG00alY3YUVFLWN6bC03WEVtOVl0aEVSM2hJZWt5a3VlcWVycFVrS3JwemRBeVNPbW92aU9sVGNPcDZELXloWUpydjBhSWFSbUpZdTc5a2NnN2Y2UjRHNWY4elk0b1F4U0ZxMFF4NjBmYmdqT2ZlQk5WQWlZZ9IBkgFBVV95cUxORUtMbzhHRkVMeUhlSGNDd1hnSUdOMC02bjhnVmhoX1dVYW0wV3BJanlYOG00bTVERF9PNmxMMjVyeGxSN2d2MWk2OG4zUHdXd2pxdE96U2tVRXZ6b1FycGdwMi1KM1QyUXowWmpHa3c2aXFHZnN3dTRVd3JIMHFKcEdaeVNfRzNUY0xseUxYdWw1Zw</guid></item><item><title>对12,000名儿童进行的大脑研究重写了医生认为多动症药物的工作原理-研究发现</title><link>https://studyfinds.org/brain-scans-how-doctors-thought-adhd-medications-work/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;&lt;div class="post-featured-image"&gt;&lt;img src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Adderall-ADHD-medicine-1200x800.jpeg" alt="Closeup of Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) Medication Adderall"&gt;&lt;p class="post-featured-image-caption"&gt;Adderall is commonly prescribed medication for ADHD. (© Alex DiStasi  - stock.adobe.com)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-stimulants-mimic-a-night-of-sound-sleep-rather-than-directly-boost-attention"&gt;Stimulants Mimic A Night Of Sound Sleep Rather Than Directly Boost Attention&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-in-a-nutshell"&gt;In A Nutshell&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not attention networks:&lt;/strong&gt; ADHD medications primarily affect brain regions controlling arousal and wakefulness, not the attention networks scientists believed they targeted for 80+ years.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sleep connection:&lt;/strong&gt; Taking stimulants produced brain patterns nearly identical to getting adequate sleep. Sleep-deprived kids’ brains were temporarily “rescued” by medication.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No cognitive boost for well-rested kids:&lt;/strong&gt; Children without ADHD who got enough sleep saw zero improvement in grades or test scores from stimulants, only faster reaction times.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Still works for ADHD:&lt;/strong&gt; Medications help children with ADHD by increasing wakefulness and making boring tasks feel more rewarding, not by enhancing attention circuits as previously thought.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Taking an ADHD medication produces brain patterns nearly identical to those of getting a good night’s rest, according to the largest brain imaging study of stimulant drugs ever conducted. The finding challenges decades of assumptions about how these medications work and raises a practical question for families and clinicians: for some kids, how much of “focus trouble” is actually a sleep problem in disguise?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers from Washington University School of Medicine analyzed brain scans from 11,875 children ages 8-11 and found that stimulants like &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/ritalin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Ritalin&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/adderall/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Adderall&lt;/a&gt; primarily affect regions associated with arousal and wakefulness, not the attention networks doctors have long believed they targeted. The brain changes closely matched those seen when comparing well-rested versus &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/sleep-affecting-child-appetite/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sleep-deprived children&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Most remarkably, children who hadn’t gotten enough sleep but took stimulants showed brain patterns indistinguishable from well-rested children. The medications appeared to rescue the brain from sleep deprivation, at least temporarily.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Not the Attention Networks After All&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For decades, scientists believed &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/ADHD-medications-scaled.jpg"&gt;ADHD medications&lt;/a&gt; worked by boosting activity in brain networks responsible for attention and cognitive control. The new findings, published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; paint a different picture.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Among 5,795 children with complete high-quality brain scan data, 337 had taken a stimulant on the morning of their scan. The largest medication-related changes appeared in brain regions linked to arousal and wakefulness, not in the regions scientists have long associated with &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/focus/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;focus&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/concentration/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;concentration&lt;/a&gt;. The study was large enough to easily detect even small changes in attention networks, yet found none.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The second-biggest effects occurred in brain regions governing reward. These systems help determine which tasks are worth pursuing. Rather than improving attention directly, stimulants may make &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/boredom/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;boring tasks&lt;/a&gt; feel more rewarding, increasing persistence without boosting cognitive ability.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-144611"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-1200x800.jpeg.webp 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-475x317.jpeg.webp 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-768x512.jpeg.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-400x267.jpeg.webp 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-378x252.jpeg.webp 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-276x184.jpeg.webp 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-600x400.jpeg.webp 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-1200x800.jpeg" alt="Parent giving her young child a prescription drug pill" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-1200x800.jpeg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-475x317.jpeg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-400x267.jpeg 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-378x252.jpeg 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-276x184.jpeg 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-600x400.jpeg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;ADHD drugs help children improve their focus and concentration, but not by targeting parts of the brain that control attention. (© ShunTerra – stock.adobe.com)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Sleep Crisis Connection&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/sleep/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sleep connection&lt;/a&gt; may explain more than how stimulants work. In this study, only about half of kids reported getting the recommended 9 hours of sleep per night. Among children in the full study cohort taking stimulants on scan day, only 20.7% met the study’s strict ADHD criteria, though most met broader diagnostic standards.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The behavioral data reinforced the sleep link. Children with less sleep who took stimulants showed the clearest improvements in school grades. Well-rested children without ADHD saw no academic benefit from the medications. Stimulants appeared to compensate for insufficient rest rather than boost cognitive abilities beyond normal.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Sleep duration itself was associated with improvements in &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/more-sleep-boost-your-gpa/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;school performance,&lt;/a&gt; cognitive test scores, and working memory. Getting adequate sleep provided benefits similar to those stimulants offered children with ADHD or sleep deprivation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers measured brain activity while children rested in a scanner, then confirmed their findings in a controlled study where five adults were scanned extensively, both with and without Ritalin. The adult study showed the same patterns: decreased activity within motor and sensory networks and increased connections between those regions and reward systems, with no changes in attention networks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To further confirm the arousal connection, researchers compared their findings against three independent brain studies using different measurement techniques. All three pointed to the same conclusion: stimulants primarily affect the brain’s wakefulness system.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The cognitive testing data aligned with these brain findings. Among children without ADHD who got adequate sleep, taking stimulants provided no improvement in school grades, standardized test scores, or accuracy on working memory tasks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Benefits were concentrated in two groups: children diagnosed with ADHD and children who weren’t getting enough sleep. For children with ADHD, stimulants brought their performance up to their peers’ level. For sleep-deprived children regardless of ADHD status, stimulants showed &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/adhd-drugs-reduce-risk-of-death/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;the clearest benefit&lt;/a&gt; in improving school grades.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This pattern shows stimulants work less by boosting cognitive ability and more by compensating for deficits in arousal and motivation. The one universal effect was faster reaction times, which improved by about 100 milliseconds across all children taking stimulants.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;picture decoding="async" class="wp-image-147389"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-1200x799.jpg.webp 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-475x316.jpg.webp 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-768x512.jpg.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-400x266.jpg.webp 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-378x252.jpg.webp 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-276x184.jpg.webp 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-600x400.jpg.webp 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-1200x799.jpg" alt="Little girl battling insomnia at night can't sleep and lies awake in bed with a clock" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-1200x799.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-475x316.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-768x512.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-400x266.jpg 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-378x252.jpg 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-276x184.jpg 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-600x400.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Poor sleep could be a critical driver of ADHD symptoms. (Photo by SB Arts Media on Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Smart Drug Myth&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The findings cast doubt on the widespread belief that stimulants act as cognitive enhancers for people without ADHD. While these medications are increasingly used by students and professionals seeking a mental edge, the study found no cognitive benefits among well-rested children without &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/attention/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;attention problems&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Previous research has shown that people taking stimulants often feel their performance has improved even when objective measurements show no benefit or slight impairment. The subjective confidence boost doesn’t match reality for those already performing well.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study confirmed a well-established pattern: stimulants help low-performers more than high-performers. The medications appeared to bring underperforming children (whether due to ADHD or sleep deprivation) up to baseline rather than elevating anyone’s abilities above normal.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There’s no question as to whether stimulant medications help children with ADHD. The data clearly shows they do. Children with ADHD who took stimulants &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/major-adhd-treatment-review-reveals-best-options-medications-adults-children/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;showed improvements&lt;/a&gt; in school grades and cognitive test performance compared to those who didn’t take medication.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Rather, the study reframes how these medications work. Instead of directly boosting attention circuits, stimulants increase general arousal and boost the motivational value of tasks. This makes them effective for ADHD not because they improve focus per se, but because they increase drive to persist at unrewarding activities and reduce task-switching behavior.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research included children taking various formulations: methylphenidate (Ritalin), dexmethylphenidate (Focalin), mixed amphetamine salts (Adderall), and lisdexamfetamine (Vyvanse). All showed similar brain patterns despite chemical differences between drugs.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Warning About Masking Sleep Problems&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While stimulants temporarily rescued brain activity in sleep-deprived children, researchers warn this doesn’t make sleep deprivation acceptable. Growing evidence points to serious &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/poor-sleep-fuel-mental-health/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;long-term consequences&lt;/a&gt; of insufficient sleep in children, including increased risk of depression, cellular stress, and neuronal loss.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The rescue effect appears to work only while medication is active. What happens when drug levels drop in the afternoon remains unclear. The researchers note that mounting evidence points to cumulative health consequences of long-term sleep deprivation. The short-term brain improvements don’t address the broader health impacts of chronic insufficient rest.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Since sleep disturbance is both a common symptom of ADHD and a frequent side effect of stimulant treatment, the research prompts doctors to carefully assess sleep problems before and after prescribing these medications.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/parenting/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Parents&lt;/a&gt; might question whether their child’s attention problems stem from ADHD or simply from not getting enough rest. The study shows that addressing sleep issues could provide some of the same cognitive benefits as medication without pharmaceutical intervention.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Among children in the full study cohort, 7.8% were prescribed stimulants and 6.2% took them on scan day. The medications are used for various conditions beyond ADHD, including traumatic brain injury, narcolepsy, and as appetite suppressants, reflecting real-world prescribing patterns.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research represents one of the largest brain imaging studies of stimulant medications ever conducted. However, limitations exist. The study lacked precise information about medication timing and formulation for individual children, which could have led to underestimating medication effects. The study also couldn’t separate effects of specific medications or &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/adhd/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ADHD subtypes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;These medications work, but perhaps not the way doctors and patients have long believed. Rather than fine-tuning attention circuits, stimulants appear to solve attention problems by increasing wakefulness and making tasks feel more rewarding. For the millions of American children &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/adhd-medication/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;prescribed these drugs&lt;/a&gt;, the research doesn’t change whether they should take them. But it does change how we understand what the medications are doing in their brains.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-quaternary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-paper-summary"&gt;Paper Summary&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-limitations"&gt;Limitations&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The researchers note several limitations to their findings. The study examines a large, diverse group of children taking different stimulant medications and diagnosed with various ADHD subtypes, which reflects real-world treatment but limits the ability to investigate effects of specific drugs or diagnostic categories. The ABCD Study lacked precise data on medication timing and formulation (immediate versus delayed release) for individual participants, which may have led to underestimating the effects of stimulants on brain connectivity. The study could not account for all pharmacokinetic factors that influence how drugs work in the body. The term “attention” is itself imprecise and multifaceted, making it difficult to directly compare findings across different studies that may define and measure attention differently. Comparison with previous research is complicated by limited availability of source data from earlier studies and the use of different brain parcellation methods and network definitions across studies. The precision imaging validation study, while providing highly detailed data from each participant, included only five healthy adults without ADHD, limiting statistical power for some analyses. The study focused on acute effects during scanning and did not assess longer-term effects or what happens when medication wears off.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-funding-and-disclosures"&gt;Funding and Disclosures&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This work was supported by multiple grants from the National Institutes of Health (NIH) including EB029343, MH121518, MH129493, NS123345, NS098482, DA041148, DA04112, MH115357, MH096773, MH122066, MH121276, MH124567, NS129521, NS133486, NS140256, DA057486, and MH129616. Additional funding came from the National Spasmodic Dysphonia Association, Mallinckrodt Institute of Radiology pilot funding, the McDonnell Center for Systems Neuroscience, the Behavior Research Foundation, the Taylor Family Institute Fund for Innovative Psychiatric Research, and the Extreme Science and Engineering Discovery Environment (XSEDE) Bridges at the Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center. Two of the senior authors (D.A.F. and N.U.F.D.) disclosed financial interests in Turing Medical and may benefit financially if the company successfully markets FIRMM motion-monitoring software products. They may receive royalty income based on FIRMM technology developed at Washington University School of Medicine and Oregon Health and Sciences University and licensed to Turing Medical Inc. Both are co-founders of Turing Medical Inc. These potential conflicts of interest are reviewed and managed by Washington University School of Medicine, Oregon Health and Sciences University, and the University of Minnesota. The data used in this study came from the Adolescent Brain Cognitive Development (ABCD) Study, a multi-site longitudinal study funded by the National Institutes of Health and additional federal partners.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-publication-information"&gt;Publication Information&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Stimulant medications affect arousal and reward, not attention networks&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authors:&lt;/strong&gt; Benjamin P. Kay, Muriah D. Wheelock, Joshua S. Siegel, Deanna M. Barch, Damien A. Fair, Nico U.F. Dosenbach, and colleagues from Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis, University of Minnesota, Oregon Health &amp;amp; Science University, and other institutions. The lead contact and corresponding author is Benjamin P. Kay (&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="3153545f5b505c585f1f5a504871464442455d1f545544"&gt;[email protected]&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X#"&gt;Benjamin P. Kay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Journal:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Volume 188, Issue 26, Pages 7529-7546.e20, December 24, 2025 | &lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; S0092-8674(25)01373-X&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study was published as open access. Data are publicly available through the ABCD Study database (doi: 10.15154/1503209) and Zenodo (doi: 10.5281/zenodo.17916532).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Study Finds</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:11:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQVGE4Q01IZWlfM3FnYTVCMEFzODZRUG9nWDF5TGZwckExaXMtOW16dWZOenRId1NIRGVTRzh6VzZjSE9BWVR6UHRSbnVtc3lYRkpuWnJqaVBraEQxSjl6blVwWWhYd2hVWTFhOGxSYmwwME5aV1RKZlUxMTlxS0x5N0dLWQ</guid></item><item><title>“超级老人”关于如何过健康生活的5个提示-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/25/super-agers-advice-healthy-life/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TO6TPK6QLRHQLAHDAWNLSTXVUY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Many of us want to age well — staying in good physical and cognitive health into our 80s, 90s, 100s and even beyond. Winning the genetic lottery can help in that quest. But even if you don’t have the genes linked to &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/11/25/longevity-organ-aging-disease/" target="_blank"&gt;longevity&lt;/a&gt;, you can increase your chances of aging well with certain lifestyle choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPbDF0Q3ZveUxPdzlsbGpGTlRjdlBjSjBKSEZEN1pWNW5WMWR4OXNOWDZaazladUdlNlp1NFJwbEhMY2J4bjZHSGNyM181Ymg1emEtcVlhLWdrVzFRaE9pN3haNTljb0l3d1F2S2doZ1RwN3pLMUNNLVNydGE0WFBzVEFiM0NOazdNcHVJ</guid></item></channel></rss>