<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>减肥刺拳如何改变城市生活-《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/2164f23c-9602-4bcd-9c39-f310861dfd48</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMicEFVX3lxTE9jQmNBZC1yZy1CNjduLUlDWWo0ZGxkTHpmWFFveFpkQ29nN2tEaHgwTHlxLXF1WjRWRUQ0UHplX0NDZXROV25NekFhbTZtRFY4XzYtSVZpVll0ZzA3LVFBUWw4ZkdrdVFmVWNlOUlUODI?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;How weight-loss jabs are changing life in the City&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Financial Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMickFVX3lxTE1FWFpUekY0U1VWZEowZDJ2UVdjYnA2bEFUQmo4M0dJTUlvWHBjZXN5NnRtV1hNN1dETGJIaXdVSTY0VEVHLXhjamptNTAzQVdXVkdGSmNrZGdUSDV5TGRidVZnbFByTmJKRUVPQ0dVMEtQUQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Searching for new weight loss treatments&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;pharmaphorum&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxPRVVCdVNZdE1GOTFHcVpELTF6Rzl4OWRyTXpEZHd3MFZNb25vS0hZQzZSRHZOSFRRQm5sQ1lKY1dtRkN4UDRWRlZJeHlpeEJvZ081RUJ4TGJodEExNWpzcGcydXJVRTN4US1oQjBXRDVQMWJzUndXUjNaa0dRX3FIOUNrb05uRjg4elpRZW45X3NFUEMtWHJNVlNaMmZ2T05zemI0OEsyN294TFBodHdwLW1lNHEzQ09H?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Weight-loss jab prescriptions double as doctors tackle obesity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiY0FVX3lxTE5JdVQ0NjB0c2pSWi1YSmRuMWZmSGcxNEFrbzdOdnU2WlBBaFg5VW5oUkxsTU8zaDNPMFhRVVA3bXdHQlpNSm9sbS1uemRyVVJ6aFludHgzSHNmU0E5cTZuZ2pwZw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;A Shot at Better Health?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Enable Magazine&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxOM1gzTDZ3UVUzLW9oWGJKcU1iVTJMNWFTT05wODlUZm02bEI1QXFUOE9xSG9fNmloQllPVUxEb0JmcUFVTVZ3VzgtRUhoQ0pWa2hHdXVFeGU3VzlQbWk4UDdLQkhKQnYybGdXYUh1TE1VbnV5NndIbTZpX3ZtckVsbzRwQV9oelpQaVFnQ25SQ05IYnZ1YTZrbFBuSmhrTFo1MkxPSg?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Obese Scots prescribed weight-loss drug in record numbers&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Telegraph&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:00:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9jQmNBZC1yZy1CNjduLUlDWWo0ZGxkTHpmWFFveFpkQ29nN2tEaHgwTHlxLXF1WjRWRUQ0UHplX0NDZXROV25NekFhbTZtRFY4XzYtSVZpVll0ZzA3LVFBUWw4ZkdrdVFmVWNlOUlUODI</guid></item><item><title>我最奇怪的圣诞节：在节礼日，我在水槽里呕吐–并开始怀疑我有一个神秘的状况-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/26/my-weirdest-christmas-vomited-mysterious-condition</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Waking foggy-headed and with the room spinning on 26 December is surely not an uncommon condition. Who among us hasn’t felt the effects of overindulgence on &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/christmas" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Christmas&lt;/a&gt; Day?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;These were my immediate thoughts when I rose in such a state in my parents’ house in Dublin two years ago. An hour later, the room continued its relentless swirl, nausea was building and it was becoming hard to stand. So far, so Christmas hangover. I remained in bed and waited for things to blow over. They didn’t. Gradually, family members stuck their heads into my childhood bedroom and wondered if everything was OK. I could only say that I felt quite strange.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After a couple of hours, I thought I was over the worst, so I joined my mother, sister and wife in the kitchen. Moments later, they watched on helplessly as I vomited in the kitchen sink, a silent bond created between them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This process repeated itself several times over the next day, so I visited a doctor. The GP diagnosed &lt;a href="https://www.meandve.org.uk/information-and-support/symptoms-and-conditions" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;a case of vertigo&lt;/a&gt;: not any Hitchcock-infused vision, but dizziness and nausea, usually caused by inner ear problems. Often this lasts only seconds, but there can be more prolonged incidents. I was prescribed medication to restore order.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The wider oddity was that, at the time, I was working as a producer on a podcast documentary for BBC Sounds called &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p0lgrwds" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Havana Helmet Club&lt;/a&gt;, investigating &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2024/apr/01/havana-syndrome-linked-to-russian-unit-media-investigation-suggests" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Havana syndrome&lt;/a&gt; – the 2016 case of mystery brain injuries affecting CIA agents and US embassy officials in Cuba and farther afield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-19m4xhf"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;I wondered if somehow I had imagined myself into sickness&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;I had spent the previous year researching all aspects of this strange story: starting with the array of symptoms the patients had begun experiencing, seemingly out of nowhere. Most reported hearing piercing sounds in their homes in Havana, followed by overwhelming headaches, dizziness, nausea and, eventually, lasting brain trauma. There was speculation about &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2021/jun/02/microwave-weapons-havana-syndrome-experts" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Russian microwave weapons&lt;/a&gt; and jokes about an “immaculate concussion”. Politicians, scientists, diplomats and security experts argued endlessly about it. Some claimed people had simply imagined it or overreacted to the sound of crickets – suggestions that the victims were rather hostile to. Doctors explained that even if there wasn’t a weapon, other triggers – physical and mental – could cause a dramatic reaction in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Shortly before my own incident, I had been listening to an interview a colleague had done with a neurologist. The doctor was talking about how, when you become aware of a certain part of your body, your mind can then overly focus on it. If you’re told you have a family history of heart disease, for example, you might suddenly start noticing how you feel out of breath walking up stairs. In the weeks after listening to this, I had occasionally noticed mild head rushes when I bent over or stood up quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In my vertigo-addled state, I attempted to explain all of this to the doctor. I wasn’t claiming I had been dragged into a dastardly spy plot. More, I wondered if somehow I had imagined myself into sickness. Could something a person had read about take possession of their body? When I finished this spiel, she looked at me politely, said, “Right, yes,” and explained it wasn’t an unusual affliction. The pills should do the trick after a week, she told me, and if it happened again I would need vestibular physiotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She was right, of course, and it passed relatively smoothly. But it did make me think of everyone who had been caught up in the case of Havana syndrome. As well as needing care, many were consumed by a need to know what had happened to them. My illness was minor, but I could see how easily such thinking can take over when you get struck down out of the blue. The list of causal factors for vertigo and vestibular disorders includes everything from lying down to standing up, air travel and much else in between. Most dismayingly for someone in their 40s, it &lt;a href="https://www.meandve.org.uk/information-and-support/symptoms-and-conditions/bppv" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;“becomes progressively more common with age”&lt;/a&gt;. We are where we are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Rather than go down the rabbit hole, I decided it was better just to be grateful that my bout of ill health had occurred the day &lt;em&gt;after&lt;/em&gt; my big Christmas dinner – even if the medication did mean I could only sip non-alcoholic “champagne” on New Year’s Eve. Perhaps a fate worse than vertigo itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNYTNONDhUOFBWVEFDZ2ZTUXRNNDZRam5WQXgwTjhDUFhwZnFlTHpmMnB4N3pma0NJZHRtb1VHczhFa2RneWM4RFBCVXZnNjlHbGtkY2JhUENGbkNNbDZJcmxSaW44LXA2RjQ4VTYwLTQtVFNIS3ZhVDNOeVdTUGU2T2JRc2JjeVBkRUdGQU50YjJDOGZqMm51MzV3ckpZWFZDMEpFeXhB</guid></item><item><title>在日本树蛙体内发现强效抗癌药物- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/powerful-anti-cancer-drug-discovered-inside-japanese-tree-frog</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Scientists have discovered a promising new approach to fighting  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="186339" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; in the gut bacteria of a Japanese tree frog, with one strain completely shrinking tumors in mice, with no severe side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese tree frog (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Japanese_tree_frog"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dryophytes japonicus&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) wasn't a lucky find. We know amphibians and reptiles &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/026119290703500514"&gt;rarely develop cancer&lt;/a&gt;, and researchers from the Japan Advanced Institute of Science and Technology wanted to see whether transferring gut bacteria from frogs to mice might have any anti-cancer effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of 45 different bacterial strains from frogs, newts, and lizards were shortlisted for testing, with 9 strains showing notable tumor-fighting capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most impressive of the bunch was the frog bacteria, &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ewingella_americana"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ewingella americana&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/simple-supplement-combo-could-help-fight-deadly-brain-cancer"&gt;Simple Supplement Combo Could Help Fight Deadly Brain Cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings suggest that gut microbiomes of lower vertebrates harbor numerous uncharacterized bacterial species with exceptional therapeutic potential," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2025.2599562"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186342" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186342" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CancerAction.jpg" alt="Cancer treatment diagram" class="wp-image-186342 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CancerAction.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CancerAction-600x319.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186342" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The bacteria seem to enlist the help of immune cells to fight cancer. (Iwata et al., &lt;em&gt;Gut Microbes&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;While other strains showed short-lived anti-tumor effects, a single dose of &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; didn't just shrink tumors in treated mice – their tumors disappeared completely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, when cancer cells were reintroduced 30 days later to mice treated with &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-vaccine-for-two-deadly-cancers-shows-promise-in-clinical-trial"&gt;tumors didn't develop&lt;/a&gt; in the following month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further analysis revealed that &lt;em&gt;E. americana &lt;/em&gt;works in two ways: It attacks tumor tissue while also amping up the body's immune response, enlisting extra help from T cells, B cells, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/22313-neutrophils"&gt;and neutrophils&lt;/a&gt; – key fighters in the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers think &lt;em&gt;E. americana's &lt;/em&gt;effectiveness lies in the way it has evolved to survive in low-oxygen environments (such as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/simple-supplement-combo-could-help-fight-deadly-brain-cancer"&gt;cancer tumors&lt;/a&gt;) that typically suppress immune cells and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-023-01332-8"&gt;reduce the effectiveness&lt;/a&gt; of chemotherapy drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on these preliminary animal studies, &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; seems fairly safe, too. The bacteria were cleared quickly from the bloodstream of mice, didn't cause any long-lasting toxicity, and didn't appear to affect healthy organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Injections of &lt;em&gt;E. americana &lt;/em&gt;were also more effective at shrinking tumors in mice than several current treatments, including &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doxorubicin"&gt;doxorubicin&lt;/a&gt;, a chemotherapy drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These results suggest that &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; represents a promising therapeutic candidate with an acceptable safety profile suitable for potential clinical development," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2025.2599562"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's still early days, and much more testing is needed to see whether the findings of these &lt;a href="https://www.crick.ac.uk/research/animal-research/why-and-how-we-use-animals/why-do-we-use-mice-in-research"&gt;animal studies&lt;/a&gt; could translate into humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also want to test &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; against other types of cancers in animal models, see how it works in combination with other treatments, and experiment with drug-delivery methods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safety will be paramount if bacterial treatment is to progress to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="186339" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;E. americana&lt;/em&gt; are bacteria after all, and can &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/antibiotics13060559"&gt;cause infections&lt;/a&gt; in humans. Figuring out if they can be used in people without any harmful effects will be a challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, scientists are exploring other ways of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-are-hacking-bacteria-to-fight-cancer-then-self-destruct"&gt;co-opting bacteria to kill cancer cells&lt;/a&gt;, with at least one bacterial therapy already used to treat some cases of bladder cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frogs and other reptiles may add to that arsenal in time by providing another source of potential cancer therapeutics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings demonstrate the vast untapped potential residing within diverse microbial ecosystems and highlight the critical importance of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-species-of-tiny-pumpkin-toadlet-discovered-in-brazils-cloud-forests"&gt;biodiversity conservation efforts&lt;/a&gt; in advancing medical science and therapeutic innovation," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2025.2599562"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2025.2599562"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gut Microbes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 21:02:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQVENmaTZFeURhalBUazFhOWFPMkhPMElZbzhCNHFRT3VReVY1YWJpc0pqd0NxeW9fd0F5UGQtNWNodThVSkNLVnRGSDJsbXBIZ2Q4Yi0taEZWY2FhY2YtNDlUYUdzeWhXYVZ6aUZGdEtmMjNfVEFadDM4ZlVGM2ZZS3VaQlI5WHZjMEhqUkhxSzhidXVCRGc</guid></item><item><title>实验性阿尔茨海默氏症药物可以及早预防疾病- NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/alzheimers-drug-nu-9-prevent-disease/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:33:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFB3M05hbWN1MDZIdTBURVpjQ3pCUllYNWhXOGZpUUh5NXhQUzVNaHU3bEgzX1l2UVFzdFJJYmdDb0w0dVlidmRraDB0dXpYZTktVkFEbWt1a0g1bUQxYXdrTlRVUDk2WVdOcGhpOXhlUTVOcExMdktXVWNJSHdJdjDSAYQBQVVfeXFMT3lTYXQ1RDBQYm5TQ0xNT3BNMjZBaGVDbjVNVFJRdjlqN3JCR2xqY21GdHY5T2U5VVdERlgtbk9XRml5RHo0dW1QdjJSYklMQmdSbDdKUVJUVnJXSDlVc1ZNQWpMT2I1QkEzVzJxSmJ2Y1lodENKMmpYeW9KYjNkUXRHV3N2</guid></item><item><title>根据科学家的说法，新的植物性血清显示在几周内头发再生- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/plant-based-serum-shown-in-lab-tests-to-boost-hair-growth-in-weeks/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team of scientists has created a daily scalp hair growth serum, using a tropical plant-based extract, that has proven to regrow hair and improve hair thickness in just 56 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The test enrolled 60 adults in a randomized, double-blind trial run by researchers in Taipei. Each person used one milliliter nightly across the scalp for eight weeks, and changes were tracked with standardized imaging. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Initial results showed a 25 percent increase in hair thickness, compared to the placebo group, in less than two months&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-fast-signal-for-hair-growth"&gt;Fast signal for hair growth&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Male-pattern &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/how-a-natural-sweetener-improves-hair-loss-treatment/"&gt;hair loss&lt;/a&gt; is common, and some current treatments do help, but results vary and take months. This short, controlled test that moves the needle faster is drawing global attention for obvious reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead researcher Dr. Tsong Min Chang of &lt;a href="https://sbc-biotech.com/"&gt;Schweitzer Biotech Company&lt;/a&gt; (SBC) led the clinical work in Taiwan. The team set out to see if a multi-part serum could nudge more follicles into active growth within a few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people try over-the-counter serums with mixed ingredients and vague claims. A tightly designed, blinded study offers cleaner signals than marketing before and after photos.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-hair-growth-serum-ingredients"&gt;Hair growth serum ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The proprietary serum uses mild &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/drinking-coffee-may-reduce-frailty-in-aging-adults/"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt; and panthenol, a moisturizer many shampoos already carry. On top of that, the formula added extracellular vesicles – tiny packets released by cells that carry signals – derived from a plant species called &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Centella_asiatica" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Centella asiatica&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also included fibroblast growth factor 7, a protein cue that supports hair-producing skin cells. The mix further added insulin-like growth factor 1, a protein signal that promotes follicle growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those choices were not random. Growth factor biology links these signals to hair cycling, and careful delivery can matter for effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-the-test-was-done"&gt;How the test was done&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Volunteers ages 18 to 60 were randomly assigned to five groups, including a placebo. Technicians measured density, thickness, length, and shedding at days 14, 28, 42, and 56 using standardized tools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four active arms stacked ingredients stepwise, from a simple base, to base plus growth factors, to base plus plant vesicles, to a full combination. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The design used placebo controls and blinding, a good way to reduce bias in a small study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-hair-growth-changed-by-day-56"&gt;Hair growth changed by day 56&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across most measures, results improved as more components were combined, with the full formula on top. Hair density rose by almost 25 percent in the combination group compared with a smaller shift on placebo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strands also measured thicker in that group. The study authors suggest the plant material may support scalp health around follicles. These outcomes hint at synergy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stepwise gains across the arms suggest each component added something, with the trio together giving the largest effect on density at the study’s endpoint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;a href="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143300/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1m.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143306/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1s.webp" alt="Representative photographs of the participants in Group E on Day 0 and Day 56 after treatment. Credit: medRxiv" class="wp-image-1991078" srcset="https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143306/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1s.webp 300w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143306/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1s-150x150.webp 150w, https://cff2.earth.com/uploads/2025/10/16143306/hair-growth_test-photos_plant-formula_medRxiv_1s-32x32.webp 32w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 300px) 100vw, 300px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Representative photographs of the participants in Group E on Day 0 and Day 56 after treatment. Click image to enlarge. Credit: medRxiv&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-short-trial-big-questions"&gt;Short trial, big questions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study involved healthy adults rather than people with clear pattern hair loss. It lasted only eight weeks, which is short relative to a full hair growth cycle and not long enough to judge durability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Company employees and consultants worked on the project and reported the outcomes, which raises routine questions about bias. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Independent replication and longer follow up are essential before any claims move beyond a small controlled test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was no head-to-head comparison with proven therapies. A direct run against minoxidil and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/daily-dose-finasteride-magic-pill-regrows-hair-heals-prostate-boosts-heart-health/"&gt;finasteride&lt;/a&gt; would show whether the new mix adds more than what is already available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-context-in-hair-growth-research"&gt;Context in hair growth research&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hair grows in cycles that include resting and growth phases. The growth phase, called &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/finally-a-cure-for-baldness-scientists-regrow-hair-using-stem-cells/"&gt;anagen&lt;/a&gt;, the several month window when hair actively lengthens, is where many therapies try to act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Signals that include IGF-1 and FGF-7 influence follicle behavior in lab systems and animal models. A scholarly overview outlines how these signals extend the growth window, with supporting growth factor details.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Centella asiatica&lt;/em&gt; also appears in cosmetic research. Topical preparations that deliver plant-derived vesicles have shown skin tolerance and signs of anti-inflammatory action in small human studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ingredient list also included caffeine and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Panthenol" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;panthenol&lt;/a&gt;, which are common in shampoos. Caffeine has been explored for scalp microcirculation, while panthenol primarily conditions the hair shaft rather than stimulating new growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-next-phase-of-testing"&gt;Next phase of testing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Larger trials should enroll people with diagnosed pattern hair loss and report absolute changes in hairs per square inch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They should track photographs, shedding counts, and patient-reported outcomes, and they should compare results with minoxidil and finasteride directly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safety deserves close tracking because growth cues are biologically active. Trials should monitor &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/fat-injection-therapy-offers-hope-for-reversing-baldness/"&gt;scalp&lt;/a&gt; irritation, unwanted shedding at the start of treatment, and any systemic effects even if risk is expected to be low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manufacturers will also need to show lot-to-lot consistency. If plant vesicle cargo drives benefit, batches must be standardized or variability will swamp the signal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-where-this-leaves-patients-now"&gt;Where this leaves patients now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evidence-based options still matter most in today’s world. &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/finally-a-cure-for-baldness-scientists-regrow-hair-using-stem-cells/"&gt;Minoxidil&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/daily-dose-finasteride-magic-pill-regrows-hair-heals-prostate-boosts-heart-health/"&gt;finasteride&lt;/a&gt; remain the proven standards from randomized trials and medical guidance, and they work best when started early in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Set expectations accordingly. Even with clean eight-week data, hair biology moves on the scale of months, not days, and gains usually require steady use to maintain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, the new data from the &lt;em&gt;Centella asiatica&lt;/em&gt; serum are very intriguing, but more tests are needed. They show a measurable signal in a strict but short test and justify moving to larger studies with hard, patient-centered endpoints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2025.09.10.25335404v1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;medRxiv&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 20:29:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNZzlkY09RWUtPOWdRR1NFdXlINWdxYjYxUzJ5VkQ3MmFWRUNneXdBcXZRX3JzR2l2V1pKNEpDLXhzc0RucW5DMGR4N29mQkk0ZUpFLU1iZEh4S2xvelFTWGVKZHVkYnF3bGhnWWsta0ZBVFFCLUY4dVdLZ2lsaTRlaFlPdmZ0QmJGOVFObTgzQ2JFMlBCY2lrTzZB</guid></item><item><title>对12,000名儿童进行的大脑研究重写了医生认为多动症药物的工作原理-研究发现</title><link>https://studyfinds.org/brain-scans-how-doctors-thought-adhd-medications-work/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;&lt;div class="post-featured-image"&gt;&lt;img src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/08/Adderall-ADHD-medicine-1200x800.jpeg" alt="Closeup of Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD) Medication Adderall"&gt;&lt;p class="post-featured-image-caption"&gt;Adderall is commonly prescribed medication for ADHD. (© Alex DiStasi  - stock.adobe.com)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-stimulants-mimic-a-night-of-sound-sleep-rather-than-directly-boost-attention"&gt;Stimulants Mimic A Night Of Sound Sleep Rather Than Directly Boost Attention&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-in-a-nutshell"&gt;In A Nutshell&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not attention networks:&lt;/strong&gt; ADHD medications primarily affect brain regions controlling arousal and wakefulness, not the attention networks scientists believed they targeted for 80+ years.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sleep connection:&lt;/strong&gt; Taking stimulants produced brain patterns nearly identical to getting adequate sleep. Sleep-deprived kids’ brains were temporarily “rescued” by medication.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No cognitive boost for well-rested kids:&lt;/strong&gt; Children without ADHD who got enough sleep saw zero improvement in grades or test scores from stimulants, only faster reaction times.&lt;/li&gt;



&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Still works for ADHD:&lt;/strong&gt; Medications help children with ADHD by increasing wakefulness and making boring tasks feel more rewarding, not by enhancing attention circuits as previously thought.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Taking an ADHD medication produces brain patterns nearly identical to those of getting a good night’s rest, according to the largest brain imaging study of stimulant drugs ever conducted. The finding challenges decades of assumptions about how these medications work and raises a practical question for families and clinicians: for some kids, how much of “focus trouble” is actually a sleep problem in disguise?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers from Washington University School of Medicine analyzed brain scans from 11,875 children ages 8-11 and found that stimulants like &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/ritalin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Ritalin&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/adderall/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Adderall&lt;/a&gt; primarily affect regions associated with arousal and wakefulness, not the attention networks doctors have long believed they targeted. The brain changes closely matched those seen when comparing well-rested versus &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/sleep-affecting-child-appetite/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sleep-deprived children&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Most remarkably, children who hadn’t gotten enough sleep but took stimulants showed brain patterns indistinguishable from well-rested children. The medications appeared to rescue the brain from sleep deprivation, at least temporarily.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Not the Attention Networks After All&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For decades, scientists believed &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/ADHD-medications-scaled.jpg"&gt;ADHD medications&lt;/a&gt; worked by boosting activity in brain networks responsible for attention and cognitive control. The new findings, published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; paint a different picture.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Among 5,795 children with complete high-quality brain scan data, 337 had taken a stimulant on the morning of their scan. The largest medication-related changes appeared in brain regions linked to arousal and wakefulness, not in the regions scientists have long associated with &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/focus/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;focus&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/concentration/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;concentration&lt;/a&gt;. The study was large enough to easily detect even small changes in attention networks, yet found none.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The second-biggest effects occurred in brain regions governing reward. These systems help determine which tasks are worth pursuing. Rather than improving attention directly, stimulants may make &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/boredom/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;boring tasks&lt;/a&gt; feel more rewarding, increasing persistence without boosting cognitive ability.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-144611"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-1200x800.jpeg.webp 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-475x317.jpeg.webp 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-768x512.jpeg.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-400x267.jpeg.webp 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-378x252.jpeg.webp 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-276x184.jpeg.webp 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-600x400.jpeg.webp 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-1200x800.jpeg" alt="Parent giving her young child a prescription drug pill" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-1200x800.jpeg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-475x317.jpeg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-400x267.jpeg 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-378x252.jpeg 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-276x184.jpeg 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/Child-medication-600x400.jpeg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;ADHD drugs help children improve their focus and concentration, but not by targeting parts of the brain that control attention. (© ShunTerra – stock.adobe.com)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Sleep Crisis Connection&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/sleep/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sleep connection&lt;/a&gt; may explain more than how stimulants work. In this study, only about half of kids reported getting the recommended 9 hours of sleep per night. Among children in the full study cohort taking stimulants on scan day, only 20.7% met the study’s strict ADHD criteria, though most met broader diagnostic standards.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The behavioral data reinforced the sleep link. Children with less sleep who took stimulants showed the clearest improvements in school grades. Well-rested children without ADHD saw no academic benefit from the medications. Stimulants appeared to compensate for insufficient rest rather than boost cognitive abilities beyond normal.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Sleep duration itself was associated with improvements in &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/more-sleep-boost-your-gpa/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;school performance,&lt;/a&gt; cognitive test scores, and working memory. Getting adequate sleep provided benefits similar to those stimulants offered children with ADHD or sleep deprivation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers measured brain activity while children rested in a scanner, then confirmed their findings in a controlled study where five adults were scanned extensively, both with and without Ritalin. The adult study showed the same patterns: decreased activity within motor and sensory networks and increased connections between those regions and reward systems, with no changes in attention networks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To further confirm the arousal connection, researchers compared their findings against three independent brain studies using different measurement techniques. All three pointed to the same conclusion: stimulants primarily affect the brain’s wakefulness system.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The cognitive testing data aligned with these brain findings. Among children without ADHD who got adequate sleep, taking stimulants provided no improvement in school grades, standardized test scores, or accuracy on working memory tasks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Benefits were concentrated in two groups: children diagnosed with ADHD and children who weren’t getting enough sleep. For children with ADHD, stimulants brought their performance up to their peers’ level. For sleep-deprived children regardless of ADHD status, stimulants showed &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/adhd-drugs-reduce-risk-of-death/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;the clearest benefit&lt;/a&gt; in improving school grades.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This pattern shows stimulants work less by boosting cognitive ability and more by compensating for deficits in arousal and motivation. The one universal effect was faster reaction times, which improved by about 100 milliseconds across all children taking stimulants.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-octonary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;picture decoding="async" class="wp-image-147389"&gt;
&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-1200x799.jpg.webp 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-475x316.jpg.webp 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-768x512.jpg.webp 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-400x266.jpg.webp 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-378x252.jpg.webp 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-276x184.jpg.webp 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-600x400.jpg.webp 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;
&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-1200x799.jpg" alt="Little girl battling insomnia at night can't sleep and lies awake in bed with a clock" srcset="https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-1200x799.jpg 1200w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-475x316.jpg 475w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-768x512.jpg 768w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-400x266.jpg 400w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-378x252.jpg 378w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-276x184.jpg 276w, https://studyfinds.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Child-insomnia-600x400.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;
&lt;/picture&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Poor sleep could be a critical driver of ADHD symptoms. (Photo by SB Arts Media on Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Smart Drug Myth&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The findings cast doubt on the widespread belief that stimulants act as cognitive enhancers for people without ADHD. While these medications are increasingly used by students and professionals seeking a mental edge, the study found no cognitive benefits among well-rested children without &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/attention/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;attention problems&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Previous research has shown that people taking stimulants often feel their performance has improved even when objective measurements show no benefit or slight impairment. The subjective confidence boost doesn’t match reality for those already performing well.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study confirmed a well-established pattern: stimulants help low-performers more than high-performers. The medications appeared to bring underperforming children (whether due to ADHD or sleep deprivation) up to baseline rather than elevating anyone’s abilities above normal.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There’s no question as to whether stimulant medications help children with ADHD. The data clearly shows they do. Children with ADHD who took stimulants &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/major-adhd-treatment-review-reveals-best-options-medications-adults-children/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;showed improvements&lt;/a&gt; in school grades and cognitive test performance compared to those who didn’t take medication.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Rather, the study reframes how these medications work. Instead of directly boosting attention circuits, stimulants increase general arousal and boost the motivational value of tasks. This makes them effective for ADHD not because they improve focus per se, but because they increase drive to persist at unrewarding activities and reduce task-switching behavior.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research included children taking various formulations: methylphenidate (Ritalin), dexmethylphenidate (Focalin), mixed amphetamine salts (Adderall), and lisdexamfetamine (Vyvanse). All showed similar brain patterns despite chemical differences between drugs.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Warning About Masking Sleep Problems&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While stimulants temporarily rescued brain activity in sleep-deprived children, researchers warn this doesn’t make sleep deprivation acceptable. Growing evidence points to serious &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/poor-sleep-fuel-mental-health/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;long-term consequences&lt;/a&gt; of insufficient sleep in children, including increased risk of depression, cellular stress, and neuronal loss.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The rescue effect appears to work only while medication is active. What happens when drug levels drop in the afternoon remains unclear. The researchers note that mounting evidence points to cumulative health consequences of long-term sleep deprivation. The short-term brain improvements don’t address the broader health impacts of chronic insufficient rest.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Since sleep disturbance is both a common symptom of ADHD and a frequent side effect of stimulant treatment, the research prompts doctors to carefully assess sleep problems before and after prescribing these medications.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/category/parenting/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Parents&lt;/a&gt; might question whether their child’s attention problems stem from ADHD or simply from not getting enough rest. The study shows that addressing sleep issues could provide some of the same cognitive benefits as medication without pharmaceutical intervention.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Among children in the full study cohort, 7.8% were prescribed stimulants and 6.2% took them on scan day. The medications are used for various conditions beyond ADHD, including traumatic brain injury, narcolepsy, and as appetite suppressants, reflecting real-world prescribing patterns.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research represents one of the largest brain imaging studies of stimulant medications ever conducted. However, limitations exist. The study lacked precise information about medication timing and formulation for individual children, which could have led to underestimating medication effects. The study also couldn’t separate effects of specific medications or &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/adhd/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;ADHD subtypes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;These medications work, but perhaps not the way doctors and patients have long believed. Rather than fine-tuning attention circuits, stimulants appear to solve attention problems by increasing wakefulness and making tasks feel more rewarding. For the millions of American children &lt;a href="https://studyfinds.org/tag/adhd-medication/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;prescribed these drugs&lt;/a&gt;, the research doesn’t change whether they should take them. But it does change how we understand what the medications are doing in their brains.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-quaternary-background-color has-background is-layout-constrained wp-block-group-is-layout-constrained"&gt;
&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-paper-summary"&gt;Paper Summary&lt;/h3&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-limitations"&gt;Limitations&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The researchers note several limitations to their findings. The study examines a large, diverse group of children taking different stimulant medications and diagnosed with various ADHD subtypes, which reflects real-world treatment but limits the ability to investigate effects of specific drugs or diagnostic categories. The ABCD Study lacked precise data on medication timing and formulation (immediate versus delayed release) for individual participants, which may have led to underestimating the effects of stimulants on brain connectivity. The study could not account for all pharmacokinetic factors that influence how drugs work in the body. The term “attention” is itself imprecise and multifaceted, making it difficult to directly compare findings across different studies that may define and measure attention differently. Comparison with previous research is complicated by limited availability of source data from earlier studies and the use of different brain parcellation methods and network definitions across studies. The precision imaging validation study, while providing highly detailed data from each participant, included only five healthy adults without ADHD, limiting statistical power for some analyses. The study focused on acute effects during scanning and did not assess longer-term effects or what happens when medication wears off.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-funding-and-disclosures"&gt;Funding and Disclosures&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This work was supported by multiple grants from the National Institutes of Health (NIH) including EB029343, MH121518, MH129493, NS123345, NS098482, DA041148, DA04112, MH115357, MH096773, MH122066, MH121276, MH124567, NS129521, NS133486, NS140256, DA057486, and MH129616. Additional funding came from the National Spasmodic Dysphonia Association, Mallinckrodt Institute of Radiology pilot funding, the McDonnell Center for Systems Neuroscience, the Behavior Research Foundation, the Taylor Family Institute Fund for Innovative Psychiatric Research, and the Extreme Science and Engineering Discovery Environment (XSEDE) Bridges at the Pittsburgh Supercomputing Center. Two of the senior authors (D.A.F. and N.U.F.D.) disclosed financial interests in Turing Medical and may benefit financially if the company successfully markets FIRMM motion-monitoring software products. They may receive royalty income based on FIRMM technology developed at Washington University School of Medicine and Oregon Health and Sciences University and licensed to Turing Medical Inc. Both are co-founders of Turing Medical Inc. These potential conflicts of interest are reviewed and managed by Washington University School of Medicine, Oregon Health and Sciences University, and the University of Minnesota. The data used in this study came from the Adolescent Brain Cognitive Development (ABCD) Study, a multi-site longitudinal study funded by the National Institutes of Health and additional federal partners.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h4 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-publication-information"&gt;Publication Information&lt;/h4&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Title:&lt;/strong&gt; Stimulant medications affect arousal and reward, not attention networks&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authors:&lt;/strong&gt; Benjamin P. Kay, Muriah D. Wheelock, Joshua S. Siegel, Deanna M. Barch, Damien A. Fair, Nico U.F. Dosenbach, and colleagues from Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis, University of Minnesota, Oregon Health &amp;amp; Science University, and other institutions. The lead contact and corresponding author is Benjamin P. Kay (&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection" class="__cf_email__" data-cfemail="3153545f5b505c585f1f5a504871464442455d1f545544"&gt;[email protected]&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X#"&gt;Benjamin P. Kay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Journal:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(25)01373-X" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Volume 188, Issue 26, Pages 7529-7546.e20, December 24, 2025 | &lt;strong&gt;DOI:&lt;/strong&gt; S0092-8674(25)01373-X&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study was published as open access. Data are publicly available through the ABCD Study database (doi: 10.15154/1503209) and Zenodo (doi: 10.5281/zenodo.17916532).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Study Finds</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:11:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQVGE4Q01IZWlfM3FnYTVCMEFzODZRUG9nWDF5TGZwckExaXMtOW16dWZOenRId1NIRGVTRzh6VzZjSE9BWVR6UHRSbnVtc3lYRkpuWnJqaVBraEQxSjl6blVwWWhYd2hVWTFhOGxSYmwwME5aV1RKZlUxMTlxS0x5N0dLWQ</guid></item><item><title>“超级老人”关于如何过健康生活的5个提示-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/25/super-agers-advice-healthy-life/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TO6TPK6QLRHQLAHDAWNLSTXVUY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Many of us want to age well — staying in good physical and cognitive health into our 80s, 90s, 100s and even beyond. Winning the genetic lottery can help in that quest. But even if you don’t have the genes linked to &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/11/25/longevity-organ-aging-disease/" target="_blank"&gt;longevity&lt;/a&gt;, you can increase your chances of aging well with certain lifestyle choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPbDF0Q3ZveUxPdzlsbGpGTlRjdlBjSjBKSEZEN1pWNW5WMWR4OXNOWDZaazladUdlNlp1NFJwbEhMY2J4bjZHSGNyM181Ymg1emEtcVlhLWdrVzFRaE9pN3haNTljb0l3d1F2S2doZ1RwN3pLMUNNLVNydGE0WFBzVEFiM0NOazdNcHVJ</guid></item><item><title>阻碍小鼠体重增加的肠道细菌- Phys.org</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2025-12-gut-bacteria-weight-gain-mice.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Phys.org</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 18:20:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE1Nb2E4Sl90ZDhGVzFQZFBqV0FQOHJaMzZkUk1tR2p5MlRtalV6ZTQ1UDhhR05DTjY5UWt1M3p4WGg2TlV3MTJUUlpIT0dpdTltNHFHTktrdnhhN1M1ZVhkYlprT1Nuak1YaEF6c1NNN3R4dw</guid></item><item><title>这种流行的止痛药可能弊大于利- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251225080723.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A large review of existing research suggests that tramadol, a strong opioid commonly prescribed for chronic pain, does not provide much meaningful relief. The analysis, published online in &lt;em&gt;BMJ Evidence Based Medicine&lt;/em&gt;, found that while tramadol can reduce pain, the improvement is modest and falls below levels typically considered clinically important.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings also point to a higher likelihood of serious side effects, including heart disease. Based on these results, the researchers conclude that tramadol's risks likely outweigh its benefits and say its use should be reduced as much as possible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Tramadol Is So Widely Used&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tramadol is a dual action opioid that doctors often prescribe for moderate to severe acute and chronic pain. Because of this, it appears in several clinical guidelines for pain management, according to the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prescriptions for tramadol have risen sharply in recent years, making it one of the most frequently used opioids in the United States. This growth may be driven by the belief that tramadol carries fewer side effects and is safer and less addictive than other short acting opioids, the authors note.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gaps in Previous Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although earlier systematic reviews have included tramadol, none offered a broad evaluation of both its effectiveness and safety across different types of chronic pain. The researchers say this left important questions unanswered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To address this, they searched research databases for randomized clinical trials published up to February 2025. These studies compared tramadol with placebo (dummy treatment) in people with chronic pain, including those with cancer related pain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the Trials Included&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final analysis covered 19 clinical trials involving 6506 participants. Five studies examined neuropathic pain, nine focused on osteoarthritis, four looked at chronic low back pain, and one studied fibromyalgia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants had an average age of 58, with ages ranging from 47 to 69. Most studies used tablets, and only one tested a topical cream. Treatment periods lasted from 2 to 16 weeks, with follow up ranging from 3 to 15 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Small Pain Relief, Higher Risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the results were combined, the data showed that tramadol did reduce pain, but only slightly and not enough to meet standards for clinically effective relief.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eight trials tracked serious side effects during follow up periods of 7 to 16 weeks. Analysis of these studies showed that tramadol was linked to about double the risk of harm compared with placebo. This increase was largely due to more reported "cardiac events," including chest pain, coronary artery disease, and congestive heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tramadol use was also associated with a higher risk of certain cancers. However, the researchers caution that the short follow up makes this result "questionable."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Common Side Effects and Study Limits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across all trials, tramadol was tied to a greater risk of milder side effects such as nausea, dizziness, constipation, and sleepiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors acknowledge that many outcomes were at high risk of bias. They suggest this likely means the benefits of tramadol are overstated while its harms are understated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opioid Risks in a Broader Context&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers emphasize the wider impact of opioid use, noting: "Approximately 60 million individuals worldwide experience the addictive effects of opioids. In 2019, drug use was responsible for approximately 600,000 deaths, with nearly 80% of these fatalities associated with opioids and approximately 25% resulting from opioid overdose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In the United States, the number of opioid-related overdose deaths increased from 49,860 in 2019 to 81,806 in 2022. Given these trends and the present findings, the use of tramadol and other opioids should be minimized to the greatest extent possible."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team concludes: "Tramadol may have a slight effect on reducing chronic pain (low certainty of evidence) while likely increasing the risk of both serious (moderate certainty of evidence) and non- serious adverse events (very low certainty of evidence). The potential harms associated with tramadol use for pain management likely outweigh its limited benefits."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 16:53:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1aUTltNC05Z2Ywdmp3VjVKS0Fpak12ZDY2Z3J6OUhnQlE5ekFOVWNDUUlsdk12TGwzMkRaSGpWcElSS0oxV2ZaZjVTRzNlTk15UFRJOWFWWlhtVTRHc1QzTmxNaUcteE1Ea2RoemF5cw</guid></item><item><title>小RFK表示，美国应该在疫苗方面将目光投向欧洲。这可能意味着美国人会越来越少。- Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/25/rfk-jr-europe-on-vaccine-schedule-00704242</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQeUxkRDU5RmY1LWpuSHBndmxwOWRzVE50RHFpQk8zbXhyZXBBSU9YYVlkUktGSkpCeEgzeTU4TTJZT3ZzOE5fcEZaNnBJUmlZZUdxWHZnSkRlOHR3LU93ZEhmY3hrd1NhTlJScXJoNnA5U0FST0xLYXRWUEMwVnA3SmVCZ1RHMDh2clBJ</guid></item><item><title>专家揭示假日菜肴会增加您患癌症的风险-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15307625/holiday-foods-colon-cancer-bacteria.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The holidays are a time for coming together with family, tearing open presents and, of course, eating heaps of hearty, delicious food. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;However, health experts warn that some of your festive favorites may come with a side of deadly consequences&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Processed meats, fried foods and sugary desserts have all been shown to induce harmful inflammation and damage DNA in the colon - potentially leading to cancer - over extended periods of time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Expert warnings come as colorectal &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-2b763af0-dac0-11f0-8942-5515e5e6263b"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; rates have been rising steadily among adults under the age of 55 throughout the past decade, according to recent studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Advanced-stage diagnoses in this younger population are also increasing, often having spread to other organs, making the cancer harder to treat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;But, experts have said it's not just potential future health risks to worry about - some foods put you in immediate danger of ingesting deadly bacteria.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The stars of the holiday table - such ham, certain side dishes and even classic cocktails - could be breeding grounds for &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15324801/boars-head-deli-products-recalled-listeria.html"&gt;bacteria that infect millions of Americans every year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To lower the risk of cancer and foodborne illnesses, doctors and food safety experts have told the Daily Mail which foods to approach with a little extra caution - and which to avoid entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;As families prepare for festive gatherings, health experts warn that certain foods can influence long-term colorectal cancer risk&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Turkey, ham and processed meats&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Elaine Siu, a dietitian and supervisor of clinical nutrition services at City of Hope in California, told the Daily Mail that processed meats like ham, bacon and sausage are classified by the World Health Organization (WHO) as Group 1 carcinogens, meaning there is strong evidence they can cause cancer in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She pointed&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15266129/bacon-kill-you-nitrate-processed-meat-cancers.html"&gt; to research&lt;/a&gt; showing that just 50g per day (about two slices of bacon or one hot dog) can increase colorectal cancer risk by 18 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One of the biggest problems is that processed meats are packed with preservatives, Dr Krushangi Patel, a medical oncologist also at City of Hope, told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those common additives include sodium nitrite (used to preserve color and prevent bacterial growth), sodium erythorbate and ascorbate (antioxidants to stabilize color and flavor) and sodium phosphate (used to retain moisture and improve texture).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These meats are generally high in sodium, which can raise blood pressure and contribute to gastric cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The combination of preservatives, sodium levels and processing at high temperatures can also play a role in disrupting the gut microbiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Raw turkey can contain salmonella Campylobacter, which can lead to bloody diarrhea, stomach cramps and vomiting (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Suneel Kamath, a gastrointestinal oncologist at the Cleveland Clinic in Ohio, said that disruption - which damages beneficial bacteria - 'makes the colon more prone to forming cancer cells.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As for food safety, turkey and ham must be prepared correctly to eliminate illness-causing bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ham, for instance, can carry salmonella, one of the leading causes of food poisoning in the US. Sickening 1.3 million Americans every year, the bacteria leads to bloody diarrhea, severe stomach cramps, vomiting and loss of appetite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While most people recover on their own or have no symptoms, the bacteria can be especially dangerous to young children and the elderly, both of whom have weakened immune systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 420 Americans die from salmonella every year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Darin Detwiler, food safety expert at Northeastern University in Boston, told the Daily Mail that raw ham also contains Campylobacter, which sickens 1.5 million people in the US annually and causes fever, stomach cramps and diarrhea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'These bacteria thrive in undercooked meat, particularly in thick areas near the bone,' he said. 'Improper thawing, such as leaving a frozen bird on the kitchen counter, can also give bacteria a chance to multiply.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Detwiler, who is also a former advisor to the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/fda/index.html" id="mol-743b40d0-d793-11f0-b88c-e72179d70611"&gt;FDA&lt;/a&gt; and US Department of Agriculture (USDA), warns those cooking a turkey or ham against leaving it on the counter to defrost, as it can fall into the 'danger zone' of temperatures, between 40F and 140F.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Always thaw meat in the refrigerator,' he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Sugary cocktails may raise the risk of colon cancer, experts warn. Some eggnog often uses raw eggs, which contain salmonella (stock image of eggnog)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Alcoholic and sugary drinks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many people are still unaware that alcohol can cause cancer, said Kamath, who pointed out that acetaldehyde, a toxic byproduct of alcohol metabolism, can damage DNA and trigger mutations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Holiday celebrators should also note, according to Siu, that alcohol is classified by the WHO as a Group 1 carcinogen and is a known risk factor for colorectal cancer, even at moderate levels. She noted that sugary and ultra-processed cocktails such as eggnog are common holiday indulgences that have been linked to increased colorectal cancer risk when consumed in excess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10764622/"&gt;2023 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; of 17 studies found that drinking more sugar-sweetened beverages was associated with a 17 percent higher risk of colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So, she advised staying within the recommended limits during the festive season: no more than one drink per day for women and no more than two drinks per day for men. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Frequent holiday drinking can also disrupt sleep, irritate the digestive tract, weaken the immune system and increase inflammation, placing extra stress on the body, Dasgupta added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;While store-bought eggnog is pasteurized to kill bacteria, homemade, traditional versions are often made with raw eggs, which carry salmonella. While alcohol &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;added to the drink can help kill bacteria by causing bacterial molecules to break down, it doesn't completely eliminate the risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Detwiler suggested sticking with the store-bought beverage, but warned drinkers against letting it sit out in a serving container for hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The USDA recommends pasteurizing or heating eggnog to at least 160F to kill off bacteria before consuming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Cranberry sauce runs the risk of being contaminated with bacteria if it comes into contact with raw meat (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Cranberry sauce and other side dishes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mashed potatoes, mac and cheese and green bean casserole are often key players in holiday dinners. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While these 'are typically safe when freshly cooked,' they tend to be left out at room temperature for long periods of time while other dishes finish cooking or so guests can grab additional servings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;That's when the problems can arise, Detwiler told the Daily Mail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Gravy is particularly risky because it provides an ideal environment for Clostridium perfringens, a bacterium that can cause gastrointestinal illness if food is not kept hot or cooled quickly,' he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Detwiler added that side dishes made with milk, butter or cream support the growth of listeria if left out. The USDA recommends leaving dishes out for no longer than two hours at a time so temperatures do not dip into the 'danger zone.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cranberry sauce is naturally acidic and high in sugar, which helps inhibit bacterial growth. The low pH in highly acidic foods interferes with bacteria's cellular processes and stops them from multiplying. Sugar reduces the amount of water available in food, which dehydrates bacteria and stops it from growing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, cranberry sauce 'isn't entirely risk free,' Detwiler said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If it's made from scratch and prepared on surfaces contaminated by raw meat or poultry, cross-contamination becomes a concern.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Fried foods&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patel pointed out that while fried holiday favorites, such as doughnuts, fritters and crispy appetizers, are not harmful when enjoyed occasionally, a diet consistently high in fried foods has been linked to increased risk of colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One concern is that f&lt;span&gt;rying foods at high temperatures can produce compounds like acrylamides and advanced glycation end products (AGEs), which may increase cancer risk over time. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Acrylamides can be converted in the body to substances that damage DNA, potentially causing mutations that trigger cancer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;AGEs, on the other hand, promote oxidative stress and chronic inflammation, and activate pathways that encourage cell growth, creating an environment favorable to tumor development. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kamath noted that these foods also fall under the umbrella of ultra-processed products (UPFs), a category increasingly tied to immune and microbiome disruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;UPFs are foods that are highly processed and industrially formulated. Additionally, in contrast to whole foods, UPFs often contain additives, emulsifiers, preservatives, sweeteners and refined ingredients that disrupt the gut microbiome, promote chronic inflammation and contribute to tumor development in the colon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research over the past decade has linked high consumption of UPFs to increased colorectal cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Traditionally fried holiday foods, however, can be made healthier by baking or air-frying instead of deep-frying, which reduces harmful compounds and excess fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:35:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNSUpDVU5SZnY1c3UwelI2eExZM3Vhd0Z2NEJxWnY0bW55bHNsRDJOTVJfR1JGVG5Ga0VIOHlxekdfTEwyY0hHSWs2N3FIa2lQUm5Ca0lMbmZ3dXR4UWl5ajdVcU9XTFpELTd0eENmdVJzb01ZemlFeE5mSFNCZFFpOWRTRktBUGNoZzg5bnE1cmJEVUpMc2Yw</guid></item><item><title>心理学家利用特定的心态来保持积极的态度，研究结果- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/psychologists-tap-into-a-specific-mindset-to-stay-positive-study-finds</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxNck56OU1iRzJYY2FxdEtYRWxEM3YtM01FdzU5TmVaVXpIaEdYVE1ZbUdwVXI2LW1UZXVnTVZFV0c2MWFoRVVONmFDZFVXcVhqWXB0WmpOZmRGUzhaVzNKV2J6UGtSX3M3cGpPTS1aLU1aRmxjeDNkZklPY0JtcjV5TnkzYzNjYzZqLVFyYmE2VDJYdG5Iaml6UzFSbEhqUjhk?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Psychologists Tap Into a Specific Mindset to Stay Positive, Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ScienceAlert&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxPVTBRQVlPdmpwaEswVUc1WGItU0I3alg2OHZQcjFkZnctRjNpLXFXV2VxN0ZTNzM0MmRtZzhFcE5qZ1dQRDdkS09rbXJ3WWpFYU9OTnY5QXVYekgxSkxrV1lyNHk5MFVoOGp2R1E0Q3YwSVJkTjNETndnWjg3MUp5QWNNMzY3VDZkUHlKUHAxS0RpRHR6WVR6d0V0ODhDSTh5SEptd2swSEw2WWJQVC1wT9IBtgFBVV95cUxQLTV4a19DRVFodVRXbDVmdUpGVlI5SThsSXlYVHdWcnFtQVNNYzlUejZJc0NDOFQzTkU2Z2UwZUxfaGROSkhiYXpZeUJiVEhRTHdCTlZnWFlzMHJBeG9waVcwVWI3U21sWWJRVThYWVFoSS05Z25xMGhvRTJpLWZkQ1pVYjJBNXRNZzlQeTNfd180NkhQb1VGMDV5cjJJaTJUZFI0dE9QWFQ5eW0yWUFBZ01LZERQdw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;The True Art of Wellbeing: A Mindset Shift Beyond Positivity&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Devdiscourse&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNeFhiWG0yT0F3MUVuUU80T3p1NTc0bXJ0TTMweldHTE80SzBlVFZuR3VvZEw4NV8xLWthWXJhNVROWTZINWhTU3RzZU5lc3FkaU9HZEZKMEszQk9EdEl1Y3pQVlM5eTRPeFBmb1RxbEFLOEZWSmgyWXlCYS1OY1IwZGVTSE1UMFl6UzFF?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Positive psychology experts don't follow their own advice. What they actually do may be the key to well-being&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Medical Xpress&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNck56OU1iRzJYY2FxdEtYRWxEM3YtM01FdzU5TmVaVXpIaEdYVE1ZbUdwVXI2LW1UZXVnTVZFV0c2MWFoRVVONmFDZFVXcVhqWXB0WmpOZmRGUzhaVzNKV2J6UGtSX3M3cGpPTS1aLU1aRmxjeDNkZklPY0JtcjV5TnkzYzNjYzZqLVFyYmE2VDJYdG5Iaml6UzFSbEhqUjhk</guid></item><item><title>尊敬的医生： 65岁以上的人应该多久接种一次RSV疫苗？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2025/12/dear-doctor-how-often-should-people-older-than-65-get-the-rsv-vaccination.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OWYZPM2A4RGIJB672SNCYX32DM"&gt;DEAR DR. ROACH: My husband and I are over 65. We got the respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) vaccinations two years ago. I’m reading mixed reports on how often we should be getting them. -- N.W.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZEJTBKFZDBFZHBBNWIYD5PV7HE"&gt;ANSWER: Along with influenza and COVID, RSV is yet another virus that causes respiratory disease in adults -- one that is especially dangerous for young children and older adults. It is recommended to be discussed for those who are over the age of 60.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3NINZBBJ6RAWPNC4B4VZJYGONY"&gt;People younger than 60 with moderate to severe immune system diseases, such as those that deal with an organ (especially lung) or a stem-cell transplant, should also consider vaccination. I recommend the vaccine to all adults over 75 and to those over 60 who have risk factors such as chronic heart or lung disease, complicated diabetes, or hemodialysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KLOLW5IA55HGTBCZH7Q65B5L6M"&gt;At the current time, booster doses of the RSV vaccine are not recommended. This may change; although there is evidence that immunity wanes after a year, repeat doses were not found to be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KVF24K3KTZDAFKOSBLDSBTYRO4"&gt;DEAR DR. ROACH: When I was about 6 years old in the early ’40s, my 16-year-old brother was sent to a sanitarium for tuberculosis patients. He was there for 18 months and was a survivor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ARJQBPK52NCF3EKSXI3NJH6XSE"&gt;During this period of time, we (the family) went regularly for chest X-rays and some kind of test that involved a needle in my forearm. Why aren’t X-rays done today -- not to detect tuberculosis but to look for cancer? CT scans are expensive and sometimes involve a long wait, so why not do a simple X-ray for starters? And then if they see something, perhaps they can do a CT scan? -- N.C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SLKL5RRCMJFI5E7NFDBF7KV73I"&gt;ANSWER: Many physicians and scientists at Johns Hopkins, Memorial Sloan-Kettering, and other first-rate institutions have sought to answer the question of whether annual chest X-rays led to a reduction in the risk of dying from lung cancer. But unfortunately, the consensus of opinion is that chest X-rays do not lead to an improvement in lung cancer mortality. There were tens of thousands of participants in these studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NBWMU2K4B5C65EQ4LGB7VJGRJU"&gt;You are also right to think that a CT scan might be more useful. Studies have shown that for a subset of people who are at a high risk, screening with a CT scan does lead to a reduction in lung cancer deaths. Specifically, lung cancer screening should be considered for people between the ages of 50-80 (Medicare will pay up to age 77) who are in generally good health; those who have smoked at least 20 “pack years” (such as a pack a day for 20 years, two packs a day for 10 years, or a half pack a day for 40 years); and those who currently smoke or have quit within the past 15 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SALM4LIHEBGN3ANNCAWUPIDQMU"&gt;The benefit from lung cancer screening is modest; it takes about 250 people to be screened annually for three years to prevent one lung cancer death. Still, this is significant, and I do discuss lung cancer screening with my eligible patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3UTZXFHD7VFW7M3GWVTCS4GIU4"&gt;Finally, the best way by far to prevent lung cancer is to quit smoking as soon as possible. If you are a smoker, your doctor has many ways to help you quit. Calling a quit line, such as 800-QUIT-NOW, will connect you with your state service. You can also text QUITNOW to 333888, and there are web-based programs such as Smokefree.gov and apps like quitSTART from the National CANCER Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JYP7VFMJNFGDBPE7SIG4MUGEHI"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dr. Roach regrets that he is unable to answer individual letters, but will incorporate them in the column whenever possible. Readers may email questions to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu"&gt;&lt;i&gt;ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; or send mail to 628 Virginia Dr., Orlando, FL 32803.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AUMP2LSRGJBWVFXGMISV4TEA2E"&gt;&lt;i&gt;(c) 2022 North America Syndicate Inc.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U7EQ3GITRJHTXMWUUBM53ZNYZM"&gt;&lt;i&gt;All Rights Reserved&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxQNlRlWC1UeWJSbjV2VEFkMEpYOS14YS1yWGljbjEyZ0pqbVdiMTIxNFFrek1IbzAyQ0x5a2V3VTB2MXl4Um1pSVlaZ19JQWdvUHc0MWs3UmV2N00tbUFoT0FBaElUUWdOTDZYQWtQSk1oTzVtRFhVR2g2S1FEdUNkb1B5Z2xRdmpqZ2VZZnc3Mm9lcnVsU09pdmxvUDZseHZnbGo4cXk0V3BfYkR4dURnbWVNV2FIQWU1QzZ0atIB0AFBVV95cUxPbjFyR29PbXVMQ0VTeEY1ZXQ5dnZTSU1EVlJtcHNWSUhza3gtYVZtekRWRC1FdjNKQkFORDB1XzE5Q1FuY2ZNdVlreUFhaUNsekkyOE5EY1RNZ25iT2ItaE03VERpVnZTT1ZaeVlDcEY0cjZUYW1iN3hneEF6ZWFZTWw0NXlxaE9ZRi1uOUU1bFl6UVVrSTNGaTh6cXJEZmk3dWZiRndVblAwb3p5cVpZbFl1emtmWndWWFNHNGNxNmEtOVp3UG0xWHprTHhiZEg2</guid></item><item><title>学生们认为他们遇到了麻烦。“相反，他们了解到匿名捐赠者的5000万美元礼物正在支付他们的学费-雅虎加拿大新闻</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/students-thought-were-trouble-instead-140000087.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;An anonymous donor gave approximately $50 million to be put toward the University of Washington's Medical Laboratory Science Program&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The money would help pay for the tuition of students enrolled in the UW’s Medical Laboratory Science Program’s senior-year clinical rotations and will also “help expand enrollment to 100 students over the next ten years"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Students in this field will go on to perform patient lab tests at hospitals and clinics and for public health agencies and conduct research in academic and commercial laboratories, among other jobs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some students at the University of Washington will now have their tuition covered — and it’s all thanks to an anonymous donor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The University of Washington announced in a &lt;a href="https://newsroom.uw.edu/news-releases/gift-to-help-cover-tuition-for-students-in-lab-medicine" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:press release;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt; earlier this month that the donor’s approximately $50 million donation will help pay for undergraduate students enrolled in the UW’s Medical Laboratory Science Program, covering their senior-year tuition for their clinical rotations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to the school, the donation will be put toward the tuition of in-state students — which costs between $4,000-$5,000 — for all medical laboratory science seniors. There are currently 70 students in the program, including 35 who have begun their senior-year clinical rotations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I was shocked at first, and it took a second for me to process that they are going to pay our tuition. And then I felt a lot of relief,” Jasmine Wertz, 30, a senior in the program said in UW’s press release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Speaking with the &lt;a href="https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/uw-anonymous-50m-gift-will-cover-tuition-for-med-lab-science-students/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Seattle Times;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;Seattle Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, fellow student Jennifer Wang said the group had no idea &lt;em&gt;what &lt;/em&gt;was coming ahead of the announcement event, just that they'd been told to prepare for big news — and to “dress properly."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“We thought we were going to be in trouble,” Wang said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smith Collection/Gado/Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; A photo of the campus of the University of Washington in Seattle, Washington&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The students who graduate from the program, which trains students to perform clinical lab tests, can take several professional pathways, including performing patient lab tests at hospitals and clinics, conducting research in academic and commercial laboratories and teaching at colleges and universities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Some people don’t even know we exist, or they think it’s robots or something,”  Dr. Geoff Baird said while speaking with the &lt;em&gt;Seattle Times.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But as another school official put it while speaking with the students, "you are the glue, in many ways, of our entire health system."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You are the unsung heroes. You work behind the scenes that allow all of the health care machinery to work," added Dr. Tim Dellit, CEO of UW Medicine and the dean of the School of Medicine, according to the newspaper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Their jobs can be demanding, especially when students are also trying to hold down part-time jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Our schedule is very demanding, especially when we start clinical rotations for 40 hours a week," Jasmine Wertz explained in the university's press release. "It's very hard to find time between studying and doing rotations to be able to hold a job.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Wertz added that she wanted to thank the anonymous donor saying, “Just thinking of the gift they’ve given to so many people. Thank you for acknowledging our major and our career as a viable source of healthcare.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The money that was donated will also be put back into the program to “help expand enrollment to 100 students over the next ten years.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This is particularly important as the school noted that Washington state faces a shortage of “medical laboratory specialists as the demand for lab services has grown.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The university went on to note that only there are only two programs in Washington state that offer "baccalaureate-level medical science degrees."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Karen Ducey/Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; A sign outside the UW Medicine Research facilities in South Lake Union on December 10, 2020&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“This donor’s selfless generosity will allow us to reduce the debt burden for our students and attract more young people to the field to ensure that our region has the skilled laboratory workforce that is so critical to high-quality, timely patient care,” said Dellit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk: PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“This extraordinary gift advances one of our highest priorities: making a UW education accessible and debt-free and enabling students who are passionate about healthcare to pursue their goals,” added UW President Robert J. Jones. “Its profound impact on student success will lead to more trained healthcare professionals and better health for all Washington residents."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/students-thought-they-were-in-trouble-instead-learned-50m-donation-was-covering-tuition-11860492" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQN0VhMFRCWWZHMGNHQXZEZlZGT250SXIxb1BaaE54UVY2amE4aXY4VlVfUkMxb0dOREhkVmVrTHJteDlycXhwWnJacmtLbXlfZkVnb0lrQlVFcmJtaWs2ai1fcEJmSGZBVVdiVkx6WTN6cnVYYmY5RWNyWk5kNVFaN1lrUGc</guid></item><item><title>血液测试可以预测谁最容易患上常见遗传性心脏病--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/dec/25/blood-test-predict-risk-inherited-heart-condition-hypertrophic-cardiomyopathy</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists are developing a simple blood test to predict who is most at risk from the world’s most common inherited heart condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Millions of people worldwide have hypertrophic cardiomyopathy (HCM), a disease of the heart muscle where the wall of the heart becomes thickened. It is caused by a change in one or more genes and mostly passed on through families.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Some feel fine most of the time and have few or no symptoms. But others can suffer complications, such as heart failure and abnormal heart rhythms, which can lead to a cardiac arrest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The problem is there is no cure. Doctors also &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/jan/08/outdated-guidelines-mean-doctors-failing-to-spot-heart-condition-in-women" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;do not know which patients&lt;/a&gt; with the genetic condition are most at risk from deadly complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But now a team of scientists from universities including Harvard and Oxford have found a way to forecast risk for people living with HCM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The blood test could identify those patients most in danger of complications, enabling them to be monitored more closely or receive life-saving treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In a landmark study, the team measured the levels of a protein, N-terminal Pro-B-type natriuretic peptide (NT-Pro-BNP), in the blood of 700 HCM patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;NT-Pro-BNP is released by the heart as part of normal pumping. But high levels are a sign the heart is working too hard. Those with the highest levels had poorer blood flow, more scar tissue and changes in their heart which could lead to atrial fibrillation or heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A blood test measuring NT-Pro-BNP could transform the care of millions of people with the world’s most common inherited heart condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study leader, Prof Carolyn Ho, the medical director of the cardiovascular genetics centre at Harvard medical school, said the test could help “target the right therapies to the right patients at the right time”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She added: “Continued studies on blood biomarkers will lead to better understanding of HCM so that, in future, we can offer our patients a blood test to identify who is at high versus low risk of experiencing serious consequences of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“People with the highest risk could be targeted for potentially life-saving treatments as they stand to receive the greatest benefit, while those at lowest risk could avoid unnecessary treatment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Lara Johnson, 34, from Southampton in the UK, is one of many who could benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="3eeff211-4533-46b2-bfc2-0e18861b2e1f" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":13,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Parasite cleanses: why are so many people obsessed with intestinal worms?","elementId":"3eeff211-4533-46b2-bfc2-0e18861b2e1f","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/2025/dec/09/parasite-cleanses-people-obsessed-intestinal-worms"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Eight years ago, she began experiencing breathlessness and fatigue. After being referred by her GP for hospital tests, she was diagnosed with HCM. Several relatives on her father’s side were subsequently also diagnosed with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“One of the hardest parts of living with HCM is the constant uncertainty, never knowing what might change next,” Johnson said. “A simple blood test, which could help identify future risks earlier, would take away so much of that anxiety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;She added: “It could give people like me a chance to prepare and adjust our lifestyles as needed, and help us to feel more in control. That kind of clarity wouldn’t only help me, it would make a world of difference for my whole family.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Bryan Williams, the chief scientific and medical officer of the British Heart Foundation, which funded the research, said the test “could benefit patients around the world”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“After a diagnosis of HCM, patients and their families want to know what the future holds. This study shows that measuring various proteins circulating in the blood could help predict how the heart is functioning and future risk of complications from heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This new method may also provide insights in the evolution of the structure and function of the heart in people with HCM that could point to new ways of treating this condition to reduce future risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxPUlppcm1LVVd3MDZPbEtJd25TX3Y4Z2NwdDh2d3RWcTJhLTNBN3BJaHAtX3BlMUxOdDVfSkF3Vlk1TG1NcU1JVDVWRUNkU183VFJMc0M0SEJZQWJmRm5HczA3OTFzY3pmNGJxaEtqOVcxeXpRSW5QS255QUhJODhKdkNYNV9mNWxhdTZfNl9Gai0tQ1VQQVRUOG9kTlVjNDN6ckhYQnJyMjUxcncyNkp6YWpISXR3QlNkN29jRlNuelZWRzQ</guid></item><item><title>如果您正在感受这11件事，您可能会陷入生存模式- YourTango</title><link>https://www.yourtango.com/self/feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anxiety and stress are a normal, though bothersome, part of life for many people. But when a person is stuck in "survival mode," a non-stop cycle of fight or flight, it has repercussions on our mental and physical health. According to &lt;a href="https://drgiamarson.com/the-negative-impact-of-prolonged-survival-mode-what-can-you-do-to-thrive/" rel="nofollow"&gt;psychologist Dr. Gia Marson&lt;/a&gt;, "Stressful stimuli cause a physiological and psychological response called survival mode. This... involves the release of stress hormones and the activation of our stress-response systems. Our mind and body become focused on combating danger."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though survival mode is a defense mechanism meant to protect against imminent threats, modern stressors like school, work, and family can trap people in a vicious state of survival. Whether it's suffering from exhaustion or feeling unable to focus, if you're feeling these things, you're probably stuck in survival mode. So, it's crucial to identify these signs to prevent further turmoil&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;If you're feeling these 11 things, you're probably stuck in survival mode&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Everything feels urgent&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-everything-urgent.png" alt="woman looking at watch with a sense of urgency" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode everything feels urgent" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Andrii Iemelianenko | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.humnutrition.com/blog/how-to-get-out-of-survival-mode/" rel="nofollow"&gt;psychotherapist Kiara Luna&lt;/a&gt;, a person may be experiencing survival mode if they have an urgent sense to take care of specific tasks right away. "We often get into this state where we feel a sense of urgency over non-urgent items because we're operating from fear, anxiety, and even anger. Those emotions are sending a signal to our brain that we must act now," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This heightened state puts immense strain on our mental and emotional well-being, which can lead us to operate in survival mode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/someone-stops-doing-these-things-home-theyre-low-key-struggling"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If Someone Stops Doing These 11 Things In Their Home, They're Low-Key Struggling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. You're always tired&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-always-tired.png" alt="extremely tired woman yawning" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode always tired" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;MAYA LAB | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of the process of preparing our bodies for survival mode includes extending more energy than usual. Our bodies do this &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/staying-healthy/understanding-the-stress-response" rel="nofollow"&gt;by raising our cortisol levels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this is useful for a short duration of time, prolonged use tires our body, depleting our energy sources close to zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/subtle-signs-not-just-stressed-completely-exhausted-emotionally"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;15 Subtle Signs You're Not Just Stressed, You're Completely Exhausted Emotionally&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. You anger easily&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-anger-easily.png" alt="angry woman yelling" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode anger easily" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Krakenimages.com | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're feeling anger at the slightest things, you're probably stuck in survival mode. Maybe your partner loaded the dishwasher the "wrong" way or another car cuts you off in traffic. And it's &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/straightforward-signs-stress-no-longer-normal-no-matter-how-much-you-deny-it"&gt;not just a one-off — this happens every day&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your partner makes you roasted garlic chicken instead of plain roasted chicken? Irritated. Your children say one word to you after you get home from a long day of work? Irritated. The server gives you BBQ chicken wings instead of buffalo chicken wings? Irritated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://hbr.org/2022/01/what-to-do-when-youre-stuck-in-the-survival-zone" rel="nofollow"&gt;author Tony Schwartz&lt;/a&gt; pointed out, "The survival zone is when your energy is high, but negative. When we feel threatened or devalued, control of our nervous system shifts from the prefrontal cortex to the sympathetic nervous system and we move into fight-or-flight mode. People in this zone are anxious, impatient, irritable, fearful, and self-critical."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-signs-woman-who-has-been-through-lot-life-according-research"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Subtle Signs Of A Woman Who Has Been Through A Lot In Life, According To Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. Nothing feels good enough&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-nothing-feels-good-enough.png" alt="sad stressed man not feeling good enough" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode nothing feels good enough" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;DedMityay | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not being able to enjoy the activities you once loved is a gut-wrenching experience, but you can't help it. Nothing ever feels good enough. The book you just read is trash, the date your partner took you on was horrendous, and that good grade you got on your paper could have been better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're experiencing this feeling every day, you're likely in survival mode. Because even the tiniest accomplishments just aren't enough for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/small-things-you-can-do-morning-so-you-dont-want-get-back-bed-and-hide"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Small Things You Can Do In The Morning So You Don't Want To Get Back In Bed And Hide&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. No day feels like a good day&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-no-day-good-day.png" alt="stressed man in survival mode having a bad day" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode no day feels like a good day" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;wavebreakmedia | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you find yourself constantly feeling that no day is a good day, this could be a sign of multiple underlying mental health issues. While &lt;a href="https://drbrookeweinstein.com/" rel="nofollow"&gt;occupational therapist Dr. Brooke Weinstein&lt;/a&gt; identifies this as a sign of survival mode, it's crucial to delve deeper into the root cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to highlight that this emotional state aligns with other mental health issues beyond survival mode, making it essential to seek professional guidance to tackle the problem more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/phrases-people-use-to-pretend-theyre-fine-when-theyre-absolutely-not"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 Phrases People Use To Pretend They're Fine When They're Absolutely Not&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;6. You wake up stressed&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-wake-up-stressed.png" alt="woman sitting up in bed feeling stressed" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode wake up stressed" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;yourphotopie | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://acceleratedresolutiontherapy.com/are-you-in-survival-mode/" rel="nofollow"&gt;experts from Accelerated Resolution Therapy&lt;/a&gt;, "Stress becomes chronic when a person experiences frequent stress-producing stimuli without a return to comfortable normalcy in between stressors. As a result, the body and mind cannot return to a rested state. Individuals experiencing chronic stress are hypervigilant, physically tense and 'on edge,' unable to return to a deepened, relaxed state required for recovery," they explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health/strange-signals-body-sends-when-under-too-much-stress"&gt;stress can create immense problems&lt;/a&gt; such as anxiety, depression, and sleeping disorders, as well as digestive issues, sweating, headaches, dizziness, and weight fluctuations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/reasons-people-who-are-always-tired-can-never-fall-asleep-usually-have"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People Who Are Always Tired But Can Never Fall Asleep Usually Have These 11 Reasons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;7. You feel anxious for no reason&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-anxious-no-reason.png" alt="woman holding chest feeling anxious for no reason" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode anxious for no reason" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have you been anxious a lot lately? For instance, your friends want to go out to a nice restaurant and you're so anxious because you don't know what to wear. Or maybe you're cooking a nice dinner for your partner but you're anxious because what happens if they don't like it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're feeling anxious and unsure of why, &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-warning-signs-someone-in-survival-mode-according-research"&gt;you're probably stuck in survival mode&lt;/a&gt;. Lately, you may be feeling on edge. You wake up anxious, get dressed anxious, and you're constantly working feeling anxious. No matter what, your heart feels as if it's going to fall out of your chest every single day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/signs-youre-more-anxious-than-average-person"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 Signs You're More Anxious Than The Average Person, According To Psychology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;8. You find yourself zoning out and unable to focus&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-zoning-out-unable-focus.png" alt="woman zoning out outside unable to focus" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode zoning out unable to focus" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Twinsterphoto | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether it's in a meeting or while you're in a conversation with someone, you can't seem to pay attention. Pinching yourself doesn't work and rubbing your eyes somehow makes it worse. According to &lt;a href="https://www.newswise.com/articles/the-mental-fatigue-you-feel-is-called-cognitive-dulling-and-you-are-not-alone-if-you-are-experiencing-it" rel="nofollow"&gt;licensed psychologist and assistant professor Jennifer Bahrman&lt;/a&gt;, cognitive dulling is "a form of mental fatigue that l&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/psychology-tools-stop-zoning-out-stress-dissociate"&gt;eads to difficulty concentrating&lt;/a&gt;, decreased productivity, and a decline in emotional and mental health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This can occur due to our bodies constantly living in survival mode. Cognitive dulling can cause issues with our productivity and a decline in our mental and physical health, which, in the long run, can affect both our personal and professional lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/psychology-tools-stop-zoning-out-stress-dissociate"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;According To Psychology, 5 Simple Tools Can Stop Zoning Out When Stress Makes You Dissociate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;9. You feel overwhelmed&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-overwhelmed.png" alt="overwhelmed stressed man sitting at home" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode feel overwhelmed" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;voronaman | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be hard to focus on important tasks when you're constantly in fight or flight, and your sense of uncertainty can quickly escalate into powerful emotions. This may &lt;a href="https://www.newportinstitute.com/resources/mental-health/feeling-overwhelmed/" rel="nofollow"&gt;lead to forgetfulness, confusion, and withdrawal&lt;/a&gt;. Over time these can snowball into bigger issues such as depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, if you're feeling these things, you're probably stuck in survival mode. And if that isn't bad enough, being overwhelmed on a daily basis &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2732004/" rel="nofollow"&gt;can be a catalyst for dependency issues&lt;/a&gt; and many other disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/if-youve-stopped-enjoying-these-things-its-sign-youre-more-burned-out-you-think"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If You've Stopped Enjoying These 11 Things, It's A Sign You're More Burned Out Than You Think&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;10. You engage in destructive behaviors&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-destructive-behaviors.png" alt="woman engaging in destructive behaviors being unproductive" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode engage in destructive behaviors" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Stokkete | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of us have engaged in destructive behaviors at some point, whether it was throwing a pillow or breaking up an otherwise healthy relationship. However, when experiencing constant stress, our coping mechanisms tend to be a bit more extreme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overeating and dependency issues are just some of the &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-signs-someone-path-of-self-destruction"&gt;many dangerous destructive behaviors we engage in&lt;/a&gt; when under constant stress. If you're experiencing these problems, it's essential to seek out professional help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/habits-people-need-slow-down"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;10 Worrisome Habits Of People Who Need To Slow Down, According To Psychology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;11. You're easily startled&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/if-feeling-these-things-youre-probably-stuck-survival-mode-easily-startled.png" alt="startled woman covering her mouth" title="if you're feeling these things you're probably stuck in survival mode easily startled" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Anatoliy Karlyuk | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you the type of person who is easily startled when someone taps you on the shoulder and greets you? Do you jump out of your skin when you hear an unexpectedly loud noise? Startling easily is biologically programmed into us when we are in survival mode in order to keep us safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Startling easily in this way means your nervous system is working in overdrive, which can cause exaggerated reactions. Eventually, however, this leads to exhaustion from hypervigilance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/unhappy-people-almost-always-do-these-things-before-leaving-house"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unhappy People Almost Always Do These 11 Things Before Leaving The House&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marielisa Reyes is a writer with a bachelor's degree in psychology who covers self-help, relationships, career, family, and astrology topics.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="midcat-most-popular"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Related Stories From YourTango:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="rc-widget-c743d1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>YourTango</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:35:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNbGZNTHEwemdnUlJ5emlRLXhTYkk0SDBjQm4zQ2JNMHprUTNtUjE0amFIOFpuM0JRc2hOZkhqOGRiNFBSVGpQZnlvX0VOcDJFOFR3RnRlVW5IT3NJS013UkJsOTVyOWN0VXNYMGpnNWJxV1hHcmo1TlE5bjVkTEVLVXo1ZWVNUTVkMUVrX3BIOA</guid></item><item><title>营养学家说，没有镁就无法吸收维生素D ，导致骨骼健康状况不佳|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-says-vitamin-d-cannot-be-absorbed-without-magnesium-causing-poor-bone-health-101766663986985.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-says-vitamin-d-cannot-be-absorbed-without-magnesium-causing-poor-bone-health-101766663986985.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Vitamin D deficiency is far more common than most people realize. Globally, more than 1 billion people are deficient in vitamin D, and nearly half the population has vitamin D levels that are lower than normal. While vitamin D is widely known for supporting bone strength, immunity, and overall health, many people do not absorb or use it properly. That is because vitamin D does not work alone. It needs magnesium to convert it into its active form inside the body. Without enough magnesium, vitamin D can remain inactive, even if you are taking supplements regularly. Together, these two nutrients support stronger bones and better muscle function.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/magnesium_1766664794164_1766664813372.jpg" alt="Vitamin D works better when your body has enough magnesium.(Adobe Stock)" title="Vitamin D works better when your body has enough magnesium.(Adobe Stock)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/magnesium_1766664794164_1766664813372.jpg" alt="Vitamin D works better when your body has enough magnesium.(Adobe Stock)" title="Vitamin D works better when your body has enough magnesium.(Adobe Stock)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Vitamin D works better when your body has enough magnesium.(Adobe Stock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why is magnesium essential for the body?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magnesium is a vital mineral involved in multiple biochemical reactions in the body. It plays a key role in energy production, nerve function, muscle movement, and maintaining healthy bones and teeth.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dietician Vidhi Chawla, founder of FISICO Diet and Aesthetic Clinic, says magnesium&lt;span class="highlight"&gt; helps &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/is-it-true-that-beet-juice-lowers-blood-pressure-in-just-3-hours-dietician-suggests-consuming-around-200-ml-every-day-101766137186411.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="regulate blood pressure"&gt;regulate blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; and improves insulin sensitivity, which may lower the risk of type 2 diabetes. It also supports athletic performance by moving glucose into muscles and reducing lactic acid buildup, which helps prevent fatigue.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Magnesium is especially important for bone health. It regulates calcium and vitamin D levels, improves bone density, and supports proper bone crystal formation. This becomes even more important for women after menopause, when the risk of osteoporosis increases.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;How does magnesium help activate vitamin D?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people focus only on vitamin D supplements, but magnesium is what allows your body to actually use vitamin D effectively. A review published in The Journal of the American Osteopathic Association found that vitamin D cannot be properly metabolized without sufficient magnesium levels. This means vitamin D may remain stored and inactive in the body for nearly 50 percent of people.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Magnesium is required by enzymes in the liver and kidneys to convert vitamin D into its active form, especially vitamin D3. Once activated, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/orthopaedic-experts-share-5-foods-to-prevent-vitamin-d-deficiency-and-maintain-bone-health-during-sun-deprived-winters-101766582027818.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vitamin D"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; supports calcium absorption, strengthens bones and teeth, improves muscle function, and helps regulate blood pressure and immunity.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As Chawla explains, “Taking vitamin D without adequate magnesium is like having fuel but no ignition. Both nutrients need to work together for optimal benefits.”&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5 key benefits of taking magnesium with vitamin D&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Better vitamin D absorption&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magnesium activates vitamin D, helping the body absorb and use it efficiently.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;2. Stronger bones and teeth&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, they improve calcium absorption and bone mineral density, reducing fracture risk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;3. Improved muscle function&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This combination helps reduce muscle cramps, spasms, and tension.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;4. Supports heart health&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magnesium helps regulate blood pressure, while vitamin D supports cardiovascular function.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;5. Better mental well-being&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both nutrients play a role in reducing symptoms of anxiety, fatigue, and low mood.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Best food sources of magnesium&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;“To naturally increase magnesium levels, include foods such as spinach, almonds, cashews, walnuts, pumpkin seeds, avocados, dark chocolate, edamame, and fatty fish like salmon and mackerel,” says Chawla.&lt;/span&gt; If needed, magnesium supplements can be added after consulting a doctor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Recommended daily dosage&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For adults and children aged 9 and above, the upper limit for magnesium supplements is 350 mg per day, excluding dietary intake. Excess intake may cause diarrhea, cramps, or kidney issues.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The upper limit for vitamin D from all sources is 100 mcg (4000 IU) per day. Too much vitamin D may lead to nausea, confusion, or kidney stones. Dosages should always be personalized under medical guidance.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Signs of magnesium deficiency&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/magnesium-deficiency-5-silent-signs-like-eye-twitching-that-you-should-never-ignore-101765990566862.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Magnesium deficiency"&gt;Magnesium deficiency&lt;/a&gt; often goes unnoticed. When symptoms appear, they may include loss of appetite, fatigue, muscle cramps, tremors, numbness, mood changes, and irregular heartbeat. Addressing magnesium levels can significantly improve how your body responds to vitamin D.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;(Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.)&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 12:16:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7wFBVV95cUxOd2hScTNZS2IzRnJ3OWhtb2Y3V3doTTM3UDlMMExRUFNkVWg5TG12czQ0TE1BekczcWZMYVZWbHR3bHUtVE04YnBDNXJZYUNzR0cxV21oclBBN01zdTBKTl9Xb1JfdjFSWUl1SnNYbm5KVTBiWXFYUVBOd3VuN0xUeS1US20yZ1FOeTY4LVFncTF1SnlpY2tXMDE5WGRJVHpoQUIyV3NVWTRCd1JpUGRveWpFMEpkZmJtZlN6SndMa1Z6X09hWTczTWt5VThFbTZBb3BkZ3U1eWZMblNIR3ZONzNPV2E2OUI3NDBRcDRZY9IB9AFBVV95cUxQRm41c3hVLXZKMDlFTFVvZU42dW4zVG5BRzlmanJFd3NHSUwzN1psM19RVzBlV1NMZTF2QUxwSndxeEsySnlqVzdaSHlMcDNocllicEoycjFsZnZWUUpfZ0s4WURRTm9XeUJySlZ1NE9fRVNNbDRfWXlhY2NJb2xVNkRwaWxWelVyUzVnWG5HSjI3c3V1WkU4Ym00WlExTTRNakU4VFVxQXlkSFN1SWU0S3MzaEFKMHFmNEdLaDZ5MndrczM5UHFGaHVCVjZnbEZ6OTNGNVlKTWh1ZE1QWnFSWEhZcXlEc0RzWlJsM3VjMXdacUc4</guid></item><item><title>她克服了不孕症和严重的心脏病，在圣诞节前夕生下了双胞胎-波士顿环球报</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/25/metro/christmas-twins-infertility-ivf-mass-general/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Wood, of Epping, N.H., began dating her now-husband, Chris, the day before &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/tag/covid-five-years-later/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.bostonglobe.com/tag/covid-five-years-later/"&gt;the pandemic shut down daily life&lt;/a&gt; in March 2020. As restrictions set in, they dated cautiously, meeting outdoors, measuring to make sure they stayed at least 10 feet apart, calling and texting each other between meetings. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Later that spring,&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;Wood started noticing heart flutters and palpitations that left her short of breath, even during routine activities. At first, she wasn’t sure whether it was stress or something more serious.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;She sought medical care and was diagnosed with PVC-induced cardiomyopathy, a condition caused by frequent premature ventricular contractions — basically, extra beats — that can weaken the heart muscle and dilate it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;An initial attempt to treat the condition failed, but medication helped stabilize Wood’s symptoms. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;In 2022, Abby and Chris got married and soon decided to expand their family. But they had trouble conceiving. They tried&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;intrauterine insemination and then &lt;a href="https://google.com/search?q=jessica+bartlett+and+ivf+and+bostonglobe&amp;amp;sca_esv=f33afe38d9b8e84c&amp;amp;rlz=1C5GCEM_enUS1163US1168&amp;amp;ei=jqxMaZ3VF9erptQPoLzEqQc&amp;amp;ved=0ahUKEwid1P6f49eRAxXXlYkEHSAeMXUQ4dUDCBE&amp;amp;uact=5&amp;amp;oq=jessica+bartlett+and+ivf+and+bostonglobe&amp;amp;gs_lp=Egxnd3Mtd2l6LXNlcnAiKGplc3NpY2EgYmFydGxldHQgYW5kIGl2ZiBhbmQgYm9zdG9uZ2xvYmUyBxAhGKABGAoyBxAhGKABGAoyBxAhGKABGAoyBRAhGKsCSKgUUJoHWKcScAF4AJABAJgBhAGgAdsOqgEEMy4xNLgBA8gBAPgBAZgCAaACd5gDAIgGAZIHAzAuMaAH-hOyBwMwLjG4B3fCBwMyLTHIBwSACAA&amp;amp;sclient=gws-wiz-serp" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://google.com/search?q=jessica+bartlett+and+ivf+and+bostonglobe&amp;amp;sca_esv=f33afe38d9b8e84c&amp;amp;rlz=1C5GCEM_enUS1163US1168&amp;amp;ei=jqxMaZ3VF9erptQPoLzEqQc&amp;amp;ved=0ahUKEwid1P6f49eRAxXXlYkEHSAeMXUQ4dUDCBE&amp;amp;uact=5&amp;amp;oq=jessica+bartlett+and+ivf+and+bostonglobe&amp;amp;gs_lp=Egxnd3Mtd2l6LXNlcnAiKGplc3NpY2EgYmFydGxldHQgYW5kIGl2ZiBhbmQgYm9zdG9uZ2xvYmUyBxAhGKABGAoyBxAhGKABGAoyBxAhGKABGAoyBRAhGKsCSKgUUJoHWKcScAF4AJABAJgBhAGgAdsOqgEEMy4xNLgBA8gBAPgBAZgCAaACd5gDAIgGAZIHAzAuMaAH-hOyBwMwLjG4B3fCBwMyLTHIBwSACAA&amp;amp;sclient=gws-wiz-serp"&gt;IVF&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;That’s when their fertility doctors gave them a warning: In the rare event that an implanted embryo split, carrying multiples could be&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;dangerous and even fatal for Abby Wood, given her heart condition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Their first embryo transfer took, and things were looking up. But Wood was soon diagnosed with Ovarian Hyperstimulation Syndrome, an exaggerated response to increased hormones during fertility treatments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I ended up getting really, really sick. I was incredibly uncomfortable,” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Wood went to Mass. General Hospital to get checked out, and doctors there advised her to take a pregnancy test.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I wasn’t supposed to take a test for another two days, and I was afraid it was going to be negative,” she said. “They said, ‘We have a bet going that you’re pregnant.’”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;So she took the test at the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I got to see those two lines that we had been hoping for for so long,” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;It was a surreal feeling that she got to share with her mom, who accompanied her to the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I remember looking at my mom like, ‘Oh my God, it’s my turn.’”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;She quickly FaceTimed Chris, who was at work, to share the good news. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;A couple of weeks after finding out she was pregnant, Wood and her husband went to their first ultrasound appointment. She said she likes to be prepared, so she browsed the web for what to look for.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I just wanted a viable, healthy baby,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="" class="image | relative margin_bottom_16
          margin_top width_full
          false
          false
          "&gt;&lt;figure class="font_primary false
               false
              false
            " id="img-NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE"&gt;&lt;img id="img-NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE-image" alt="Twins Clive (left) and Simon Wood at their home." class="height_a width_full invisible width_full--mobile width_full--tablet-only" data-src="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440" data-srcset="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 1440w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 1280w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 1024w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 820w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 600w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 420w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 240w" src="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440" srcset="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 1440w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 1280w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 1024w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 820w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 600w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 420w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/NVTISRVFOY6OVSQYMRJWS456EE.jpg?auth=e443f56a8c7a930911964939ad81c5c6d171c11e80c59d10bf1caa15ab640764&amp;amp;width=1440 240w" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption class=" img_caption | margin_horizontal_0--mobile margin_horizontal_0--tablet
        "&gt;&lt;span class="caption | margin_right_half"&gt;Twins Clive (left) and Simon Wood at their home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit uppercase"&gt;Suzanne Kreiter/Globe Staff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;But when the ultrasound began, she saw unfamiliar images on the screen. The doctor told her the unlikely had happened: The embryo had split, and she was carrying twins.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The news came as a shock.&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It’s like we finally got to this point, but I felt like I couldn’t celebrate because I thought I was going to die or lose my babies,” she said. “I couldn’t be happy because I didn’t know what was going to happen.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;But two new doctors at Mass. General assured her otherwise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;One of them was Dr. William Barth Jr., chief of obstetrics, who saw Wood after the ultrasound revelation. He described her as “very worried.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;But, based on her most recent tests and overall health, Barth said the risks appeared manageable with close monitoring. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Encouraging her to continue the pregnancy&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;was not a decision he took lightly. In the most severe cases, he said, doctors advise patients against moving forward. But that was not the case for Wood.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Dr. Whitney Coppolino, a cardiologist at Mass. General to whom Barth referred Wood, agreed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“We’ve seen this before,” she said. “Between myself and Dr. Barth, we felt very confident that we could get her through it.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Abby Wood spent much of her pregnancy shuttling between New Hampshire and Mass. General — more than two hours roundtrip — where she was followed closely by a multidisciplinary team. She saw Barth every couple of weeks and then weekly as her pregnancy advanced, while Coppolino monitored her heart function throughout, increasing the frequency of visits in the third trimester. At different points, Wood wore monitors to track changes in her heart rhythm, a precaution both doctors&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;said helped guide treatment decisions. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Thirty-four weeks went by, and she was almost there. Suddenly, a routinely scheduled echocardiogram showed her heart function had dropped significantly, an early sign that her heart was struggling to keep up with the physical demands of carrying twins. Coppolino&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;told her she was showing early signs of heart failure. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="" class="image | relative margin_bottom_16
          margin_top width_full
          false
          false
          "&gt;&lt;figure class="font_primary false
               false
              false
            " id="img-ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY"&gt;&lt;img id="img-ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY-image" alt="Abby Wood fed Clive and Simon." class="height_a width_full invisible width_full--mobile width_full--tablet-only" data-src="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440" data-srcset="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 1440w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 1280w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 1024w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 820w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 600w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 420w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 240w" src="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440" srcset="https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 1440w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 1280w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 1024w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 820w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 600w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 420w, https://bostonglobe-prod.cdn.arcpublishing.com/resizer/v2/ET2K73CJQS4LEPZ6H2LFEL2RVY.jpg?auth=977a5783e95b16a9317183db89e366c4e1201bae3adbc573accc9ddc2cd868f7&amp;amp;width=1440 240w" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption class=" img_caption | margin_horizontal_0--mobile margin_horizontal_0--tablet
        "&gt;&lt;span class="caption | margin_right_half"&gt;Abby Wood fed Clive and Simon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit uppercase"&gt;Suzanne Kreiter/Globe Staff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Abby Wood was admitted to Mass. General so doctors could adjust her medication and monitor her closely, weighing how long her heart could safely withstand the pregnancy. She was  scheduled for an emergency C-section a week later, on Dec. 24.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Christmas is Wood’s favorite holiday. She remembers it was snowing, and her husband ordered a small fake tree with decorations to brighten their hospital room. But she was still scared.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I kept telling them, the doctors and nurses, I’m sure they knew it. They took really good care of me,” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Then, just after 11 a.m.,&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Simon and Clive Wood were born. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I felt like I could finally take a deep breath,” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The twin boys were born at 35 weeks and were treated in the hospital’s neonatal intensive care unit. Their mother remained hospitalized for several days to monitor her and her sons’ health. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The family was home together before the New Year. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;In the months after giving birth, Wood continued to be monitored by her cardiology team. This fall, she underwent a&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;minimally invasive procedure&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;to correct her heart rhythm. It worked, and she is now recovered from her PVC-induced cardiomyopathy. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;This Christmas Eve, the family celebrated the twin’s first birthday at home.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Now a year old, Simon and Clive are already showing distinct personalities, Wood said. She can tell them apart easily; Chris still sometimes struggles. “The twins are best friends,” she said. “They hold hands all the time.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Wood left her job teaching preschool to stay home with the twins. She said she’s learning to give herself more compassion after everything she’s endured.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I’ve asked a lot of my body over the years,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Christmas morning will be quiet this year, she said, just the four of them. The twins will receive a few simple gifts — snowsuits, books, and blocks — along with traditions she grew up with, including a book from Santa on Christmas morning and new pajamas on birthdays.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;She said she’s deeply grateful for the medical care she received.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;A year ago, she said, she was focused on survival.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Now,” she said, “I get to focus on being their mom.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Sadaf Tokhi can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:sadaf.tokhi@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;sadaf.tokhi@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:39:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxORzBvbTlVRUNVOVY2QlNDR1B3YXV6NEtTYTlIdnktMkNFc3ppb3liNmctMWRJT2owdHN0RHY3SWxLUnhlWVZIalJQUGsyY3Q2ejhGZnJFZ2FXX0h4c0EyMWhTdzBSQWhBM2JKb2pGNGotdEtKRDYyTjUtY3k4VzVZZDBUN1BQbnlZejJ6LURFZEZ4QnUy</guid></item><item><title>完美早餐的速查表： AIIMS培训的胃肠病学家为第一顿饭评分10种流行食物|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cheat-sheet-for-the-perfect-breakfast-aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-rates-10-popular-foods-for-the-first-meal-101766660884255.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyMainDiv" class="fullStory tfStory current videoStory story__detail storyAf101766660884255 " data-vars-storyid="101766660884255" data-story-section="lifestyle" data-story-subsection="health" data-vars-author="Debapriya Bhattacharya" data-premium-story="false" data-performance-type="not-set" data-story-title="Cheat sheet for the perfect breakfast: AIIMS-trained gastroenterologist rates 10 popular foods for the first meal" data-collapse-article="true"&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoTopPageBanner dHide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="stickyCard"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h1 class="hdg1"&gt;Cheat sheet for the perfect breakfast: AIIMS-trained gastroenterologist rates 10 popular foods for the first meal&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;div class="actionDiv flexElm topTime"&gt; &lt;p class="dateTime secTime storyPage"&gt;Published on: Dec 25, 2025 05:04 pm IST &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="googleFollow mHide"&gt; &lt;button class="htEchoShareBarDesk"&gt;&lt;/button&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 class="sortDec"&gt;Dr Sethi believes eggs to be the perfect breakfast food, while cereals and granola rank surprisingly low. &lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;div class="storyDetails taboola-readmore"&gt; &lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/cheat-sheet-for-the-perfect-breakfast-aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-rates-10-popular-foods-for-the-first-meal-101766660884255.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Breakfast is known to be the most important meal of the day. Everyone has their own favourites when it comes to curating the meal. However, not all popular breakfast items are equally beneficial for our health.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/pexels-photo-1495534_1766661446687_1766661465893.jpeg" alt="Granola is not as healthy a breakfast food as it appears to be, warns Dr Sethi. (Pexel)" title="Granola is not as healthy a breakfast food as it appears to be, warns Dr Sethi. (Pexel)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/pexels-photo-1495534_1766661446687_1766661465893.jpeg" alt="Granola is not as healthy a breakfast food as it appears to be, warns Dr Sethi. (Pexel)" title="Granola is not as healthy a breakfast food as it appears to be, warns Dr Sethi. (Pexel)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Granola is not as healthy a breakfast food as it appears to be, warns Dr Sethi. (Pexel)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/florida-gastroenterologist-lists-5-cheat-codes-to-stimulate-bowel-movement-apples-pears-berries-and-more-101766651628556.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Florida gastroenterologist shares 5 cheat codes to stimulate bowel movement: Apples, pears, berries, and more"&gt;Florida gastroenterologist shares 5 cheat codes to stimulate bowel movement: Apples, pears, berries, and more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Taking to Instagram on 25 December, Dr Saurabh Sethi, a California-based gastroenterologist trained in AIIMS, Harvard, and Stanford Universities, ranked some of the most common &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mumbai-based-nutritionist-shares-4-foods-to-avoid-for-breakfast-coffee-oranges-tomatoes-and-more-101766123244036.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="breakfast"&gt;breakfast&lt;/a&gt; options across the globe based on how they impact “&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-shares-4-bad-vs-good-vs-excellent-foods-for-gut-health-beans-oats-berries-and-more-101765872908499.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="gut health"&gt;gut health&lt;/a&gt;, digestion, energy levels, and &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/genesis/between-feasts-and-fasts-finding-balance-for-blood-sugar-during-weddings-and-festivals-101765950606083.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="blood sugar"&gt;blood sugar&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Some (breakfast foods) keep your gut happy and energy stable, while others can silently trigger bloating, crashes, and cravings later in the day,” highlighted Dr Sethi in the caption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Eggs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 10/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eggs provide the best quality protein, are highly bioavailable, and keep us full, shared the doctor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Greek yoghurt&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 9/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Greek yoghurt has high protein content and is a rich source of gut-friendly probiotics. However, Dr Sethi advised opting for the unsweetened varieties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Oatmeal&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 8/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oatmeal provides slow carbs along with beta-glucan fibre for steady energy. However, we should choose steel-cut or rolled oats and avoid instant oats.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Avocado toast&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 8/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A great source of healthy fats and fibre that keeps us satiated.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Paneer / Cottage cheese&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 8/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Paneer, or cottage cheese, contains slow-digesting casein, which helps keep hunger away.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Tofu&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 8/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent source of complete plant protein with metabolic benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7. Smoothie&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 7/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;According to Dr Sethi, smoothies are only good if balanced with vegetables, but are bad if fruit-heavy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;8. Peanut butter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 7/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Peanut butter is a good source of filling fats and protein, but portion size matters when it comes to weighing benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;9. Idli / dosa&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 6/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fermented but carb-heavy, it is important to always pair with protein to create a balanced meal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;10. Cereal / granola&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rating - 2/10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These are often ultra-processed with hidden sugars and seed oils.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="recommendedSliderContextual" id="recommendedSliderContextual-101766660884255" data-vars-story_id="101766660884255" data-vars-story_section="lifestyle" data-vars-author="Debapriya Bhattacharya" data-vars-story_headline="Cheat sheet for the perfect breakfast: AIIMS-trained gastroenterologist rates 10 popular foods for the first meal"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" class="trendTopsSHow" id="trendTopsSHow-101766660884255"&gt; &lt;div class="trendTops"&gt;  &lt;div class="trendInlineSeo"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;label class="moreBtn1" for="trendTopsSHow-101766660884255"&gt;&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="followHT trendSeo__1"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="bottomSeoParaEcho1"&gt; &lt;div id="bottomSeoParaEcho"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="mb5 mt5" id="bottomBreadCrumb"&gt; &lt;div class="breadcrumbs"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Home_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/" data-vars-event-cta="News"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Lifestyle_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle" data-vars-event-cta="Lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Health_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle/health" data-vars-event-cta="Health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Cheat sheet for the perfect breakfast: AIIMS-trained gastroenterologist rates 10 popular foods for the first meal &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="bottomSeoParaEcho pb0"&gt; &lt;label class="moreBtn" for="trendTopsSHow-101766660884255" id="spanSeeLessEcho"&gt;See Less&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;p class="relatedStoryCricket"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="saranyuPlayer" id="saranyu-player"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="relatedStory2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="us-ad align-center mb10 mt10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="htEchoShortsEntryPoint" data-size="enlarged"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="affiliate-shop-now" id="affiliate-shop-now"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:34:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgJBVV95cUxQY2VjSmZYRV9FMzZ0eWtyc2d2Q2QyU1JHcGtYRWRFcFd6RktiSnZWdUthR3ZkRDB3RjM1cVhYODN6TlhZSmpobjE2SWc5T1llT0RMM1NuTm9zNTBCd25FOTdIZHlROFhYQ1U2WUl1d0VaUW5vSmF0OTlCa3p2VVFDaUxfanFxNjZjYVB6aFhycldsVGZDTlI5UWNsenpaekJlbXlzVjU4ZVZpTHFoMXk1Vy1iWklTVUtxbjgwTEF6SHYyRkhHUzFrNEt4ZnVpUDR2NEpoVDFSbjNBVV9BWDh5WjVIUWlGVThOQmlfbi1sdFhZc3BQQXVTbENNY3ptYU1wQWhOeG9jeWZQMl9PcHfSAZMCQVVfeXFMUHlObGVRbFpGekpFbnpxX2VKUnc2ZmlsY1FJbmkzQU1QTFlreXJydWxzc3k0Qy1LbFUtSldEQ3BsdWtDTjFWVHhlT3dIT0RHYzl0dlNYbEIxQlQzQVZRMm5CQmpMbDNYLUgydngxcjROeHlwQTZJdV9SV3B2VlpnTWxQZUVaZWNWTHNEUFJhQjlGRGR1V3ZOSU9uWXY3dFQwV292MU5rZ3VpSU1TU2Y4MEpmU1hQZmlGVE5wWVJ2TTlzM3NHVzI2M1A3Q2R2MURCclozdFpFcmh0bWFCaDk3MV8zLWQ1c3RHNHVvY3ZqMzVKZU1ja2kxSmFMVkY1bkNtYWlJN1BtUU1RdUhYMHJadWpxeHc</guid></item><item><title>用药过量危机正在好转- Salon.com</title><link>https://www.salon.com/2025/12/25/the-overdose-crisis-is-turning-around/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="article__content page-article"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Overdose deaths &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2024/11/15/cdc-overdose-set-to-dip-below-100000-for-the-first-time-since-2020/"&gt;are falling&lt;/a&gt; at a pace the United States has not seen in decades. Centers for Disease Control projections show a nearly &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/nvss/vsrr/drug-overdose-data.htm"&gt;&lt;span&gt;25% decline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for the twelve months ending in April 2025. But the meaning of that decline shows up long before it appears in national reports. It shows up in a son who makes it home from work, in a daughter who stays in treatment long enough to rebuild her life, in the quiet, daily act of someone returning home to the people who love them. It shows up in having another table setting at the holiday dinner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These moments of return do not happen by chance. They happen because public policy finally &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;aligns with evidence and because communities were able to use tools we already know save lives. Policymakers &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://chir.georgetown.edu/tackling-another-public-health-emergency-recent-state-and-federal-policies-to-increase-opioid-use-disorder-treatment-access/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;expanded access&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to medications for opioid use disorder, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.samhsa.gov/substance-use/treatment/statutes-regulations-guidelines/buprenorphine-telemedicine-prescribing"&gt;&lt;span&gt;protected telehealth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for addiction treatment and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pew.org/en/research-and-analysis/issue-briefs/2025/09/state-policy-approaches-to-expand--naloxone-access"&gt;&lt;span&gt;widened community access&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to naloxone. People are home for the holidays because life-saving systems were finally allowed to fully function.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="right_quote"&gt;
&lt;p class="insert-quote"&gt;Whether this progress continues depends on the choices we make now. As we head into 2026, the foundational policies that saved lives this year could disappear before the next holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Whether this progress continues depends on the choices we make now. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;As we head into 2026, the foundational policies that saved lives this year could disappear before the next holiday season.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lifesaving tools that have driven the decline remain vulnerable. Medications for &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/opioids"&gt;opioid&lt;/a&gt; use disorder — especially buprenorphine and methadone — cut the risk of death by more than half. Yet for years, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ecfr.gov/current/title-21/chapter-II/part-1306/subject-group-ECFR1eb5bb3a23fddd0/section-1306.07"&gt;&lt;span&gt;federal rules&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and insurance barriers have kept these treatments out of reach. Even now, many patients face bureaucratic paperwork hurdles, such as prior authorization requirements, which interrupt care and separate patients from necessary prescriptions. States have worked to close these gaps by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2949875924001401"&gt;&lt;span&gt;expanding mobile treatment programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://americanhealth.jhu.edu/news/bringing-addiction-treatment-primary-care-settings"&gt;&lt;span&gt;embedding addiction treatment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; into primary care, specifically in Texas and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pew.org/en/research-and-analysis/fact-sheets/2025/12/how-massachusetts-addresses-substance-use-disorders-in-primary-care-settings"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These changes increased the odds of survival, but the initiatives &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://nasadad.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/04/The-Substance-Use-Workforce-Crisis-Drivers-Challenges-and-Promising-Strategies_POST-2.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;remain under-resourced&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and at-risk. In recent years, telehealth has become one of the most powerful drivers of improved access. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S2949875925001432"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; shows that patients who begin treatment virtually stay in recovery at similar or higher rates than those who start in person. While skeptics remain, the data confirm that telehealth provides quality care without increasing overdose risk. This is especially important to rural counties and households without reliable transportation, where telehealth means the difference between care instead of a crisis. But in 2026, those flexibilities &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cms.gov/files/document/telehealth-faq-updated-11-26-2025.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;will vanish&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; unless Congress acts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Additional changes to insurance coverage expose how quickly people can lose access and be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;pushed out of treatment. &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/medicaid"&gt;Medicaid&lt;/a&gt; covers nearly half of non-elderly adults with opioid use disorder, paying for the critical treatment services that get people to recovery. But this backbone &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2025/03/21/cutting-medicaid-could-worsen-overdose-and-erase-recent-progress-in-treating-addiction/"&gt;is weakening&lt;/a&gt;. During the unwinding of pandemic protections, more than 23 million people have lost Medicaid coverage, which is often &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/medicaid/medicaid-enrollment-and-unwinding-tracker/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;due to paperwork errors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; rather than changes in eligibility. This number is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aha.org/news/headline/2025-07-21-cbo-projects-obbba-increase-uninsured-10-million-federal-deficit-34-trillion"&gt;&lt;span&gt;estimated to increase significantly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; following the passage of the &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/big_beautiful_bill"&gt;One Big Beautiful Bill&lt;/a&gt;, which according to the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office (CBO), will &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/medicaid/allocating-cbos-estimates-of-federal-medicaid-spending-reductions-across-the-states-enacted-reconciliation-package/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;slash Medicaid and Children’s Health Insurance Program (CHIP) spending&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by nearly $1 trillion over a decade and eliminate over 10 million people from the programs. Similarly, the CBO warns that about 1.5 million Americans will be uninsured in 2026 if Congress delays extending the ACA enhanced tax credits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want more sharp takes on politics? &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/newsletter?utm_source=onsite&amp;amp;utm_medium=organic&amp;amp;utm_campaign=standing-room-only-edit-signup"&gt;Sign up for our free newsletter&lt;/a&gt;, Standing Room Only, written by Amanda Marcotte, now also a weekly show &lt;a href="%E2%80%9Dhttps://www.salon.com/2025/06/13/standing-room-only-amanda-marcotte-salon-youtube-podcast/%E2%80%9D"&gt;on YouTube or wherever you get your podcasts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Congress has the power to address these lapsing policies in 2026 and needs to act — just as it did with the bipartisan reauthorization of the SUPPORT for Patients and Communities Act, which promises to continue federal funding for core recovery programs and to address overdose. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But maintaining the status quo is not enough to resolve the fracture points where people still fall out of care. In 2026, Congress should pass legislation to ensure that Americans who are most vulnerable to fatal overdose, such as those entering and leaving jail and prison, receive evidence-based, lifesaving treatment. Congress can grow the treatment workforce by funding and expanding peer recovery support workers. These proposals follow the same evidence that drove the decline in 2025.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The drop in overdose deaths this year is real. It reflects years of work by clinicians, community &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;groups, families and bipartisan lawmakers who chose data over dogma. But a decline does not &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;equal victory. It equals a narrow window of opportunity. The difference between momentum and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;reversal now runs through the legislative decisions that will shape 2026. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just like this holiday season, families will gather again next December. Some seats will be filled because of the policies that worked in 2025. Others will stand empty if those policies unravel in 2026. The country already knows which choices save lives. What remains unclear is whether it will keep making them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="layout_template_wrapper read_more"&gt;
&lt;div class="red_white_box"&gt;
&lt;p class="red_box"&gt;Read more&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="white_box"&gt;about this topic&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Salon.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:30:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTFByR0tuZUdWSmxBNWtTT3p6S3JyWlVUSTA0cE0wVDJ0Vk9qQ3RQcjkxVVRfTVl0QUZzZGhjcVpfNUI2NXJoX1g1NHZoV3QwNTdiYjZTdEEtSjFLNXZNYldfZThHdEM3alNTUnBETUhaeW5NRVM2em11LWprdw</guid></item><item><title>5项早晨站立锻炼， 40岁后早餐前肚子变平-吃这个不是那个</title><link>https://www.eatthis.com/morning-standing-exercises-flatten-stomach-after-40/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content single-post-content"&gt;
																			&lt;p class="tagline"&gt;No floor work needed, these 5 standing moves wake up your core before breakfast.&lt;/p&gt;
												
																			
																		
						
						
						&lt;p&gt;While turning 40 has many upsides, waking up typically means more soreness and less excitement for morning workouts compared to when you were younger. And the idea of getting down on the floor for crunches or grinding through a lengthy cardio session before breakfast can feel more draining than energizing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The good news is you don’t need intense morning workouts or hour-long cardio sessions to tighten your midsection. Instead, all you need are standing exercises to boost your body composition as you age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While no exercise can literally “spot reduce” belly fat, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/endocrinology/articles/10.3389/fendo.2025.1409474/full" target="_blank"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; show that daily movement and strength training exercises combined with light-to-moderate cardio performed consistently can improve insulin sensitivity, preserve lean muscle, and support fat loss. Additionally, morning exercise can help &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://journals.physiology.org/doi/full/10.1152/japplphysiol.00001.2019" target="_blank"&gt;combat overnight stiffness&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/physiology/articles/10.3389/fphys.2019.00762/full" target="_blank"&gt;enhance blood flow&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-025-02659-8" target="_blank"&gt;boost your metabolism&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more, we chatted with &lt;b&gt;James Brady&lt;/b&gt;, a personal trainer at &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.origym.co.uk/blog/author/jbrady/" target="_blank"&gt;OriGym&lt;/a&gt;, who shares his top five morning standing exercises for those 40-plus to flatten your stomach before breakfast. Read on for the exercises and detailed instructions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(And when you’re done, don’t miss these &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/chair-exercises-shrink-belly-pooch-over-50-no-planks/" target="_blank"&gt;5 Chair Exercises That Shrink Belly Pooch Better Than Planks After 50&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="bodyweight-squats" class="o-slide-title" data-num="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bodyweight Squats&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/l83R5PblSMA?si=jSGruoD8y8f6cWKJ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;6254a4d1642c605c54bf1cab17d50f1e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Squats are king when it comes to compound exercises. That’s because this classic move engages multiple large muscle groups at once. “Bodyweight squats activate the largest muscle groups in the body and quickly raise the heart rate,” explains Brady. “This helps increase calorie burn early in the day while building lean muscle that supports long term weight loss.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet about shoulder-width apart and your toes slightly turned outward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage your core while keeping your chest upright and your shoulders relaxed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Push your hips back as if sitting into a chair while bending your knees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower until your thighs are roughly parallel to the floor (or as far as you can go comfortably).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive through your heels to stand back up while squeezing your glutes at the top.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform three to four sets of 10 to 12 reps. Rest for 60 to 90 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed karma_unit--halfpage"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="standing-knee-drives" class="o-slide-title" data-num="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Standing Knee Drives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/lGsMmiLMj3o?si=XPSDehA5UlJ0HoJI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike high-impact exercises, standing knee raises increase your heart rate gradually while reinforcing coordination and stability, both of which tend to decline without regular practice after 40.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Standing knee drives combine gentle cardio with core engagement, helping to improve balance while encouraging blood flow and energy production,” explains Brady. “This exercise supports weight loss by increasing movement efficiency and metabolic activity without feeling overwhelming in the morning.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand tall with your feet hip-width apart and your hands resting lightly at your sides or on your hips.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift one knee toward your chest while keeping your torso upright.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage your core to control the movement rather than swinging your leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower your foot back to the floor with control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alternate sides while moving smoothly and rhythmically.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Aim for three to four sets of 12 to 15 reps per side. Rest for 60 to 90 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="jumping-jacks" class="o-slide-title" data-num="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jumping Jacks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/iSSAk4XCsRA?si=TdkawKsjhJ1JpDWC" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jumping jacks often get overlooked because they seem basic, but they’re undeniably one of the most efficient full-body movements you can do. “Jumping jacks are a simple but powerful exercise that elevate the heart rate and get your full body moving,” Brady says. “From a weight loss perspective, they’re great as they burn calories and improve cardiovascular fitness with minimal setup.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet together and your arms relaxed at your sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step or jump your feet out wide while raising your arms overhead.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your core engaged and your chest lifted throughout the movement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return to the starting position with control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue at a steady, comfortable pace rather than rushing the reps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jump for 30 to 45 seconds without stopping. Rest for 90 seconds and repeat two to three more times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="standing-torso-twists" class="o-slide-title" data-num="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Standing Torso Twists&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/h6XyzlM8m24?si=35Xd0CrrwVfSbM9R" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Morning stiffness in the spine is common after 40, especially after hours of sleep. Fortunately, this movement can help restore mobility while lightly engaging your obliques (side abs) and deep core muscles that support posture and rotation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Standing torso twists focus on the core and obliques while promoting spinal mobility, which is particularly beneficial after sleep,” explains Brady. “Although lower impact, they support weight loss by making other physical activity feel easier throughout the day.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet shoulder-width apart and your knees slightly bent.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bring your arms out in front of you or place your hands across your chest.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rotate your torso slowly to one side while keeping your hips facing forward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Return to center, then rotate to the opposite side.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Move in a controlled, fluid motion without forcing the range of motion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete 15 to 20 reps per side, resting for 60 to 90 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="marching-in-place-with-arm-swings" class="o-slide-title" data-num="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Marching in Place With Arm Swings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/1IC-B4A91Ds?si=WgJVmtHGQUmcbrXl" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Marching in place may look simple, but it’s a powerful way to wake up the nervous system and reinforce coordination between the upper and lower body. “Marching in place with arm swings gently raises the heart rate while encouraging coordination and full body circulation,” Brady tells us. “This movement supports fat loss by helping people ease into activity and build consistency, which is one of the biggest drivers of sustainable weight loss.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand tall with your arms relaxed at your sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift one knee while swinging your opposite arm forward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower your foot and repeat on the other side.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your movements smooth and controlled rather than rushed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain steady breathing and upright posture throughout.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform this movement nonstop for three to four sets of 30 to 45 seconds. Rest for 60 to 90 seconds between sets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

																		
																	&lt;/div&gt;
										&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio"&gt;
	&lt;p class="c-article-short-bio__name"&gt;Adam Meyer, RHN&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
		Adam is a health writer, certified holistic nutritionist, and 100% plant-based athlete.					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="c-article-short-bio__more" href="https://www.eatthis.com/author/adam-meyer/"&gt;Read more about Adam &lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Eat This Not That</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 11:00:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQcTlpTkhmcnR2Y2xKdi1MMHplaGI0MkxtTDNHOVRKT2dlSGhKeTZaekx6cWl2NVVoSF9NejlvSVNUOUF0RDVTdW5QZ3JqbUZMOGJWSW9BUlRRQm5paHUxb2EtRnJtbWVmRUo4OTFIVnlkWUUtbF9DQVMzYVJqVnpNMWdn</guid></item><item><title>当我放屁时，我会避免食物昏迷，睡得更好—这就是为什么它有效-汤姆的指南</title><link>https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/fart-walking-could-be-the-key-to-sleeping-better-after-christmas-dinner-heres-why</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;

&lt;p id="a49896fe-957d-4874-a98e-4126fde560a1"&gt;The Christmas dinner has been eaten, the dishes done and you're faced with the post-roast slump. A nap on the coach is probably calling you're name, but sleep experts urge you take a 'fart walk' instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="fancy-box" id="c942fbcd-29b6-452e-a8e5-130204790763"&gt;&lt;p class="fancy_box-title"&gt;New year, new bed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="fancy_box_body"&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure "&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=""&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Future)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="fancy-box__body-text"&gt;Is your mattress due an upgrade in 2026? Our guide to the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/mattresses/best-mattress" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/mattresses/best-mattress"&gt;best mattresses&lt;/a&gt; online helps you find the right one for your budget and sleep needs, all tried and tested by our sleep experts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="b488df11-ee14-4071-b7c1-d7898376c900" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;The most commonly cited benefits of fart walking are improved digestion, better blood sugar regulation and reduced bloating, so why are we writing about it on Tom's Guide's sleep desk? Well, all of these things are tied in with getting a good night's rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="b488df11-ee14-4071-b7c1-d7898376c900-1"&gt;"Walking after eating helps us get &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/how-to/how-to-sleep-better" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/how-to/how-to-sleep-better"&gt;better sleep&lt;/a&gt; by reducing stress, managing blood sugar levels, and improving digestion by stimulating the gastrointestinal tract," says Physician and Medical Director &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://wellbridge.org/contributors/edmond-hakimi/" target="_blank" data-url="https://wellbridge.org/contributors/edmond-hakimi/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Dr. Edmonds Hakimi&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although there's no scientific studies specifically looking at '&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/fart-walking-is-trending-heres-everything-you-need-to-know" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/fart-walking-is-trending-heres-everything-you-need-to-know"&gt;fart walking&lt;/a&gt;' (we're not sure that title would sit well in an academic journal), science checks out on general walking for better sleep — and the sleep experts I've consulted approve of the trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-9511b0f6-a29c-4e86-933a-b5fe22116179" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-fart-walking-3"&gt;What is fart walking?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="21a40acc-8672-4c28-93ac-9e3cdb0e010c"&gt;The fart walking technique is simple: You get up and go for a short, relaxed walk just after finishing a meal to stimulate your bowels and release gas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kudos for the trend and its catchy name go to Canadian cookbook author &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.mairlynsmith.com/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.mairlynsmith.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Marilyn Smith&lt;/a&gt;, who now names herself 'The Fart Walking Lady'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Debuting fart walking in a social media video, Smith explains taking a gentle walk in the evening after dinner can not only help you release gas, but also reduce your risk of developing type two diabetes and help you "age wonderfully."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-DauQof4UEtkABVbcsTDZPN" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-DauQof4UEtkABVbcsTDZPN slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get instant access to breaking news, the hottest reviews, great deals and helpful tips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="e3ccd17f-80bf-40f4-936b-8952f06abe16"&gt;Health-conscious TikTokers have soaked up her advice and, thankfully, it's not any old social media fad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the lack of direct science on the fart walk, there's plenty of evidence backing up how it can help you sleep at night, especially after an indulgent meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-5c2f5e99-2d16-4e60-abea-f22c743416cf" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="walk-your-way-to-better-sleep-3"&gt;Walk your way to better sleep &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="ed9e1b76-672b-4c10-860f-f6d62a089ad6"&gt;Walking, no matter the time of day, offers great sleep benefits. Seriously, studies show it &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/daily-exercise-reduces-sleep-apnea-risk-new-study" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/daily-exercise-reduces-sleep-apnea-risk-new-study"&gt;reduces the risk of sleep apnea &lt;/a&gt;and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6801055/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6801055/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;boosts sleep quality&lt;/a&gt;, as well as leading to more &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/deep-sleep" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/deep-sleep"&gt;deep sleep&lt;/a&gt; and a regulated &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/circadian-rhythm" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/circadian-rhythm"&gt;body clock&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Walking helps you sleep better by influencing both physiological and psychological factors, including regulating your body clock, reducing stress, and inducing physical tiredness," says &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.soaak.com/team/dr-paul-harris-nd" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.soaak.com/team/dr-paul-harris-nd" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Dr. Paul Harris&lt;/a&gt;, Medical Director of Soaak Technologies with over 50 years experience in Naturopathic and Functional medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="ac6607fb-418a-48e6-968b-396015af3cf4"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="e913bdea-73da-455b-9ece-c358ffb8fe77"&gt;"For best sleep benefits, morning walks are great for setting your internal clock (circadian rhythm) and boosting daytime energy, while gentle evening walks 30 to 90 mins before bed [aka a fart walk] relieve stress and signal winding down," he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, how exactly does fart walking pave the way for better sleep? From improved digestion to body temperature regulation, ahead you'll find out all the reasons why a fart walk could save your sleep this holiday season...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-4-reasons-fart-walking-helps-you-sleep" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-4-reasons-fart-walking-helps-you-sleep"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4 reasons fart walking helps you sleep &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a id="elk-5935d3c1-a861-463a-ba39-0303fbafd1ab" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="1-it-improves-digestion-3"&gt;1. It improves digestion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="68218562-b63d-4b52-ae43-d7f4f88b6546"&gt;Time and time again, experts have warned about how your &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/5-eating-habits-that-are-keeping-you-awake-at-night-and-3-sleep-friendly-alternatives" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/5-eating-habits-that-are-keeping-you-awake-at-night-and-3-sleep-friendly-alternatives"&gt;eating habits impact sleep&lt;/a&gt;. Eating too close to bedtime is particularly associated with negative sleep outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Providing a buffer between mealtime and bedtime, a fart walk is the ideal way for your body to sort through sustenance before bed, getting digestion out the way before your body starts winding down to rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="117dc800-952d-43b8-bd09-d103d1464eee"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="340e842c-713e-4f44-9f09-16ce40af3d91"&gt;"A gentle walk after eating supports digestion. It wakes up your digestive system so that food can be digested and move past the stomach before sleeping," says certified integrative physician and sleep expert &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/gb/contributors/jacob-teitelbaum-md" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.psychologytoday.com/gb/contributors/jacob-teitelbaum-md" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Jacob Teitelbaum, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Otherwise, people are more prone to nighttime acid reflux, which disrupts sleep." This can also help you avoid the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/how-to-sleep-with-gerd-5-steps-from-a-sleep-doctor" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/how-to-sleep-with-gerd-5-steps-from-a-sleep-doctor"&gt;symptoms of GERD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-9520611f-9fe1-46c3-bca2-47985f2430a5" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="2-it-relieves-stress-3"&gt;2. It relieves stress &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="45c972c0-d43d-48c0-8280-013847838041"&gt;It's no secret that &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/stress-often-wakes-me-up-in-the-middle-of-the-night-why-it-happens-and-how-sound-therapy-is-helping-me-sleep-better" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/stress-often-wakes-me-up-in-the-middle-of-the-night-why-it-happens-and-how-sound-therapy-is-helping-me-sleep-better"&gt;stress and sleep&lt;/a&gt; just don't get along. You don't even need to be a bundle of nerves for stress to impact your rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, underlying stress (those worries constantly sitting at the back of your mind) can creep up at bedtime, keeping you awake staring at the ceiling way later than you intended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But worry not, a fart walk could take that stress away. Walking and moving in general is &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11298280/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11298280/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;scientifically proven&lt;/a&gt; to lower stress and boost feel-good hormones like serotonin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plus, a post-meal stroll physically eases the discomfort of bloating, which often exacerbates stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="a2dfcbff-da40-4933-8fd8-ec7ef5457f7e"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="1ec0d09d-5cf7-4870-8e8e-f6c9a280162e"&gt;"Easy walks help you to burn off excess adrenaline and release stress, so you can ease into the rest and relax part of the nervous system (the parasympathetic nervous system)," says Teitelbaum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the parasympathetic nervous system activated, your heart rate is slower and you're sure to feel calmer and more ready to nod off by the time your head hits the pillow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-15dc926a-0e99-41ea-9a8b-9c965b501883" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="3-it-aids-blood-sugar-management-3"&gt;3. It aids blood sugar management&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="7f26959b-56c6-4523-90fd-ccdcffc3bbf3"&gt;As mentioned above, improve blood sugar regulation is one of the beauties of fart walking, and this can set you up for a more peaceful night's sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the OG fart walking TikTok, Smith says fart walking helps maintain blood sugar levels — "keeping them from ricocheting all around" — particularly among older individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the science of fart walking and blood sugar is yet to be studied in depth, one &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35268055/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35268055/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;small study&lt;/a&gt; showed a 30-minute walk after eating can help curb blood sugar spikes, which is good news for sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="37016d44-6836-44b5-87aa-8ed4c5c2a9dd"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="d227ec1b-bf76-44bc-91c3-b5e08fd290ff"&gt;From hormonal interference to nighttime awakenings, unstable blood sugar levels are no good for sleep. Rapid sugar spikes after eating (thanks to glucose in food) spike &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/cortisol" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/cortisol"&gt;cortisol&lt;/a&gt;, making it harder to fall or stay asleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, high blood sugar levels cause thirst and urination, making you get up more frequently at night. On the flip side, low blood sugar can cause disrupting &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep-problems/night-sweats" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep-problems/night-sweats"&gt;night sweats&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood sugar can also interfere with sleep cycles with unstable glucose levels reducing &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/deep-sleep" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/deep-sleep"&gt;deep sleep&lt;/a&gt;. Without plenty of this restorative sleep stage, you won't feel as refreshed upon waking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-how-to-fart-walk-for-better-sleep" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-to-fart-walk-for-better-sleep"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to fart walk for better sleep&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul id="1cf40b35-3127-46a9-99ef-b1e6b7e6b8a6"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When should you walk?&lt;/strong&gt; Just after dinner&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How long should you walk for?&lt;/strong&gt; 15 to 30 minutes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What about intensity?&lt;/strong&gt; It should be a light rather than vigorous walk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="3cff57de-a11f-4323-8971-7dedb1674759"&gt;It can certainly be tempting to curl up on the sofa after your festive dinner and snooze the afternoon away. But that can lead to a lot of tossing and turning once bedtime rolls around. Instead, experts urge you to take a fart walk before hitting the hay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://aimvein.com/pages/meet-dr-emma-lin" target="_blank" data-url="https://aimvein.com/pages/meet-dr-emma-lin" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Dr. Emma Lin&lt;/a&gt;, a board-certified Pulmonologist and Sleep Medicine Specialist, offers a word of warning: "There’s no need for speed," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The idea is to increase your heart rate slightly and engage your lungs, but not to the point that you find yourself too alert afterwards."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="b46bb51a-4920-4956-8329-60bb0811dc67"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="d8936479-52c5-4667-85fc-0e350057619e"&gt;A &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30374942/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30374942/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;2019 study in Sports Medicine&lt;/a&gt; did confirm, after all, that vigorous exercise ending an hour or less before bed can impair sleep efficiency and sleep time, and make it harder to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/how-to-fall-asleep-fast" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/how-to-fall-asleep-fast"&gt;fall asleep fast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, science indicates that, for the biggest benefit, you should get out and walk as soon as possible after a meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10036272/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10036272/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; by German researchers found walking stopped blood sugar levels becoming too high when undertaken as soon as possible after a meal rather than after a longer interval or before eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the space between your fart walk and actually getting into bed, it's important you keep your body in that calm space by following a sleep-friendly evening routine. This routine will look different for everyone depending on your responsibilities and preferences. &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/dont-bother-dark-showering-theres-a-much-easier-alternative-and-it-helps-me-fall-asleep-fast" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/dont-bother-dark-showering-theres-a-much-easier-alternative-and-it-helps-me-fall-asleep-fast"&gt;Dark shower&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/best-before-bed-stretches" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/sleep/best-before-bed-stretches"&gt;pre-bed stretch&lt;/a&gt;, anyone?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tom's Guide</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 10:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxQUTJIbTlZaGQ0RFFnc2ZXdjVyRmY4NVh3NFBScXp0QnRsRmxOb092Z0YtODlzMlF1YnNMWGVZazZNQUZQUm1uNnFxemRDUUctcGhKX25pbVFMUlB4eUVzRzNWQkxGbGRfTHdCUTBZdWtuOV8xY3c3Q1dKX2dBcHJLWGZ5cUVoSDdQUEh1WXJoSUVxOXA1U1FxOThZcERxbmV4VnViNWE0SXFfaGI0Skk5THVkMXZya0tVWTI3RjI3Yw</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现了一种恢复痴呆症患者脑血流的方法- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251225031247.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A potential new way to treat reduced brain blood flow and certain forms of dementia is beginning to emerge. Scientists at the University of Vermont Robert Larner, M.D. College of Medicine have uncovered new details about how blood circulation in the brain is controlled and how vascular problems might be reversed. Their preclinical research, published December 22 in &lt;em&gt;Proceedings of the National Academy of Sciences&lt;/em&gt;, suggests that replacing a missing phospholipid in the bloodstream could help restore normal brain blood flow and ease dementia-related symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This discovery is a huge step forward in our efforts to prevent dementia and neurovascular diseases," says principal investigator Osama Harraz, Ph.D., assistant professor of pharmacology at Larner College of Medicine. "We are uncovering the complex mechanisms of these devastating conditions, and now we can begin to think about how to translate this biology into therapies."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Rising Burden of Dementia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer's disease and related dementias affect about 50 million people worldwide, and that number continues to grow. The increasing prevalence places heavy pressure on families, caregivers, and health care systems. Ongoing research is working to untangle how proteins, inflammation, neural signaling, and malfunctioning brain cells contribute to these disorders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Work in the Harraz lab centers on how cerebral blood flow is controlled and how blood vessels communicate through molecular signals. A major focus is Piezo1, a protein found in the membranes of cells that line blood vessels. Piezo1 helps regulate brain blood flow by sensing physical forces created as blood moves through the brain's vascular network. Its name comes from the Greek word for "pressure." Earlier research showed that Piezo1 behaves differently in people who carry certain genetic variations of the Piezo1 gene.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Key Lipid That Keeps Blood Vessels in Check&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new study, titled "PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; Corrects an Endothelial Piezo1 Channelopathy," offers fresh insight into how Piezo1 influences cerebral blood flow. The findings also show that conditions such as Alzheimer's disease are linked to abnormally high Piezo1 activity in brain blood vessels. To better understand why this happens, the research team examined a phospholipid called PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;, which is found in brain cell membranes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; plays an essential role in cell signaling and ion channel regulation -- a complex process that controls when protein pores in cells open and close. The researchers discovered that PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; normally acts as a natural suppressor of Piezo1. When PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; levels fall, Piezo1 becomes overly active, disrupting normal blood flow in the brain. When the team added PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; back into the system, Piezo1 activity decreased and healthy blood circulation was restored. These results suggest that increasing PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; levels could form the basis of a new treatment strategy aimed at improving brain blood flow and supporting brain function.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps Toward Future Treatments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Future studies will focus on understanding exactly how PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; interacts with Piezo1. Researchers want to determine whether PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; attaches directly to specific parts of the protein or changes the surrounding cell membrane in ways that limit channel opening. Additional work will also explore how disease-related declines in PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; remove this regulatory control, allowing Piezo1 to remain overactive and impair cerebral blood flow. Gaining clarity on these mechanisms will be critical for developing therapies based on restoring PIP&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; or directly targeting Piezo1 to improve neurovascular health in dementia and related vascular disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 08:55:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBvaHlFUzBHanpKNDJadmM5OW9zOE9hbXdpSTZNYjltT1lVYXdlT1hya3V4ekRTdTU4VHdBTkxIUmMxQk5abDV0R3pZemVKTjdQdUZRbnZwU0Q0NlMweVZRZWlJRHFBSklBOUNJdVAyOA</guid></item><item><title>不明原因的体重增加？医生透露这可能是甲状腺活动不足的迹象|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gained-unexplained-weight-doctor-reveals-it-may-be-a-sign-of-underactive-thyroid-101766644639293.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/gained-unexplained-weight-doctor-reveals-it-may-be-a-sign-of-underactive-thyroid-101766644639293.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/chennai-fitness-trainer-with-18-years-of-experience-shares-4-mindful-hacks-to-prevent-weight-gain-due-to-overeating-101766492474363.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Weight gain"&gt;Weight gain&lt;/a&gt; is usually associated with a sedentary lifestyle, frequent consumption of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/dermatologist-explains-why-simply-cutting-out-junk-food-does-not-cure-acne-busts-5-common-acne-myths-101759478620994.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="junk food"&gt;junk food&lt;/a&gt;, or insufficient physical activity. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;However, when the numbers on the scale continue to rise despite mindful eating habits and regular movements, then the cause may be deeper, beyond behavioural or lifestyle factors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/weight_gain__1766645134269_1766645134504.jpg" alt="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/25/550x309/weight_gain__1766645134269_1766645134504.jpg" alt="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Underactive thyroid causes your weight to gain. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/ahmedabad-physician-shares-the-key-foods-and-nutrients-you-should-include-in-your-diet-for-a-healthier-thyroid-101765873817961.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Ahmedabad physician shares the key foods and nutrients you should include in your diet for a healthier thyroid"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ahmedabad physician shares the key foods and nutrients you should include in your diet for a healthier thyroid&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To understand one of these unseen causes, HT Lifestyle connected with Dr Gaurav Jain, senior consultant of internal medicine at Dharamshila Narayana Superspeciality Hospital, Delhi. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;According to him, unexplained weight gain can often be linked to an imbalance in the thyroid gland, which plays a crucial role in regulating the body's metabolism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;When the thyroid becomes underactive, a condition known as hypothyroidism, the body’s metabolic processes slow down, leading to gradual and often confusing weight gain,” he explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;How do you know if your weight gain is connected to a thyroid imbalance? Some subtle signs are often attributed to other causes, as they tend to overlap with common health issues. This is why paying closer attention to these symptoms is crucial so that you can distinguish and identify.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Gaurav Jain shared 5 signs:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Weight gain despite normal eating habits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Jain explained that weight gain is the first red flag with an underactive thyroid, particularly when there has been no major change in diet or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;Why does this happen? He explained, “A sluggish thyroid slows down the body's calorie-burning rate, leading to fat accumulation, particularly around the abdomen.” Another key indicator that he informed is that weight is very hard to lose, even if you are regularly exercising.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Persistent fatigue and low energy levels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exhaustion is generally linked to stress or burnout. In fact, fatigue overlaps with several mental and physical issues, which is why it is often overlooked. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;However, Dr Jain pointed out that persistent, unexplained fatigue can also be an early sign of an underactive thyroid, especially when it occurs alongside gradual weight gain and low energy levels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He described why this happens: “&lt;span&gt; Thyroid hormones are essential for energy production. When levels drop, the body feels constantly tired and sluggish. This ongoing fatigue reduces physical activity, further contributing to weight gain and a feeling of heaviness in the body.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Dry skin, hair fall and slow nail growth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/07/24/550x309/hair__1753345225207_1753345225312.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="You experience a lot of hairfall with an underactive thyroid. (Shutterstock)" title="You experience a lot of hairfall with an underactive thyroid. (Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;You experience a lot of hairfall with an underactive thyroid. (Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Changes in the skin, hair, and nails may look like cosmetic issues that require you to change your skincare, haircare or manicure routine, but sometimes they can be associated with deeper health issues.&lt;/span&gt; Dr Jain cautioned that an underactive thyroid affects the skin's ability to retain moisture, making makin it dry, rough, and less elastic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He named some changes, “Hair fall is common, and hair may become thin or brittle. Nails often grow more slowly and may appear weak or ridged.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Hormonal imbalance and menstrual changes in women&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Thyroid health is closely linked to reproductive health, which means it can impact hormone levels and make women more likely to experience problems associated with hormonal disruptions when the thyroid is underactive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Describing how the menstrual flow gets affected, “In women, hypothyroidism can disrupt menstrual cycles, making them irregular, heavy or painful.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Jain also elaborated that low thyroid hormone levels can disturb hormonal balance, leading to fluid retention and increased fat storage, which can result in unexplained weight gain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Neck swelling, eye symptoms and digestive slowdown&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/25/550x309/stomach_pain_1756092360701_1756092366710.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Unhealthy gut causes weight gain.(Shutterstock)" title="Unhealthy gut causes weight gain.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Unhealthy gut causes weight gain.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;Physical changes in the neck and eyes, along with digestive issues, can also point to thyroid dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Jain shared these 3 signs related to these areas:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;An enlarged thyroid may appear as a swelling in the neck and can sometimes cause difficulty in swallowing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mild vision disturbances, blurred vision and puffy eyes may also be present.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Digestion slows down, leading to bloating and constipation, which can add to weight gain and discomfort.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the doctor warned about a couple of important points. Firstly, unexplained weight gain and other subtle symptoms should not always be dismissed. Secondly, with the increasing use of non-iodised salts and changing dietary patterns, early and subclinical thyroid disorders are increasingly common.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 07:54:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxNUDI0ajJ4aU9yOTBrSVZERUMwc3IxZFYtR2MwQVFUMm04X1NqaDMyX0t1VjYxcW9yd2s1ZFRfOV9UQkJsa0ZIVUZGd1NkbHd2S2YzUXNPUEVsMm1BOGtuVF93eXlRXzBBUW1fOTNVZnVmUlBkTjFiTXAyMTNia2U0TkNoVnNsNnBIRVYwNUNJTk1EMnVvRkFuTkpFc2p0ZVdGYmJpTFRWOE93M21tbFRZTS1sVmJIRE1lTjdONnNhUXlsbVd0VlZzX0U4blBBSFFSNUtnMGplaDNZODNJX0pJbEpNc9IB6AFBVV95cUxOMUc1eTVjQkNLSFZyWFQ4UlpGTTByQ2ZVa0g1NzIyOTZ4cTlSbkVpbFFFdUZTRkVZd3gxTDYtaXNyc1k2NW5ibG9adHg0TEZvNkc2MVZUUHVyc3JvbW5wNHRLeWZPVEhwaEFQa1lmZGtyak5SOGdSWVdQcmFHdUJ1ZHF6M3pyRFY4VWEyb0NzOFlPd2dpcHRfckp4T2QwZEg2VmNkSm5LaHdoem1PVHAwWDZIU083VTEyR3hUaEJmLWlHUTVmYkVEZF8wbWRDeEdKek1SVVliamZNZUJTUno3UzBZem5FY0Rs</guid></item></channel></rss>