<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>帕金森病患者在深脑刺激手术中演奏单簧管-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/10/22/parkinsons-disease-clarinet-deep-brain-stimulation/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RLIZARSPDVBHJJMHCOC25FBICQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;LONDON — The doctors prepared to carry out the brain surgery, their medical tools laid out. Their patient, wide awake on the operating table, was given an instrument of her own: her clarinet, which she began to play.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 19:01:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxQaEQ2VVh1V2VPWXA0Qjd5MVJyWGhXRXY4a1ZwUkdCeWt5OHZnWnlkLVh1VUhZc0MyNWdkTzQxR0o4MThMcDNpaXlacjVJa1A2TU1MaHp2OWlDSlZnQ3FvdHVfVTRIU3ZtNXktUDJIQ3pBRDRmY2hXcTB4MkRRTE9Gdk1YVUxXNUVJbEJ0ejFnSEUwMWY2S2VnLWZQMXNYVUpxS0E</guid></item><item><title>研究比较了抗抑郁药的副作用，发现体重、心率等方面的变化差异很大- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/antidepressants-side-effects-weight-heart-rate-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Antidepressants, medications used to treat depression, anxiety and other health conditions, can cause a wide range of physiological side effects depending on which one you take, according to a new study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the study, published Tuesday in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736%2825%2901293-0/fulltext" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;The Lancet&lt;/a&gt;, researchers analyzed more than 58,000 participants to compare 30 antidepressants with a placebo for an average of eight weeks, finding "clinically significant" differences between the drugs' effect on blood flow and metabolism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The differences noted in the study include weight change, heart rate, blood pressure and total cholesterol.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For weight change, researchers found some antidepressants, including maprotiline and amitriptyline, were associated with weight gain in almost half of participants — about a 4-pound average increase with maprotiline, for example. However, other drugs, such as agomelatine, were associated with weight loss in 55% of patients who lost approximately 5.5 pounds on average. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For heart rate, some drugs caused increases — like a 14 beats-per-minute increase on average for nortriptyline — while others caused decreases, such as an average decrease of 8 beats-per-minute for fluvoxamine.  &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kidney and liver function, electrolyte levels and heart rhythm were not majorly effected by most antidepressants, according to the study.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings should not deter people from taking antidepressants, which remain effective treatments, the study's authors write, but instead should highlight the need for better tailoring of treatments to best fit a patient's health and preferences. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We do know that these medications are life-saving and life-changing, but they can have variation from person to person depending on a person's metabolism, their age (and) what other medications they're on," psychiatrist Dr. Sue Varma, who was not involved in the study, said on "CBS Mornings Plus" Wednesday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Untreated depression also can cause the side effects explored in the study, including weight gain or loss, Varma added, making it important to "weigh the risks and the benefits" of medications.  &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She suggests doctors make it clear to patients that antidepressants can potentially exacerbate underlying conditions like elevated cholesterol or diabetes, make a plan to monitor side effects carefully and provide an array of lifestyle interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Let's not cause panic, but these medications do have really important side effects," Varma said.  &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/section&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 17:42:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOZnFiRG5UcGxzU1ZSY0hQLW5TYmljV2RhOVN5RjVnaEFBWTBjaUhxcFQ4THlEcU9CeFBfRTBQQ0t6cnZ1dnJpVUJJLUZUbXJhcGJHRFdoRXkzcnBTSnJRZUdCWnZFd0xGb3ZLbk9uR2VQTWFyd2ZvYUFpZ3JSbERwdjJZYWFJYUtTb0HSAY8BQVVfeXFMTVZONWhFR2h4SXV1YXVPd1c0X0pSU1ZxNTczb1p5c2lGVFFnRjhOWmNFdmdZd1RLV01HbEtlUGd2QTdDeDd1Q0M4MEU0bGRCVXJ0Y25fVVVXclNZdXZzMnYtM1hJWXJleXd5OXJ0UTRrTzJZMGU5TlhCaHBGakNaV0YtQTV5VHhJVEpiZmNyYjQ</guid></item><item><title>田纳西州31所学校爆发手足口病日托- ABC新闻-突发新闻、最新新闻和视频</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/hand-foot-mouth-disease-outbreak-hits-31-schools/story?id=126752726</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;An outbreak of hand, foot, and mouth disease (HFMD) has hit Tennessee, affecting dozens of schools in Shelby County, which includes the city of Memphis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The county health department said cases were first identified in August, but health officials were not notified until early September.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Since then, 31 schools and three child care centers have been affected and at least 178 students and staff members have fallen ill, according to an &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.localmemphis.com/article/news/health/health-alert/more-than-30-schools-170-people-affected-by-hand-foot-and-mouth-disease-schd-reports/522-bbdd8fb9-2396-48e1-9b91-cb67c7909c0c" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;update&lt;/a&gt; from the Shelby County Health Department (SCHD).  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;SCHD said it is working closely with schools and child care providers to monitor cases and prevent further spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The department did not list the schools affected, but at least one is Sherwood Elementary in Memphis, according to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.localmemphis.com/article/news/education/hand-foot-and-mouth-disease-confirmed-at-sherwood-elementary/522-0864ac1b-7899-41f2-abb1-187336fcfe2e" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;local ABC News affiliate WATN-TV&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Parents received alerts about HFMD cases through email, robocalls and text messages with district officials saying extra steps were being taken to disinfect classrooms, WATN reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Close-up of human palms showing hand-foot-mouth disease symptoms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Yaroslav Litun/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;HFMD is a disease that is most common in children under 5 years old, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/hand-foot-mouth/about/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Most patients have mild symptoms for seven to 10 days, which can include fever, sore throat, painful mouth sores that blister and a rash on the hands and feet, the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/hand-foot-mouth/about/index.html#cdc_disease_basics_symptoms-signs-and-symptoms" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;HFMD is very contagious and &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/hand-foot-mouth/about/index.html#cdc_disease_basics_causes_risk_spread-how-it-spreads" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;can spread&lt;/a&gt; when people come into contact with droplets from a person sneezing, coughing or talking; objects and surfaces that have virus particles; fluid from blisters; and feces, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"While most cases of hand, foot, and mouth disease are mild, the virus spreads easily in group environments like schools and day cares," Dr. Bruce Randolph, SCHD director and health officer, said in a press release. "Parents should keep sick children home until they are fever-free, feeling well, and any mouth sores or blisters have improved."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;To &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/hand-foot-mouth/about/index.html#cdc_disease_basics_prevention-prevention" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;prevent the spread of HFMD&lt;/a&gt;, the CDC recommends washing hands often with soap and water for at least 20 seconds, helping children wash their hands, avoid touching the face with unwashed hands, cleaning and disinfecting frequently touched surfaces and avoiding close contact with an infected person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;There is currently no treatment specifically for HMFD. Patients usually recover on their own and can &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/hand-foot-mouth/about/index.html#cdc_disease_basics_treatment-treatment-and-recovery" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;take steps to manage symptoms&lt;/a&gt;, including using over-the counter medications for pain and fever and making sure to stay hydrated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Because HFMD normally causes mild illness, the CDC says children can continue to attend school or child care centers as long as they don't have a fever, have no uncontrolled drooling from mouth sores and feel well enough to be in class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;However, the agency noted that local health departments may require children with HFMD to remain home to control an outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News - Breaking News, Latest News and Videos</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 17:23:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxNb0xsMlFqUTlycDFLSy1IUURjVXhldU40VEhiaUplYXpUZnF6NTBpak5nd084RnRKalFKM25NbENlbnV5QjE3S1Zia3Z4cmY2UkpQV0l0TmlWMVNBbG9EYTM2djZ0cFpyNFBzOFA3OTlhSElzVWt4RnR5WWZzdldxVjdxRFg3WmJMM3ZMdUludDB5aTBfRXNIYdIBngFBVV95cUxOdG03OEo1MGg3eGNMWTRIUjFqWmY0TlNFMGVTX1YwQ2E4MHE0OVM4aWtLT2VaVmxoYzVmVGw3ZE1YRjdSWUltbzVqaU5IYzJqMHA5UXdPeTc3ZXFBeFFxNkQ3TDFEc0w1Z1AwRDdFa3FiNW9FSndtSjhBYjNfTDlvX09QMUdoNnZoaDRRTDFmNzliQjZBUUxucElLNndSZw</guid></item><item><title>草病：充满急诊室的神秘大麻综合症-新闻自由</title><link>https://www.thefp.com/p/grass-sick-cannabinoid-hyperemesis-syndrome-marijuana</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div dir="auto" class="body markup"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I genuinely thought I was going to die.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the middle of the night, Shaylin Schlosser jolted awake and began throwing up uncontrollably. Her abdomen seized with a shooting pain worse than anything she had ever felt. In between bouts of vomiting, she screamed out in agony. She heard a neighbor’s window slam shut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eventually, Schlosser mustered the strength to call a ride to the emergency room, where she was diagnosed with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21665-cannabis-hyperemesis-syndrome" rel&gt;cannabinoid hyperemesis syndrome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; (CHS), a condition caused by heavy marijuana use that entails vomiting, nausea, and intense cramps that can last for days on end. While a hot shower can offer temporary relief, there is only one cure: Quit smoking weed for good.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Free Press</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:55:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQelFCLVA3eGdBdkRMU0xTTXZPaHlpeDYtUU1QbkwxZThYS1E3QlFYNVBIM2sxLUdhOGliejJSTFNlUEx4Q3ZnS2lGcm15Sm1Ebm9mRTlkLS14TWZQZk9Ra3BwZjFXNUEwbzdSZl9FaU1JcmJfXzRXWlA0SGJDaGZycTNvOA</guid></item><item><title>我以为我只是抑郁...但医生诊断我患有世界上最致命的疾病-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15216819/depressed-tuberculosis-deadliest-lung-disease.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A woman suffering from crippling &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/depression/index.html" id="mol-628cf340-af59-11f0-beb6-1b3d6930e422"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt; and anxiety was found to have the world's deadliest disease ravaging her entire body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The 43-year-old from &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/massachusetts/index.html" id="mol-62949460-af59-11f0-beb6-1b3d6930e422"&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt; was admitted to the psychiatric ward at Harvard-affiliated Massachusetts General Hospital with severe depression and plans to commit suicide by overdosing on medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She had several severe stressors in her life, including bipolar disorder, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/domestic-violence/index.html" id="mol-628d4160-af59-11f0-beb6-1b3d6930e422"&gt;domestic violence&lt;/a&gt;, financial troubles and limited access to stable housing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, she also had spent the past two months suffering from a dry, hacking cough. Throughout her hospital stay, her breathing and oxygen levels increasingly worsened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;X-ray scans showed several small nodules spread across the woman's lungs, a sign of bacteria. In additional scans, doctors found the lesions in the liver, lymph nodes, pancreas and brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After nine weeks, biopsies and bacterial samples came back positive for mycobacterium tuberculosis, the bacteria that causes tuberculosis, &lt;span&gt;a respiratory condition &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15082229/maps-reveal-deadliest-disease-tuberculosis-concerning-rise.html"&gt;dubbed the deadliest disease on the planet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; due to resistance to certain antibiotics and increased spread in developing countries that lack modern antibiotics. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Though rare in the US today, affecting just a few thousand Americans every year, tuberculosis most often strikes people with weakened immune systems, those living in prisons or homeless shelters and people born in countries with higher rates of the disease. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The anonymous woman had been diagnosed with human immunodeficiency virus (&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/hiv_aids/index.html" id="mol-628e2bc0-af59-11f0-beb6-1b3d6930e422"&gt;HIV&lt;/a&gt;) 17 years earlier and had limited access to her medications for two years leading up to her emergency room visit, which could have made her vulnerable to TB, doctors treating her &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMcpc2412536?logout=true#sec-4"&gt;wrote in a medical journal&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;An unidentified woman visited Massachusetts General Hospital with depression, suicidal thoughts and persistent dry cough. She was diagnosed with tuberculosis that had spread to multiple organs, including her brain (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above x-ray scan shows nodules in the woman's lungs from tuberculosis &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She also regularly smoked crack cocaine, as well as a pack of cigarettes every day and drank alcohol frequently, all of which may have damaged her lungs and kept her immune system from fighting off the bacteria. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The woman was found to have disseminated tuberculosis, a severe form of the disease that strikes multiple organs, including her brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The bacteria may have triggered inflammation and reduced production of the amino acid tryptophan, which is crucial for producing mood-boosting serotonin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Though she had significant stressors in her life, doctors suggested the TB may have exacerbated her mental health issues. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Today, TB infects a few thousand Americans every year and kills about 500, far fewer than cancer, heart disease and dementia. The threat is much more prevalent in developing countries, however, and TB kills 1.2million people worldwide each year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;TB in the US was on a steady decline from 1993 until 2020, when the overall number of cases hit an all-time low of 7,170. But in 2021, that number jumped to 7,866.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prevalence has gone up every year since. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The latest CDC data shows the US provisionally recorded 10,347 TB cases in 2024 - up eight percent from the year before and the highest tally since 2011, when there were 10,471 cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above scans show nodules in several of the woman's organs. Image A is a scan of her lungs, with arrows pointing toward the nodules. Image B shows an arrow pointing toward an enlarged lymph node. Image C shows arrows drawing attention to nodules in the liver and head of the pancreas, and Image D shows a nodule in the woman's brain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cases are now on the rise in 80 percent of US states, which experts have blamed missed cases and distrust of doctors forged by the Covid pandemic.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The demographics of TB have also shifted, starting in 2001. That was the first year the CDC reported more non-US born citizen patients than US-born, meaning immigrants and travelers were the driving force behind infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;TB spreads through airborne droplets that are released into the air when a person with active TB coughs, sneezes or speaks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the early stages, symptoms include a persistent and unexplained cough, sometimes coughing up blood or chest pain. Patients may also suffer from unexplained weight loss, loss of appetite, fever and night sweats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In later stages, patients may have severe breathing difficulties and extensive lung damage, and the infection may spread to other organs or the back, causing pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Deaths are most often due to respiratory failure caused by bacterial damage to the lungs. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But in cases like the woman's, TB in the brain can damage vital tissues and increase pressure in the skull, causing nerve cells to die off. Eventually, this can lead paralysis and strokes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tuberculosis can be prevented with the Bacillus Calmette-Guerin (BCG) vaccine. Though, due to the generally low risk, it is not routinely offered in the US, except for to children regularly exposed to people with active TB or healthcare workers in areas with increased spread. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The woman in the case report spent 33 days in the hospital receiving antibiotics and steroids for the TB and antiretrovirals, which reduce the viral load from HIV. She was discharged to a medical facility for homeless people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Three months later, she was hospitalized again for depression and suicidal ideation due to housing concerns and has since completed antituberculosis treatments again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She is recovering from drug addiction as well.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:16:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxOLTRocUR6X01UMnRHQjJyRTQ1Z2xwdV85bVFPTDVpVGdCZ19sX0tESE1tWHNQSlEwdlJkbExPSUpIUzI4aDRTNW5vVDhMNDNjWVhIYlFlMTRUTnNmLVJseFRQYmdzdC1aZTRENl9Ic2tyMkYycGpSa3pFOHZzWU01Qm1ET1RoTVhVb2N6TWpNNUNGd0Y4b2sxZnY5aG9HWWNKQ1gxbNIBqgFBVV95cUxQTXZRYXBVVk5ad1J4bkR2d19VU1lXQTRpanY2ZVJ3eTUtTEgxZGdjRGhKejVCZlRmRTVKLWUxWEF6ajItTFk3VF9MUWE5ZUhVMGZmelZKc2lDY1FNbktpbTBlLWZFUmx6Z2k0YXU0UTRIUFBWMElHeVAzbTBFM2h5U3ZadmRjdmxKeFo1cVF4R2JCNWhxem1pOGE5eVAxdjZtV0xrRWIzTFpIQQ</guid></item><item><title>这些癌症正在全球范围内飙升--不仅仅是在年轻人身上--Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/these-cancers-are-surging-across-the-globe-and-not-just-in-younger-people-2000675469</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl "&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Certain cancers are becoming a bigger problem for just about everyone. New research shows cases of several obesity-related cancers have been rising across the globe and across different age groups.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Scientists in the UK examined cancer surveillance data spanning 15 years from dozens of countries, including the U.S. They found that, in most countries, several cancer types had increased in both younger and older adults, all of which are linked to obesity. The findings suggest that the surge in cancer cases seen recently isn’t just limited to the young, as some past research and media reports have highlighted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;A widespread rise&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Numerous studies have spotted a rise in specific cancers among the young. Earlier this summer, for instance, Dana-Farber researchers &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/gastrointestinal-cancers-are-surging-among-younger-americans-2000631264"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; a steady increase of gastrointestinal cancers in Americans under the age of 50, dating back over a decade.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The researchers behind this current study wanted to take a more expansive look at recent cancer trends, however, both internationally and across the lifespan.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They analyzed data on annually reported cancer cases between 2003 and 2017 from 42 countries in Asia, Europe, Africa, North and South America, and Australia. They focused specifically on 13 types of cancer that past studies have shown may be increasing in young adults.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;In most of the countries, the researchers found a clear rise in 6 cancer types among adults under the age of 50 during those years: thyroid cancer, breast cancer, colorectal cancer, kidney cancer, endometrial cancer, and leukemia. But they also found a similar increase in new cases among older adults for five of these cancers. The sole exception was colorectal cancer; an increase of these cases in older adults was only seen in half the countries, and the rate of this increase was generally larger in younger adults.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Interestingly enough, rates of liver, oral, esophageal, and stomach cancer also actually decreased for younger people in more than half the countries studied.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What this means for cancer prevention&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The findings, &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-24-02718"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Tuesday in the Annals of Internal Medicine, don’t mean that the reported cancer rise in young adults has been a mirage. But it does complicate things.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;If cancer cases are generally rising across age groups, for instance, that suggests risk factors common to most everyone are to blame, rather than something only affecting young adults. That’s important to know, since scientists and health organizations might otherwise focus only on studying or trying to reverse this rise in young people. Notably, all of the cancer types that might be increasing in both younger and older adults are linked to obesity—a condition that has become more prevalent throughout the world.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“These findings can help inform future research and clinical and public health guidelines,” the authors wrote in their paper.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;At the same time, the still apparent difference in colorectal cancer trends points to unique health risks that younger people might be facing. Some research has &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/scientists-may-have-figured-out-why-young-people-are-getting-colorectal-cancer-more-often-2000594349"&gt;indicated&lt;/a&gt; that younger people could be getting exposed more to certain gastrointestinal infections, for instance.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:15:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxNb0xWdzgtSXkybmwzVDBGNzdqUERsaVZQNHVzTmp3TERkV2JoYldJeDBpU0FVSlRmN25xUzJQMFZJdkE2X2NjTVFKZWhqUk5XRmRQSnp6c0Q2QTUwcGxvb3JKWjd2bzkwbzhTa2lvQVJDTkJwQ0RORHhEb0EwTlF4Mk1ZclZnaGl2UlpaaW9kZThrSkduYS1HZGhkVkcxTnVaYWVjR09udw</guid></item><item><title>每次我参加某项活动回家时，我的女朋友都会恳求我做爱。实际上没有人会参与其中。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/10/sex-advice-intese-sweaty-activity-turn-on.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22oqlc008sbokv0zaieph8@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Jessica and Rich here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22sj4r001e3b79kt3y5bx7@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="22" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22sfzo00123b79tid59zof@published"&gt;My girlfriend loves to have sex after I get home very sweaty from the gym. This should be a good thing. Wrong!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="78" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh25ocoy004z3b7990ga40y7@published"&gt;I can’t stop feeling insecure about how much I must smell and how gross I am after an intense workout. But according to her, she loves it and it drives her wild. I really want to believe her, but it’s hard to trust that someone could enjoy the smells of body odor and sweat. Is there a way I can let loose and enjoy this more? Or should I just put a stop to the post-gym second workout?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22sg1000133b7957ajy3b2@published"&gt;—I Smell!&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22sg2m00143b798zosbw44@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear I Smell!,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="53" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22sg5x00153b79cmrujdn8@published"&gt;Take it from me, a disinterested third party, people enjoy the smell of BO and sweat. Not all BO and sweat are made alike, and if the sweat isn’t fresh (and, for example, dries on clothes that aren’t removed or, worse, reworn), it can smell sour. But good BO can be &lt;em&gt;so good&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="89" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22sg7h00163b79jlc8871x@published"&gt;Your girlfriend is hardly alone. In fact, there’s a gay party in New York called &lt;a href="https://pheromonenyc.com/"&gt;Pheromone&lt;/a&gt; that &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/02/09/style/this-party-stinks-thats-the-point.html"&gt;caters to&lt;/a&gt; guys who want to stick their noses in each other’s pits. Read up a little more on this kink, and it may be easier to understand that, yeah, some people like this a lot. It requires very little of you to allow your girlfriend to indulge (merely raising an arm, if that), and if you can be comfortable with that, you should. She’s expressed how into it she is—believe her.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="149" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22sg9600173b79p95xdjkn@published"&gt;But getting to be comfortable with that can be a big ask. In the United States, we’re generally taught to scrub away our natural odors, and that can ingrain in us a sense that we smell bad. There may be no getting around this for you. With the knowledge that what your girlfriend is asking for is highly common, see if you can just relax and let her do her thing with your post-workout body. If you find yourself unable to get into it or with lingering discomfort, maybe you don’t rock full post-workout funk. Maybe you let her enjoy you in the morning, before you’ve showered or put on deodorant. Or at the end of the day, when your deodorant has run out. Test your own boundaries of comfort. If you ultimately conclude that any amount of funk is too much for you to unleash, that’s totally OK.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmh23nz47003i3b79qjve0b9n@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmh23o4gm003s3b79gxn6kq1y@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmh23o1nc003n3b791ihfusi5@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23nfw3002n3b79qdayzz6r@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="90" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23nrzw002t3b791b095k1z@published"&gt;When I married my husband 20 years ago, he was handsome, tall, witty, and athletic. Well, he’s still tall, witty, and cute. But time is beginning to catch up with him. His hair is thinning, and he’s not as slim and fit as he used to be. Basically, he’s aging. And I’m afraid I don’t find him as attractive as I did before. For that reason, I’ve been making excuses, and our sex life has been lacking lately. I’m just not as attracted to him as I used to be.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="98" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23nrzy002u3b79rw01to5w@published"&gt;I know this sounds shallow. I’m also aging, and what’s worse, men often trade their wives for younger models. I don’t want to trade my husband for a younger man, but is there anything I can do to feel more attracted to him as he (and I) keep getting older? I love this guy. I don’t want to leave him just because he has a little less hair and can’t fit into ultra-tight leather trousers anymore, but I never thought I’d have to wonder how to stay physically attracted to your aging spouse. How do people do this?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23nrzz002v3b79mcwhoot5@published"&gt;—Don’t Want to be a Shallow Gal&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="8" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23nrzz002w3b79umk2vd6c@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Don’t Want to be a Shallow Gal,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="150" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23nrzz002x3b79qlp0sdyo@published"&gt;Usually, when this issue comes up, at least in this column, it presents with less specificity. People feel less compelled to have sex with a long-term partner for reasons that they often can’t quite spell out. The spark is gone, sex is less exciting. It’s hard to even muster the effort to qualify “blah,” because, well, that’s blah for you. In those cases, usually my advice is to apply Esther Perel’s methods of creating eroticizing distance in your relationship, as detailed in &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Mating-Captivity-Unlocking-Erotic-Intelligence-ebook/dp/B000UODXP0/ref=sr_1_1?crid=1ORNN2XAXU0CZ&amp;amp;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.bXIETwz6rg35EJfbpa4eyUiUlcEoJVKlMs9LiYHOqblAJzKIemTav2l00ugUSJJW7ORQlh-We27SCj6Lwk9lviXae-tZ4B6u-YU5GEfHTPQqVV-LlBAHezu-SlAbgecF9IKKzRf950upYZbF7_o91Y0PEDCoN6BjPoO3w7cJkmNOCMb9wb_ZPbDVJPpAO6DWBxVv-1KOUCgfE8nv5fpogL7Gxntk4J0m657sQ6boPB0.fubgQNBPTZ1szWcsr9vCQZ16tiGwdRVyPqj7xpkTABY&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;keywords=mating+in+captivity+esther+perel&amp;amp;qid=1760910376&amp;amp;sprefix=mating+in+captiv,aps,120&amp;amp;sr=8-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mating in Captivity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The idea is to shake yourselves out of routine by, for example, changing venues (via a weekly hotel sex date, for example) or erotic letters. Seeing an old partner with new eyes can make sex more exciting. You may want to try something like this (or at least read Perel&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;for more ideas and to think about whether they could even apply to your situation).&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="178" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23nrzz002y3b79nmj6y4pz@published"&gt;But if this is an issue with type (i.e., you’re into people who are younger than your husband), what can you do? You like what you like. You may want to play with the idea of sensation/exploration to help bring you in—if there is stuff you haven’t tried but want to, like toys, kink, or groups, that might be a way to recharge things. You could also kind of do an anti-Perel and focus on sex as not a carnal way to get your rocks off, but as an expression of love and appreciation for this person who has been by your side for 20 years. That might not be so exciting, but it could at least give you an attainable goal. If nothing here works, consider counseling—either solo or couples. The latter could, of course, require you to be honest about your lessened attraction to your husband, which might be hard. But a third party’s help regaining it or at least relearning how to find sex exciting with your partner might make the momentary awkwardness worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmh23nwdd003d3b795n3dmr6a@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmh23vo7b004e3b79ns0gmmdq@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Us Your Questions About the Workplace!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="36" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23vo7b004f3b79h9qtiy5v@published"&gt;The columnists behind our advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmh23ocb3003y3b79zqb5syib@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns01002z3b791u9wii6g@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="61" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns0100303b79mfmpuf0w@published"&gt;My husband, who is 63, and I, a 58-year-old woman, have been married for 39 years. We were married young, but all was well. In his early 30s, our sex life changed, and we started having more time between having sex. He was very into his hobbies, and at times, I felt left out since I was home with our daughters.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns0100313b7979jfr2g0@published"&gt;Fast forward through his 30s to 50s, and there would be months between intimacy. I’m almost 10 years younger and still wanted to be with him. I love him very deeply, and I know he loves me. But he just doesn’t seem interested in me. This has harmed my self-esteem greatly. Time moved forward, and he began to have erectile dysfunction issues. I begged him to go to the doctor. He finally did and received medication. He tried them once, and that was it. They either didn’t work or it’s me that’s the problem. I cannot remember the last time we had sex, but it has been years.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns0200323b79g84uhjho@published"&gt;As expected, we’ve grown apart in multiple ways. Politically, he has become far more conservative, and I’ve become more liberal. This applies since it is one more division and one less thing we can discuss together. About 15 years ago, we went to therapy. He was fine with the two of us together. I don’t know what happened in his one time in individual therapy, but our therapist stated to me in my next session that I should divorce him, which seemed a surprising statement to me. I didn’t act on that because frankly, that’s not how we were raised. He will not go back to therapy.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="57" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns0200333b7964680d9v@published"&gt;Now I’m older and more frustrated with the separation emotionally, physically, and with our differing perspectives. What can I do to make this change for the better, or is this as good as it gets? Is it too late at my age to consider divorce? I don’t want to be alone for the rest of my days.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns0300343b79bflf1gbg@published"&gt;—Living Alone and Married&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns0300353b7937gokw6a@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Living Alone and Married,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="129" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns0300363b79mtgqyo0y@published"&gt;It’s never too late for a divorce. If your concern is about restarting your life and finding another partner, realize that people can and do find love at any age. Besides, if that is what’s preoccupying you, you’re looking way into the future when you should be concentrated on your immediate situation. Forget how you were raised (easier said than done, I know)—why stay in something if it’s not serving you? Do you want to spend the rest of your life in a situation that you find sexually frustrating with someone whom you seem to be drifting further and further away from? If you do, you don’t have much of a shot at finding new love, at least not ethically. If you leave, you open your world to chance.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="221" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns0300373b79y4kombw5@published"&gt;I’m not saying that your letter reads like the only way for you to be happy is to divorce. I’m an optimist, and I know that even seemingly desperate situations can be turned around. I believe in the power of love. But some things concern me here. There seems to be a communication breakdown between you and your husband. He got ED meds, they didn’t work, and why seems to be a mystery. From that, I infer that he talked little about what was actually going on with him. The thing about PDE5 inhibitors is that they don’t tend to be effective &lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/pde5-inhibitors#sildenafil-viagra"&gt;without a will to have sex&lt;/a&gt; (i.e., horniness). They facilitate blood flow, but something needs to get the blood flowing. This does not mean that the problem is you (though it certainly could be that your husband isn’t attracted to you—I don’t want to sugarcoat this and dismiss that possibility entirely). It could also have something to do with him physically (a hormonal issue, for example) or sexually (perhaps he has a fetish that is not being catered to, or it could have something to do with his sexuality, like maybe he’s asexual). We don’t know because he’s not saying, and maybe part of why he’s not saying is that he’s not investigating. Shame could also be a factor.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="137" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh23ns0400383b79f0h6i3xb@published"&gt;If I’m reading your letter right, it seems like your couples counselor saw you individually, which is not usually how these things go, and that they then told you to divorce your husband without explanation. That entire interaction sounds strange to me. When you write that he will not go back to therapy, I am assuming that the situation turned him off therapy altogether, including couples therapy. If that is not the case, find a different couples therapist and go. If it is, what can you do? You can’t make him get the help that your relationship greatly needs. Having a discussion in which you state that you are considering separation/divorce might help him see the gravity of the situation. It seems that might be one of the few tools that you have left. Consider using it.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22t2ut001l3b795mf69nrj@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmh22t77u001z3b795iskb3ke@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="64" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmh22t4ji001s3b79vfpso1qs@published"&gt;I am a bisexual cis woman who’s been married to a heterosexual cis man for the past three years (both in our mid-30s). Throughout our relationship, we have spoken openly about our sexuality, and while he’s had some explorative experiences with men, he’s been sure that he is straight. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/06/drunk-boyfriend-sexuality-sex-advice.html"&gt;Over the past several months though, he’s been making more explicit comments about men’s bodies.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmh22oqlc008vbokvfnj7dpe6@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNa1ZmRU9pRTYwX2VrNnBKcG1Fakx0cUxicms2ODJXalJmVVNOOGxIbG1oUVJnelN3R1BkVUpqczNkQWo3MHRfOXhoNnhEejk1V3JNMnJjRkxaZklXQTdCWG5SRFMyd2RMZHo1NGpDdWViLUkwS1hHM2daQk55RTloRUZpMXRNdw</guid></item><item><title>COVID-19疫苗可能帮助一些癌症患者对抗肿瘤-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/mrna-vaccine-cancer-immunotherapy-pfizer-moderna-c632dacabb9208050b399da90630318f</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — The most widely used &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/vaccines-covid-shots-fda-kennedy-pfizer-children-9ce19908ae7afb354732aa162fd28532" rel="nofollow"&gt;COVID-19 vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; may offer a surprise benefit for some cancer patients – revving up their immune systems to help fight tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with advanced lung or skin cancer who were taking certain &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/4c83cc7cc92a430b8c026691e77815c2" rel="nofollow"&gt;immunotherapy drugs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; lived substantially longer if they also got a Pfizer or Moderna shot within 100 days of starting treatment, according to preliminary research being reported Wednesday in the journal Nature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And it had nothing to do with virus infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/mrna-kennedy-rfk-jr-covid-flu-51babaaeb003c45473080a52d67d7d72" rel="nofollow"&gt;the molecule that powers those specific vaccines, mRNA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, appears to help the immune system respond better to the cutting-edge cancer treatment, concluded researchers from MD Anderson Cancer Center in Houston and the University of Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The vaccine “acts like a siren to activate immune cells throughout the body,” said lead researcher Dr. Adam Grippin of MD Anderson. “We’re sensitizing immune-resistant tumors to immune therapy.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has raised skepticism about mRNA vaccines, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/kennedy-vaccines-mrna-pfizer-moderna-1fb5b9436f2957075064c18a6cbbe3c9" rel="nofollow"&gt;cutting $500 million in funding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for some uses of the technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this research team found its results so promising that it is preparing a more rigorous study to see if mRNA coronavirus vaccines should be paired with cancer drugs called checkpoint inhibitors — an interim step while it designs new mRNA vaccines for use in cancer.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A healthy immune system often kills cancer cells before they become a threat. But some tumors evolve to hide from immune attack. &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=viRPsgoqfas&amp;amp;list=PLslqZ7OaczKEUNNDVq-u_OE31P2k7UwKc&amp;amp;index=19" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Checkpoint inhibitors remove that cloak&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. It’s a powerful treatment – when it works. Some people’s immune cells still don’t recognize the tumor.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;Messenger RNA, or mRNA, is naturally found in every cell and it contains genetic instructions for our bodies to make proteins. While best known as the &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/nobel-prize-medicine-71306bd18785477f3a85a69caa6e09c9" rel="nofollow"&gt;Nobel Prize-winning technology behind COVID-19 vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, scientists have long been trying to create personalized mRNA “treatment vaccines” that train immune cells to spot unique features of a patient’s tumor.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;The new research offers “a very good clue” that maybe an off-the-shelf approach could work, said Dr. Jeff Coller, an mRNA specialist at Johns Hopkins University who wasn’t involved with the work. “What it shows is that mRNA medicines are continuing to surprise us in how beneficial they can be to human health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grippin and his Florida colleagues had been developing personalized mRNA cancer vaccines when they realized that even one created without a specific target appeared to spur similar immune activity against cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Grippin wondered if the already widely available mRNA coronavirus shots might also have some effect, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the team analyzed records of nearly 1,000 advanced cancer patients undergoing checkpoint inhibitor treatment at MD Anderson – comparing those who happened to get a Pfizer or Moderna shot with those who didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccinated lung cancer patients were nearly twice as likely to be alive three years after beginning cancer treatment as the unvaccinated patients. Among melanoma patients, median survival was significantly longer for vaccinated patients – but exactly how much isn’t clear, as some of that group were still alive when the data was analyzed.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Non-mRNA vaccines such as flu shots didn’t make a difference, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—-&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:08:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxOSnV5ZUZlZ1dJM3FJc0xyWnA4eDNJVzNZVEJaRnF6S3J0NjhxOUFxU0pQQ2IwMHV2R182dGNfemd5NDFVMnlzQlRGU1BYdDlqUkFOWXFNQ2xMZWltQ1B5X21MZ0txR2xOZDF6ckYwc0dPSV9NbGIyVFZUaTVWX0p0S1VfU28wekFPSU53RW82cnlaVGZJQnRDZ0EzY3RDSmNpSHZfSWdxZ0lkUlRN</guid></item><item><title>肠道致病细菌逃避ROCK驱动的上皮细胞挤压-自然</title><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-09645-0</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="c-article-section__content" id="Sec8-content"&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading" id="Sec9"&gt;Mice&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;All mouse studies complied with relevant ethics regulations and were approved by either the Genentech Institutional Animal Care and Use Committee (IACUC) in an Association for Assessment and Accreditation of Laboratory Animal Care (AAALAC)-accredited facility or by the Oregon Health and Science University IACUC. Mice were housed in individually ventilated cages within animal rooms maintained on a 14-h–10-h light–dark cycle. Animal rooms were temperature and humidity controlled, at 20–26 °C and 30–70%, respectively, with 10–15 exchanges of air in the room per hour. &lt;i&gt;Rock1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rock2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Villin.creERT2 mice on a C57BL/6J genetic background have been described previously&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 35" title="Sambandam, A. et al. Obligate role for Rock1 and Rock2 in adult stem cell viability and function. Heliyon 9, e14238 (2023)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR35" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e1782"&gt;35&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Experimental cohorts of female mice were generated through two rounds of breeding: first &lt;i&gt;Rock1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/+&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rock2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/+&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Villin.creERT2 mice were crossed to &lt;i&gt;Rock1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/+&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rock2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/+&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; mice, and then their offspring were bred together (either &lt;i&gt;Rock1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rock2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Villin.creERT2 × &lt;i&gt;Rock1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rock2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; or &lt;i&gt;Rock1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;+/+&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rock2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;+/+&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Villin.creERT2 × &lt;i&gt;Rock1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;+/+&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rock2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;+/+&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;). Before infection with &lt;i&gt;C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt; DBS100, mice aged 12–14 weeks (Extended Data Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig9"&gt;5h&lt;/a&gt;) or 5–8 weeks (Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig4"&gt;4i–k&lt;/a&gt; and Extended Data Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig9"&gt;5j&lt;/a&gt;) were treated by intraperitoneal injection with 75 mg kg&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; tamoxifen in sunflower oil for five consecutive days. Four hours after the final tamoxifen injection, mice were infected with &lt;i&gt;C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt;. Mice were grouped by genotype or by treatment with no randomization. The C57BL/6J female mice in Extended Data Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig9"&gt;5i&lt;/a&gt; were from the Jackson Laboratory and were eight weeks old at the time of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt; were streaked out from glycerol stocks on MacConkey agar plates at 37 °C overnight. A single colony was inoculated into 10 ml Luria broth (LB) and grown on a shaker at 37 °C overnight. The overnight culture was diluted 1:100 and grown to log phase (optical density at 600 nm (OD&lt;sub&gt;600 nm&lt;/sub&gt;) of around 0.5 after approximately three hours). Bacteria were collected by centrifugation at 6,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt; for 15 min, washed twice with phosphate-buffered saline (PBS) and prepared for infection by equalization to 1 × 10&lt;sup&gt;10&lt;/sup&gt; CFUs per ml (1 OD&lt;sub&gt;600 nm&lt;/sub&gt; = 8 × 10&lt;sup&gt;8&lt;/sup&gt; bacteria per ml). Mice were fasted for four hours and then dosed by oral gavage with 5 × 10&lt;sup&gt;9&lt;/sup&gt; (Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig4"&gt;4i–k&lt;/a&gt; and Extended Data Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig9"&gt;5j&lt;/a&gt;) or 2 × 10&lt;sup&gt;9&lt;/sup&gt; (Extended Data Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig9"&gt;5h,i&lt;/a&gt;) CFUs of &lt;i&gt;C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt; (strains described below). Mice had access to food and water ad libitum after infection. At six or ten days after infection, mice were euthanized and gastrointestinal samples, including colon and caecum, were collected. Tissues were resected and splayed open, and the luminal contents were removed and resuspended in pre-weighted tubes containing 1 ml PBS. Tissues were later washed with PBS to remove non-adherent bacteria. Colon, caecum or spleen homogenate was plated on MacConkey agar containing 100 mg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; streptomycin (Extended Data Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig8"&gt;4e&lt;/a&gt;) or LB agar containing nalidixic acid (Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig4"&gt;4e&lt;/a&gt;) to determine CFUs. Mice were picked and treated by the same individual, so blinding to genotype and treatment as well as during data collection and analysis was not possible. No statistical methods were used to predetermine sample size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec10"&gt;Intestinal permeability assay&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Female &lt;i&gt;Rock1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rock2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Villin.creERT2 mice and control Villin.creERT2 littermates, aged five to eight weeks, were administered tamoxifen intraperitoneally at a dose of 90 mg kg&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; in sunflower oil for five consecutive days. Mice underwent food restriction for 12 h before receiving a 600 mg kg&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; oral gavage of 4 kDa FITC–dextran. Four hours later, blood and faecal pellets were collected, and FITC fluorescence (485/528 nm ex/em) was measured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec11"&gt;Bacteria&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;EHEC O157:H7 EDL933 (ATCC700927) and &lt;i&gt;C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt; DBS100 (ATCC51459) were obtained from the American Type Culture Collection (ATCC). A nalidixic-acid-resistant strain was derived from DBS100 by first growing 1 ml DBS100 overnight. The culture was centrifuged, resuspended in 100 µl PBS and plated on LB agar containing 30 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; nalidixic acid. This resistant strain was used to generate the &lt;i&gt;nleL&lt;/i&gt; mutant. The &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;i&gt;C. rodentium nleL&lt;/i&gt; open reading frame (ORF) was replaced with a kanamycin resistance cassette from the pACYC177 vector using lambda red recombinase expressed by pKD46 (refs. &lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 36" title="Datsenko, K. A. &amp;amp; Wanner, B. L. One-step inactivation of chromosomal genes in Escherichia coli K-12 using PCR products. Proc. Natl Acad. Sci. USA 97, 6640–6645 (2000)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR36" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e1968"&gt;36&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 37" title="Heckman, K. L. &amp;amp; Pease, L. R. Gene splicing and mutagenesis by PCR-driven overlap extension. Nat. Protoc. 2, 924–932 (2007)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR37" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e1971"&gt;37&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;). Gene replacement was verified by colony PCR (&lt;i&gt;E. coli ΔnleL::kanR&lt;/i&gt;), and whole-genome sequencing (&lt;i&gt;C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt; DBS100 WT and &lt;i&gt;C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt; DBS100&lt;i&gt;ΔnleL::kanR&lt;/i&gt;). The&lt;i&gt; C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt; DBS100 WT assembly was generated using a combination of 75-bp paired-end Illumina reads and Oxford Nanopore Technologies long reads from isolate-derived total genomic DNA. The assembly and polishing of the combined long- and short-read data were performed using MicroPIPE v.0.9 (ref. &lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 38" title="Murigneux, V. et al. MicroPIPE: validating an end-to-end workflow for high-quality complete bacterial genome construction. BMC Genomics 22, 474 (2021)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR38" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e1991"&gt;38&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;). Illumina reads were mapped onto the &lt;i&gt;C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt; DBS100 WT genome using GSNAP (v.2013-10-10)&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 39" title="Wu, T. D. &amp;amp; Nacu, S. Fast and SNP-tolerant detection of complex variants and splicing in short reads. Bioinformatics 26, 873–881 (2010)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR39" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e1998"&gt;39&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Single-nucleotide variants were detected using in-house R scripts, which used the Bioconductor packages GenomicRanges&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 40" title="Lawrence, M. et al. Software for computing and annotating genomic ranges. PLoS Comput. Biol. 9, e1003118 (2013)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR40" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2002"&gt;40&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, GenomicAlignments&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 40" title="Lawrence, M. et al. Software for computing and annotating genomic ranges. PLoS Comput. Biol. 9, e1003118 (2013)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR40" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2006"&gt;40&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; VariantTools and gmapR. Only base calls with a phred quality score of at least 30 were used for variant calling. Knockout of &lt;i&gt;nleL&lt;/i&gt; was confirmed by visual inspection of read pile-ups using the Integrative Genomics Viewer&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 41" title="Robinson, J. T. et al. Integrative genomics viewer. Nat. Biotechnol. 29, 24–26 (2011)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR41" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2014"&gt;41&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Bacteria were transformed by electroporation with the pBR322-AmpR-dasherGFP plasmid&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 11" title="Luchetti, G. et al. Shigella ubiquitin ligase IpaH7.8 targets gasdermin D for degradation to prevent pyroptosis and enable infection. Cell Host Microbe 29, 1521–1530 (2021)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR11" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2018"&gt;11&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; to visualize bacteria, and complementation of &lt;i&gt;C.r.ΔnleL::kanR&lt;/i&gt; was achieved by transformation of the mutant strain with pBR322-GentR-nleL-COMP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The primers used to generate recombineering insertions (5′ to 3′) include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C.r.DBS100_NleLF1: ACAGGCAGAACTGGAGAATG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C.r.DBS100_NleLR1: GGGCGATTCAGGCCTGGTTTATCGCACTCCTTCTACTTAG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C.r.DBS100_NleLkanF1: CTAAGTAGAAGGAGTGCGATAAACCAGGCCTGAATCGCCC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C.r.DBS100_NleLkanR1: ATAATATTCATCTATGGTCTCTAAA&lt;span class="u-small-caps"&gt;acaaccaattaaccaa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C.r.DBS100_NleLF2: &lt;span class="u-small-caps"&gt;ttggttaattggttgt&lt;/span&gt;TTTAGAGACCATAGATGAATATTAT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C.r.DBS100_NleLR2: AATAACGAACATAATTTTCG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDL933_NleLF1: TACAGGGACAGAAAGTTGTCC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDL933_NleLR1: GGGCGATTCAGGCCTGGTAGAACTACAATGGCATAAAGAT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDL933_NleLkanF1: ATCTTTATGCCATTGTAGTTCTACCAGGCCTGAATCGCCC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDL933_NleLkanR1: ATAATATTCATCCATGGTCTCTAAA&lt;span class="u-small-caps"&gt;acaaccaattaaccaa&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDL933_NleLF2: &lt;span class="u-small-caps"&gt;ttggttaattggttgt&lt;/span&gt;TTTAGAGACCATGGATGAATATTAT&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDL933_NleLR2: TATGATTCTCCACGATTTGC&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Outside primers to check insertion include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C.r.DBS100_NleL_OUTF: GCTGGATGAAGTGGGCAGTGA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C.r.DBS100_NleL_OUTR: TCTCCACGATTTGTCCAG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDL933_NleL_OUTF: AATCTGACATCTTATTTGTGGG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDL933_NleL_OUTR: CTATAGTAACAAAAACATATTAATCTG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec12"&gt;Cell culture&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;EA.hy926 (ATCC), 293T (ATCC), HT-29 (ATCC) and Caco-2 (ATCC) cells were cultured in Dulbecco’s modified Eagle’s high-glucose medium (DMEM) supplemented with 10 mM HEPES pH 7.4, 1× Glutamax (Gibco), 1× penicillin–streptomycin (Gibco), 1× non-essential amino acids (Gibco), 1 mM sodium pyruvate (Gibco) and 10% (v/v) fetal bovine serum (FBS, VWR) at 37 °C with 5% CO&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;. Single-nucleotide polymorphism (SNP) profiles were compared with SNP calls from internal and external databases to determine or confirm ancestry. All cell lines tested negative for mycoplasma contamination before to storage or use at our institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Caco-2 infections, bacteria were streaked from glycerol stocks onto trypticase soy agar (TSA) and used for experiments within one week. Caco-2 cells (3.5 × 10&lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt;) were plated in six-well plates in antibiotic-free DMEM. On the same day, a single colony of the desired strain was grown at 37 °C overnight in 5 ml terrific broth (TB). Overnight cultures were diluted 1:50 in TB and grown until bacteria reached an OD&lt;sub&gt;600 nm&lt;/sub&gt; of 0.6–0.8. Bacteria were pelleted at 3,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt;, washed with PBS and then incubated in fresh PBS at room temperature for 15 min. After one further wash with PBS, bacteria were resuspended in DMEM without supplements. Caco-2 cells were infected with an MOI of 25 (1 OD&lt;sub&gt;600 nm&lt;/sub&gt; = 8 × 10&lt;sup&gt;8&lt;/sup&gt; bacteria per ml) by centrifugation at 1,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt; for 10 min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intestinal organoids from C57BL/6J mice, or &lt;i&gt;Rock1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;Rock2&lt;/i&gt;&lt;sup&gt;&lt;i&gt;fl/fl&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Villin.creERT2 mice and control Villin.creERT2 mice, were generated as described&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 35" title="Sambandam, A. et al. Obligate role for Rock1 and Rock2 in adult stem cell viability and function. Heliyon 9, e14238 (2023)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR35" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2134"&gt;35&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. After 2–15 passages, organoids were disrupted into single-cell suspensions. IEC monolayers were established by seeding 50,000–60,000 cells into translucent 24-well Matrigel-coated transwell inserts with a pore size of 0.4 µm in organoid medium&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 42" title="Miyoshi, H. &amp;amp; Stappenbeck, T. S. In vitro expansion and genetic modification of gastrointestinal stem cells in spheroid culture. Nat. Protoc. 8, 2471–2482 (2013)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR42" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2138"&gt;42&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; (L-WRN conditioned supernatant, 10 µm Y-27632 (MedChemExpress) and 50 ng ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; mEGF (Thermo Fisher Scientific)). Cultures were grown for ten days. For ERT2-Cre induction, cells were treated 48 h before the experiment with 250 nM 4-OHT. Transwells were transitioned to antibiotic-free medium without Y-27632 the day before infection. Monolayers were infected with &lt;i&gt;C. rodentium&lt;/i&gt; (WT or Δ&lt;i&gt;nleL&lt;/i&gt;) in the exponential growth phase at an MOI of 0.25. After four hours, the medium was changed to prevent the overgrowth of non-adherent bacteria. After a further 16 h, the cells were treated with 10 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; PI (or 50 nM SYTOX green) for 30 min, washed with PBS and then fixed in 4% paraformaldehyde for 10 min. The fixed cells were permeabilized with 0.2% Triton X-100 and stained with 4′,6-diamidino-2-phenylindole (DAPI) and 0.165 µM AF647–phalloidin (Thermo Fisher Scientific).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IEC monolayers for experiments with FlaTox were grown identically and Y-27632 was removed 24 h before FlaTox treatment. For Villin.creERT2 monolayers, 250 nM 4-OHT was administered 48 h before stimulation. Monolayers were administered 2 mg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; anthrax lethal factor N terminus fused to &lt;i&gt;Legionella pneumophila&lt;/i&gt; flagellin (LFn-FlaA)&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 34" title="Scott, W. P. &amp;amp; Rauch, I. Inducing pyroptosis with FlaTox, RodTox, or NeedleTox. Methods Mol. Biol. 2641, 27–36 (2023)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR34" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2161"&gt;34&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, 4 mg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; protective antigen&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 34" title="Scott, W. P. &amp;amp; Rauch, I. Inducing pyroptosis with FlaTox, RodTox, or NeedleTox. Methods Mol. Biol. 2641, 27–36 (2023)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR34" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2167"&gt;34&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; (PA) and 10 μg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; PI (or 50 nM SYTOX green). The medium contained 10 µM Y-27632 or 2.5 mM cytochalasin D (Sigma) as indicated. Monolayers were fixed after 30 min and stained with DAPI as described above. For imaging, transwell membranes were cut out with a razor blade, placed on a microscopy slide, layered with Vectashield hardening mounting medium and coverslipped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For transparent monolayers, TrypLE-dissociated organoids were seeded on Matrigel-covered 96-well tissue culture plates at 30,000 cells per well in 50% L-WRN conditioned supernatant containing 3 µM CHIR99021 (Cayman Chemical) and 10 μM Y-27632 (MedChemExpress)&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 43" title="Geiser, P., van Rijn, J. M. &amp;amp; Sellin, M. E. Time-lapse imaging of inflammasome-dependent cell death and extrusion in enteroid-derived intestinal epithelial monolayers. Methods Mol. Biol. 2641, 203–221 (2023)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR43" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2178"&gt;43&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Twenty-four hours later, the medium was changed to antibiotic-free L-WRN with 3 µM CHIR99021 without Y-27632. Forty-eight hours later, monolayers were infected with 1 × 10&lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt; &lt;i&gt;C. rodentium ΔnleL&lt;/i&gt; or &lt;i&gt;ΔnleL&lt;/i&gt; + pNleL after overnight culture and redilution for exponential growth. Plates were spun at 300&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt; for 10 min to help with epithelial attachment of bacteria and then incubated overnight at 37 °C and 5% CO&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;. After 11 h of infection, the wells were washed once with warm PBS and new medium was added containing 1 μg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; PI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec13"&gt;IEC imaging and cell-extrusion analysis&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fixed IEC monolayers on transwells were imaged on an inverted Leica SP8 confocal microscope using a 40× oil (numerical aperture 1.3) objective. Imaging parameters on the Leica LAS X (v.3.7.5) software were set to acquire DAPI, PI, SYTOX green and GFP (bacteria). Three-dimensional (3D) confocal &lt;i&gt;z&lt;/i&gt;-stacks were acquired using Nyquist sampling rates. Six to seven fields of view were acquired for each sample. The 3D datasets were processed and analysed using the Imaris Spots tool to quantify cellular extrusion levels. In brief, a Gaussian blur image filter was first applied to all channels to reduce background noise. Afterwards, the Imaris Spots tool was used to segment and isolate DAPI- and PI-positive or SYTOX-green-positive cells (PI&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt;DAPI+ or SYTOX&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt;DAPI&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt;) from the 3D image stacks. A low threshold intensity was set for the PI and SYTOX channel so that both infected and uninfected cells were segmented using the Imaris Spots tool. After segmentation, the shortest distance metric in Imaris was used to calculate the distance between the centroids of a PI&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; or SYTOX&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; spot and the closest DAPI&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; spot. A batch Imaris run to segment spots of DAPI&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; and PI&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; or SYTOX&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; cells was performed using identical segmentation parameters. The shortest distance metric was then extracted and used for quantification of the cell-extrusion analysis of all samples. Bacteria exhibiting GFP signals were filtered out by segmenting and masking them using a pixel classifier in Imaris. After this masking procedure, the shortest distance between SYTOX-green-positive cells and DAPI-positive cells was measured to analyse extrusion events, as detailed above.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For live imaging of transparent monolayers, plates were imaged for two hours in a live imaging set-up (Celldiscoverer 7), recording oblique/bright-field and red fluorescence with a Hammamastu Orca Flash 4.0 camera. Images were taken using the 5×/0.35 NA objective with the addition of the 2× optovar. Images were collected on the Celldiscoverer 7 in intervals of 60 s with the exposure and light source intensity of oblique and red channels set at 5 ms and 15%, and 50 ms and 30%, respectively. Focus was maintained throughout the time-lapse using the Zeiss definite focus system. Extrusion was quantified in a blinded manner, by recording the time from the first noticeable changes in cell shape to the finished extrusion of PI-positive cells in the bright-field/oblique channel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec14"&gt;IL-18 enzyme-linked immunosorbent assay (ELISA)&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;One hundred microlitres of medium from transwell infection experiments, collected immediately before infected monolayers were fixed for microscopy, was analysed with mouse IL-18 DuoSet ELISA (R&amp;amp;D Systems DY7625-05) according to the manufacturer’s instructions and quantified using a standard curve. Untreated medium background was subtracted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec15"&gt;CytoTox-Glo viability assay&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twenty-five microlitres of supernatant medium, collected immediately before infected monolayers were fixed for microscopy, was mixed with 12.5 µl of CytoTox-Glo reagent (Promega) and incubated for 15 min at room temperature. The luminescence was assessed as per the manufacturer’s recommendations. Untreated medium background was subtracted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec16"&gt;Transepithelial electrical resistance assay&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medium was exchanged on monolayers on the day of infection and they were allowed to equilibrate for 20 min at room temperature. Transepithelial resistance was recorded in each transwell with an epithelial voltohmmeter (EVOM2, World Precision Instruments). The background resistance of an empty transwell with medium was subtracted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec17"&gt;Plasmids and lentiviral vectors&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The genetically barcoded &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; effector library was maintained in the lentiviral vector pMIN-ducer (Genscript). cDNAs encoding N-terminal 3×Flag-NleL, NleL(C753A), the PPR domain (amino acids (aa) 135–371), or the NEL domain (aa 372–782) were expressed using pMIN-ducer or pCDNA3.1Hygro(+) (Genscript). cDNAs encoding Myc–GST-tagged CARDs (Extended Data Table &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="table anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Tab2"&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;) were cloned into pCDNA3.1:Zeo(+) (Genscript). cDNAs encoding C-terminal Rho-1D4-tagged caspase-1, caspase-4 or caspase-1/4 CARD swap chimeras (aa 1–80, 1–10, 6–15, 11–20, 16–25 and 21–30) were cloned into pCDNA3.1Hygro(+) (Genscript). cDNAs encoding C-terminal Rho-1D4-tagged ROCK1, ROCK2, ROCK2ΔPH (aa 1–1,141), ROCK2-PH (aa 1,142–1,354) and C-terminal truncations (20 aa from Δ20–240) were cloned into pCDNA3.1Hygro(+) (Genscript). For transient expression in 293T cells, 3 × 10&lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt; cells were plated in 10-cm dishes and transfected the next day with 3 µg of pCDNA3.1Zeo(+) total plasmid DNA using Lipofectamine 2000 (Thermo Fisher Scientific). Proteins were expressed for 24 h before being collected for downstream manipulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For lentiviral packaging, 2.5 × 10&lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt; 293T cells in 10-cm plates were transfected with 5 µg pMIN-ducer, 10 µg pCMV-Δ8.9 and 0.5 µg pCMV-VSVG (1:2.3:0.2 mole ratio). Virus-containing supernatants were collected after 72 h, passed through 0.45-μm syringe filters and used immediately for infection of EA.hy926, Caco-2 or HT-29 cells (2 × 10&lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt; cells seeded into six-well plates the previous day). Virus was supplemented with 10 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; polybrene (Millipore) during infections. After 48 h, transduced cells were selected with 4 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; puromycin (Takara). Mock-infected cells were used to judge selection duration and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec18"&gt;Positive selection screen&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lentiviral library was packaged using 12 15-cm plates of 293T cells. Each plate (2.7 × 10&lt;sup&gt;7&lt;/sup&gt; cells) was transfected with 50.8 µg DNA (library plasmid, pCMV-Δ8.9 and pCMV-VSVG plasmids at a molar ratio of 1:2:0.2) using Lipofectamine 2000 reagent (Thermo Fisher Scientific). At six hours after transfection, the medium containing the transfection mix was replaced with fresh medium supplemented with 1 U ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; DNase I, 5 mM MgCl&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; and 20 mM HEPES pH 7.2. After overnight culture at 37 °C, this medium was replaced with fresh medium. After another 24 h, the lentivirus-containing medium was collected, pooled, passed through a 0.45 µm filter and concentrated by ultracentrifugation (Thermo Fisher Scientific, S50-A fixed angle rotor, 100,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt;). Concentrated lentivirus was resuspended in PBS containing 1% bovine serum albumin (BSA) and aliquots were stored at −80 °C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EA.hy926 cells were infected at an MOI of 0.3 to ensure a single integrant frequency of 97% with 1,000-fold coverage. On day 1, EA.hy926 cells were seeded into two 10-cm plates (1.2 × 10&lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt; cells each). On day 2, cells were infected with lentivirus diluted in DMEM supplemented with 10 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; polybrene (Millipore). On day 3, virus-containing medium was replaced with fresh DMEM. On day 4, cells were expanded into a 15-cm plate. On day 5, antibiotic selection was initiated with DMEM containing 2 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; puromycin (Takara). After a further five days, cells were expanded into four 15-cm plates with antibiotic-free DMEM, and cultured for two days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For LPS screens, EA.hy926 containing the &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; effector library were seeded into six 15-cm plates (1.5 × 10&lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt; cells per plate). &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; effectors were induced with 250 ng ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; doxycycline for 48 h. For each plate, cells were lifted with TrypLE Express (Thermo Fisher Scientific), washed with PBS, resuspended in 110 µl Buffer R (Neon, Thermo Fisher Scientific) and electroporated (three plates with and three plates without 7 µg LPS) using the Neon Transfection System 100 µl kit. Electroporated cells were washed with PBS and plated in six-well dishes containing fresh DMEM. Electroporated control cells were passaged until LPS-electroporated cells recovered. After 11 days, genomic DNA was isolated from LPS-resistant and control cells using the Gentra Puregene Cell kit (QIAGEN). The barcoded regions were amplified by PCR and then sequenced by next-generation sequencing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec19"&gt;Next-generation sequencing and analysis&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;For submitted PCR amplicons, 40 ng DNA was used to generate sequencing libraries with the KAPA HyperPrep kit (Roche) that incorporated custom adapters and library amplification PCR primers from Integrated DNA Technologies. Amplicon libraries were quantified and the average library size was determined using the NGS Fragment kit in Fragment Analyzer (Agilent Technologies). Libraries were pooled and the Qubit dsDNA HS Assay kit (Thermo Fisher Scientific) was used to quantify the pool. Library pools were sequenced on a HiSeq 2500 (Illumina) to generate a minimum of three million paired-end 75-base-pair reads for each sample. A sample ORF matrix was generated by counting exact matches of ORF barcodes in the sample FASTQ files. The count matrix was normalized by library-size-based factors. Differentially enriched ORFs were identified using DESeq2 (ref. &lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 44" title="Love, M. I., Huber, W. &amp;amp; Anders, S. Moderated estimation of fold change and dispersion for RNA-seq data with DESeq2. Genome Biol 15, 550 (2014)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR44" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2331"&gt;44&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;) by comparing LPS-treated cells with control cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec20"&gt;Cell assays&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;For EA.hy926 cell death assays, 8 × 10&lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt; cells per well were seeded into 96-well plates. The following day, cells were treated with 250 ng ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; doxycycline (Takara). After a further 24 h, cells were transfected with ultra-pure &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; O111:B4 LPS (0.5 µg per well, InvivoGen) using Lipofectamine LTX transfection reagent (0.2 µl per well, Thermo Fisher Scientific), or treated with 25 µM Val-boroPro (Millipore) for 24 h. LDH release was measured by CytoTox Non-radioactive Cytotoxicity Assay (Promega). Cells were cultured with the membrane-impermeable nuclear dye YOYO-1 (Thermo Fisher Scientific) to determine the kinetics of cell death. Cells were imaged every 30 min for 24 h in an IncuCyte S3 (Essen BioScience, 10× objective). Nuclear-ID (Enzo) was added to cultures after the last time point to quantify total cell numbers. Image quantification was performed using Incucyte Base Analysis software. Results were plotted as the percentage of YOYO-1&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; cells within the total population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec21"&gt;Immunoblotting and immunoprecipitation&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cells were washed with PBS and lysed in RIPA buffer (25 mM Tris HCl pH 7.6, 150 mM NaCl, 1% NP-40, 1% sodium deoxycholate and 0.1% SDS) supplemented with protease inhibitors (Halt, Thermo Fisher Scientific). Lysates were clarified by centrifugation at 20,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt; for 30 min. For immunoprecipitation, soluble lysates were incubated with 20 µl Flag-M2–sepharose (MilliporeSigma), Rho-1D4–sepharose (Rho-1D4 Ab, University of British Columbia, coupled to cyanogen bromide-activated sepharose beads, GE Healthcare) or GST–sepharose (MilliporeSigma) for one hour at 4 °C. Beads were washed with lysis buffer, and captured proteins were eluted with 100 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; 3×Flag peptide (MilliporeSigma), 10 mM reduced glutathione peptide (MilliporeSigma) or 250 µM Rho-1D4 peptide (TETSQVAPA, Genscript) overnight at 4 °C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec22"&gt;Antibodies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antibodies recognized actin (clone C4, MP Bio, 0.1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;), β-tubulin (ab15568, abcam, 0.1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;), Myc tag (9B11, Cell Signaling Technology, 1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;), Flag epitope (M2-HRP, Sigma-Aldrich, 1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;) ROCK1 (Cell Signaling Technology, 1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;), ROCK2 (Cell Signaling Technology, 1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;), phospho-MLC2 (Cell Signaling Technology, 1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;), p66β (Bethyl, 1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;), Rho-1D4 (Novus, 1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;), ubiquitin (VU-1, LifeSensors, 1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;), K11-linked polyubiquitin&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 45" title="Matsumoto, M. L. et al. K11-linked polyubiquitination in cell cycle control revealed by a K11 linkage-specific antibody. Mol. Cell 39, 477–484 (2010)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR45" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2394"&gt;45&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, K48-linked polyubiquitin&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 46" title="Newton, K. et al. Ubiquitin chain editing revealed by polyubiquitin linkage-specific antibodies. Cell 134, 668–678 (2008)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR46" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2399"&gt;46&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; and K63-linked polyubiquitin&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 46" title="Newton, K. et al. Ubiquitin chain editing revealed by polyubiquitin linkage-specific antibodies. Cell 134, 668–678 (2008)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR46" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2403"&gt;46&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; (1 µg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec23"&gt;Identification of NleL substrates&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Proteomic analyses were performed on EA.hy926 expressing doxycycline-inducible 3×Flag-NleL. Cells were treated with doxycycline for zero, one, two, four or six hours (in duplicate except for the one-hour treatment), and collected by scraping into 50 mM HEPES pH 8.5, 9 M urea, 150 mM NaCl and protease inhibitors (Roche). Lysates were rotated end-over-end at room temperature for one hour, and then centrifuged at 15,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt; for 20 min. Soluble lysate containing 20 mg protein was reduced (5 mM dithiothreitol (DTT), 45 min at 37 °C), alkylated (15 mM iodoacetamide (IAA), 20 min at room temperature in the dark) and quenched (5 mM DTT, 15 min at room temperature in the dark). Proteins were pelleted by chloroform–methanol precipitation, resuspended in 8 M urea, 20 mM HEPES, pH 8.0, diluted to 4 M urea and digested for four hours at 37 °C with lysyl endopeptidase (Wako) at an enzyme-to-protein ratio of 1:100. The sample was diluted further to 1.3 M urea and subjected to overnight enzymatic digestion at 37 °C with sequencing-grade trypsin (Promega) at an enzyme-to-protein ratio of 1:50. The peptides were acidified with 20% trifluoroacetic acid (TFA, final concentration 1%), centrifuged at 18,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt; for 15 min and desalted using a Sep-Pak C&lt;sub&gt;18&lt;/sub&gt; column (Waters).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Approximately 500 µg of eluted peptides from each treatment was lyophilized and reserved for global proteome abundance. The remaining eluted peptides were lyophilized and used for K-ε-GG analysis. For global proteome samples, 100 µg of peptides from each sample was dissolved in 20 mM HEPES pH 8.0 at 1 mg ml&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;. Isobaric labelling was performed using TMT11-plex reagents (Thermo Fisher Scientific). Each unit (0.8 mg) of TMT reagent was allowed to reach room temperature immediately before use, pelleted in a benchtop centrifuge and resuspended with occasional vortexing in 41 µl anhydrous acetonitrile (ACN) before mixing with peptides (29% final ACN concentration). After incubation at room temperature for one hour, the reaction was quenched for 15 min with 20 µl of 5% hydroxylamine. Labelled peptides were combined in equimolar ratios and dried. The TMT-labelled sample was re-dissolved in 80 µl 0.1% TFA and centrifuged at 16,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt;, and the supernatant was processed further. Offline high-pH reversed-phase fractionation was performed on a 1100 HPLC system (Agilent) using an ammonium formate buffer system. Peptides (400 µg) were loaded onto a 2.1 × 150 mm, 3.5-µm 300 Extend-C&lt;sub&gt;18&lt;/sub&gt; Zorbax column (Agilent) and separated over a 75-min gradient from 5% to 85% ACN into 96 fractions (flow rate = 200 µl per min). The fractions were concatenated into 24 fractions, mixing different parts of the gradient to produce samples that would be orthogonal to downstream low pH reversed-phase LC–MS/MS. Fractions were dried and desalted using C&lt;sub&gt;18&lt;/sub&gt; stage-tips as described&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 47" title="Rappsilber, J., Mann, M. &amp;amp; Ishihama, Y. Protocol for micro-purification, enrichment, pre-fractionation and storage of peptides for proteomics using StageTips. Nat. Protoc. 2, 1896–1906 (2007)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR47" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2437"&gt;47&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Peptides were lyophilized and resuspended in buffer A (2% ACN and 0.1% formic acid) for LC–MS/MS analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For quantification of K-ε-GG peptides, lyophilized peptides were reconstituted in 1× detergent containing IAP buffer (Cell Signaling Technology) for immunoaffinity enrichment. Enrichment for K-ε-GG peptides was performed at 4 °C on a MEA2 automated purification system (PhyNexus) using 1 ml PhyTips (PhyNexus) packed with 20 µl ProPlus resin coupled to 200 µg of anti-K-ε-GG (Cell Signaling Technology) antibody. PhyTip columns were equilibrated for two cycles (one cycle = aspiration and dispensing, 0.9 ml, 0.5 ml min&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt;) with 1 ml 1× IAP buffer before contact with peptides. PhyTip columns were incubated with peptides for 16 cycles of capture, followed by 6 cycles of wash, twice with 1 ml 1× IAP buffer and 4 times with 1 ml water. Captured peptides were eluted with 60 µl 0.15% TFA in eight cycles in which the volume aspirated or dispensed was adjusted to 60 µl. Enriched ubiquitylated peptides were prepared as described&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 48" title="Rose, C. M. et al. Highly multiplexed quantitative mass spectrometry analysis of ubiquitylomes. Cell Syst. 3, 395–403.e4 (2016)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR48" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2446"&gt;48&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. Labelled peptides were combined, dried and resolubilized in 0.15% TFA for high-pH reversed-phase fractionation using a commercially available kit (Thermo Fisher Scientific). Fractionation was performed with a modified elution scheme in which 11 fractions were collected (F1, 13.5% ACN; F2, 15% ACN; F3, 16.25% ACN; F4, 17.5 ACN; F5, 20% ACN; F6, 21.5% ACN; F7, 22.5% ACN; F8, 23.75% ACN; F9, 25% ACN; F10, 27.5% ACN; and F11, 30% ACN) and then combined into 6 fractions (F1 + F6, F2 + F7, F8, F3 + F9, F4 + F10 and F5 + F11). Peptides were lyophilized and resuspended in 10 µl buffer A for LC–MS/MS analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec24"&gt;Mass spectrometry&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;LC–MS/MS analysis was performed by injecting 5 µl of each fraction on an Orbitrap Lumos mass spectrometer (Thermo Fisher Scientific) coupled to a Dionex Ultimate 3000 RSLC (Thermo Fisher Scientific) using a 25-cm IonOpticks Aurora Series column (IonOpticks) with a gradient of 2% to 30% buffer B (98% ACN, 2% H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O with 0.1% FA, flow rate = 300 nl per min). All samples were analysed with a total run time of 180 min. The Orbitrap Lumos collected FTMS1 scans at 120,000 resolution with an AGC target of 1 × 10&lt;sup&gt;6&lt;/sup&gt; and a maximum injection time of 50 ms. FTMS2 scans on precursors with charge states of 3–6 were collected at 15,000 resolution with CID fragmentation at a normalized collision energy of 35%, an AGC target of 2 × 10&lt;sup&gt;4&lt;/sup&gt; (proteome) or 2 × 10&lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt; (K-ε-GG) and a max injection time of 100 ms (proteome) or 200 ms (K-ε-GG). Synchronous precursor selection (SPS) MS3 scans were analysed in the Orbitrap at 50,000 resolution with the top eight most intense ions in the MS2 spectrum subjected to HCD fragmentation at a normalized collision energy of 55%, an AGC target of 2 × 10&lt;sup&gt;5&lt;/sup&gt; and a max injection time of 100 ms (proteome) or 350 ms (K-ε-GG).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MS data were searched using Mascot against a concatenated target–decoy human database (downloaded August 2017) containing common contaminant sequences, and the protein sequence of &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; NleL ligase with a precursor mass tolerance of 50 ppm, 0.8 Da fragment ion tolerance and tryptic specificity up to 2 (proteome) or 3 missed cleavages (K-ε-GG). For global proteome analysis, the following modifications were considered: carbamidomethyl cysteine (+57.0214), TMT-labelled N terminus (+229.1629) and TMT-labelled lysine (+229.1629) as static modifications, and oxidized methionine (+15.9949) and TMT-labelled tyrosine (+229.1629) as variable modifications. For analysis of K-ε-GG peptides, TMT-labelled diglycine-modified lysine (+343.2059) was also included as a variable modification. Peptide spectral matches for each run were filtered using linear discriminant analysis to an FDR of 2% and subsequently in aggregate to a protein-level FDR of 2%. TMT-MS3 quantification was performed using Mojave, and only peptide-spectrum matches (PSMs) that had isolation specificities greater than or equal to 0.5 were considered for the final dataset. The abundance of ubiquitylation on each peptide or each identified protein was estimated by using a model fitted with Tukey median polish summarization with imputation of missing values below a censoring threshold of 28. For each pairwise comparison, the change in abundance (log&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; ‘fold’ values) and the results of an ANOVA test were reported. We used the implementation of these methods in MSstats v.3.16.0 (ref. &lt;sup&gt;&lt;a data-track="click" data-track-action="reference anchor" data-track-label="link" data-test="citation-ref" aria-label="Reference 49" title="Choi, M. et al. MSstats: an R package for statistical analysis of quantitative mass spectrometry-based proteomic experiments. Bioinformatics 30, 2524–2526 (2014)." href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#ref-CR49" id="ref-link-section-d40633257e2476"&gt;49&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;). Data were further processed in R to produce figures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec25"&gt;Protein expression and purification&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; NleL S170-R782 WT/C357A constructs were expressed as N-terminal His fusion constructs in &lt;i&gt;E. coli&lt;/i&gt; Rosetta 2 (Millipore). Bacterial cell pellets were frozen and stored at −80 °C. Cells were resuspended in lysis buffer (50 mM Tris pH 8.0, 200 mM NaCl, 5 % glycerol, 5 mM MgCl&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;, 1 mM TCEP or 2 mM 2-mercaptoethanol, plus protease inhibitors (Roche), DNase and lysozyme) and lysed by microfluidization, and the lysate was clarified by centrifugation at 20,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt; for one hour. The soluble lysate was passed through a 2-µm filter. NTA Superflow resin (QUIAGEN) or TALON Superflow (GE Healthcare) were used for affinity purification. The resin was incubated with the clarified lysate at 4 °C for one hour and then washed with up to 2 l of wash buffer (50 mM Tris pH 8.0, 200 mM NaCl, 5 % glycerol and 1 mM TCEP or 2 mM 2-mercaptoethanol). Proteins were eluted in wash buffer supplemented with 250 mM imidazole pH 8.0 (Sigma). NleL proteins were concentrated and purified by size-exclusion chromatography using a Superdex 200 column (GE Healthcare) pre-equilibrated with 50 mM Tris pH 8.0, 300 mM NaCl, 5% glycerol and 1 mM TCEP. Pure-protein-containing fractions were pooled, concentrated and stored at −80 °C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C-terminal 1D4-tagged human caspase-4 (full length 1–377), human ROCK1 (full length 1–1,354) and human ROCK2 (full length 1–1,388, kinase domain 1–409, PH domain 1,142–1,388) were purified from 293T cells. Cell pellets were resuspended in 10 mM HEPES pH 7.4, 150 mM NaCl, 10% glycerol, 1 mM MgCl&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;, 1 mM TCEP containing protease inhibitor cocktail (Halt) and benzonase. Lysates were clarified by centrifugation at 20,000&lt;i&gt;g&lt;/i&gt; for 30 min at 4 °C. 1D4–sepharose was used for purification. Lysates were incubated with resin for one hour at 4 °C and washed three times with lysis buffer. Proteins were eluted with 25 μM 1D4 peptide in 10 mM HEPES pH 7.4, 150 mM NaCl, 10% glycerol, 1 mM MgCl&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; and 1 mM TCEP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec26"&gt;In vitro ubiquitylation assays&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reactions contained 2.5 ng µl&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; human E1 enzyme (Boston Biochem), 0.125 µg µl&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; ubiquitin (Boston Biochem), 0.01 µg µl&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; Ube2D3 (Boston Biochem), 0.01 µg µl&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; NleL, 0.1 µg µl&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; human caspase-4, ROCK1 or ROCK2, 50 mM Tris pH 8.0, 50 mM NaCl, 5 mM MgCl&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt; and 0.1 mM DTT. Reactions were initiated with 5 mM ATP, incubated at 37 °C and quenched with LDS sample loading buffer (Thermo Fisher Scientific).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec27"&gt;Statistics&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;P&lt;/i&gt; value calculations for the mass spectrometry analyses in Fig. &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="figure anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#Fig2"&gt;2a&lt;/a&gt; are described above. All other statistical analyses were performed using GraphPad Prism v.9 and v.10.4.2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="c-article__sub-heading c-article__sub-heading--divider" id="Sec28"&gt;Reporting summary&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further information on research design is available in the &lt;a data-track="click" data-track-label="link" data-track-action="supplementary material anchor" href="/articles/s41586-025-09645-0#MOESM2"&gt;Nature Portfolio Reporting Summary&lt;/a&gt; linked to this article.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Nature</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:05:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTE0xV25rV1JmYUxGN2JWRWpJUzZGeVJ2Nk9mYnhFbVF2b0F6MVpTTDZQMjhwX3MtbDg2TmRkYklUQnVrOGI1UDZnaUNPVi03b2FFYjVLN2RQYUp1UnBxTW1V</guid></item><item><title>科学家创造抗经典猪瘟的猪--《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/oct/22/scientists-create-pigs-resistant-to-classical-swine-fever-gene-editing</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Pigs that are resistant to a deadly viral disease have been created by scientists at Edinburgh’s Roslin Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The gene-edited animals remained healthy when exposed to classical swine fever (CSF), a highly contagious and often fatal disease. The virus was eradicated in the UK in 1966, but there have been several outbreaks since and it continues to pose a major threat to pig farming worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Classical swine fever is a devastating disease for livestock and farmers as we saw with the outbreak in the UK, 25 years ago,” said Helen Crooke, mammalian virology deputy leader at the Animal and Plant Health Agency (APHA), where the pig trial was performed. “Hopefully this breakthrough can help bolster the resilience of the livestock sector to the disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Classical swine fever, also known as hog cholera or pig plague, causes fever, skin lesions, convulsions, diarrhoea – and often death within 15 days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the UK, periodic outbreaks since the 1960s, have led to the culling of 75,000 pigs. And in countries such as China, Russia and Brazil, where the disease is endemic, CSF is controlled through costly and labour-intensive vaccination programmes and international trade restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Christine Tait-Burkard, a group leader at the Roslin Institute, said: “This virus has a severe effect on animal welfare and productivity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The latest study, the first to demonstrate resistance through gene editing, targeted a gene responsible for producing a protein called DNAJC14. This protein had been shown to play a critical role in the replication of pestiviruses (the virus family that includes CSF) once they enter the cell. Previous studies in cells had found that altering just a few letters of the DNA code blocked viral replication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the latest study, scientists at the Roslin Institute created a line of pigs with the same precise edits to their DNA. Four of the pigs were then exposed to CSF, along with four control pigs, at APHA’s biosecure facility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A week after inoculation, the control animals were showing symptoms of the disease and had high levels of the virus in their blood. By contrast, the gene-edited pigs were completely healthy and showed no signs of infection. Several generations of gene-edited pigs were monitored and no adverse effects on health or fertility were observed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The same gene is involved in the replication of pestiviruses that infect cattle and sheep – less severe diseases, but ones that continue to circulate in the UK – and the team is now investigating whether the same edit confers resistance for these species.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The advance comes as many countries are relaxing rules around gene editing in agriculture, with the UK’s &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2024/nov/02/scientists-dismayed-as-uk-ministers-clear-way-for-gene-editing-of-crops-but-not-animals" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Precision Breeding Act&lt;/a&gt; paving the way for gene-edited crops. Countries including the US, Japan and Brazil have already approved gene-edited livestock. Based on previous work at Roslin, Genus, a company based in Basingstoke, has generated pigs that are resistant to a virus that causes porcine reproductive and respiratory syndrome, which have been approved for sale in the US and are expected to go on the market there in 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="d32ffb06-942b-4e9c-846a-356bea728b3e" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":11,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Scientists dismayed as UK ministers clear way for gene editing of crops - but not animals","elementId":"d32ffb06-942b-4e9c-846a-356bea728b3e","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/science/2024/nov/02/scientists-dismayed-as-uk-ministers-clear-way-for-gene-editing-of-crops-but-not-animals"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Simon Lillico, research scientist at the Roslin Institute and a co-author, said: “In my mind there is a moral imperative that if we can make animals that are disease resistant then we probably should do.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Emily Clark, of EMBL’s European Bioinformatics Institute, who was not involved in the research, said: “Decades of genomic research have made it possible to pinpoint and precisely edit the genes involved in disease resistance. Research like this is helping to create healthier animals, reduce losses for farmers in areas affected by swine fever, and marks a major step forward in using genomics-enabled innovation to build resilience to disease in livestock populations.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The findings are published in the journal &lt;a href="https://10.0.3.248/j.tibtech.2025.09.008" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Trends in Biotechnology&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxOZXpGQXgtN1poWklBcjZ6YllHZmk5cS1Ia2RSLU44YW5EOHVFMnh5TkhZSjVCQ3R1REdneHFfdkNjcER2ODM0UWhENEc2d2huRUM2RGtXM25Zc1dVOHg3T1AxRmZRbEY0blh2OXNwdzQtcmt6SVB2eEZDVXN4UXpnd293eHFQcC11bkthYUlkQ3J6OUVtajNPcWlWY19IVmFCRXRsLTRTbERmVTBhYjN0Z1N4XzlzWDhrbkE</guid></item><item><title>带状疱疹疫苗不仅可以预防疼痛，还可以挽救您的生命- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/shingles-shots-dont-just-prevent-pain-they-might-save-your-life-2000674980</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl "&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;A vaccine that prevents one of the most painful infections around could be good for your brain and heart, too. New research out this week shows the shingles vaccine is linked to a lower risk of several serious health conditions.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Scientists at Case Western Reserve University examined the health records of Americans over the age of 50. Those protected against the viral infection were less likely to develop heart disease, stroke, and a common form of dementia, they found. The findings are the latest to suggest that shingles can cause long-term consequences throughout the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The lingering threat&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/shingles/symptoms-causes/syc-20353054"&gt;Shingles&lt;/a&gt; is caused by the varicella-zoster virus, the same germ responsible for chickenpox in children. Chickenpox typically causes a brief, if miserable, bout of illness. But afterward, the virus can survive and lie dormant in our bodies for decades. When our immune system weakens, either due to age or other factors, varicella-zoster can then reawaken and spark shingles.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the second time with varicella-zoster is usually much worse. Shingles can cause excruciating pain and distinctive rashes that last for several weeks. Even after the infection is beaten back again, some people can be left with lingering, potentially lifelong nerve pain.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thankfully, the shingles vaccine is highly effective at preventing its return and is widely recommended for adults over 50. In recent years, studies have also started to indicate that this protection extends beyond the infection itself.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Protection for the brain and heart&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this latest study, the researchers analyzed the medical records of more than 174,000 adults in the U.S. They tracked the health outcomes of people vaccinated for shingles for up to seven years and compared them to similar people who instead received the pneumococcal vaccine—another vaccine recommended for older people. This second group acted as a sort of control.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;All in all, compared to controls, people vaccinated for shingles had a 27% lower risk of being diagnosed with blood clots and a 25% lower risk of heart attack or stroke. They also had a 50% lower risk of vascular dementia, a form of the condition caused by blood vessel damage in the brain, and a 21% lower overall risk of dying during the study period.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The team’s findings were recently presented at IDWeek 2025, the annual conference of the Infectious Diseases Society of America and other related organizations.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Shingles is more than just a rash—it can raise the risk of serious problems for the heart and brain,” said study author Ali Dehghani, doctor of internal medicine at Case Western Reserve University’s School of Medicine, in a &lt;a href="https://www.idsociety.org/news--publications-new/articles/2025/shingles-vaccine-lowers-risk-of-dementia-major-cardiovascular-events/"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; released by the IDSA. “Our study findings show that the shingles vaccine may help lower those risks, especially in people already at higher risk for heart attack or stroke.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This type of research is observational, meaning it can’t directly prove a causative link between shingles vaccination and a reduced risk of these conditions. But other studies have also supported the idea that preventing shingles can prevent &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/the-shingles-vaccine-could-be-a-secret-weapon-against-heart-attacks-2000598150"&gt;heart attacks&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/unique-study-is-latest-to-show-shingles-vaccine-can-prevent-dementia-2000583567"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;. So given the already well-established benefits of the vaccine, these findings should just provide added motivation to get your shingles shots as soon as you’re eligible (the only currently approved vaccine is a two-dose series).&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 13:45:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNZlJ5OW9KcmdQWGtBbk9pbmw5QW9lSFZKbHhXNUtqRDZ1WERudi1iRkFrVFdQLU5tZ3hqVmZEeWlWZVU0aV9iVE1YOWc3bkZnOS1wdS1tY01mOW5JNGJVU0pfWjlaRXgzTEV6MW9LWWstSF9jc0lQTWxRNWo3NFlhMllRY0R0ZFd5S2NFWGNvT0dRNzlIQzM0S1hn</guid></item><item><title>得益于新的定义，美国人在一夜之间变得“更胖”而没有增加一磅- tyla.com</title><link>https://www.tyla.com/news/america-obesity-new-definition-bmi-research-health-458374-20251022</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;If you're American, there's a chance you just became 'obese' overnight without actually gaining any weight - yes, really.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;As per a Centres for Disease Control and Prevention 2024 report, more than 2 in 5 &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/us-news"&gt;US&lt;/a&gt; adults are classified as obese, and that number could be set to skyrocket following new &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;This is because the criteria for &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/life/signs-obesity-bmi-weight-loss-900862-20250115"&gt;diagnosing the condition is changing&lt;/a&gt;, meaning even if you weren't classed as having the health concern previously, the new guidelines mean you could now fall into that category.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/world-news"&gt;World&lt;/a&gt; Health Organisation describes obesity as a 'chronic complex disease defined by excessive fat deposits that can impair health'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Many adults with obesity also have other serious chronic diseases, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/news/type-1-half-diabetes-symptoms-rare-disease-explained-393947-20250915"&gt;including diabetes and heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, as a result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;As &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/health-and-families/obesity-definition-us-adults-bmi-b2846733.html?fbclid=IwY2xjawNlr0dleHRuA2FlbQIxMABicmlkETFhWnE4N1BsQkg0UkJvQmpUAR4Rp7DHimPcU6S9dWOMMCCfVjunhWCcEoZTHCcB8J-Sbf9oC8czk7vkOgj6UQ_aem_hvR9Hxu5ktL6Szj15t4RVw"&gt;per&lt;/a&gt; the Independent, doctors in Massachusetts said last week that the definition of obesity should be expanded beyond a simple body mass index (BMI) test, to instead include how fat is distributed across the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;A new definition of obesity in the US means the number of people affected has jumped from 40% to 70% (Getty Stock Image)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The BMI test has long caused debate over whether it's the most effective way to measure obesity, mainly because it doesn't take into account factors like muscle mass, age, and sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Essentially, it doesn't distinguish fat from fat-free mass, such as muscle and bone and other bodily tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;So, someone with lots of muscle &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="v"&gt;could wrongly be considered obese&lt;/a&gt;, simply because their body weighs more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The criticisms prompted researches to establish a new framework, which takes into account not only BMI, but also other anthropomorphic measures such as waist circumference, waist-to-hip ratio, and waist-to-height ratio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Under the new framework, a person is &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/life/woman-weight-loss-audio-tape-069691-20250724"&gt;classified as having obesity&lt;/a&gt; if they have a high BMI plus at least one elevated anthropometric measure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Putting their new method to the test, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/science"&gt;researchers&lt;/a&gt; tried it out on a group of more than 300,000 patients - and the results were quite shocking, as seen published &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2840138?utm_source=For_The_Media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_term=101525"&gt;in&lt;/a&gt; JAMA Network Open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;They discovered that by using this new framework, the number of obese people in the US made a huge heap from 40 percent to 70 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;That's right - if this study is anything to go by, 70% of the US is technically considered obese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;BMI has long been criticised for how accurate it is and the new framework takes additional factors into account (Getty Stock Image)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The doctors involved believe that this statistic reflects reality across the American population, meaning that a shocking one in four people would be considered obese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Researchers said the sharp rise was even more pronounced among older adults and those newly added individuals on the list also had a higher risk of adverse health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It claims that those with anthropometric-only obesity - who would not have been classified as having obesity by the traditional definition - had a higher risk of diabetes, cardiovascular disease, and mortality than people without obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Co-first author Lindsay Fourman, MD, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1101828"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; in a statement: "With potentially 70 percent of the adult population now considered to have excess fat, we need to better understand what treatment approaches to prioritise.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;At least 76 organisations have reportedly endorsed the new guidelines, including the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.tyla.com/life/cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic-syndrome-explained-us-716722-20251021"&gt;American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt; and The Obesity Society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Senior author Steven Grinspoon, MD, added: "We have always recognised the limitations of BMI as a single marker for obesity because it doesn't take into account body fat distribution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“Seeing an increased risk of cardiovascular disease and diabetes in this new group of people with obesity, who were not considered to have obesity before, brings up interesting questions about obesity medications and other therapeutics."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>tyla.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 13:27:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNOURCVVE5TG9KazRSOUlzaDR4TE0ySzNQRGVFeXhqT0xteU55VVBnWDB1cExaMnoxSnByX1RuRjdfRlFxUlNxN29kOTl5RjRiWWNTNkpreU1fZ0NKU1lUT0hYTUlmY1NGTzJmcF9sQURzdjc3X1F5SjVVVG5YbFV1V2tqVEN3VlJOV2VRSnZpUWR6Ry00bDh3</guid></item><item><title>“有毒二人组”可能是阿尔茨海默病背后的隐藏触发因素-科学日报</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251022023113.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;For decades, scientists have known that Alzheimer's disease is marked by sticky plaques and tangled proteins in the brain. In recent years, research has also shown that the brain's blood vessels play an important role in how the disease develops. Yet despite decades of progress, this deeper understanding has not led to fully effective treatments. The main obstacle has been the uncertainty around the exact biological chain of events that leads to brain cell loss.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Toxic Interaction Between Amyloid and Blood Proteins&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New findings now reveal a damaging partnership between two key molecules: amyloid beta (Aβ), a peptide known for forming plaques, and fibrinogen, a major blood protein involved in clotting. When Aβ attaches to fibrinogen, it produces unusual clots that resist breakdown. These stubborn clots are linked to inflammation and damage in blood vessels, and even very small amounts of the complex appear to set off early signs of Alzheimer's, including loss of synapses, swelling in the brain, and leaks in the blood-brain barrier. The results strengthen the case that vascular dysfunction contributes directly to neurodegeneration and highlight a promising new therapeutic target: the Aβ/fibrinogen complex.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It takes a larger amount of Aβ or fibrinogen alone to cause serious damage in the Alzheimer's brain," says Erin Norris, research associate professor in the laboratory of Sidney Strickland at Rockefeller. "But when the two complex together, you only need very small amounts of each to cause damage. There's a synergistic effect with Aβ and fibrinogen."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Investigating a Long-Standing Hypothesis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strickland's Patricia and John Rosenwald Laboratory of Neurobiology and Genetics has been studying this Aβ/fibrinogen link for almost twenty years. Earlier work from the group showed that Aβ binds to fibrinogen and connected that interaction to the progression of Alzheimer's disease. At the time, the idea that blood vessel problems could play a major role in Alzheimer's was controversial. "Only recently, with a number of breakthroughs in the field, did people begin to believe that the vascular system is involved in AD pathogenesis," Norris says. "Since our initial findings, we've been focused on studying the mechanisms that explain how a dysfunctional vascular system impacts AD."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Identifying the complex was only the beginning. The researchers wanted to know how much damage it could cause on its own. They recreated low concentrations of the Aβ/fibrinogen complex in the lab and applied it to thin slices of mouse brain tissue as well as to living mice. This allowed them to observe its effects under tightly controlled conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We wanted to really show the damage -- to zoom in on exactly how pre- and post-synaptic terminals were being harmed," says Research Associate Elisa Nicoloso Simões-Pires.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their experiments revealed that while Aβ and fibrinogen alone caused little harm, even small amounts of the combined complex led to major problems. It damaged synapses, increased inflammation, and disrupted the blood-brain barrier -- all signature features of Alzheimer's disease. When the researchers used antibodies that stopped Aβ from binding to fibrinogen, the harmful effects were significantly reduced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We showed that the complex actually induces blood-brain barrier leakage, when the proteins alone did not," Simões-Pires says. "Disruption of the blood-brain barrier allows for blood proteins to cross into the brain, which lead to additional harm."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clues to Early Alzheimer's and Potential Treatments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One strength of the study is that it used both isolated brain tissue and live mice. "It was an in vitro and in vivo project, both providing the same outcome," Norris says. "We are much more confident in our results when we can show the same thing in culture and in a living organism." Next, the team plans to explore the mechanism -- why does this complex cause so much trouble?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There may also be clinical implications, because the study suggests that even small amounts of the Aβ/fibrinogen complex can trigger the features of Alzheimer's disease long before cognitive symptoms appear. Mice exposed to the complex, for instance, also showed elevated levels of phospho-tau181, a biomarker used in humans to detect Alzheimer's years before symptoms arise. This result raises the possibility that the current study is mimicking the earliest stages of AD progression and that early intervention targeting the complex itself could delay or prevent it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While many mechanisms contribute to Alzheimer's, the team believes this particular pathway deserves more attention. "It's not a simple disease," Simões-Pires says. "A lot of other factors can induce neurotoxicity, and we certainly do not propose that inhibiting this complex formation would cure AD. But perhaps targeting this complex would alleviate some of the pathologies and be even more effective in combination with other therapies."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These discoveries bring researchers one step closer to understanding how damage spreads in the Alzheimer's brain -- and how stopping a single toxic interaction could make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Science Daily</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 13:20:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFA1cGxxb0lJakpHTVlGcWlNYU5xeUQyYlBIT2I0LWJ5RkpXOXhfVlV5Y1NZR1dWNXhSeElTaEJMQkJNT1cwNFFYdHVRdEIzalJTTGdUeTJxMlM0ZHZHY1A4SjJoU1JNamdXZmV0NVZZcw</guid></item><item><title>对演讲感到紧张？为什么有些人使用β受体阻滞剂来治疗焦虑。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/10/22/beta-blocker-anxiety-stage-fright/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="B4WCI6L5SZF77OEYJ2UCVYSCQI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When performing onstage, Dania Hallak, a singer and songwriter, sometimes found she couldn’t hit lower notes. Her vocal coach suggested it was performance anxiety. Hallak saw her doctor, who prescribed a beta blocker, a class of drugs more commonly used to treat heart issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:31:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxPenRMMU5aSkFKWGoySHRyT29HdW5yanpLem4wVnY4NDdfUFhOWjZZMlk5SERPcHhzYlVZWV9pRFlmc3NuQ2htdloxUXdydl9jMzZYdHoyYjViQ2RfNXYzR0F6N3RpNEl6QnFZVnlobTZxUG9obHFRRU8yOWNKNFVoR2J0ZmhyUFRQMUFLTndB</guid></item><item><title>越来越多的工人正在使用减肥药物。这花费了他们的雇主一大笔钱- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/22/economy/weight-loss-drugs-kff-employer-survey</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15xkcd006o26nkbj3j4emt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Weight loss drugs are proving to be super popular among many workers with job-based health insurance. But GLP-1 medications are busting their employers’ budgets, leading some firms to rethink their coverage.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000b356nwyypmzry@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The share of very large firms covering these drugs for obesity soared to 43% this year, up from 28% last year, according to KFF’s latest annual &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.kff.org%2Fehbs&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CTami.Luhby%40cnn.com%7Cc69cf664776b4c40810908de100dc423%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638965848813438983%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=IniV8PEDIsA5e3qIr0csq9UENlHcJO0on2bkGaZXtzI%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;Employer Health Benefits Survey&lt;/a&gt;, which was released on Wednesday. These employers, who have more than 5,000 workers, are much more likely than their smaller counterparts to offer such a benefit.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000c356n3krydd27@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Among firms with between 200 and 999 staffers, only 16% provide coverage of drugs for weight loss this year, the same as last year, according to KFF, a nonpartisan health policy research group.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000d356n9k9f6erz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            GLP-1 drugs, which treat diabetes, obesity and certain other conditions, have been in great demand since they came on the market a few years ago because they help patients shed pounds. While employers typically cover the medications for diabetes, fewer of them do so for weight loss, in part because of the drugs’ high prices — which have also &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/01/08/health/weight-loss-drug-insurance-denials/index.html"&gt;limited Americans’ access&lt;/a&gt; to them. The list price of Wegovy, for instance, is about $1,350 for a month’s supply, though discounts are available.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000e356n474nvlle@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Employers, however, recognize that covering the medications for weight loss is a valuable benefit to attract and retain talented staffers. Notably, even among firms that don’t do so, nearly half said the benefit is “very important” or “important” for employee satisfaction. More than 36 million people with job-based insurance have a body mass index that would medically qualify them for a GLP-1 drug.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000f356n456eun78@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Large employers know these new high-priced weight-loss drugs are an important benefit for their workers, but their costs often exceed their expectations,” Gary Claxton, KFF senior vice president, said in a statement. “It’s not a surprise that some are rethinking access to the drugs for weight loss.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000g356n8fnvp1z6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Costs are higher than forecast because more workers are taking advantage of the benefit, KFF found. Nearly 60% of large firms said usage of the medications for weight loss is higher than they predicted, while two-thirds of such employers said the impact on their prescription drug spending was “significant.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000h356n8j6boi8f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            One employer KFF surveyed found that it spent more on GLP-1 medications than any other drug this year, up from 32&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; place last year.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000i356nzh04gyih@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A large retailer told KFF, “Before we knew it, we spent half a million dollars and we’re projected to go up to $1.2 million the following year.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000j356nk42d22xt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The high costs of GLP-1 drugs have long been a source of frustration for many Americans. President Donald Trump set off a kerfuffle last week when he said that the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/17/health/ozempic-trump-oz"&gt;medications&lt;/a&gt; would soon be available for $150, prompting Mehmet Oz, the Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services administrator, to step in and say negotiations are ongoing.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000k356n1wgxwp3o@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many employers told KFF they were looking at reducing coverage of the drugs through steps such as limiting eligibility to those with higher body mass indexes or requiring workers to participate in weight management programs.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000l356nweh83jjv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “You have to have a coach, and then you can only stay on it for a certain amount of time before you have to get reevaluated,” one large manufacturer told KFF.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000m356nq90t3bsg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Other firms told KFF they have decided to drop the benefit for weight loss.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000n356n05wwvanj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, employers will likely have to reconsider their coverage again in coming years, especially as more workers demand coverage, and the drugs are approved for even more medical conditions. Plus, prices coming down.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000o356n7431ymgd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We’re still writing the story of what GLP-1 coverage looks like in employer plans,” said Matthew Rae, associate director of the Program on the Health Care Marketplace at KFF.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000q356nsp2gk5xy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            GLP-1 drug costs – and prescription drug prices in general – are also contributing to a rise in premiums.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000r356nawov76si@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Annual insurance coverage for a family hit $27,000, on average, this year, up 6% from 2024, according to KFF’s survey. Workers contribute $6,850 toward the cost, on average, while employers pick up the rest of the tab.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000s356nfkh0ly5a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Meanwhile, individual coverage topped $9,300, on average, this year, up 5% – with employees shouldering $1,440 of the cost and employers paying the rest.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000t356nvlscox5a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Over the past five years, the growth in premiums has been largely in line with inflation and wage increases.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000u356njd36arps@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/04/business/health-insurance-premiums-cost-increase"&gt;coverage for 2026&lt;/a&gt; could be much pricier, according to several benefits consulting firms. KFF also points to GLP-1 medications, hospital prices and tariffs as factors that could push up premiums and out-of-pocket costs for workers next year.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh15ze54000v356ncdv3zyr6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There is a quiet alarm bell going off,” Drew Altman, KFF’s CEO, said in a statement. “Employers have nothing new in their arsenal that can address most of the drivers of their cost increases, and that could well result in an increase in deductibles and other forms of employee cost sharing again, a strategy that neither employers nor employees like but companies resort to in a pinch to hold down premium increases.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:10:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPMXdMUnNLR0Q2UjJEWVpJRmNBUXRJbEZQbC1NbzdmM0dHN0VWU0EtdVhLRmhiVkJGckpTb0ZBbXlJejNDbWE0Q0JJNDliV0NOSjBrOUFUeGNwZ3VzTEQ0OVpudjJYLXR1MFFUVmtBMlpHa0pDMnhxN0p5dUw1OUh3QlZ3</guid></item><item><title>跨性别女性的激素治疗改变了数十种蛋白质，以适应其性别认同- IFLScience</title><link>https://www.iflscience.com/hormone-therapy-for-trans-women-shifts-dozens-of-proteins-to-align-with-their-gender-identity-81235</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p data-pasted="true"&gt;A new study highlights just how flexible the human body can be by demonstrating that in adult transgender women receiving &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/who-calls-for-delivering-gender-affirming-care-to-protect-trans-people-65773" target="_blank"&gt;gender-affirming hormone therapy&lt;/a&gt;, several key proteins became altered to more closely match their forms in cisgender women. As well as changing the way someone’s body looks on the surface, the results show that feminizing hormones have impacts at a molecular level, with implications for susceptibility to various health conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="piano-gate" id="piano-gate"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, led by scientists at the Murdoch Children’s Research Institute (MCRI) in Victoria, Australia, included 40 adult trans women receiving one of two common forms of gender-affirming hormone treatment: estradiol, coupled with either cyproterone acetate or spironolactone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A suite of 5,279 blood proteins was examined before starting treatment and after six months. The proteins from the participants were also compared against &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/hidden-changes-to-us-health-data-swapping-gender-for-sex-spark-fears-for-public-trust-79894" target="_blank"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; from cisgender women taken from the UK Biobank, a long-running study of 500,000 people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What the researchers discovered was that over time, receiving hormones caused protein changes in the trans women that made them more closely align with those in &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/sex-and-gender-operate-differently-in-the-brain-finds-study-of-nearly-5000-kids-75133" target="_blank"&gt;cisgender women&lt;/a&gt;. Of the top 100 proteins that normally differ between males and females, 36 and 22, respectively, shifted towards the “female” form in the trans women after either hormone regimen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results were similar to what is seen in &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/menopause-misconceptions-what-actually-causes-the-symptoms-of-menopause-63920" target="_blank"&gt;menopausal&lt;/a&gt; women who receive &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/new-drugs-heart-health-and-chimpanzees-heres-the-latest-in-menopause-research-76493" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;hormone replacement therapy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="trendmd-suggestions" data-pid-resource="RRUGNY3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For transgender women we found gender affirming hormone therapy alters the levels of many protein biomarkers that reflect what happens clinically,” explained senior author and MCRI Associate Professor Boris Novakovic in a &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1102367" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="piano-inline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This may go onto impact the risk of allergic and autoimmune diseases, which tend to affect more females, but decrease the risk of heart disease, more commonly seen in males. This highlights that human biology is malleable and that even in adulthood, our bodies respond to sex hormone changes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as decreases in some protein biomarkers linked to male reproduction, there were also increases in proteins involved in body fat, breast development, immune function, and good heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decrease in proteins linked to sperm formation was particularly notable in the group receiving cyproterone, which was put down to the fact that this particular combination treatment causes a greater drop in testosterone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings could have implications for how transgender people receiving hormones are monitored over the long term. Novakovic said that as well as considering aspects of health that are unique to trans women, it’s important that providers recognize that trans women may also face similar health challenges to cisgender women. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equally, these findings could help optimize hormone therapy itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Studying proteins could help with the development of personalised treatment approaches by monitoring the effectiveness of gender affirming hormone therapy in trans women and help us with early detection of potential side-effects on heart health or immune function,” explained co-author Professor Ada Cheung. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study was relatively small and only looked at feminizing gender-affirming hormones, so more research will be needed to assess whether similar changes may be seen in &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/gender-affirming-mastectomies-have-an-overwhelmingly-low-regret-rate-70184" target="_blank"&gt;transgender men&lt;/a&gt; or non-binary individuals receiving masculinizing hormones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s been established that &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/male-and-female-mammals-have-different-pain-receptors-and-we-dont-know-why-74613" target="_blank"&gt;biological sex&lt;/a&gt; affects the risk of certain diseases – females are more prone to autoimmune conditions, but males are more susceptible to a range of infectious diseases, for example. Gender-affirming hormone therapy is an &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/hormone-therapy-in-teens-associated-with-better-mental-health-for-transgender-people-62209" target="_blank"&gt;important treatment&lt;/a&gt; for many trans and non-binary people experiencing gender dysphoria, so a better understanding of how it impacts the body – even down to the molecular level – is vital to protect the &lt;a href="https://www.iflscience.com/genderaffirming-hormone-therapy-is-not-bad-for-young-hearts-new-study-reports-59767" target="_blank"&gt;long-term health&lt;/a&gt; of this patient population. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-025-04023-9" target="_blank"&gt;Nature Medicine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>IFLScience</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:07:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxPaFc1NERqTElhdmdMcHBuWi1HUmFZNGpXRUZGaXNpRFkyLXg2cFNaVEhEdDNpMnplbXZ6ZDNhbUdwcC15Q1BZOU91anRVMlpOZkNZUmpiQVZBWTdOb3FXM1NaQUtnblpoQXpMMlZCcXhrZDVXVi16V1BYejhWY1pSLU9rZ2tBeXljREF1bVkweVA1bzhqZ0ZWWmNSRDhuY3RCbTRILWk5WTFYS3RNUDZZang3QkQwMTg1eHJJMVNOblRGZG5L</guid></item><item><title>随着呼吸道病毒季节的开始，联邦政府的关闭在监测方面留下了严重的空白- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/22/health/disease-surveillance-government-shutdown</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihilh008r25pg56cgc6j1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The federal government shutdown has brought respiratory virus surveillance to a halt at the national level, leaving local governments, health systems and the general public with critical blind spots as the season starts to ramp up.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa000053b6ngwyj4mdj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Key federal reports on flu, Covid-19 and RSV haven’t been updated in nearly a month, even as virus activity picks up.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh10vqrs00043b6qjh70ehgu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            These viruses kill tens of thousands of people in the US each year and hospitalize hundreds of thousands more, but they typically follow seasonal patterns and don’t spread as quickly as diseases like measles.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa000043b6nc5ovmpx6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            During a shutdown, national disease surveillance reports are updated only if they “protect from imminent loss of life,” said Dr. Caitlin Rivers, an epidemiologist and director of the Center for Outbreak Response Innovation at the Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh208e8f00033b6nkrj2s5hx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The federal government’s measles response is an “active public health intervention” and permitted by law to continue, according to a statement from the US Department of Health and Human Services, but the shutdown “thwarts the CDC’s ability to continue to publish routine flu data from its public health partners”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa100063b6n0eaplexy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention’s general &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/respiratory-viruses/data/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Respiratory Illness Data Channel&lt;/a&gt; – which offers insight into viral activity through trends in early warning signs like &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nwss/index.html?cove-tab=1" target="_blank"&gt;wastewater&lt;/a&gt; surveillance and emergency department visits – was last updated September 26, a few days before the shutdown began. ﻿Weekly updates from the more specific &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/week-38.html" target="_blank"&gt;FluView&lt;/a&gt; have stopped, as have summary reports from &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/resp-net/dashboard/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;RESP-NET&lt;/a&gt; that tracks hospitalizations for Covid-19, flu and RSV from a network of hospitals across the country. At that time, flu and RSV were already showing signs of increasing activity and Covid-19 levels were elevated.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0z7rzy000y3b6q9qlxiy77@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            According to the latest 2025-26 respiratory disease season outlook from the CDC, the US “will likely have a similar number of combined peak hospitalizations due to COVID-19, influenza, and RSV compared to last season.” Last season, the agency &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu-burden/php/data-vis/2024-2025.html" target="_blank"&gt;estimates&lt;/a&gt; there were between 610,000 and 1.3 million flu hospitalizations and up to 130,000 flu deaths. There were also hundreds of thousands of &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/php/surveillance/burden-estimates.html" target="_blank"&gt;Covid-19 hospitalizations&lt;/a&gt; and between 44,000 and 63,000 deaths.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa100073b6nmog5ns7b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For people who manage their health, it’s like weather or traffic reports blinking out,” Rivers said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0z8hue00113b6qqjnaub5b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In response to questions about how the federal government is working to inform the public about respiratory virus risk and plans to adapt if the shutdown lasts long-term, HHS said the shutdown may delay answers.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0za5ia00153b6q67q41bop@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The Trump Administration is committed to reopening the government for the American people. During the Democrat-led shutdown, mission-critical activities at CDC will continue,” the agency said in a statement.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0vyd2p00003b6qr05rj1r4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some information is still being collected by states and reported to the CDC during the shutdown, and it is often made available to the public through state dashboards. But a coordinated national assessment of trends is a necessary part of preparedness, experts say, and that has lapsed.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000a3b6nvyk7lqrb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The single most important aspect of any response to a problem is communication – clear, sustained communication to the profession and to the general public – and any lack of information impairs that communication,” said Dr. William Schaffner, an infectious diseases expert at Vanderbilt University and spokesperson for the National Foundation for Infectious Diseases.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000b3b6nrnp0pxoh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            RSV, for example, follows a predictable pattern each season, experts say: Viral activity starts in the southern part of the country and moves north. &lt;a href="https://www.floridahealth.gov/diseases-and-conditions/respiratory-illness/respiratory-syncytial-virus/_documents/2025-w41-rsv-summary.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Activity&lt;/a&gt; is already on the rise in Florida, and two outbreaks were reported in the southeastern part of the state, Rivers noted in her latest newsletter.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000c3b6n9bihkuek@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Without national coordination, however, other states and local jurisdictions might lack visibility into Florida’s trends and other cues they’ve historically used to plan for their own response.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000d3b6nx6dt8x4g@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The severity and progression of each flu season can be quite unpredictable, experts say, but national analysis of data and trends can help make the season’s outlook less blurry.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000e3b6nzidskqtg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s the old scouting motto, ‘Be prepared,’” Schaffner said. “The information is so important to everyone in the health care world because it allows hospitals and clinics and emergency rooms to brace for what’s coming. It allows them to anticipate what their staffing needs are, their supplies … and take care of patients in a much more coherent fashion.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000f3b6nwnbsdegi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            National surveillance also helps capture more comprehensive data on the virus variants that are circulating, he said, which can help raise the alarm about a potentially more severe season if the vaccine isn’t a good match or about the rise of any particularly concerning varieties such as bird flu.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000g3b6ndd4geuih@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Laboratory testing capacities at the CDC and expert guidance to analyze local trends may also be hampered during the shutdown, experts say. Lack of visibility on emerging threats is of particular concern because of surveillance pauses. Many&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;CDC researchers will also miss IDWeek, the largest annual meeting of infectious disease experts in the nation, because of the shutdown.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000h3b6namioawfj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many people have also come to use federal respiratory virus information to manage their own health. Infectious diseases don’t stay within state boundaries, and experts say many folks want a broader view of the situation – particularly if they’re traveling for the holidays.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh10otdz00013b6qy3ncp20x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It can drive some decisions around vaccination, too.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000i3b6n2725t11w@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Anne Zink, former chief medical officer for the state of Alaska, says she knew an epidemiologist who would wait to get the flu vaccine until the data started to show an uptick in activity.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa1000j3b6naf5yna5v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “[Protection from] the flu vaccine doesn’t last for that long, so he would want to get it early enough that it would cover him for the season but late enough that it wouldn’t run out before the end of the season,” she said. “So he was always in this space that data needs to be accessible and available to everyone to be able to make that decision.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ypenp00063b6ql3z76vz5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Although the process may be more complicated and less thorough, it’s still possible to get a read on respiratory virus trends.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0xbtqb00053b6nkcam9cf6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The necessary state and local groundwork to track viruses is continuing, and state health departments are still updating respiratory virus dashboards. Rivers has started compiling all of the publicly available data into her &lt;a href="https://caitlinrivers.substack.com/" target="_blank"&gt;newsletter&lt;/a&gt; each week.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0xebal00083b6noy5bmwuv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Zink recently helped launch the Population Health Information and Visualization Exchange, or &lt;a href="https://www.pophive.org/" target="_blank"&gt;PopHIVE&lt;/a&gt;. Hosted by the Yale School of Public Health, the platform brings public and private health datasets together for a more comprehensive and real-time look at a wide range of health trends than was available before.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0xh6hv000b3b6ncasmluc3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For a long time, the government hasn’t been doing exactly what we needed it to do,” Zink said. “This is a filling a gap that’s existed long before a shutdown, and it’s just now maybe getting a little more attention because of that.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ypyzn000a3b6q27apt9kr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            With many pathogens, a brief lapse in surveillance – as due to a government shutdown – is manageable, said Dr. John Brooks, an infectious disease physician and expert in HIV prevention who previously served as chief medical officer for CDC’s Emergency COVID-19 Response.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0yrd89000e3b6qs4m5z8ot@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There may be a period of delay, there may be a hiccup here or there, but generally it continues. We catch up,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0xhpqe000e3b6nqvunu6tv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But in the meantime, some data and surveillance problems can’t be fixed by cobbling various sources together.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa100113b6nk1yo6gcl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “As a general principle, the places where you’ll see problems arising first are in those pathogens that are transmitted most quickly and spread most rapidly,” Brooks said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa100123b6n8obsauz8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Measles &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/10/health/measles-outbreaks-utah-arizona-south-carolina"&gt;outbreaks&lt;/a&gt; continue to cause dozens of cases each week in the US, and the CDC has maintained weekly data reporting accordingly.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa100133b6n53lzlyt0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Flu can also spread quickly, which makes “the need to be on top of the data even more acute” than for something like HIV, Brooks said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa100153b6n3bz95sv0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But there’s a deeper concern about losing visibility on certain groups that are most affected by particular pathogens because of broader policies of the Trump administration. Soon, transgender people will no longer be reported in federal surveillance for HIV, despite having one of the highest diagnosis rates.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0yycj5000q3b6q774eeb2q@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Recently formed groups such as the West Coast Health Alliance and the Northeast Public Health Collaborative — in which state health departments have banded together to issue public health guidance separate from the CDC — may be a “needed second perspective” when it comes to tracking disease, Brooks said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0ihwa100173b6nquv1060c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            While the work of the groups has been more focused on counterbalancing flawed guidance and policy from the CDC, Brooks said, forming these relationships now&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;also puts them “one step ahead” if the need arose to fill gaps in data surveillance.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0xi2d5000h3b6ng1c2ku1f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In all cases, though, surveillance data creates “that fidelity of information to make sure that you are not missing where problems occurring, and so that you can bring the resources necessary to those persons to protect them and take care of them,” Brooks said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg3001r3b6qc5jofj2q@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Experts say that a pause in respiratory virus surveillance was an expected consequence of the government shutdown. Once it’s over, though, the actions the government prioritizes to ramp reporting back up will be important to watch.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg3001s3b6qbwq6av23@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “When there’s a shutdown, the catchup is really expensive, so things don’t tend to come up very quickly,” said Dr. Demetre Daskalakis, who recently resigned as director of the CDC’s National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases. “They tend to take a little bit of lead time because of the need to catch up on whatever’s been left behind.”
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg3001v3b6qib0fwnku@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The time needed for that catchup is exacerbated by broader turmoil at the CDC, he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg3001w3b6q5gq2f3qh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            According to estimates from a local union representing federal workers, about a quarter of the CDC’s workforce – about 3,000 workers – have been fully separated since the beginning of the year. Additional attempted reductions in force, or RIFs could effectively bring cuts to the agency up to a third.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg3001x3b6q7di625gb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Employees of the National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases are among the hundreds of CDC workers who were recently &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/12/health/fired-cdc-staffers-reinstated"&gt;fired in error and reinstated&lt;/a&gt; the next day.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg3001y3b6q84bkzbnu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            And the Trump administration could use the shutdown as a strategy to delay certain reporting – such as data around vaccine uptake – even longer, Daskalakis said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg3001z3b6qrrqg1vv9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “National Immunization Survey data as well as other data streams that people tend to look at to see what’s happening with vaccine coverage are also hampered by the shutdown,” he said. Seasonal vaccination coverage is already off to a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/08/health/covid-vaccines-for-children-delay"&gt;slow start&lt;/a&gt; because federal Covid-19 vaccine recommendations came later than usual.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg300203b6qsxavkikl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It makes me concerned that [the administration] may not prioritize that, so we won’t have visibility into what’s happening on the national point of view for vaccine coverage late into the season,” Daskalakis said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg300213b6qput5i5oz@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As public health &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/09/health/rfk-approval-cdc-trust-vaccines-kff"&gt;struggles with trust&lt;/a&gt; in the US, experts say that access to timely, accurate data is critical.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh0zhgg300223b6qmhq70rh5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “To deal with an outbreak in the most successful fashion, you have to be able to communicate the latest information quickly to both medical professionals and medical institutions and to the general public,” Schaffner said. “If you don’t have the information, the communication becomes much less precise and much less useful, and that may feed the mistrust, concern and questions that the public has already about the public health system.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh208we700073b6nqktz78ge@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;em&gt;CNN’s Meg Tirrell contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 12:00:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPNjQ2REk3clBXSGpycEplRnljQnZJaXhZQVl5bnZ0eTJGQXhZc3ZqaGVMc29JNGNNV2o1VDNZWFdXMmF0YmJBalloSW1LOFdXMjF3S3B1VXVGR0FWOGpVck9JWmE1MmZ1Z0lJZC1DTnIyWUNnTDZfZlFTTDRKb0pTcDZlWmk</guid></item><item><title>灰色头发的人，快乐！灰色可能与天然癌症防御有关- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/gray-haired-people-rejoice-the-gray-might-be-related-to-a-natural-cancer-defense-2000675051</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl "&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;While graying hair might feel like just one more unpleasant symptom of aging, new research reveals that it may actually be the result of a biological process that defends against cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In a study led by the University of Tokyo and published earlier this month in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41556-025-01769-9"&gt;Nature Cell Biology&lt;/a&gt;, researchers used lab mice to investigate how a type of stem cell reacts to DNA damage, revealing a connection between hair graying and a form of skin cancer called melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;DNA damage, aging, and cancer&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Our body’s cells are continuously faced with internal and environmental agents that can cause DNA damage, which plays a role in both aging and cancer. Scientists have struggled to pin down the specifics of this role, especially how damaged stem cells impact tissue health in the long term.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/tests-procedures/bone-marrow-transplant/in-depth/stem-cells/art-20048117"&gt;Stem cells&lt;/a&gt; are cells that can self-renew (make more of themselves) and differentiate (turn into other cells). Within this context, the team specifically analyzed melanocyte stem cells (McSCs)—stem cells that produce mature melanocytes, pigment-producing cells that give color to hair and skin. In mammals, McSCs live in hair follicles in the form of immature melanoblasts (melanocytes’ precursors), where they perpetuate pigmentation.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The researchers found that, in response to DNA double-strand breaks, McSCs permanently differentiate and are then lost, which results in graying—a process called seno-differentiation. However, when McSCs come into contact with some carcinogens, they maintain their ability to self-renew and expand clonally. Simply put, they avoid seno-differentiation even when DNA is damaged, pushing McSCs “toward a tumor-prone fate,” according to a University of Tokyo &lt;a href="https://www.ims.u-tokyo.ac.jp/imsut/en/about/press/page_00079.html"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“These findings reveal that the same stem cell population can follow antagonistic fates—exhaustion or expansion—depending on the type of stress and microenvironmental signals,” Emi Nishimura, lead author of the study and a biologist at the University of Tokyo, said in the statement. “It reframes hair graying and melanoma not as unrelated events, but as divergent outcomes of stem cell stress responses.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Two potential fates&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;In other words, both results may come from how McSCs react to DNA damage, when they can go one of two ways—differentiate and leave the system (which leads to graying) or carry on dividing, where the persistence of damaged McSCs could ultimately result in a tumor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;While the researchers emphasize that their research does not indicate that graying hair prevents cancer, it does suggest seno-differentiation to be a protective pathway triggered by stress that does away with possibly detrimental cells.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“McSC fate tracking in mice revealed that McSCs undergo cellular senescence-coupled differentiation (seno-differentiation) in response to DNA double-strand breaks, resulting in their selective depletion and hair graying, and effectively protecting against melanoma,” the researchers explained in the study.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So next time you or an older family member complains about their gray hair—remember that it might be a trait that naturally protects against cancer.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 10:31:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxPY1BKMmR6RndHaVY0cno3cjJ0TU5nU1pmeFVoSzJaOE83Zmxwa2xnX2VRRW9OLWdtdFVSc25GSEhvQi1Tbm01dlJCT2ZwR3oteWpQZFJvcDA1dy1YZ3p3MkxHc2ZhUl94WHNlWDlCYUFIYkpBdHdja2dRYldkbTl6Y2doY2xyTVJINjNHeEJNS0NKaUkwZS1WejNOTk9naWd6bXROWHFDTmRqam9TUUY5aQ</guid></item><item><title>肠癌的所有体征和症状都被解释为在诊断后死亡的妈妈，她忽略了这些体征和症状- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/bowel-cancer-symptoms-australia-mum-krystal-maeyke-939510-20251022</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;A mum who tragically died from advanced bowel cancer earlier this year urged people to be aware of the symptoms of the disease in the final months of her life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Krystal Maeyke, 39, passed away on 5 July, more than two years after she first began to notice signs that something wasn't quite right with her &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;But as she was 'fit, healthy, exercising daily and eating a wholesome, balanced &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/food-and-drink"&gt;diet&lt;/a&gt;', the mum brushed off her concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"I thought it wasn't anything sinister," Krystal told the Daily Mail prior to her death, explaining that she &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/mum-stage-four-bowel-cancer-shared-symptoms-034325-20251021"&gt;ignored several symptoms&lt;/a&gt; for around three months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;These included sharp stabbing pains in her stomach, which left her 'in agony', however, she initially put them down to possible 'food intolerances'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The mum-of-one eventually reached her breaking point in May 2023, and she was airlifted from her remote home in &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/australia"&gt;Australia&lt;/a&gt; to the Alice Springs Hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Recalling what happened when she arrived at the medical facility, Krystal explained: "I underwent a series of tests. That’s when I knew it was something serious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"I was woken up later that night by a doctor whose words I will never forget. 'Krystal, I've got bad news...You have cancer'...I thought it wasn’t anything sinister."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Krystal Maeyke admitted she 'ignored' some symptoms before she received the devastating diagnosis (TikTok/@stoneinthe0cean)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'Cancer hurts'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Experts informed the mum that the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/cancer"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; had spread 'everywhere' - and had taken over her abdomen, liver and ovaries after beginning in her bowel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Krystal then realised that the disease was the source of the stabbing pains which had tormented her for months, while the strange lump she had felt under her skin was actually a tumour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Never in a million years would I think that I would have this cruel disease in my body trying to kill me," she said. "Cancer hurts."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Krystal also realised that &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/bowel-cancer"&gt;bowel cancer&lt;/a&gt; was to blame for a host of other unusual symptoms she had experienced in the run-up to her devastating diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;She recalled how she had began to feel 'tired all day, everyday' but presumed her fatigue was a result of being a 'busy mum'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Krystal admitted she also dismissed her irregular bowel movements as irritable bowel syndrome (IBS), although this is &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/symptoms-bowel-cancer-poo-tiktok-young-people-839368-20251017"&gt;a common sign of bowel cancer&lt;/a&gt; which a lot of sufferers report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;The mum had experienced stabbing pains in her stomach for months (Getty Stock Image)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'I would wake up during the night drenched in sweat'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;'Persistent night sweats' also plagued the mum in the months leading up to her diagnosis, however, she believed these were just down to the warm weather.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Krystal &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-14875445/woman-stage-four-bowel-cancer-sobs-common-symptom-ignored.html"&gt;continued&lt;/a&gt;: "I would wake up during the night drenched in sweat, enough so I had to change clothes and sheets. Some nights it would happen a few times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"It was summertime and I slept with the air con on and a fan, so I just thought it was my air con not keeping up with the summer heat. So I ignored this sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"The relationship between night sweats and cancer is unclear. However, researchers believe multiple factors may be involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Your body’s fight against cancer is one of them. Another is changes in hormone levels caused by the cancer and your body’s response."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Experts explain that time is really of the essence when it comes to bowel cancer, as the 'earlier that it’s found, the more treatable it’s likely to be'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;So if you seem to be experiencing any of the common symptoms of the illness, which can affect anyone of any age or gender, you should get checked out by your GP as soon as possible to be on the safe side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Krystal passed away on 5 July this year (TikTok/@stoneinthe0cean)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the symptoms of bowel cancer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/uk-news"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt;'s&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;leading bowel cancer &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/charity"&gt;charity&lt;/a&gt;, Bowel Cancer UK, has shared a list of key signs for you to keep an eye out for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;This &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.bowelcanceruk.org.uk/about-bowel-cancer/symptoms/"&gt;includes&lt;/a&gt;: bleeding from your bottom, blood in your poo and a change in your pooing habits - whether that's going more or less often, or experiencing diarrhoea or constipation that might come and go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Losing weight without explanation can also be a red flag, as can feeling excessively tired without reason.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Lastly, you will want to book an appointment with your doctor if you experience any strange stomach pains or if you feel a lump inside your tummy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Having these symptoms doesn’t always mean you have bowel cancer, but it’s still important to find out what’s causing them," Bowel Cancer UK says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Prior to her passing, Krystal launched a GoFundMe to raise money for her young son Maison, which can still be donated to. You can check it out &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/a-journey-of-strength"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’ve been affected by any of these issues and want to speak to someone in confidence, contact Macmillan’s Cancer Support Line on 0808 808 00 00, 8am–8pm seven days a week&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 10:03:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxQSzZUblc3c2ppSm1Dem1DSmJ2UTBjajkyQzZNandVaUlRNC1iVDdnTmtPdkxzaW9zV1g3Yy1GSDhBMXdXdzZ5VGhtQmN4VWpNUXM1RnB1dENYQ2VKNkNSNlVxNU4yakRDT2xvYXRxSjZWcXZJekZtSWR6a2xDT3NKdUNMSEZQUHVnbUNCTWk0YkpMc1JpUDRUN1A0VGU2QjJfN24xY3F3</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，心理锻炼可以逆转与衰老相关的大脑变化- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/10/22/nx-s1-5581409/mental-exercise-reverse-brain-change-aging-acetylcholine</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-94391" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                A new study finds that cognitive training can increase the levels of a key chemical messenger in the brain responsible for decision-making, and reverse a process associated with aging.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    adventtr/iStockphoto/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        adventtr/iStockphoto/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Scientists are &lt;a href="https://games.jmir.org/2025/1/e75161" target="_blank"&gt;reporting&lt;/a&gt; the first compelling evidence in people that cognitive training can boost levels of a brain chemical that typically declines with age.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A 10-week study of people 65 or older found that doing rigorous mental exercises for 30 minutes a day increased levels of the chemical messenger &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK557825/" target="_blank"&gt;acetylcholine&lt;/a&gt; by 2.3% in a brain area involved in attention and memory.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;The increase "is not huge," says &lt;a href="https://www.mcgill.ca/neurology-neurosurgery/etienne-de-villers-sidani-md" target="_blank"&gt;Étienne de Villers-Sidani&lt;/a&gt;, a neurologist at McGill University in Montreal. "But it's significant, considering that you get a 2.5% decrease per decade normally just with aging."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So, at least in this brain area, cognitive training appeared to turn back the clock by about 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The chemical change observed after intensive brain training is persuasive, says &lt;a href="https://www.bu.edu/psych/profile/michael-hasselmo-d-phil/" target="_blank"&gt;Michael Hasselmo&lt;/a&gt;, director of the Center for Systems Neuroscience at Boston University, who was not involved in the study.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It was compelling enough that I thought, 'Maybe I need to be doing this,'" he says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The result backs earlier &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/10613518/" target="_blank"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; in animals showing that environments that stimulate the brain can increase levels of certain neurotransmitters. Studies of people have suggested that cognitive training can &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/07/28/nx-s1-5477556/aging-brain-health-lifestyle-diet-exercise-social-alzheimers" target="_blank"&gt;improve thinking and memory&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Never skip brain day &lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The study, funded by the National Institutes of Health, comes amid a proliferation of online brain-training programs, including Lumosity, Elevate, Peak, CogniFit and BrainHQ.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But it has been hard to know whether these programs really work, says de Villers-Sidani, who directs the cognitive disorders clinic at McGill's Montreal Neurological Institute.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"They had a positive impact on some cognitive measures," he says, "but then the question was, how much is it changing the brain and how is it changing the brain?"&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So de Villers-Sidani and a team of researchers decided to see whether mental exercise could increase levels of acetylcholine, a neurotransmitter that's closely associated with cognitive performance.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Acetylcholine levels typically begin a gradual decline around middle age. The levels drop sharply, though, in people with Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The team studied 92 healthy people who were 65 or older.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Half the participants spent 30 minutes a day playing computer games like solitaire and Candy Crush.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The others spent the same amount of time each day doing cognitive exercises that are part of the scientifically tested program BrainHQ. The program challenges users to remember the type and location of items that appear and disappear with increasing speed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's really targeted at attention and speed of processing, and it kind of pushes you to the limit," de Villers-Sidani says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The researchers used a &lt;a href="https://jnm.snmjournals.org/content/63/Supplement_1/33S" target="_blank"&gt;special kind of PET scan&lt;/a&gt; to detect changes in acetylcholine levels in the anterior cingulate cortex, a brain region that's important for making decisions and detecting errors.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"I was not sure we would find anything, to be honest," de Villers-Sidani says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;But they did. In people who played games like solitaire, acetylcholine levels were unchanged. But in people who did cognitive training, there was a significant increase.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Acetylcholine levels also increased in other brain areas, including the hippocampus, which plays a key role in memory.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Even modest changes are meaningful, Hasselmo says, because acetylcholine does more than carry messages in the brain. It also modulates the behavior of neurons in ways that affect learning, memory and attention.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So when a person takes, say, a high dose of the motion sickness drug scopolamine — which blocks the effects of acetylcholine — things start to go awry.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"If you block the neuromodulator function in the brain, a person can't even think," Hasselmo says. "You go into a delirious state."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;On the other hand, even small increases in acetylcholine can have a "profound and notable effect" on memory and thinking in older people.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hasselmo notes that the &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8949236/" target="_blank"&gt;earliest Alzheimer's drugs&lt;/a&gt; reduced symptoms by increasing levels of acetylcholine. Now, he says, intensive brain training has the potential to achieve similar gains and stave off cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQdzVEZHRJWjFHcWxhb2FJVWpndGlES1FzTEZuYzJHWXBYNzZKNTdHVUVweG95OHdUZ3duMmNuN2g0MktTMXZUMHptTGpZZTFWcXF6aWlkNWZaUy05dDVVS3V6UkduZ0VuZFRpMTFvWXV3WTNIU1JxWld5XzNkNE5fbHJCbU53N2d3ZzNDNDV0UVlBR01oNlV2MUNOUFNGc0RxbGVN</guid></item><item><title>禽流感卷土重来--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/22/health/h5n1-bird-flu.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 09:02:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE9vQWVnTGpoaUFRaEJiSHlZYzJxaktiOFROUTUyd3AtM093el9FSnFRTnh6d25hbDFxcGFiMVR0YUxFZ3IyUUM4M3NGYmhoeDZoX0R3ZjFrVklEbzRWQXNOcHZ0MHQ1YjJFN3VfcA</guid></item><item><title>“我着火了” ：睾丸激素正在让女性恢复性欲—然后是一些-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/22/magazine/testosterone-women-health-sex-libido-menopause.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 09:00:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNRW1yWlVsYmJMalZYRy1PR1VGaGFFV0pyR0U2VFdjc2ZTVThFZ3BMX2gwbFZrbDR5TjZhMnR4VklCYWgxdHppMXhuNERRUEZ0TVVJQnlqSTgzNGxseEZ6ZHY3dHFiRExWb3liZ2oybGRJTl80MUdRT1luMFNJbUlCYXFLbVhuaEVQeTZlZy1FbXBXNi0zRG1iSnlWZw</guid></item><item><title>耐药细菌比抗生素推进得更快-有线</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/resistant-bacteria-are-advancing-faster-than-antibiotics/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;The proliferation of&lt;/span&gt; difficult-to-treat bacterial diseases represents a growing threat, according to the World Health Organization's (WHO) Global Antibiotic Resistance Surveillance Report. The &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/13-10-2025-who-warns-of-widespread-resistance-to-common-antibiotics-worldwide"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; reveals that, between 2018 and 2023, &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/tag/antibiotic-resistance"&gt;antibiotic resistance&lt;/a&gt; increased by more than 40 percent in monitored pathogen-drug combinations, with an average annual increase of 5-15 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;According to data reported by more than 100 countries to WHO's Global Antimicrobial Resistance and Use Surveillance System (GLASS), one in six laboratory-confirmed bacteria in 2023 proved &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-antibiotic-resistance-crisis-has-a-troubling-twist/"&gt;resistant to antibiotic treatment&lt;/a&gt;, all related to various common diseases globally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Superbugs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;For the first time, &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/9789240116337/"&gt;this edition of the report&lt;/a&gt; includes prevalence estimates of resistance to 22 antibiotics used to treat urinary tract, gastrointestinal, bloodstream, and gonorrheal conditions. The analysis focused on eight common pathogens: &lt;em&gt;Acinetobacter spp&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Escherichia coli&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Klebsiella pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Neisseria gonorrhoeae&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;non-typhoidal Salmonella spp&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Shigella spp&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Staphylococcus aureus&lt;/em&gt;, and &lt;em&gt;Streptococcus pneumoniae.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The results show that resistant gram-negative bacteria pose the greatest threat. Of particular note are &lt;em&gt;Escherichia coli&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Klebsiella pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt;, which are associated with bloodstream infections that can lead to sepsis, organ failure, and death. "More than 40 percent of &lt;em&gt;E. coli&lt;/em&gt; and more than 55 percent of &lt;em&gt;K. pneumoniae&lt;/em&gt; strains worldwide are now resistant to third-generation cephalosporins, the first-choice treatment for these types of infections," the report warns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;These microorganisms are joined by &lt;em&gt;Salmonella&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Acinetobacter&lt;/em&gt;, which are also developing resistance to essential drugs such as carbapenemics and fluoroquinolones. This reduces therapeutic alternatives and forces the use of last-resort antibiotics, which are often expensive and difficult to access, especially in low- and middle-income countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Medicine Lags Behind&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“Antimicrobial resistance is outpacing advances in modern medicine, threatening the health of families worldwide," said WHO director-general Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus in a statement. "We must use antibiotics responsibly, and make sure everyone has access to the right medicines, quality-assured diagnostics, and vaccines.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Optimizing surveillance systems and obtaining accurate data is an urgent task. Although there has been progress, it is still insufficient. Between 2016 and 2023, the number of countries participating in GLASS quadrupled from 25 to 104. However, 48 percent did not report data in 2023, and almost half of those that did report lacked sufficient infrastructure to generate reliable data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;WHO warns that addressing this problem must be a priority in regions such as Southeast Asia and the Eastern Mediterranean, where one in three reported infections is resistant, as well as in Africa, where one in five has the same condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOZjl1R2RhOXpfTFl6UnhRYmlvUFdfR201bm9adFJHSTZCa1NMbUpmbFRGSjJuanRvVnE2RXBxVnhNaEV3YnNFdmtudEVsTGFUeGxsaVd1a3lsUEZqV3lGc0Q4YmZINDh6WnZVcnJJX2puYzNYdVktbTRpQlcxQ2w3R1hkYWRZdHBYbElfNEl3</guid></item><item><title>斯坦福大学首位女性法学博士/医学博士候选人--《斯坦福日报》</title><link>https://stanforddaily.com/2025/10/21/stanford-sees-its-first-female-j-d-m-d-candidate/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="elementor-widget-container"&gt;
					
&lt;p&gt;Josie Pearce ’26 J.D. M.D. ’29, always knew that she wanted to be a lawyer. What she didn’t expect was to become a doctor too. Now she is the first female J.D./M.D. candidate at Stanford, according to her law school advisor Elizabeth Di Giovanni, who cited records from the registrar’s office. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As one of just a handful of J.D./M.D. candidates in Stanford’s history, she’s now carving a unique path at the intersection of law, policy and medicine.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I was one of those kids where people said, ‘You would make a good lawyer.’ I don’t know if that’s really a compliment but nonetheless, a lot of my law school friends were told that at a very young age,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Pearce graduated from Dartmouth College in 2020 with a degree in government. After graduation, she began working as a legal assistant in Boston. However, her passion for medicine soon led her to enroll in Harvard’s post-baccalaureate Premedical Program while working full-time. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I remembered back to high school, liking science, despite taking zero science classes at Dartmouth as a government major. I thought, if I did this, I would combine my passion for law, public health and health policy. That was where the dream was born,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Pearce’s interest in medical school stems from her personal experience with lupus, a chronic autoimmune disease. She has been an advocate for the disease since she was a teenager, highlighting her experiences through competition in pageants.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I’ve had lupus since I was 15, and around 2021, I completely changed my diet and lifestyle. I went plant based and started focusing on sleep and exercise. So I went from someone who was on medication and told, ‘You’re going to be on this medication for the rest of your life,’ to getting off medication,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Juggling law and medicine degrees is no small feat, but Pearce says that she has become used to the balancing act.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It was a ton of work to be working full-time at a law firm and doing a post-bacc. I would finish a whole day of work and then be like, ‘Oh no, I have to go take my chemistry exam.’ It wasn’t super normal, but I just loved it,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For Pearce, a southern California native, Stanford was an obvious fit.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Stanford produces innovators. They admit people who are so excited to do things that have never been done before and then give them every resource imaginable to go after their goals. I wanted to come to a place where I was excited to do both degrees and the institution was excited about it,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Pearce is now in her first year of medical school, and is using her credits to count toward her final year of law school. She is president-emeritus of the Veterans Legal Assistance Program at Stanford Law School and is on the Stanford Law Review. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Like a grandma, I’ve been going to bed at 8:30 p.m. recently. Ultimately, I’ve been trying to stay healthy and just focus on getting enough sleep every single night,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Through her journey, Pearce aims to start conversations about the connection between diet, lifestyle and health. Though she is unsure what career she wants to pursue after graduation, Pearce hopes to work in health policy, with a specific focus on food and nutrition. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“How are people eating? How are people best able to spend SNAP dollars? These are things I want to influence so that Americans are no longer dying from diseases that are completely preventable with lifestyle changes,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Stanford Daily</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 05:26:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNU200UURlWUJ0NDI5N3llZlczQ2dRWFJwakNWcHprMnYxTEFmWGM2M09laEJ0bloyOUV2X1Z1dnJGT25Mb3JPUjc4UW1xQ2o0czdicGdER042NzF5Z1hIQWpabU9DWjhpUVVlZWdnbGxOUWJ0cF82WUtfdUliV3oyM2VhU3NmZnhMb0VDVElhdw</guid></item><item><title>追求长寿和战胜死亡--英国《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/68958af4-7103-452c-83ec-2e85f17abf4f</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;FT Digital Edition: today’s FT, cover to cover on any device. This subscription does not include access to ft.com or the FT App.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 04:00:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE8zYWZpeUpqTXAydFN3aHBNY3gwQ3hKZ2FwYm9lVVBSeGlaTkhGajNoWC1sb29QaDRvMkp1bGpKLTZPVUFQSUx4aDEyS1lIUS1FeXdGZjZwaTNVd0VQT2ZyRE5XTW9TbERhUmJyaklLSF8</guid></item><item><title>这种未知的致命健康综合症影响近90 ％的美国成年人–你能得到吗？ - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/this-unknown-deadly-health-syndrome-affects-nearly-90-of-u-s-adults-could-you-have-it/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 03:04:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOcy1EdXhDUTBPTHh0X1pJTEFvMkJhUGRCSTFhSWw0ZjhoYUc1eG9jSUsxa1BsaHJVMERzcEd4YlVaODBIRXRtRTgxT1h3VG5HYVpUV01WdkU5ZzFfY2ZSbzBicXo2ZVZWOTZzU1ZFdlVwWG1Rcjg5ODE4Ukc1YXR1UlhWbjlseGRLdlNTZlRiTnJXeWwxckxvM1Q1V1lKTTJ3TVpNVHJ5MTY2UTVOaHJzXw</guid></item><item><title>科学家在发现流行饮料产品中的危害后发出警告： “重大担忧” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/scientists-issue-warning-finding-concerning-030000087.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;How do you take your tea? With milk, sugar, and microplastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Troubling new research published in the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0278691525004867" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Food and Chemical Toxicology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Food and Chemical Toxicology&lt;/a&gt; journal has found an abundance of microplastics in teabags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study, which tested green, sage, linden, and chamomile teas from five popular Turkish brands, found microplastic fibers in all the samples. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10389239/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Previous studies;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Previous studies&lt;/a&gt; had found microplastics in black tea, but it appears that even herbal teas are not safe from contamination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Many tea bags are made from plastic, which then leach microplastics into your drink as it brews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why are microplastics so concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Microplastics are tiny fragments of plastic less than 5 millimeters long. They are formed by larger pieces of plastic partially degrading, and these small pieces are incredibly difficult to eliminate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;On top of that, they're causing serious health concerns. These tiny fragments are shed everywhere, ending up in the air, oceans, soil, and food sources. Humans and animals then ingest and inhale the particles. Microplastics have been discovered in blood, saliva, liver, kidneys, and placenta, according to a &lt;a href="https://magazine.hms.harvard.edu/articles/microplastics-everywhere" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:report;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; from Harvard Medicine magazine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/climate-environment/2024/03/11/microplastics-health-impacts-unknown/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Washington Post;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Washington Post&lt;/a&gt; reported, microplastics have been linked to a heightened risk of heart disease, kidney disease, Alzheimer's, and fertility issues — though the science about microplastics' human health effects is still emerging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about microplastics in teabags?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The study calls the health risks linked to microplastics in tea bags a "significant concern."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The best way to reduce microplastics in your cozy cups of tea is to buy loose-leaf or find plastic-free teabags. If you do switch to loose-leaf tea, make sure to use a glass, metal, bamboo, or ceramic strainer rather than a plastic one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some brands, such as Pukka, Clipper, and 365, offer plastic-free or &lt;a href="https://www.clipper-teas.com/about/our-sustainability/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:plant-based;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;plant-based&lt;/a&gt; tea bags. Make sure to research brands' claims, as some &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2023/feb/28/tesco-accused-of-greenwashing-over-biodegradable-teabags" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:companies;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;companies&lt;/a&gt; are&lt;a href="https://www.plymouth.ac.uk/news/study-suggests-biodegradable-teabags-don-t-readily-deteriorate-in-the-environment-and-can-adversely-affect-terrestrial-species" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:greenwashing;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; greenwashing&lt;/a&gt;. Some companies may not use plastics derived from fossil fuels, but their tea bags do contain bioplastics. These are considered &lt;em&gt;less &lt;/em&gt;harmful, but it's even better for your cup of tea to be entirely plastic-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A bonus of using loose-leaf is that you can use the leaves as compost. It not only stops you from drinking avoidable microplastics, but it also stops the teabags from clogging up landfill sites, so it's a win-win situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/hacks-newsletter/?recdbbHseQFLEz9HF" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for easy tips to &lt;strong&gt;save more&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;waste less&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPSEdLLVRlNDIycVA2Z0dZcFlsSU14QlBsSmJOYjE4TDhaSm40ZXpiSlZrRDFaN05qc2xFc1hDN25ReXZZMlhzZzZPb1JzYnpGQU1iRjVyX0YyNkpnS2hOOEc3QTJ2NUh5R1FUc1BnaExZeHpzMDA1MDRYaklQSmFSLUljT1MwV1g4N1hTZzBCOTBVVk5HU3hQSmZR</guid></item><item><title>停止摄入欧米茄-3脂肪酸？研究警告称，其益处可能会“迅速”消失- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/stopping-omega-3s-benefits-may-disappear-rapidly-study-warns/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 02:39:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOS3EzUlV4a1htZDBFS3B3STNNLUNsZkpzamhZVXJXdm5LVWRrWkNTbk1IalRVbjFwZEVINzFMdTB0b284U2F3SC1QUURKOENUMmJiSzBtZHpwQU84Z1cybkJaSkNlWVVSd29lTFIwb2t6MWpoMEZGU09lMjk5aWp5amdDZGpJclVPellqSENJSQ</guid></item><item><title>新的研究表明，减肥对于逆转糖尿病前期并不是必不可少的- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/weight-loss-isnt-essential-for-reversing-prediabetes-new-study-shows</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;For people with abnormally high blood sugar levels, losing weight is &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/soups-and-shakes-diet-can-put-type-2-diabetes-into-remission-study-finds"&gt;often proposed&lt;/a&gt; as the primary approach to preventing full-blown  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="177747" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; from developing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study challenges this approach by evaluating the efficiencies of other methods to bring levels back to safer levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The international team of researchers behind the study found that the risk of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Type_2_diabetes"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; could be cut by as much as 71 percent by following dietary and exercise guidelines, even if participants lost little to no weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/vaping-increases-your-risk-of-prediabetes-study-suggests"&gt;Vaping Increases Your Risk of Prediabetes, Study Suggests&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While these findings don't dismiss the importance of losing weight in reducing &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/common-additive-combos-in-food-and-drinks-may-raise-risk-of-type-2-diabetes"&gt;diabetes risk&lt;/a&gt;, they could prompt a rethink on which outcomes to prioritize in strategies to treat prediabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Restoring a normal fasting blood sugar level is the most important goal in preventing type 2 diabetes and not necessarily the number on the scale," &lt;a href="https://www.medizin.uni-tuebingen.de/en-de/das-klinikum/pressemeldungen/meldung/744"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; diabetologist Andreas Birkenfeld, from the University of Tübingen in Germany.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study involved 1,105 people with prediabetes, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2337/db21-0526"&gt;who were advised to follow&lt;/a&gt; a 12-month program to improve their diet and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/why-exercise-is-an-important-pillar-of-any-weight-management-regimen"&gt;exercise routines to lose weight&lt;/a&gt;. Of the 234 members who hadn't lost weight by the end of the year, 51 still met the blood sugar criteria for prediabetes remission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177750" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177750" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/DiabetesChart.jpg" alt="Diabetes research chart" class="wp-image-177750 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/DiabetesChart.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/DiabetesChart-600x382.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177750" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Those who had reached prediabetes remission (R) were less likely to develop type 2 diabetes compared to those who hadn't (NR), even without weight loss. (Sandforth et al., &lt;em&gt;Nat. Med.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Follow-up checks on the participants were carried out for up to 10 years. Those in the group of 51 were some 71 percent less likely to have developed type 2 diabetes, compared to the other 183.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result is similar to the 73-percent-reduction in risk seen in participants who had &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-weight-loss-mechanism-could-one-day-trick-your-body-into-thinking-youve-exercised"&gt;lost weight&lt;/a&gt; and reached prediabetes remission after a year, compared to those who had lost weight but saw no remission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A further analysis on a subset of the volunteers revealed that the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/whether-you-carry-fat-in-your-arms-or-legs-could-predict-risk-of-dementia"&gt;location of fat storage&lt;/a&gt; in the body is a significant factor. The group whose blood sugar levels returned to normal without weight loss had a lower percentage of visceral fat (around the organs) compared to those whose blood sugar levels stayed elevated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This reflects what we know about the relationship between visceral fat and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/oby.2010.59"&gt;insulin resistance&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Exercise and a balanced diet have a positive effect on blood sugar levels, regardless of whether weight is reduced," &lt;a href="https://www.medizin.uni-tuebingen.de/en-de/das-klinikum/pressemeldungen/meldung/744"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Birkenfield. "Losing weight remains helpful, but our data suggests that it is not essential for protection against diabetes."&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_launch"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Launch" class="alignnone wp-image-177073 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers want to see the guidelines for treating prediabetes place less focus on tracking body mass, which risks discouraging those at risk of diabetes who are unsuccessful in losing weight&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In the future, guidelines for the prevention and treatment of type 2 diabetes should not only take weight into account, but above all blood glucose control and fat distribution patterns," &lt;a href="https://www.medizin.uni-tuebingen.de/en-de/das-klinikum/pressemeldungen/meldung/744"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Reiner Jumpertz-von Schwartzenberg, from the University of Tübingen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41591-025-03944-9"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 01:54:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxOUG41a1EzeGdjRE40WF8tR2J2NzE4NFVVcjdnRWJrUUI1N3gyTE5yVDBQUXdaZzBBd09uSEpTQWFjcEswLUptSjNoN0lTZlhhamkwMzdITE9GZ3NRQV9MY09icUkxYndDMG9OZEF5cTl3UDQ2d0NIZWhjeFc4RklRSmw3Y2s3VGJURWJTdk13UDd5aXdIcDJFVEpzaXlJQQ</guid></item><item><title>您的大脑比您想象的更晚达到顶峰：当思维最有效时，科学会找到合适的年龄-《经济时报》</title><link>https://m.economictimes.com/magazines/panache/your-brain-peaks-later-than-you-think-science-finds-the-right-age-when-mind-works-the-best/articleshow/124640846.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-brcount="24" class="artText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people assume that youth is the time when the mind works best, but recent research challenges this notion. While our bodies may reach their peak in early adulthood, evidence now suggests that the brain continues to develop and can perform at its highest level much later in life. Understanding when cognitive and emotional abilities peak offers a fresh perspective on aging, productivity, and leadership potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in the journal Intelligence, led by Gilles E. Gignac, Associate Professor of Psychology at the University of Western Australia, examined a wide range of psychological traits that influence real-world performance. The research focused on core cognitive abilities—including reasoning, memory span, processing speed, knowledge, and emotional intelligence—as well as five major personality traits: extraversion, emotional stability, conscientiousness, openness to experience, and agreeableness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-newpos-mgid="mgid_124640846" id="div-mgid-mid-newpos-124640846"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="E_3" class="etoro"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings revealed that several traits reach their highest levels later in life. Conscientiousness tends to peak around age 65, while emotional stability may not reach its maximum until approximately 75. Overall psychological functioning appears to crest between ages 55 and 60, before gradually declining from the mid-sixties and more sharply after age 75.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Wisdom and Moral Reasoning Improve With Age&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond personality traits, the study also highlights cognitive skills often overlooked in discussions of aging. Moral reasoning and the ability to resist cognitive biases—mental shortcuts that can distort judgment—frequently continue to strengthen into the seventies and eighties. Gignac noted that these improvements may explain why demanding leadership positions in business, politics, and other fields are frequently held by individuals in their fifties and early sixties. While certain abilities like processing speed may decline with age, gains in judgment, perspective, and decision-making help balance these changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-vdoai="vdoai_124640846" id="div-vdoai-mid-124640846"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID_INTL_300" data-loc="100" id="div-gpt-ad-858478126-1-124640846" class="country_specAD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Age Should Not Define Capability&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these positive findings, older adults still face challenges in the workforce. Age discrimination persists, even though the Age Discrimination in Employment Act of 1967 protects workers aged 40 and above. According to a survey by résumé-building platform Resume Now, nearly 90% of employees over 40 reported experiencing workplace ageism, with roughly half indicating that employers favor younger candidates. Some professions, such as airline pilots and air traffic controllers, enforce mandatory retirement ages due to the high cognitive demands of these roles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="2" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124640846" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="5" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124640846" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="3" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124640846" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s findings challenge societal assumptions about aging. History shows that many notable achievements occurred in midlife or later. Charles Darwin published On the Origin of Species at 50, Beethoven premiered his Ninth &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a rel="dofollow" href="/symphony-ltd/stocks/companyid-10473.cms" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" target="_blank"&gt;Symphony&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; at 53 while profoundly deaf, and contemporary leaders like Lisa Su have delivered significant professional breakthroughs in their fifties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gignac emphasizes that cognitive ability varies widely among individuals, and evaluations should rely on actual performance rather than age assumptions. He encourages age-inclusive hiring and retention practices, reminding society that significant achievements often occur well past what is traditionally considered “peak age.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts recommend lifestyle measures to support long-term &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/brain-health" target="_blank"&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. A diet rich in vegetables, fruits, nuts, and fish, regular physical activity, adequate sleep, and continuous learning can all help maintain cognitive functioning well into older age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While physical performance typically peaks in early adulthood, usually between ages 25 and 35, researchers note that mental and emotional abilities follow a different timeline. Rather than declining with age, key psychological traits continue developing well into middle and late adulthood. Experts also emphasize that while genetics play a role in how the brain ages, lifestyle factors make a significant difference. Regular mental challenges—such as learning new languages, playing strategic games, or engaging in creative pursuits—can help sustain memory and reasoning skills. Combined with healthy habits, these activities may delay cognitive decline and enhance overall well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also highlights how perceptions of aging often fail to match scientific evidence. Society tends to associate getting older with decline, yet data suggests that many individuals continue to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a rel="dofollow" href="/excel-realty-n-infra-ltd/stocks/companyid-29124.cms" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" target="_blank"&gt;excel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in complex thinking and emotional understanding well into their later years. Researchers believe that shifting public attitudes about age could not only reduce workplace discrimination but also encourage &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/lifelong-learning" target="_blank"&gt;lifelong learning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and engagement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;meta content="cms.article3" name="cmsei-article3"&gt;&lt;div class="inSideInd"&gt;&lt;div data-ga-action="Preference Banner InArticle Widget" data-ga-impression="Preference Banner InArticle Widget#Impressions | Preference Banner | Articleshow#url" class="Pbanner"&gt;&lt;div class="Pbannertext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img alt="ET Logo" src="https://img.etimg.com/photo/123467569.cms"&gt;&lt;p&gt; as a Reliable and Trusted News Source&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economic Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2025 01:42:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9AFBVV95cUxNUXIyZVNFYmppYkxOYVhsY2lJTDVtU19FaEQ4aG5iYzFtVHdkTTEwcURqeHFUdk5jeVRHNzBzVU9qOVl2MU1ELUVkR21yN1Z5emFmWEFJWVlKMnRRRndJaWpEWlV6NnFjelNJSExsX3ExS044cHpybEFJMWtYRjlfSWhzUEhxTzZ5TXNKTmgyX2tVV0VxcElFaGNnSklvVGdwVE1BbGVsRUV2d2N2STRrMGR6eEVIcWUxZ05fRnlVUUc5a3dNSENPM0s3bWFNLTE3RjNCWXhsb2V4eWtTX0stS2tkZXJQLWk0eTBnUFB1U0pBdXlZ</guid></item><item><title>第一个抗抑郁药副作用排行榜- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c9d65nqgd5zo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Effects of antidepressants on physical health ranked for first time&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;James Gallagher&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Health and science correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/61da/live/cd0dd240-ade0-11f0-8623-dd1b3d489f0f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/61da/live/cd0dd240-ade0-11f0-8623-dd1b3d489f0f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/61da/live/cd0dd240-ade0-11f0-8623-dd1b3d489f0f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/61da/live/cd0dd240-ade0-11f0-8623-dd1b3d489f0f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/61da/live/cd0dd240-ade0-11f0-8623-dd1b3d489f0f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/61da/live/cd0dd240-ade0-11f0-8623-dd1b3d489f0f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/61da/live/cd0dd240-ade0-11f0-8623-dd1b3d489f0f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/61da/live/cd0dd240-ade0-11f0-8623-dd1b3d489f0f.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Young woman is sat with a glass of water in one hand and a white tablet in the open palm of the other. She is looking down so you can't see her eyes and her hair is tied up. She is sat on a grey sofa in what looks like an open plan living room with the kitchen behind her. " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Side effects of different antidepressants have been ranked for the first time, revealing huge differences between drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Academics looked at the impact medications had on patients in the first eight weeks after starting treatment, with some causing patients to gain up to 2kg in weight or vary heart rate by as much as 21 beats every minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Around eight million people in the UK take antidepressants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Researchers warned the gulf in side effects could affect people's health and whether they could stick to their prescription.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;They said nobody reading this should stop their treatment, but have called for antidepressants to be closely matched to the needs of each person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There are big differences between [antidepressants] and this is important not just for individual patients, but large numbers of people are taking them, so even modest changes could have a big effect across the whole population," said researcher Prof Oliver Howes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;We've always known antidepressants affect physical health. The study by King's College London and the University of Oxford is the first to produce a ranking so the effects of medicines can be easily compared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The team analysed 151 studies of 30 drugs commonly used in depression, involving more than 58,500 patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Not everybody develops side effects but, on average, the results &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(25)01293-0/fulltext" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;published in the Lancet medical journal&lt;/a&gt; showed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;An eight-week prescription of agomelatine was linked to a 2.4kg drop in weight compared with maprotiline, which led to nearly 2kg of weight gain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;A difference of 21 beats per minute between fluvoxamine, which slowed the heart, and nortriptyline, which sped it up&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;An 11 mmHg difference in blood pressure between nortriptyline and doxepin&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Clearly no two antidepressants are built the same," said Dr Atheeshaan Arumuham, from King's College London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Those differences can stack up in ways that become clinically important, including an increased risk of heart attack or stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It means even people with the same diagnosis could be better suited to different antidepressants depending on their own preferences and other health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Which antidepressant is best for me?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In a hypothetical scenario, Sarah, 32, John, 44, and Jane, 56, have all received the same depression diagnosis and have been recommended antidepressants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But they each want to avoid different side effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For Sarah, the priority is avoiding weight gain, while John already has high blood pressure and Jane has raised cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Dr Toby Pillinger, who worked through the examples for the BBC, says each would be recommended a different medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;b id="dr-toby-pillinger-says:" class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;Dr Toby Pillinger says: &lt;/b&gt;Sarah should have an antidepressant that avoids weight gain, such as agomelatine, sertraline or venlafaxine rather than amitriptyline or mirtazapine which are more likely to increase weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;b id="dr-toby-pillinger-says:" class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;Dr Toby Pillinger says: &lt;/b&gt;John should avoid drugs such as venlafaxine, amitriptyline or nortriptyline which raise blood pressure, and would be better suited to citalopram, escitalopram and paroxetine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;b id="dr-toby-pillinger-says:" class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;Dr Toby Pillinger says: &lt;/b&gt;For Jane, some antidepressants are linked to higher cholesterol, including venlafaxine, duloxetine and paroxetine, so she might steer clear of those. Citalopram or escitalopram are more neutral on cholesterol and could suit her better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Push for 'generic, cheap medications' &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It is too simplistic to say there are good and bad antidepressants, the researchers say. Even though amitriptyline increases weight, heart rate and blood pressure it also helps with pain and struggling to sleep. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Overall, the most prescribed class of antidepressants - SSRIs such as paroxetine, citalopram, escitalopram and sertraline - tended to have fewer physical side effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Fluoxetine - an SSRI that is also called Prozac - was linked to a drop in weight and higher blood pressure, in the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Prof Andrea Cipriani from the University of Oxford said it was "impossible" to say how many of the millions of people being prescribed antidepressants should be on a different drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;However, he said there had been a push for "generic, cheap medications" that meant 85% of antidepressant prescriptions in the UK were for just three drugs: the SSRIs citalopram, sertraline and fluoxetine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He said implementing the findings of this report would see "the 85% reduce dramatically" with "more people accessing better treatments".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The researchers are developing &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.psymatik.com" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;a free online tool&lt;/a&gt; to help doctors and patients choose the right drug. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;However, that would still require a significant change in culture within the NHS. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The study also only analysed what happened eight weeks after starting treatment. Dr Pillinger said "complimentary data" meant they expected the short-term changes "will persist" but this still needs to be properly tested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Dr Prasad Nishtala, from the University of Bath which was not involved in the study, said the findings were "novel and valuable".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He said: "In a real-world setting, where patients often receive antidepressants for months or years, the cumulative risks are likely to be higher, particularly among those with chronic depression."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:53:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9JSXNjajBYMk9fZmJTZ2ZreWZnVl9IMC1SR2x5VTBlLU0tZi1DYlRKNlZzT09OcERnNG5KRERsQVBnQ1VUWXFLMGQ4ZTlESVJZVkh6VjhxbGw0Z9IBX0FVX3lxTFBCUDIxN05tX181WWFZQTVrSDJ1WUlFc3BaRGY5QjJaaXdHTU55aXpiSW43b0VNWTQ5NUN1U2VQdm44ZDN1ZUZNSG1IRXA5UndEYXhwNVJ1NHZoR05XOUZn</guid></item><item><title>同性恋者和他们分享了一个令人惊讶的地方，这个地方实际上是完美的巡游地点- Queerty</title><link>https://www.queerty.com/gays-theys-share-the-surprising-place-thats-actually-the-perfect-cruising-spot-20251021/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="cf-column"&gt;
            &lt;h2 data-translate="blocked_why_headline"&gt;Why have I been blocked?&lt;/h2&gt;

            &lt;p data-translate="blocked_why_detail"&gt;This website is using a security service to protect itself from online attacks. The action you just performed triggered the security solution. There are several actions that could trigger this block including submitting a certain word or phrase, a SQL command or malformed data.&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Queerty</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxQMFByVGFJNzZFQXdvSmZCUXFhV29RUWpRSGNIUXR5eExLVW83d1BWb0VMS1FrUGtCbzhXNzJCVkpNSjIxZ0trNDRkVmtNMF9mbWxnNDBpdWQteFpIaXdlRFl6SGZnYmJHUFRIQUZFaUxPOWgtMXcxZ3gzS3g4bktZdDl6b2o5SXh1azRuOXhqM1BRRWJyajhFQ0VjSC1xZjgzSVlpOVVxRlNlb1VpLVhPcnZ3</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，抗抑郁药的副作用因药物而异-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/21/well/antidepressant-side-effects.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 22:46:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFB2bDhPeWxEZjZlcVZLT3QxMzdmRGVFRGw5NG5DYm5CdEY5ZVV0Vko3eFUtOURlS2QyV3ltWDBHdGFINlpNRFRFeHA3V3BjNDNrZmZYYmVLVmFyX2V5ZFI3Nk1XVF9TZDBHQnNtSDNpaVJYY1pQcUQ0YmpfNlQ</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，每周步行4000步可降低老年人过早死亡的风险-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/oct/21/walking-just-4000-steps-once-week-cuts-risk-early-death-study</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Older people who only walk 4,000 daily steps once a week still reduce their risk of dying early by a quarter, a study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Staying active is known to bring a wide range of health benefits. But many people in their 60s, 70s and beyond may struggle for a variety of reasons to maintain the step count they used to reach. Until now it has been unclear how much people need to do as they age to reap the rewards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Research led by Harvard University has some answers. The large prospective study examined not only how many steps older people took but how often they reached step targets across the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Researchers found achieving 4,000 steps per day on one or two days a week was associated with a significantly lower risk of death and lower risk of cardiovascular disease (CVD), compared with not reaching this level on any day. The findings were published in the &lt;a href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/lookup/doi/10.1136/bjsports-2025-110311" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;British Journal of Sports Medicine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study followed 13,547 American women over 62, with 72 the average age. They wore activity trackers for seven consecutive days between 2011 and 2015 and were followed for over a decade. None had heart disease or cancer at the start of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the monitoring period to the end of 2024, 1,765 women died and 781 developed heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Clocking up at least 4,000 steps a day on one or two days of the week was associated with a 26% lower risk of death from all causes and a 27% lower risk of dying from heart disease, compared with not reaching this threshold on any day of the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;For those achieving this step count on at least three days of the week, the lower risk of death from any cause increased to 40%, but remained at 27% for the risk of cardiovascular death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The researchers said the important takeaway was that it is the amount people walk, rather than the number of days on which they achieve a certain number of steps, that is most important for reducing the risk of premature death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is no “best” way to take your steps, they added. The key thing is just to get your steps in. They concluded that a “greater number of steps, regardless of daily patterns, is associated with better health outcomes”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;On average, the women took 5,615 steps a day. This was an observational study, and as such no firm conclusions could be drawn about cause and effect. There were also several limitations to the research, notably that physical activity was assessed for only one week, and only in women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Nevertheless, the researchers wrote: “The present study … suggests that frequency of meeting daily step thresholds is not critical (even 1to 2 days a week of [more than] 4,000 steps a day was related to lower mortality and CVD), and that step volume is more important than the frequency of meeting daily step thresholds in the older population.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;They added: “An important translational implication of these findings is that since step volume is the important driver of the inverse associations, there is no ‘better’ or ‘best’ pattern to take steps; individuals can undertake [physical activity] in any preferred pattern (eg ‘slow and steady’ v ‘bunched patterns’) for lower mortality and CVD risk, at least among older women.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;They concluded: “These findings provide additional evidence for considering including step metrics in the next [physical activity] guidelines, and that ‘bunching’ steps is a viable option for health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 22:39:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxOOVFsNkMycFFsZGRmTW5CdUhhV0owa2V1VDRyWGJRSDZwa1cxN1h2WTlPTW0tR2VQQkZQWVd6SlhjOHJBVTdqaWNQLURHT2ZaY210XzR3czNTQkRjWTdUWk5rMDNKU0pMT053dG05aFlZaGNvcmNRX0xobk9yYnJXaXVzUVh6eXdwYlpjWmdfT1VBNTd1aVFMUURsWEJSeXlOVU13ZjdPVUwzSXd6bUE</guid></item><item><title>根据科学，每天感觉更好的秘诀- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/the-secret-to-feeling-better-every-day-according-to-science/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feeling better does not always require big changes. A week of five to ten minute practices improved emotional well-being and sleep while lowering perceived stress in 17,598 participants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The program asked people to complete simple micro-acts, such as making a gratitude list, celebrating a friend’s success, or watching a short nature video. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gains grew with consistent participation, and the largest benefits often appeared among people facing financial strain or lower social status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-tiny-actions-matter"&gt;Why tiny actions matter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elissa Epel, of the University of California, San Francisco (&lt;a href="https://www.ucsf.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UCSF&lt;/a&gt;), co-authored the study and has examined how stress shapes health for years. Her team’s results fit with evidence that brief positive activities can shift emotions and thinking in reliable ways. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large &lt;a href="https://bmcpublichealth.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/1471-2458-13-119" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt;, found that positive psychology interventions can raise &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/how-does-gut-brain-communication-affect-emotional-well-being/"&gt;well-being&lt;/a&gt; and reduce depressive symptoms. Effects were small to moderate, which is typical for low burden approaches that are easy to keep doing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ggia.berkeley.edu/bigjoy?" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The Big Joy Project&lt;/a&gt; also tracked happiness agency, the sense that your emotions are within your control, and used a single group pre-post design, which is a before-and-after measurement approach without a comparison group, to evaluate changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-the-seven-days-asked"&gt;What the seven days asked&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One day centered on gratitude, a practice with evidence from a classic randomized &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/12585811/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;trial&lt;/a&gt;, showing that listing blessings can lift mood and life satisfaction. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another day asked participants to do something kind for someone they already interact with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An awe component used a short nature video followed by a few reflection prompts. The emotion of &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25984788/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;awe&lt;/a&gt; is linked to a smaller sense of self and a greater willingness to help others, which can strengthen social connection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other days focused on sharing a moment of celebration, ranking values, and noticing daily joy. Each activity took under ten minutes, including brief check-ins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-who-benefited-most"&gt;Who benefited most&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benefits were not limited to people with many resources. The largest average gains appeared among participants reporting financial strain, lower education, lower subjective social status, or identifying as Black or Hispanic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Younger adults showed larger increases in emotional well-being and larger drops in perceived stress than older adults. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A clear &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/just-one-minute-of-short-energy-burst-exercise-every-day-can-add-years-to-your-life/"&gt;dose-response pattern&lt;/a&gt;, a trend where stronger participation leads to stronger results, pointed to consistency as a key ingredient, with full participation outperforming partial participation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-small-moments-reshape-the-brain"&gt;How small moments reshape the brain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have long known that emotional habits can change the neural pathways that govern mood and attention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When people focus on positive emotions, activity increases in the prefrontal cortex and decreases in the amygdala. These shifts may explain why simple joyful actions can help people feel calmer and more in control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Short bursts of joy may also influence the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/what-happens-to-the-body-and-mind-during-extreme-sports/"&gt;parasympathetic nervous system&lt;/a&gt;, the body’s built-in relaxation network that slows heart rate and supports recovery after stress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, repeating small positive behaviors can strengthen these calming responses, much like short workouts strengthen muscles. The biological effects may be subtle each day but meaningful when practiced regularly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-this-does-not-claim"&gt;What this does not claim&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The design did not include a control group, which means other explanations like expectation effects or outside life events cannot be ruled out. A randomized controlled trial will be important to test durability and mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The week of micro-acts is not a treatment for major depression, anxiety disorders, or trauma. It is a low cost practice that can help daily life feel more manageable while other supports are pursued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Joy is a skill they can build,” said Epel. That perspective matches the finding that people reported greater control over their own happiness after the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-to-put-this-to-work"&gt;How to put this to work&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pick one micro-act that fits naturally into your day. Do it for one week at the same time to create a steady cue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keep the action so easy that it takes five minutes. If you want more momentum, stack a second micro-act after it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Track whether your stress feels a notch lower, whether you fall asleep a bit faster, or whether your patience holds a little longer. If the practice helps, keep it and rotate a new one next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are under care for a mental health condition, check with your clinician before changing your routine. These practices can complement therapy and medication but do not replace them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-where-research-goes-next"&gt;Where research goes next&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future work needs randomization, follow up, and tests of what parts carry the weight. Hints point to shifts in attention, values, and social connection as likely drivers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dose matters here, and so does access. A short, free program that reaches many people could play a small but real role in &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/living-alone-in-america-an-escalating-public-health-crisis/"&gt;public health&lt;/a&gt;, if results hold up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40466105/#full-view-affiliation-2" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Medical Internet Research&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 21:55:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQTEZsTmJVS3dpQVpNUERvSGFzVk5nazJaYTRWd2ZlUGtYNnJJakd1OThTaXJka1dMZlBwU2g2ZFdNM1ZFYmxvWWdYVWx5VF9fNmV1akZBT2JIc1k5NE1iay1ObnJDT1EzZExrYWZEX3NrNFlWSzhKaWkzaU83c2hJbTZwUGt5dm03Q2R4dTlJZ3I</guid></item><item><title>长期生酮饮食可能会损害您的身体-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/long-term-keto-health-29841/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study reveals that while the ketogenic diet can prevent weight gain, it may cause severe long-term metabolic problems. Researchers found that mice on a long-term keto diet developed fatty liver disease and impaired blood sugar regulation due to stressed pancreatic cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These issues were especially pronounced in males, though females showed partial resistance to liver fat buildup. The findings highlight the need for caution and medical supervision before adopting keto for long-term use, as some negative effects may reverse after stopping the diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Metabolic Strain:&lt;/strong&gt; Long-term keto increased fat accumulation in the liver and disrupted insulin secretion.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sex Differences:&lt;/strong&gt; Male mice developed more severe fatty liver disease than females.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reversible Effects:&lt;/strong&gt; Some metabolic issues improved after stopping the diet, offering hope for recovery.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University of Utah&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A study published in &lt;em&gt;Science Advances&lt;/em&gt; by University of Utah Health researchers sheds light on the long-term effects of the ketogenic diet, raising important questions about its safety and efficacy for improving metabolic health. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the ketogenic diet was historically used to treat epilepsy, it has recently gained popularity for weight loss and management of conditions like obesity and type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study, performed with mice, demonstrates that the diet can have potentially dangerous impacts on metabolic health, including how the body processes fats and carbohydrates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-113502"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a person eating a keto diet." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/10/ket-health-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Despite this apparent benefit, mice fed the ketogenic diet developed severe metabolic complications, with some changes starting within days. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A ketogenic diet is a very high-fat, very low-carbohydrate diet that was originally used to treat epilepsy. The idea is that the ketogenic diet induces ketosis, a metabolic state that produces ketone bodies, which act as an alternative brain fuel, stabilizing neuronal activity and reducing seizures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this way, the diet mimics starvation, where reduced glucose availability also limits seizures, while ketones derived from fat provide the main energy source for the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, the diet has also been promoted for weight loss and metabolic health, but most studies have focused on short-term outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’ve seen short-term studies and those just looking at weight, but not really any studies looking at what happens over the longer term or with other facets of metabolic health,” said Molly Gallop, PhD, now assistant professor of anatomy and physiology at Earlham College, who led the study as a postdoctoral fellow in nutrition and integrative physiology at U of U Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The keto diet prevents weight gain&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;To address this gap, Gallop and her colleagues conducted a long-term study in mice, placing male and female adults on one of four diets: a high-fat Western diet, a low-fat high-carbohydrate diet, a classic ketogenic diet where almost all calories come from fat, and a protein-matched low-fat diet. The mice were allowed to eat as much as they wanted for nine months or longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Throughout the study, the team monitored body weight, food intake, blood fat profiles, liver fat accumulation, and the levels of blood sugar and insulin. They also investigated which genes were active in the pancreatic cells that produce insulin. Finally. they used advanced microscopy to uncover the cellular mechanisms underlying observed metabolic changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ketogenic diet successfully prevented weight gain in both sexes compared to the high-fat Western diet. Mice on the ketogenic diet maintained significantly lower body weights, with weight gain primarily attributed to increased fat mass rather than lean mass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Keto is linked to fatty liver disease&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite this apparent benefit, mice fed the ketogenic diet developed severe metabolic complications, with some changes starting within days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One thing that’s very clear is that if you have a really high-fat diet, the lipids have to go somewhere, and they usually end up in the blood and the liver,” said Amandine Chaix, PhD, assistant professor of nutrition and integrative physiology at U of U Health and senior author on the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The accumulation of fat in the liver, known as fatty liver disease, is a hallmark of metabolic disease associated with obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The ketogenic diet was definitely not protective in the sense of fatty liver disease,” Chaix added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers observed notable differences in how male and female mice responded to the ketogenic diet: males developed severe fatty liver and had worse liver function, a key marker of metabolic disease, while females had no significant buildup of fat in the liver. The scientists plan to explore why female mice didn’t get fatty liver disease in future research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h1 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Keto diet may harm blood sugar regulation&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also revealed a paradox in blood sugar regulation. After two to three months on the ketogenic diet, mice had low levels of blood sugar and insulin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The problem is that when you then give these mice a little bit of carbs, their carb response is completely skewed,” Chaix said. “Their blood glucose goes really high for really long, and that’s quite dangerous.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mice couldn’t regulate their blood sugar properly because cells in the pancreas weren’t secreting enough insulin, the researchers discovered. Probably due to chronically high levels of fat in their environment, pancreas cells showed signs of stress, unable to move proteins around like they should.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers think that the impaired blood sugar regulation is caused by this cellular stress, but identifying the exact mechanism is a future research direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, problems with blood sugar regulation reversed when mice went off the ketogenic diet, suggesting that at least some metabolic issues may not be permanent if the diet is stopped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While mice and humans differ, the findings reveal previously unexplored long-term negative metabolic health risks that individuals considering the ketogenic diet should take into account. “I would urge anyone to talk to a health care provider if they’re thinking about going on a ketogenic diet,” Gallop cautioned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;This work was supported by the National Institutes of Health, including the National Institute on Aging (grant number R01AG065993), the National Institute of Diabetes and Digestive and Kidney Diseases (grant numbers P30DK020579, F32DK137475, T32DK110966, DK108833, and DK112826), the National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute (grant number HL170575), and the National Cancer Institute (grant number R01CA222570).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Work was also supported by the Damon Runyon-Rachleff Innovation Award (DR 61-20) and the American Cancer Society (RSG-22-014-01-CCB). Content is solely the responsibility of the authors and does not necessarily represent the official views of the National Institutes of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1761082838978"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What did the study find about the long-term effects of the ketogenic diet?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: The diet prevented weight gain but led to fatty liver disease, insulin secretion problems, and poor blood sugar regulation in mice after several months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1761082850526"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Why are these findings significant about the keto diet?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: They reveal that keto’s metabolic impact may worsen over time, highlighting potential long-term health risks that short-term studies overlook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1761082881759"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Are the effects permanent?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: Some problems reversed after the mice stopped the diet, suggesting that while damaging, the effects might not be irreversible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this diet, metabolism, and health research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b3c0dcc3dbdad29dd5c1dad6c0d6ddf3dbc0d09dc6c7d2db9dd6d7c6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Sophia Friesen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://hsc.utah.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Utah&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Sophia Friesen – University of Utah&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1126/sciadv.adx2752" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;A long-term ketogenic diet causes hyperlipidemia, liver dysfunction, and glucose intolerance from impaired insulin secretion in mice&lt;/a&gt;” by Molly Gallop et al. &lt;em&gt;Science Advances&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A long-term ketogenic diet causes hyperlipidemia, liver dysfunction, and glucose intolerance from impaired insulin secretion in mice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ketogenic diets (KDs)—very-low-carbohydrate and very-high-fat diets—have gained popularity as therapeutic against obesity and type 2 diabetes. However, their long-term effects on metabolic health remain understudied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here, we show that, in male and female mice, a KD protects against weight gain and induces weight loss but over time leads to the development of hyperlipidemia, hepatic steatosis, and severe glucose intolerance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike mice on conventional high-fat diet, KD-fed mice remain insulin sensitive and display low-insulin levels. Hyperglycemic clamp and ex vivo glucose-stimulated insulin secretion assays revealed systemic and cell-intrinsic impairments in insulin secretion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transcriptomic profiling of islets from KD-fed mice indicated endoplasmic reticulum (ER)/Golgi stress and disrupted ER-Golgi protein trafficking, which were confirmed by electron microscopy showing a dilated Golgi network consistent with defective insulin granule trafficking and secretion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, these results suggest that long-term KD leads to multiple aberrations of metabolic parameters that caution their systematic use as a health-promoting dietary intervention.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 21:52:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiaEFVX3lxTE9fRHNNYkFBTUI1VTh1dEFSX1NXc29QaDRER3lWMVNEYTU1c0xwbWJ1ZHoxY2FWVEd0SjZ2dmFSRjllblBtZWFUSnU2QUNzM0lUUS1pbGlxYUJDNlp1R3dmam4ybGFpQTUw</guid></item></channel></rss>