<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>粒子物理学是死亡、垂死还是只是困难？ -广达杂志</title><link>https://www.quantamagazine.org/is-particle-physics-dead-dying-or-just-hard-20260126/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post__content wysiwyg p theme__anchors--underline "&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;This brain drain appears to be real. I spoke to Jared Kaplan, co-founder of Anthropic, the company behind the chatbot Claude. He was a physicist the last time we spoke. As a grad student at Harvard in the 2000s, he worked with the renowned theorist Nima Arkani-Hamed to open up the new directions in amplitude research that are being actively pursued today. But Kaplan left the field in 2019. “I started working on AI because it seemed plausible to me that … AI was going to make progress faster than almost any field in science historically,” he said. AI would be “the most important thing to happen while we’re alive, maybe one of the most important things to happen in the history of science. And so it seemed obvious that I should work on it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for the future of particle physics, AI makes worrying about it now rather pointless, in Kaplan’s view. “I think that it’s kind of irrelevant what we plan on a 10-year timescale, because if we’re building a collider in 10 years, AI will be building the collider; humans won’t be building it. I would give like a 50% chance that in two or three years, theoretical physicists will mostly be replaced with AI. Brilliant people like Nima Arkani-Hamed or Ed Witten, AI will be generating papers that are as good as their papers pretty autonomously. … So planning beyond this couple-year timescale isn’t really something I think about very much.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-158361 size-full" src="https://www.quantamagazine.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/QUALIA-Separator-2-2.png" alt="" srcset="https://www.quantamagazine.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/QUALIA-Separator-2-2.png 1300w, https://www.quantamagazine.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/QUALIA-Separator-2-2-520x17.png 520w, https://www.quantamagazine.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/QUALIA-Separator-2-2-768x25.png 768w, https://www.quantamagazine.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/QUALIA-Separator-2-2-98x3.png 98w" sizes="(max-width: 1300px) 100vw, 1300px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cari Cesarotti, a postdoctoral fellow in the theory group at CERN, is skeptical about that future. She notices chatbots’ mistakes, and how they’ve become too much of a crutch for physics students. “AI is making people worse at physics,” she said. “What we need is humans to read textbooks and sit down and think of new solutions to the hierarchy problem.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cesarotti was a high school junior when the Higgs boson was discovered. She grew up near Fermilab, the U.S. national lab in Illinois that houses the Tevatron, which was the world’s highest-energy particle collider before the LHC. (The top quark was discovered there in 1995.) This proximity taught her that a particle physicist was a thing you could be. Later, it turned out to be &lt;em&gt;her&lt;/em&gt; thing. “What are the fundamental building blocks of the universe — those were the questions that I was most interested in knowing the answer to,” she told me. “But what people said was, ‘Particle physics is dead. Don’t do this.’”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It may have been a fair warning; Cesarotti has yet to land a permanent job as a rising particle physicist. The subfield has continued to shrink, she and others said, as faculty hiring committees and grad students go in other directions. “Definitely all this rhetoric that there was nothing to be found and you should give up on it — people listened,” she said. “And of course that means there are fewer people. It becomes a self-fulfilling prophecy. If you’re pushing all these talented people out of trying to solve these problems into a field that it’s easier to make an impact on, then you’re setting yourself up for failure.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cesarotti echoed a sentiment I’d heard from others, which sounds correct to me as well: “Particle physics isn’t dead; it’s just hard.” It’s hard to know what to think about or look for. But the most devoted particle physicists are thinking and looking all the same.&lt;/p&gt;
        
        
&lt;p&gt;“It was easy for 125 years,” Strassler said. “One thing led to the next. That lucky century has, for now, at least in the medium term, come to an end. That could change tomorrow, or next century, or who knows.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A hint of a new lightweight particle could, in theory, show up at the LHC, or in some other experiment. Strassler is particularly excited about the study of &lt;a href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/the-first-nuclear-clock-will-test-if-fundamental-constants-change-20240904/"&gt;radioactive thorium-229 decay&lt;/a&gt;, which could reveal variations in the fundamental constants. I’m slightly partial to &lt;a href="https://www.quantamagazine.org/he-seeks-mystery-magnetic-fields-with-his-quantum-compass-20240517/"&gt;experiments looking for “axions,”&lt;/a&gt; dark matter candidates that are so lightweight that they can act a little like light itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the theory side, an obvious solution to the hierarchy problem could drop naturally out of the geometry behind scattering amplitudes. Or, if Kaplan is right, AI systems might someday suggest powerful new ideas for how the 25 particles of the Standard Model fit into a more comprehensive pattern — a possibility I didn’t foresee back when the crisis began.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clearly, further progress toward the truth remains possible in particle physics. But there’s no discovery guarantee. I’ve had more than 13 years to think about it, and it remains a disturbing prospect: All the empirical clues we can glean about nature’s fundamental laws and building blocks might already be in hand. The universe may plan on keeping the rest of its secrets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Quanta Magazine</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:39:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPVEdQZEJYVi1Cb3Y0MUZkSC1fS3dIcnItTS1qcFlQbHEzTEI4WEd0WUxDOEhVN3NJRXdCeWJBRTh5cHVhN2VQOUVoSXBzVEZ4QlRFaDNqaVNuT2JnS1o2SUdJbUJ0NlVlSzdwR1JRbWFpeHMybjhvVFBKYm5iZTU0cHNaS2lfSThEM3BBMw</guid></item><item><title>英国失去麻疹消除地位-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cgjw0xegxglo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;b id="the-uk-has-lost-its-measles-elimination-status,-the-world-health-organization-has-announced." class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;The UK has lost its measles elimination status, the World Health Organization has announced.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The move was based on the spread of cases in 2024 when there were 3,600 suspected cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Elimination status means there is no sustained transmission so this decision was largely expected, given the scale of the outbreaks in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;There were more than 1,000 cases last year as well. The move is also a reflection of the fact vaccination rates are below the 95% threshold required to achieve herd immunity - when enough people in a community are vaccinated against a disease, making it hard for the pathogen to spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The UK was first declared measles-free in 2017, but lost the status two years later, before regaining it after spread of the virus was almost halted completely in 2021 - although that was mainly because social distancing during the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Outbreaks in late 2023 meant measles started spreading more quickly again, leading to the surge in cases in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Vaccination uptake at the end of 2024 was 92% for the first dose and just below 85% for the second dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Vanessa Saliba, consultant epidemiologist at UKHSA, said: "Infections can return quickly when childhood vaccine uptake falls - measles elimination is only possible if all eligible children receive two MMRV doses before school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The NHS is making vaccination easier, including offering the second MMRV dose earlier at a new 18-month appointment to boost uptake and support elimination goals."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said older children and adults could still get vaccinated as the NHS offered catch-up jabs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Bharat Pankhania, from the University of Exeter, said: "Measles is an infection that can be prevented by vaccine - and it's extremely concerning that in the UK we now have pockets of low or no vaccine uptake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We urgently need to remedy this situation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Pankhania said that needed to include easier access to GPs, more health visitors who can immunise babies in their homes and countering wrong information about vaccine safety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 15:04:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1hU2xMQkJDS1JzekpXblFxdDJ4Z0xMTjMzR0xXTGVBX200RlpmNEpuUzhEbzN1OEpQaDRSSHVlM2ZqLW1sdlRCb0JITkMwV3JmQmdaNU8xSmw2dw</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现这项活动“显著”降低了心脏病、糖尿病风险- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/scientists-activity-significantly-lowered-heart-133000190.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A new study examined the health data of people with cardiovascular kidney metabolic syndrome (CKM) and how exercise improved their conditions’ outlook.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CKM is a term to describe the interconnection of heart disease, diabetes, and chronic kidney disease.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Even light physical activity in certain individuals proved to lower the risk of early death.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no shortage of studies on the benefits of exercise for heart and metabolic health. Researchers have found that workouts as simple as &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a69930051/walking-adds-up-to-11-years-to-life-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:walking may add 11 years to life;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;walking may add 11 years to life&lt;/a&gt;, and others have found that even 30-minute bursts of movement help &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a64889455/exercise-reduce-recurring-heart-attack-risk-study/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lower recurring heart attack risk;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;lower recurring heart attack risk&lt;/a&gt;. A new study adds more to the evidence: Scientists discovered that even light physical activity, such as walking or house chores, has the power to “significantly” lower heart disease, diabetes, and mortality risk in people with cardiovascular kidney metabolic syndrome (CKM).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meet the Experts: &lt;a href="https://www.nychealthandhospitals.org/doctors/thachil-rosy/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Rosy Thachil, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Rosy Thachil, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, cardiologist at NYC Health + Hospitals in Elmhurst; &lt;a href="https://medicine.iu.edu/faculty/61331/breathett-khadijah" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Khadijah Breathett, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Khadijah Breathett, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, executive director of the Krannert Cardiovascular Research Center at the Indiana University School of Medicine; and &lt;a href="https://manhattancardiology.com/team/dr-randy-gould/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Randy Gould, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Randy Gould, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a doctor with Manhattan Cardiology and &lt;a href="https://www.labfinder.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:LabFinder;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;LabFinder&lt;/a&gt; contributor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CKM is a term used to describe the interconnection between cardiovascular disease, type 2 diabetes, and chronic kidney disease, according to the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39705194/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:National Institutes of Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/a&gt; (NIH). An estimated 25% of participants in the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey, which spanned from 1990 to 2020, had at least one CKM condition. CKM is thought to be linked to excess or dysfunctional adipose tissue (fat), which leads to inflammation that may cause organ tissue damage and insulin resistance, leading to heart trouble, type 2 diabetes, and related issues. CKM syndrome is classified into four stages based on clinical signs and risk factors that include chronic inflammation, family history of diabetes or kidney disease, mental health and sleep disorders, and others, per the NIH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the study, published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/JAHA.125.046271" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Journal of the American Heart Association;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Journal of the American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, researchers analyzed the health data of more than 7,200 people over 20 with CKM of various stages between 2003 and 2006. The sample group wore accelerometers (activity trackers) to record their daily movement and its intensity. Approximately 14 years after the exercise data were recorded, researchers followed up on participants’ health and noted the severity of CKM. Overall, they found light physical activity to be increasingly linked to a longer life among patients with advancing stages of the condition. They also found that increasing light activity by an hour every day was linked to about a 14% to 20% lower risk of dying early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Light movement can replace sedentary time, improve circulation, support glucose handling, &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a65912601/ways-to-lower-blood-pressure-naturally/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lower blood pressure;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;lower blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, and reduce &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a38595773/what-is-insulin-resistance-syndrome/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:insulin resistance;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;insulin resistance&lt;/a&gt;—small physiologic wins that add up when repeated daily, especially in advanced disease,” explains &lt;a href="https://www.nychealthandhospitals.org/doctors/thachil-rosy/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Rosy Thachil, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Rosy Thachil, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, cardiologist at NYC Health + Hospitals in Elmhurst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though it’s important to note the limitations of the study. This was not a clinical trial; patients were not randomized to different levels of exercise, and some had more ability than others. “Behaviorally motivated patients may have been more likely to participate, and less sick patients may have been more likely to participate,” says &lt;a href="https://medicine.iu.edu/faculty/61331/breathett-khadijah" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Khadijah Breathett, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Khadijah Breathett, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, executive director of the Krannert Cardiovascular Research Center at the Indiana University School of Medicine. “This influences the findings.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the participants studied were already diagnosed with CKM, most of their active time was light and became the “main lever,” as Dr. Thachil calls it, in maintaining or improving health. “Also, the more advanced the disease, the greater the benefit: Moving from 90 minutes a day to two hours a day of light physical activity was associated with a larger absolute risk reduction in stage 4 of CKM versus stage 2,” she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is considered light activity?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Light exercise is easy to do. It includes walking and being able to have a full conversation without shortness of breath,” says Dr. Breathett. “This is the exercise that you may not consider as exercise, as your heart rate typically does not rise much. It also includes some activities of daily living, such as light housework.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other examples include casual walking, yoga, stretching, and gardening, adds Dr. Thachil. “Light exercise improves heart health and metabolism. It helps lower insulin and fat levels as well as blood sugar,” says &lt;a href="https://manhattancardiology.com/team/dr-randy-gould/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Randy Gould, M.D.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Randy Gould, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a doctor with Manhattan Cardiology and &lt;a href="https://www.labfinder.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:LabFinder;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;LabFinder&lt;/a&gt; contributor. Light activity can also increase a process known as &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK537040/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lipoprotein lipase;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;lipoprotein lipase&lt;/a&gt; activity, which improves how the body processes fats, Dr. Gould adds. “It matters because many people [with CKM] are not able to perform high-intensity activities, such as running or high-intensity cardio workouts,” he concludes. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to lightly exercise for cardio-metabolic health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The overarching goal is to be less sedentary—every minute and hour counts. “Start with ‘replace sitting’ goals, building towards two hours a day of light physical activity,” Dr. Thachil recommends. This can include walking breaks around the house or the neighborhood, chores, and errands on foot, she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Aim for 30 minutes of aerobic exercise daily,” recommends Dr. Breathett. “Start off with five minutes or 10 minutes if 30 minutes is too much. Try walking or exercising with a friend to build accountability, park farther from the entrance, take the stairs, go outside and enjoy nature, walk a block to a neighbor, walk around your superstore, join a walking club with people who have similar interests.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If feasible, keep general exercise guidelines as a goal, too, which is 150 minutes of moderate-vigorous exercise per week, says Dr. Thachil. “Frame light physical activity as a legitimate therapeutic step for people who can’t safely or realistically do moderate-vigorous physical activity yet,” she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to movement, the “essential eight” lifestyle factors for improving cardio-metabolic health include controlling blood pressure, glucose, and cholesterol (know your numbers), getting seven to nine hours of sleep nightly, quitting smoking, eating healthy, and achieving or maintaining an ideal weight, says Dr. Breathett.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The basic rules still hold true,” says Dr. Breathett. “Exercise is important for your health. Prioritize exercise today, and you may not have to prioritize managing sickness later.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Put differently: “Light activity counts,” says Dr. Thachil. “Especially if you’re high-risk.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 14:44:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPVVNsNlRWUEZVdGx1TmxPVkxlRkdNblZVWkNIbEJScWlUTGZPc0VES21DSWVqSzl5NXk5MkpHRFM4R0V6enFkUFJYMXIyMWtRR2V0WjNURUEyRm1YcUtIREFGRDctUUg1WGpxa0tlUUwybVJ4NkpjMmI4dEtTelhCbEVKUlhmMFlFLUczZWpuNDlaaWlDT3c</guid></item><item><title>医务人员未能检查睡着的母亲后，婴儿死亡-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2026/01/26/baby-dies-asleep-mother-sonny-taylor-bangor-hospital-wales/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;A baby died at three days old after NHS medics failed to wake his mother for observations while pregnant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sonny Taylor suffered catastrophic brain damage as a result of being starved of oxygen having been left “distressed for a significant amount of time”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Midwifery staff had left his mother Eve, 29, sleeping instead of waking her for observations and to listen to Sonny’s heart, an internal &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/nhs/"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; investigation report found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The baby was then delivered in a “poor condition” via caesarean section at Ysbyty Gwynedd Hospital in Bangor, Wales. He died at three days old on Oct 3 2022 as a result of sepsis and a brain injury from oxygen starvation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His parents have won an undisclosed settlement after suing the local health board. Speaking for the first time about her son’s death, Eve said: “When I went into hospital, I never could have imagined what was to follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What followed was frantic, chaotic and terrifying. I went to sleep at my emergency C-section not knowing if I would wake up or whether my baby would make it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Mother sent to wrong ward&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eve was admitted to Ysbyty Gwynedd Hospital on Sept 29, 2022 after her waters broke at 36 weeks pregnant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sonny’s heart rate was initially diagnosed as normal, but later that afternoon signs of potential infection were identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 6pm Eve’s observations and Sonny’s heart rate and movements were classed as normal. At 10pm, as Eve was asleep, observations and monitoring were not carried out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She awoke at 1.30am on Sept 30 concerned about Sonny’s reduced movement, and a registrar was called. The registrar established that Sonny had an abnormal heart rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eve was wrongly transferred to the labour ward instead of being taken for delivery, arriving at 1.43am. A call for an emergency caesarean was made. There was then a 15-minute delay to Sonny’s birth, who was delivered at 2.03am.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sonny was moved from a neonatal intensive care unit to palliative care, with the permission of Eve and her partner Thomas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;NHS apologises for ‘failings’&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thomas said that his son was “badly let down when he needed help the most”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His parents won the undisclosed settlement following legal action against the Betsi Cadwaladr University Local Health Board. Through NHS Wales, the board apologised for the “failings identified” within the investigation report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The report found a midwife should have woken Eve and performed observations and listened to Sonny’s heart rate at 10pm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sara Burns, a medical negligence lawyer at Irwin Mitchell, representing Eve, said: “While we’re pleased to have secured this settlement and appreciate the health board’s co-operation in resolving the case promptly, no amount of compensation can ever begin to make up for what the family has been through.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carol Shillabeer, the chief executive of Betsi Cadwaladr University Health Board, said: “We would like to offer our sincere sympathies to the family of baby Sonny, who sadly died in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We are deeply sorry for their loss and for the failures in care that occurred. We recognise the profound impact this has had on Sonny’s family, and we apologise unreservedly for the distress caused.”&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 13:18:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPM0hKZk16cEhFZW8zZGJ1MzFOSjJ5LVVCemxBQlVpSkhvc1lMemFPcjFxc2c4ZjRPMnNPNlZiS1ZZN09CdDQ0WDR0bVNSU2hHN0FNY1piSFNadGlKQWdNQXA3UVRKQ2IwYk55QWRvWjZpOGJOYnFHMDIwcXlHY1RYZGJuLXRWVUVGM0ZkVl9GakgyNHktVHU0RmJMUVNUSkpxdlJTaExn</guid></item><item><title>圣马特奥诊所提供预防性健康检查，起价为$ 7,500 - SFGATE</title><link>https://www.sfgate.com/local/article/biograph-preventive-health-testing-21294834.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:23:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOU2U3SUZuV3pZV1AtQll5X1FwaDZ5NmRYeXJaRDBXc0lpeXp6OUdjeFQ1bFBVUVRCRUluYmdJTHdJbWZfNW1BQmZnYkV0UGRBaWNZRHBIREdONnItTDUtNXU2UUJKTkhYWW1KeTFuZjMtSk5aajdlVlpFUnFONlUzSDEzR1VOZXZXRWtVaw</guid></item><item><title>拥有20年经验的健身教练在瘦身的同时分享5种碳水化合物： “我们的目标是吃更聪明的碳水化合物……” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-coach-with-20-years-of-experience-shares-5-carbs-to-eat-while-getting-lean-weight-loss-101769427027842.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt;&lt;p class="content"&gt;Cutting carbohydrates is one of the popular ways to create a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/chennai-fitness-coach-simplifies-weight-loss-in-3-easy-steps-and-calorie-deficit-is-the-name-of-the-game-101764916324612.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="calorie deficit"&gt;calorie deficit&lt;/a&gt; while trying to lose weight. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;However, according to Dan Go, a fitness coach with over 20 years of experience, we do not have to deny ourselves of carbs completely to hit our fitness goals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="artImage leadImage"&gt;&lt;figcaption class=""&gt;Potatoes are low in calories and high in fibre, making them a good source of carbs, according to Dan Go. (Pexel)&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Also Read | &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/ahmedabad-nutritionist-lists-best-millets-for-heart-weight-loss-digestion-and-diabetes-shares-tips-to-eat-them-right-101769421559480.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Ahmedabad nutritionist lists best millets for heart, weight loss, digestion and diabetes; shares tips to eat them right"&gt;Ahmedabad nutritionist lists best millets for heart, weight loss, digestion and diabetes; shares tips to eat them right&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Taking to Instagram on January 25, Dan shared five sources of carbohydrate that can be consumed to stay full, even while being on a fat loss journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;“Stop fearing &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/nutritionist-conducts-a-simple-experiment-to-show-how-eating-fibres-before-carbs-can-reduce-the-risk-of-diabetes-101768999467164.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="carbs"&gt;carbs&lt;/a&gt;. Start choosing the right ones,” Dan wrote in the caption. “The goal isn’t eliminating carbs. It’s eating smarter carbs that work with your deficit, not against it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;The list of five healthy carb sources is presented as follows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Potatoes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Potatoes are low in calories, high in fibre, especially the skin,” shared Dan. “This makes them incredibly filling. Also, the resistant starch and high water content help you feel satisfied longer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Blueberries&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blueberries are rich in fibre and water, which makes them low in calories but highly satiating. The fibre present in the fruit slows digestion and helps keep us full while stabilising blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Lentils&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;“Lentils are loaded with fibre and plant-based protein, both of which are proven to increase satiety and curb hunger,” stated Dan, adding that “lentils are better than rice as a carb source because they contain fewer calories, more fibre, and also higher amounts of protein.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Broccoli&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While broccoli is a green cruciferous vegetable, it is still considered to be a good source of carbohydrates. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dan considers broccoli to be the “perfect” food to volumise meals, as it is rich in fibre and water, which helps us feel full while also providing “an incredible nutrient profile.&lt;/span&gt;” This includes vitamins C and K, and folate, which support metabolism and digestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Apples&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Apples are nature’s appetite suppressants,” noted Dan. “They are naturally sweet, low in calories, and high in fibre, which helps you curb hunger and also reduce snacking.” The fibre content in apples also helps regulate blood sugar and keeps us full while being nutrient-dense, providing “vitamins and antioxidants with every bite.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 12:06:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9gFBVV95cUxQVC1YMGNGUURyYk9oTGRJYnBhQ19GektLTDBDNEtWQmZ6cFFCZEcyLTBwVV9GMF9fT0xrRVdqR1M3SF9QYUJrVlFEVXFab1Z3N1dCeWs0Mkl6ZktoUnlGMVdXczNQVjdPMjB3bzNvbEVxZW16S0pwQWx0a043UlY3Sk9OOGZmS2lDYzN2ajRkU3FvR3NaTTh2anh1bGpqckFqM00zXzdEblN5TXJxNHpnUE5RZ1VobWQ0NnFRUWpBS3VoR3NIRU1LWU9ZdjJmZ3hhTHFjd1c3dWRyeUJ2U1lnakJhRFB0TDNVbE9mSE5CR2xmQXg0Q0HSAfsBQVVfeXFMTk95eUZPMHZCOUl1eDQtNkQtSEthenk1Zk0zdEFhWHMtSUx6OEdJMGhaTzBhNk50MjV6SlVRTXp2ODN6STlRWGdjV3pfNWY4SnFsVTBxM1dSSG1kUXEtSE8wSEVvbnZLOWZweUNseGxDT3kwRGZCdXlGaEVPVG9BcU1iajNpVEF5RE5QUS1VM0RaRklmSEZMYzZCLUxQNW85c3ROUHNiNkloZWl6VElGM3cyTVZqdkxxR0FqaV90ZjZhU2tEeXFwQy1wRUxzdEoxd2pnVlFFXzVYdUFiVnJOT3hJVUpKSGtncVZCdjZjankwTkx3aTQ4ZHBtVEU</guid></item><item><title>你的阴茎真的是长寿的指标吗？布莱恩·约翰逊是这么认为的—真正的专家权衡-纽约邮报</title><link>https://nypost.com/2026/01/26/health/is-your-penis-an-indicator-of-longevity-experts-weigh-in/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;World-renowned biohacker Bryan Johnson is raising eyebrows for his &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/03/28/health/bryan-johnson-credits-shockwave-therapy-and-botox-for-titanic-erections/"&gt;shocking approach&lt;/a&gt; to erectile health.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Johnson — whose mantra is, “Don’t Die” — takes Cialis, receives penile Botox and even undergoes low-intensity shockwave therapy to his, uh, johnson to improve blood flow, enhance erections and achieve sexual performance comparable to a teenager’s.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Nighttime erections are, like, a really important health marker,” Johnson, 48, &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7qriveAV7BY" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said in 2024&lt;/a&gt;. “Men who do not have nighttime erections are 70% more likely to die prematurely. It predicts death.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"&gt;&lt;p class="wp-block-embed__wrapper"&gt;
&lt;span class="embed-youtube"&gt;&lt;iframe loading="lazy" title="Video" class="youtube-player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7qriveAV7BY?version=3&amp;amp;rel=1&amp;amp;showsearch=0&amp;amp;showinfo=1&amp;amp;iv_load_policy=1&amp;amp;fs=1&amp;amp;hl=en-US&amp;amp;autohide=2&amp;amp;start=73&amp;amp;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Biohacker Bryan Johnson is a big proponent of penile health as a key marker of biological age. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;YouTube/, The Diary Of A CEO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He’s not the only longevity-seeker making waves with his rigid regimen.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Fitness guru Ben Greenfield, 44, has experimented with &lt;a href="https://bengreenfieldlife.com/article/biohacking-articles/the-most-potent-natural-alternative-to-viagra/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;acoustic wave therapy&lt;/a&gt; and, stunningly, &lt;a href="https://bengreenfieldlife.com/article/get-effects-stem-cell-dick-injectionwithout-actually-getting-stem-cell-dick-injection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;stem cell injections&lt;/a&gt; to optimize sexual performance and vitality.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;So is penile health a true barometer of longevity? Are these biohackers playing the long game &lt;strong&gt;—&lt;/strong&gt; or overextending themselves for a pipe dream?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Post spoke with two experts about the rising interest in biohacking the penis — they shared their tip-down philosophies for protecting the crown jewels for the decades to come.&lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How does penile health reflect overall health?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Penis health is &lt;a href="https://www.browardurologycenter.com/pdf/International-Index-of-Erectile-Function-IIEF-Questionnaire.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;measured in many ways&lt;/a&gt;, [namely] erectile dysfunction (ED), orgasmic function, libido, satisfaction with intercourse and overall satisfaction,” &lt;a href="https://ryanweltermd.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Dr. Ryan Welter&lt;/a&gt;, a pioneer in regenerative cellular therapy and founder of &lt;a href="https://regenerismedical.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Regeneris Medical&lt;/a&gt;, told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Declines in penile health — particularly ED — have been established as an early predictor of cardiovascular disease, often appearing two to five years before a heart attack, Welter added.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Penile arteries are significantly smaller than the arteries that supply the heart and brain, meaning they often show the first signs of plaque buildup.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;High cholesterol and plaque buildup reduce the blood flow needed for an erection.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Penile arteries are significantly smaller than the arteries that supply the heart and brain, meaning they often show the first signs of plaque buildup. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;creativebubble – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nerve damage is also a major reason for ED because it affects signals from the brain to the pelvis.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nerve degeneration is common with age — it’s also a hallmark of diabetes, multiple sclerosis, spinal cord injury, Parkinson’s disease, stroke and Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And finally, imbalances in sex hormones can pave the way for ED. &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/09/12/health/the-truth-about-manopause-and-slow-insidious-signs-men-overlook/"&gt;Low testosterone&lt;/a&gt; reduces libido and the ability to get and maintain erections.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;“Furthermore, and this is important, happiness is one of the best predictors of longevity,” Welter said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Sexual dysfunction and depressed sexual satisfaction are indicators of unhappiness and need to be treated if longevity is the goal.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What are the red flags of poor erectile health?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Typically, men, over time, will experience erections that are not as firm as they used to be, difficulty maintaining the erection over time [and] changes in nocturnal and morning erections,” aesthetic nurse practitioner &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/injectorchris/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Chris Bustamante&lt;/a&gt;, founder of the NYC men’s clinic &lt;a href="https://www.lushfulaesthetics.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Lushful Aesthetics&lt;/a&gt;, told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It might take them longer to ejaculate or [they] may ejaculate faster. Typically, longer is more normal with age.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Sudden, drastic changes to the quality, frequency and duration of erections — especially when accompanied by symptoms like rapid weight gain, shortness of breath or fatigue — should warrant an urgent visit to the doctor, who will evaluate the cardiovascular system, hormone levels and the presence of any tumors, Bustamante said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That’s why it’s important to track morning and nocturnal erections and their general hardness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Semen is not as good of a biomarker as erections, some experts say. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;RHJ – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For his part, Johnson uses an &lt;a href="https://www.talktoadam.com/products/adam-sensor" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Adam Health sensor&lt;/a&gt; ($249) to measure his nighttime erections, garnering data on their duration, frequency and quality to generate an erection health score.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He said he also tracks his sperm count, movement and shape, penile blood flow, urination speed and prostate size.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Bustamante said erections are stronger benchmarks than semen characteristics.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It is just kind of normal sometimes for [the] volume of semen to decline with age,” he explained.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It also varies a lot from man to man, already from the beginning. So some men naturally have higher volume loads of semen versus others.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What are the common treatments for ED?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The single most important treatment for longevity and health span, particularly for the penis, is diet and exercise and maintaining good metabolic health,” Welter said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As a hard-and-fast rule, Bustamante said, you need to focus on consuming fruits, vegetables and fiber and limit red meat for its saturated fat content and processed foods for their trans fats.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Red meat and processed foods can raise blood pressure because of their high levels of sodium, saturated fats and preservatives. High blood pressure causes ED by damaging and narrowing blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Strength training is critical for penile health because it enhances blood flow, boosts testosterone and improves vascular function. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Chanakon – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In terms of exercise, Bustamante said it’s important to build muscle since “muscle is the organ of longevity.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He recommends 30 minutes of daily cardio, but warns against one popular activity.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We do see a higher correlation of ED when it comes to cyclists,” Bustamante said.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;“It doesn’t matter if you have a special, fancy seat or not,” he added. “Putting all that pressure on your perineum (the skin and tissue between your genitals and your anus) does sort of damage these nerves and vessels over time.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Lifestyle changes aside, Bustamante said low doses of Cialis relax smooth muscles in the prostate, bladder neck and penis to boost urine flow and facilitate erections.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What about those expensive biohacker tools?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Over time, men’s penises become desensitized — part of that is through sex and masturbation, and part of it is just through general aging,” Bustamante said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Helping to resensitize that tissue is a really important factor in terms of overall performance.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That’s why some biohackers are going so far as to embrace low-intensity focused shockwave devices. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Bustamante said these gizmos emit sound waves that cause micro-injuries in penile tissue, triggering the growth of new blood vessels and increased blood circulation to improve penile sensitivity and function.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Shockwave therapy and acoustic wave therapy are often used interchangeably, so it’s important to know what you’re really getting.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;This is an example of a shockwave device. Thankfully, it’s being used on a person’s shin in this picture. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;puhimec – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In general, shockwave therapy uses intense, high-energy acoustic waves, while acoustic therapy often refers to gentler, lower-intensity waves.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It is not going to be strong enough to actually penetrate the depth of this tissue,” Bustamante said of acoustic wave therapy.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It’s going to be very, very superficial, and so, therefore, it just really is not impactful.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For its part, Botox temporarily relaxes muscles by blocking nerve signals that cause muscle contraction.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Bustamante said that when it’s injected into the penis, patients tend to notice they can achieve firmer, quicker erections. But Botox typically lasts only three to four months.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“This treatment is really great to just improve someone’s quality of life when it comes to erectile function,” Bustamante said, adding that it can enhance the effectiveness of Cialis and Viagra.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;As for penile stem cell injections, this treatment has not been approved by the Food and Drug Administration.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s considered experimental, with no strong evidence of safety or effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Bustamante also warns against the increasingly popular practice of injecting salmon sperm derivatives into the penile area, as it can cause infections, allergic reactions and probably some funky smells.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Instead, he recommends and administers &lt;a href="https://www.lushfulaesthetics.com/sexual-enhancement-services/p-shot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;“P-shots,”&lt;/a&gt; injections of platelet-rich plasma from the patient’s own blood into the penis to boost blood flow and stimulate tissue repair.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“These modalities, such as shockwave and P-shot, are really beneficial in terms of people experiencing better sex lives,” Bustamante said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Worth a shot — or a shock — to get up and running?&lt;/p&gt;





		
				
								&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPVmlWQmhkMDRTS0RxZWNqa0FuTldiVDV2WFVqcThhSENYNlZDcm1uQ0dYTzd3dHZIUlpJZnBycTNTTWNhNHdod1NrM2cySWZxc3A3eURvVi1wQlRSanB0clUzMlpCbVRRWm1zNWVOUWQyRFJvRm5CVm1CZ0lRVjZaXzdQWXAtcWtMVFUwcm1aVTg2eWZZMlB3X0ZB</guid></item><item><title>我14岁时，父母把我赶出了家门。我一直梦想着让他们回来，但不是这样的。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2026/01/family-advice-kicked-out-of-house-parents.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="16" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr1qub8002rg9mc2psfx3nk@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr20fpr001c3b79s513i0p2@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr1rhpq00123b794hqdkmw9@published"&gt;When I was 14, my parents kicked me out because I was doing drugs and getting rides with random dudes. My uncle found me a couple of days later, having driven around town constantly looking for me the moment he heard about what had happened. He was a total wild man, but he put a roof over my head when nobody else would, gave me unconditional love, and helped me find my way. He helped me get into college, and he paid for it.&lt;/p&gt;

    


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="105" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr20hll001j3b79rg4h94rn@published"&gt;When he died, he left a void in my life. He also left me the house I grew up in, a large amount of money, and a successful business. Suddenly, my parents and my brothers, whom I’ve not spoken to in nearly two decades, are “reaching out.” It’s heartbreaking because I’ve always wanted my family back, but I am not stupid enough to believe that they have any interest in me. Is there a pathway for reconciliation here? Or am I just kidding myself? Am I a fool for wanting these people in my life? Or to even believe that could happen on my terms?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr20jfe001q3b79udl86ktl@published"&gt;—Misspent Youth&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr1rhrp00133b79ndxg2sjq@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Misspent Youth,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="170" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr1rhto00143b79j715nq3z@published"&gt;You are not a fool at all for missing your family and wanting them in your life. It also doesn’t make you “stupid” to believe that they would miss you, too. Many families struggle with what to do when loved ones are doing drugs and juggle two options: getting them support or giving them so-called “tough love.” It seems your parents might have thought the latter was the right thing to do. We can guess at their flawed rationale, but this doesn’t negate your feelings. They abandoned you when you were a child, and it will feel like abandonment, no matter what their intent might have been. But if you truly want to reconcile, and if you feel emotionally ready, you can always have an initial conversation. That second caveat is &lt;em&gt;crucial&lt;/em&gt; for you think about here. You’re already in a vulnerable place with the death of your uncle. You might want to consult a therapist on your own to discuss if you’re truly ready to handle seeing them again.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="127" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr1rhvp00153b79hdmh40kw@published"&gt;If you do decide to see them, I would first think of a neutral place you can meet where you feel comfortable. Is there a coffee shop or a park you go to often? Maybe you all can grab a smoothie and walk around your neighborhood if the weather’s nice. I find that it’s easier for me to have tough conversations on walks because I can look elsewhere when I need to. A good family therapist could help you all confront these old feelings together and start a fresh, new relationship on better terms. But know you can always put space between yourself and them again if you need to. None of this is binding, and you’re allowed to change your mind and follow what feels right.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr20mc0001x3b79b7htgowg@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Arionne&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmkr20uel002d3b79hhif8mpo@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="52" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkr20r9i00253b79jf975c5i@published"&gt;My daughter is 4 and my niece is almost 6; they’re the only grandchildren on my husband’s side. At my daughter’s birthday party, my sister-in-law brought two identical presents. She informed me that one was for my daughter and one was for my niece, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2019/08/in-laws-no-boundaries-care-and-feeding.html"&gt;so my niece wouldn’t get jealous and misbehave…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmkr1qub8002ug9mcl1ps1l6j@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNM3JvZGpyNHp5VjRUc1p5a3RVb0pmVTRjc3lPX3drMHhaYzd6QXJmR1lQWFZuZ0g1QmlfYnVVTFJoNm1FOExkZTd5Y1BJcjBmUHZEbnE5a01Ld0ZTT3c4ZkpiS2NmUnBGWWlrSzJwblhFYndQODhycTdBUlVhSDlSN2NzSm80UQ</guid></item><item><title>减少加工食品中的盐分可以降低高血压、心脏病和中风的发病率：研究- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/reducing-salt-processed-foods-lower-rates-high-blood/story?id=129546517</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;Reducing the sodium in pre-packaged and prepared foods may prevent thousands of cases of heart disease, stroke and death, according to two new studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The studies, published early Monday in the journal Hypertension, took place in France and the United Kingdom, countries where food giants have subtly reduced salt levels in store-bought foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Using national diet and health data, researchers in France estimated that modest decreases in bread salt content could cut adults' daily salt intake by 0.35 grams, lower their blood pressure and prevent more than 1,100 deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Researchers from the U.K. estimated that similar salt reductions in packaged foods and takeout meals could lower daily British sodium intake by 17.5%, preventing more than 100,000 cases of heart disease and 25,000 cases of stroke over 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Sodium plays important health roles, like helping blood vessels hold water. However, about 90% of Americans consume too much of it, according to the American Heart Association. Excessive sodium raises the risk of high blood pressure, a risk factor for issues such as cardiovascular disease, long-term kidney disease and cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In the United States, most sodium intake comes from foods prepared outside the home, experts say. "Americans on average get about 75% of their food from processed food of some kind—either processed foods from grocery stores, or foods that are bought at restaurants or fast-food restaurants," Dr. Daniel Jones, professor and dean emeritus at the University of Mississippi School of Medicine and chair of the 2025 American Heart Association/American College of Cardiology Blood Pressure Guideline, told ABC News. Manufacturers often add salt to processed foods in order to prolong shelf life and enhance flavor. Minimal cuts in salt, which the researchers said would not greatly affect taste, may have a significant health impact. American adults consume on average 3,500 milligrams of sodium daily, well above the AHA-recommended limit of 2,300 mg, or a tablespoon of salt, said Dr. Latha Palaniappan, associate dean for research at Stanford University School of Medicine. The daily limit for those with high blood pressure is even lower at 1,500 mg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;While processed foods may be difficult to entirely avoid, experts say cutting back on them may lead to meaningful health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"One of the things I advise my patients about is to shop as much as they can on the periphery of the grocery store. That’s generally where fresh foods are," Jones said. Natural whole foods, like fresh produce, are especially healthy. "I tell my patients to eat foods with peels, not packages, to lower their overall intake of sodium," Palaniappan said. "Read labels, be cautious with packaged foods, and prioritize fresh, minimally processed foods."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;Richard Zhang, MD, MA, is a child and adolescent psychiatry fellow at Yale School of Medicine and a member of the ABC News Medical Unit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:15:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPSTBmcjBmS3VwREZRRmQ0SHFjaWE3OHZjdXBRZmRWamsyaWl3UXpuNHFXTzhvcXdkSDJpQ0tZV19lZmZEOWdKWFFFTldIMmxncFhFUzhWVXdRNGNfZzZwRzJnR1hKNkctRUV2LUlBZlAzNHpIb2pFbzFpZW1WMkhwd19GT25rT084SExvbkV4eWd0c0VxOUZULVdKMDFETFU0OFdr0gGoAUFVX3lxTE51QlZBeW5ZZFRJT0o0aHBUMzZRVkFVSnZoYnFfYUtRMmN2ck41WUJYUmhMMHpmaG9LMGRaeXVkYVVHd20tYUs4dUg1NkdGVFNSX3hJLVV6RjA1VEFOdW9QMWszbzBtLTlwNkxKTGVWeFNhNGFNR2EzTDN0QUJYRDRiVkxPdUZCZU54czUxU1ZhUmk2SlpvYktVS2hmbzFBWXVCN2cwdXlNRQ</guid></item><item><title>人工智能妄想有多糟糕？我们要求对待他们的人。-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/26/us/chatgpt-delusions-psychosis.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE93NndRdFJEdlhQOVVOdnBYZGNrdGg3RjEzWW5udlR6cFhuMmJubU1DN1RyY1lqeTlkQjd4OEZTNUJacnZVWGxqUUhfbndsOG5pMFNPd2NIZy1jQjNWeGFJLWgxcnlyQm9vTlFuYmcxZ1hJdHFGTU1VNEJB</guid></item><item><title>间歇性禁食是否符合炒作？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/26/well/eat/intermittent-fasting.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 10:00:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE5CUUt0TXFlWEVRTmVXYVRZSkxHcUZXcEktR3FMMEVURHhxYktYMjFIaXBLMElLaWk5TERkZGRwSnVaNVdXOGNJZzJZamRyMnJ4WUl3WEo4NlQzSWxaelpuZUJCb3Bvd1NiM1ZablZCYnUzWWhrdzhmTQ</guid></item><item><title>新研究发现，终生饮酒与结直肠癌风险增加有关- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/lifetime-alcohol-linked-higher-risk-colorectal-cancer-new/story?id=129547475</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;Long-term alcohol use has been linked to higher risks of colorectal cancer, according to a study published Monday in the journal Cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Researchers found that those with heavy lifetime alcohol consumption have up to a 91% higher risk of developing colorectal cancer compared with those who drank very little. That risk significantly increased with consistent heavy consumption, whereas those who quit drinking may have demonstrated decreased risk of precancerous tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“The longer someone drinks, the longer their colon and rectum are exposed damage and impaired repair, both major mechanisms of cancer,” Dr. Lynn M O’Connor, section chief of colon and rectal surgery at Mercy Medical Center and St. Joseph Hospital in New York, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The study followed more than 88,000 adults with no prior history of cancer. Participants reported their alcohol use beginning in early adulthood and were followed for nearly a decade to track cancer outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Compared with those who averaged one drink or less per week over their lifetime, those who consumed over 14 drinks a week had a 25% higher risk of developing colorectal cancer. The link was even stronger for rectal cancer, where one's risk nearly doubled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Rectal cancer is “often more difficult to treat and more involved clinically, which makes screening and early identification all the more important,” Dr. Jeffrey Farma, a colorectal cancer specialist, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The results come as colorectal cancers are on the rise, especially in younger people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“We’re seeing an uptick in rectal cancers. If alcohol affects the lower part of the colon differently —we need to understand why,” Dr. Fola May, a GI specialist and associate director of the UCLA Kaiser Permanente Center for Health Equity, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In the study, researchers found the highest risks among people who drank heavily at every stage of life. Those who consistently exceeded recommended drinking limits across each stage of adulthood had a 91% higher risk of colorectal cancer compared with lifelong light drinkers or those with gaps in heavy drinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“These numbers are not guarantees, but signals to do something before it’s too late,” May said. “Colorectal cancer is one of the few cancers we can actually prevent or catch early, but fewer than 70% of eligible people get screened.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The study also looked at adenomas —polyps that can develop into cancer. While heavy drinking was not strongly linked to adenoma risk, those who quit drinking had significantly lower odds of developing nonadvanced adenomas compared to light drinkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“These are modifiable risks. The choices people make over time matter, and the body can respond when those risks are reduced,” Farma said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The results align with a growing body of evidence linking alcohol, a well-recognized carcinogen, to colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Colorectal screening is recommended for all adults starting at age 45 according to the United States Preventative Services Task Force. Screening tools include annual stool tests, CT scans every five years, or colonoscopies every 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“Everyone should be screened. It saves lives, and people are dying unnecessarily when they put it off,” May said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Those who may be at higher risk may need to be screened at an early age or more often than typically recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“If you’ve had prolonged heavy drinking and you develop symptoms like bleeding or persistent changes in bowel habits, you need to be evaluated — even in your 30s,” Farma said. “That’s how we catch this early and save lives.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt; Tyler Beauchamp, MD, is a pediatric resident at UNC Children’s Hospital and a member of the ABC News Medical Unit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 08:13:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNMzdpOFc0eV9Ja0tPYkZZVXRsVVRhajlIYWhTQUNqRDktNDAxaG5QNk9GeXNtQW5kTmhmeUwzOW1VOF84Tzg5bm95VER6MC1KNWhGN2ROaElWQUpTVGZrVUt6a1JFX0JFOEVOdk1vVk9MXzRvNVU4cWFnRlR1dFk3dnRrblJrYUd0UE1YeTZGa2pXUkczdFkzU1pHZnFGMDQ3SFA3N0pjLUJNZ9IBrwFBVV95cUxNd3VDMG52b2lLTkJBWDZtbVFna1BUVWVLanZnU1hhZzUxMWIxTGZoVUluMHFUYUxXWXJSMVRhX3NRWEdzTXVoLWM0NmVqSU5tSGlac1c0NENhUVdfNHZHYUdmelVHbnRMWVJSVXVqUjV3S2NnWDFHLWlfQzBGd3R1clM3bFdCVnlpa1JqTFk0Z2RZbW43WFVDYlo5Y2NjNFlhZzdFelQ3QXZ2UEZGR2VJ</guid></item><item><title>“肌肉老化对渐进式力量训练的反应非常好” —一位私人教练分享了一项5步锻炼，以在65岁后锻炼肌肉-汤姆指南</title><link>https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/aging-muscles-respond-very-well-to-progressive-strength-training-a-personal-trainer-shares-a-5-move-workout-to-build-muscle-after-65</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;

&lt;p id="1b781d73-6b42-4188-909e-914b57f4e127"&gt;Building muscle does tend to get harder with age, but that doesn't mean it stops being possible. These changes can affect people at different ages and at different rates, and when they do, it doesn't mean your fitness is suddenly on a downhill slope, or that rebuilding strength is an uphill battle you can't win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to physiotherapist and personal trainer Grace Heinrichs, currently working at&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.xclubs.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-url="https://www.xclubs.co.uk/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt; X-Club Pilates &amp;amp; Wellness&lt;/a&gt; in London, these shifts are a normal part of the aging process rather than a sign that you’ve left it too late. “There is good news in all of this, aging muscles respond very well to progressive strength training,” she says, particularly when training is approached with patience and consistency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="1b781d73-6b42-4188-909e-914b57f4e127-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;Progressive strength training, also known as &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/progressive-overload-what-is-it-and-how-does-it-help-build-muscle-and-strength" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/features/progressive-overload-what-is-it-and-how-does-it-help-build-muscle-and-strength"&gt;progressive overload&lt;/a&gt;, simply means gradually increasing the challenge placed on your muscles over time. This might look like adding a small amount of weight, increasing repetitions, or improving control and range of motion, rather than pushing harder all at once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether you’re returning to exercise or want to reinforce the fundamentals before progressing, here’s a five-move routine Heinrich recommends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-1-sit-to-stand-chair-squat-3-sets-of-10" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-sit-to-stand-chair-squat-3-sets-of-10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Sit to stand (Chair Squat): 3 sets of 10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="2699ae14-fdad-4640-a4b6-44595b760126"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ul id="caff493d-a79e-4a96-a452-e5bbd3d0c576"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sit tall on a chair with feet hip-width apart.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Press through your heels to stand up fully, keeping your chest lifted.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly lower back down to the chair with control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-2-wall-push-ups-3-sets-of-10" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-wall-push-ups-3-sets-of-10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Wall push ups: 3 sets of 10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="95b50ac5-2995-4994-8d51-a9e7724ea6f2"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ul id="94c0c799-f773-4693-94bf-3e9618afcfbd"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand a step or two from a wall, hands on the wall at shoulder height.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bend your elbows to bring your chest toward the wall.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Push back to straighten your arms, keeping your core engaged.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-3-step-ups-3-sets-of-10-per-leg" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-step-ups-3-sets-of-10-per-leg"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Step ups: 3 sets of 10 per leg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="07c66de5-2574-4815-bf2c-8f344a75e0d5"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ul id="bca1369e-14ab-45bd-bbe6-3a1a296dcb96"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Step onto a sturdy platform, step, or low bench — with or without weights.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drive through your heel to stand tall, bringing the other foot up if comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Step back down and repeat on the other leg.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-4-farmer-s-carry-3-sets-of-30-60-seconds" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-4-farmer-s-carry-3-sets-of-30-60-seconds"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Farmer's Carry: 3 sets of 30-60 seconds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="89611e4b-a9a5-4a8a-859d-cb1d4d6b24da"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ul id="59e4b30f-ab59-4ddb-8d84-2877f69d3de5"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold a weight in each hand — dumbbells, kettlebells, or even two water bottles.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand tall, shoulders back, and walk steadily for the set time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Focus on posture and controlled breathing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-5-shoulder-bridge-3-sets-of-10" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-5-shoulder-bridge-3-sets-of-10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5. Shoulder Bridge: 3 sets of 10&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="6cc01ea7-17c1-4f25-b176-3be4f2b78a77"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;ul id="3337bafe-0d9c-4aac-98dc-edc115ea25dc"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lie on your back with knees bent and feet flat on the floor, arms by your sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Press through your heels to lift your hips toward the ceiling, squeezing your glutes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lower back down slowly without letting your lower back collapse.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To make it harder, lift one knee toward your chest as you bridge, then switch sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr id="2233ca04-6b70-4d89-a574-1fe467e14366"&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE" rel="nofollow" id="e54ee4c1-8104-42f1-8bda-a1b9d4c8c7a4" data-url="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure pull-right inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check=""&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a id="elk-more-from-tom-s-guide" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-more-from-tom-s-guide"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More from Tom's Guide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="f55e6da4-63c0-4737-8568-1e822edd4443"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Follow &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE" target="_blank" data-url="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tom's Guide on Google News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=tomsguide.com" target="_blank" data-url="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=tomsguide.com" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;em&gt;add us as a preferred source&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; to get our up-to-date news, analysis, and reviews in your feeds. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr id="d44f2d42-3eb5-4c86-a9ad-767bfc045b5e"&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-Wgmv52nKKqZtLZvrdMxnm7" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-Wgmv52nKKqZtLZvrdMxnm7 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get instant access to breaking news, the hottest reviews, great deals and helpful tips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tom's Guide</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxOd0dkajZVWERCRllVd1BHZFdXc01MQTJpR3RSTlJNVDItVU9HbXdWUFA1UU9wdzhKY0NUdEsxUzhwZlJGamRyaTlBTEVVZnRpR3hNNDhtb1RiamZvcU10R19tT3R5Ym5jYkY3eUVhcURDRm0xUV9FdG9sNTJlNlFfTGVXOXRVSW56QUJRTWNydWxBdzA1RlNoUmVmNGxPWVFvNUR2dk1Jc0NYdWFDRXRmQkxBd2JlamFjaTVZSHlvNUZ0WTljN1Y1SW9IWlVZbUZTSnAyd2xzQjMyMUJjZTd3R1lzelB5SW8yR2lMa2lKMGVKQWRFYUNCQll4d0RPV19lb1NERjZn</guid></item><item><title>肠癌筛查的改变将挽救成千上万人的生命-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2026/01/26/bowel-cancer-screening-changes-will-save-lives/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;People will also begin receiving alerts via the NHS App to notify them when a screening kit is being sent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NHS estimates the move could help detect around 600 additional bowel cancers early each year in England – an increase of about 11 per cent – and identify 2,000 more people with high-risk polyps, allowing preventative surgery before cancer develops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The home-testing kit, known as the faecal immunochemical test (FIT), is offered to everyone over 50. It checks for blood in a small stool sample, which can be a sign of bowel cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By lowering the threshold from 120 micrograms of blood per gram of faeces to 80, the NHS expects to offer 35 per cent more screening colonoscopies each year to diagnose or rule out the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The change comes as the NHS prepares to launch digital alerts to boost screening uptake, as part of a radical new National Cancer Plan, to be published next week, to transform cancer care by 2035.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peter Johnson, national clinical director for cancer at NHS England, said: “This is a major step forward in bowel cancer detection and will help save hundreds more lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;‘Better early-warning system’&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Testing at a lower threshold will provide a better early-warning system, helping us spot and treat cancers earlier, often before symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Earlier detection can mean less intensive treatment and ensures the best chance of survival. In many cases, people could avoid facing cancer altogether by having dangerous polyps removed before they cause harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I would strongly encourage everyone who is sent a bowel screening test to complete it and return it as soon as possible. It really could make all the difference.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genevieve Edwards, the chief executive of Bowel Cancer UK, said the move marked “an important moment” for screening in England.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said: “Increasing the sensitivity of the test means more cancers will be prevented and found earlier, saving more lives from the UK’s fourth most common cancer.”&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQWUROOEhtYklXSG9ob1RSMmVVaE83b2tJYlFIcDlrblBZaWhzYXptclh4RklFZk5XMHI1TEpEeHk0REhrRjlrdG9iUW1kMlJBb1d3N2dUbkNrczFXVjI2cmJuRW1YNkxnbFhtYTF1bmMtVGdzREJQaXJMZ1QtaU9xcFBOazI1WU1kQ2ZuNUM5ZkZjMGpLbGc</guid></item><item><title>女性在进入中年时所面临的无形皮肤斗争-《纽约邮报》</title><link>https://nypost.com/2026/01/26/health/the-invisible-skin-struggle-women-face-as-they-transition-into-mid-life/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							





&lt;p&gt;Menopause may be best known for hot flashes and mood swings, but it can also come with many other less talked-about symptoms, including skin changes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Studies have shown that a majority of women report skin problems as they age — in particular, one they might not have experienced since their teen years.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Dr. Amy Wechsler, a dual board-certified dermatologist and psychiatrist in Manhattan, specializes in &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2026/01/22/health/constance-zimmer-reveals-how-iud-messed-with-menopause-transition/"&gt;treating perimenopausal &lt;/a&gt;and menopausal women who are battling acne — sometimes for the first time in their lives.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“For them, it’s just horrible because they’ve never had it — it’s so foreign to them,” she told Fox News Digital. “There’s so much psychological overlap and effects of acne on people in terms of lowering self-esteem and self-confidence, and causing anxiety and sometimes depression.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Midlife paradox&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For most women, there are two “peaks of acne” — one during adolescence and another at perimenopause and menopause, according to the doctor. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“There are many women who have been clear of acne for 20 years, and then, starting at around 40-ish, they start to break out again,” she said. “And this time it’s centered around their lower face, chin and jawline, which is where hormonal acne tends to occur.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Menopause brings unexpected skin changes like acne, even for women who haven’t had it since their teens. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;deniskomarov – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Women often come to see me, at age 35 to 55, complaining about wrinkles and pimples — and they feel too young for their wrinkles and too old for their pimples,” she said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While men who have a genetic predisposition for acne may continue to break out into older adulthood, for women, “there’s a particular hormonal component from the late 30s through the early 50s, around perimenopause and menopause.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The breakouts usually stop when menopause is finished, Wechsler said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some studies have suggested that taking GLP-1 weight loss and diabetes medications could increase acne prevalence, but others have not identified a link.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I see patients all day long who are taking GLP-1s, so I would imagine if there were a link, I probably would have picked up on something by now,” Wechsler said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Treatments for adult acne&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The main remedy for aging-related acne is taking &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/shopping/best-acne-skincare-products-review/"&gt;hormone-related medications.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“&lt;/strong&gt;Spironolactone is specifically for hormonal acne in women,” Wechsler said. “It blocks testosterone from binding to the testosterone receptors in the lower face.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Going on hormone replacement therapy or a birth control pill can also help with acne, she noted, but treatments will vary based on each person’s situation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Some people come in with just small blackheads and whiteheads, and they might not need something oral,” she said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Dr. Amy Wechsler, a Manhattan dermatologist, notes acne peaks in adolescence and again during perimenopause. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Fox News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Treatments range from hormone meds like Spironolactone to topical retinoids and lifestyle changes. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Jana Kollarova – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“That’s when we might prescribe something topical, often a retinoid with the brand names of Differin, Retin-A or Tretinoin. Those are often very helpful for smaller pimples. Also, they’re anti-aging, which is nice. They grow collagen.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Wechsler said she sometimes prescribes a low dose of doxycycline, an antibiotic that also works as an anti-inflammatory. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“If the acne is different or covering more of the face or the upper face, sometimes we’ll try a low dose of Accutane,” she added. “It really depends on the individual and how bad the acne is.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proactive defense&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While genetics and hormones can contribute to acne, stress can also affect the skin, the doctor said. One of the best ways to address this is to get optimal sleep, which is the “anti-inflammatory” time when the body heals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Unfortunately, many Americans don’t get enough sleep,” Wechsler said. “Adults need seven-and-a-half to eight hours. That’s when the stress molecule, cortisol, is at its lowest, and when all the healing molecules, like beta-endorphins and growth hormones and oxytocin, are at their highest.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In addition to sleep, the doctor recommends looking for ways to lower cortisol levels during the day to help reduce stress levels — such as exercising, getting fresh air, connecting with friends, and doing stretching or deep breathing.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For people who are acne-prone, Wechsler also emphasized the importance of choosing &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/02/03/health/acne-fighting-serum-infects-bacteria-that-causes-acne-with-a-virus/"&gt;the right skincare &lt;/a&gt;products.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;For people who are acne-prone, Wechsler also emphasized the importance of choosing the right skincare products. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Prostock-studio – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;




&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The main remedy for aging-related acne is taking hormone-related medications. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;st.kolesnikov – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It’s really important that all products are non-comedogenic, or oil-free,” she recommended. “That means the company has tested the product and that it will not clog your pores and cause pimples.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s also important to wash your face after exercising and at the end of the day, and to never go to sleep in makeup, the doctor advised. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For those who are bothered by acne and have not seen results after two months of taking over-the-counter products, Wechsler recommends seeing a dermatologist for help.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:38:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxOQVZkMEJVWHBJRnZPR2lpVjJhcEpyQVd1UC1kdzJnUGVFZHR5VkQyMEJDNGdZalhZN29XRXVHb1Z3Y3JwS3BabC1pZlhUekRFMGVuMkM0ZWxmUkFRZmRBY3VxVm50Rmh6ckZRQ2pVcHZ5aGVpdVcwV042YzV3Zm00VzQ3d1BfLV9LeTFXaGxXS3JVVVdjQklIbkREcWZqQUdQcG1xWFhEd0NEM2JVWmc</guid></item><item><title>我女儿的罕见川崎病被及时发现- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/ce8r20e66d0o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;My toddler's rare disease was spotted with 24 hours to spare&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="McGeoch Family A young toddler in a hospital bed. She has a drip attached to her arm, and is playing with a jigsaw while looking into the camera while evidently unwell." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;McGeoch Family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Delilah McGeoch was taken into hospital and diagnosed with Kawasaki disease aged only two&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The mum of a toddler diagnosed with a rare disease has called for greater awareness of the condition among parents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ashleigh McGeogh's two-year-old daughter Delilah was diagnosed with Kawasaki disease - a condition that is the leading cause of acquired heart disease in UK children - after 10 days of illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She was told by doctors that the condition could have become extremely serious if it had been spotted even a day later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now the Paisley mum is hoping other families can learn about the disease and spot possible symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="links-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 djqsWD"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-666b6d83-0 sc-c4fb5674-0 jYmMqa doYqeg"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="links-title" class="sc-c4fb5674-2 bBuHEW"&gt;Stories you may have missed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-devon-68098003" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Kawasaki disease&lt;/a&gt; - named after the Japanese paediatrician who discovered it, Tomisaku Kawasaki - causes blood vessels to become inflamed and affects about eight in every 100,000 children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However it can be a difficult condition to spot as several of the symptoms - such as a rash and a high temperature - can easily be mistaken for other viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It is unbelievably hard to diagnose," says Ashleigh, 31.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The problem is the symptoms mimic other viruses, so it's easy to think that they have something else, just a cold or being run down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The first sign of illness was when Delilah's temperature shot up on 2 July last year, and remained that way for several days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIR.0000000000001295" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Medical research states&lt;/a&gt; it is important for a child to be diagnosed with Kawasaki disease and begin treatment as soon as possible, ideally within the first 10 days of the fever appearing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Delilah was diagnosed exactly 10 days after her temperature started rising. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="McGeoch Family A wedding portrait of a couple and their four children. The bride is wearing a white wedding dress, while the groom is in a grey suit and a kilt. Their four children are gathered around them. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;McGeoch Family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Ashleigh and her husband Robert took Delilah to hospital&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Without treatment about one in four children with Kawasaki disease get heart complications. This can be fatal in about 2 or 3% of cases.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However treatment for the disease involves taking intravenous immunoglobulin (IVIG) - a solution of antibodies. This can cause complications in children, meaning doctors wanted to rule out any other illness before diagnosing Delilah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There isn't a test for it and the treatment can have risks as well, so they can't start giving it to young children unless they absolutely know it's Kawasaki disease," explains Ashleigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That meant Ashleigh and her husband Robert had to watch as their daughter suffered a range of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She had all of the symptoms, they came one after the other," said Ashleigh. "The high temperature came first, so I took her to the doctor and they thought it might be tonsilitis so gave her antibiotics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"By the Saturday she was getting worse and started getting golf ball sized lumps on her neck, so I took her to hospital. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She was also dehydrated and they thought it was a lymph node infection. They sent her home with antibiotics and some apple juice to drink." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="McGeoch Family A young girl with blond hair smiles into the camera while wearing a bright white and light pink dress. She is leaning against a wall." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;McGeoch Family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Ashleigh feels Delilah is now much more like her usual self after receiving treatment &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ashleigh stressed she did not blame doctors at Glasgow's Royal Hospital for Children for not diagnosing Delilah's condition faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She believes it simply shows how hard it is to be sure a child has Kawasaki disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Delilah's other symptoms included bloodshot eyes, swollen fingers, skin peeling off her hands and feet, a rash, cracked lips and a swollen, red, bumpy tongue - known as strawberry tongue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"On the Monday she was really unwell and was admitted to hospital," says Ashleigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was just one thing after the other. When she was admitted to hospital they mentioned Kawasaki disease, but wanted to rule everything else out first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We were getting frustrated as we couldn't understand why they couldn't start her on the treatment first. It was really hard watching her being poked with needles umpteen times a day, just really stressful for her and for us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Early diagnosis of Kawasaki disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Delilah soon improved after being given treatment, and Ashleigh remembers her daughter being more like her usual self within hours of taking IVIG.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She still has to undergo regular tests on her heart and has a weakened immune system, but otherwise has a clean bill of health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Ashleigh hopes that her family's experience can help other families to be aware of the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She is backing a new campaign called Light a Landmark, which will see buildings like the Glasgow Science Centre lit up in red across the country later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Robert Tulloh, a paediatric cardiologist and the chairman of the charity &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.societi.org.uk/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;the Societi Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, said: "Early diagnosis and rapid treatment reduces the risk of children with Kawasaki Disease suffering from devastating heart damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Awareness of the signs and symptoms in the UK will help significantly with this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:08:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9wVDZLaWR5ZkJSYko3b0dGSS1Ja29pSzdPdHZrVjdrUEZXcVpXQl9ORHRJNG14TW9tYzRRMG5mQ194THdQVTdvcnkzUGViWUx6dXVOUHRPOVZjZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE5JZHRUMFRtMEN2WE1KcXNYX2ZQel9Jc0Mzc3puOGMtQy1paUJ5TnBYNjFjdjVOckNBN01BbzZqUHdIdVRnc3RfYjJoQVRpZXZVd3UxRTJ1YnhnQ0V5YkQw</guid></item><item><title>我女儿的罕见川崎病被及时发现- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/ce8r20e66d0o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;My toddler's rare disease was spotted with 24 hours to spare&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3fbd/live/e685c080-f876-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="McGeoch Family A young toddler in a hospital bed. She has a drip attached to her arm, and is playing with a jigsaw while looking into the camera while evidently unwell." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;McGeoch Family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Delilah McGeoch was taken into hospital and diagnosed with Kawasaki disease aged only two&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The mum of a toddler diagnosed with a rare disease has called for greater awareness of the condition among parents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ashleigh McGeogh's two-year-old daughter Delilah was diagnosed with Kawasaki disease - a condition that is the leading cause of acquired heart disease in UK children - after 10 days of illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She was told by doctors that the condition could have become extremely serious if it had been spotted even a day later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now the Paisley mum is hoping other families can learn about the disease and spot possible symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="links-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 djqsWD"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-666b6d83-0 sc-c4fb5674-0 jYmMqa doYqeg"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="links-title" class="sc-c4fb5674-2 bBuHEW"&gt;Stories you may have missed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-devon-68098003" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Kawasaki disease&lt;/a&gt; - named after the Japanese paediatrician who discovered it, Tomisaku Kawasaki - causes blood vessels to become inflamed and affects about eight in every 100,000 children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However it can be a difficult condition to spot as several of the symptoms - such as a rash and a high temperature - can easily be mistaken for other viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It is unbelievably hard to diagnose," says Ashleigh, 31.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The problem is the symptoms mimic other viruses, so it's easy to think that they have something else, just a cold or being run down."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The first sign of illness was when Delilah's temperature shot up on 2 July last year, and remained that way for several days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIR.0000000000001295" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Medical research states&lt;/a&gt; it is important for a child to be diagnosed with Kawasaki disease and begin treatment as soon as possible, ideally within the first 10 days of the fever appearing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Delilah was diagnosed exactly 10 days after her temperature started rising. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/08af/live/0504e950-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="McGeoch Family A wedding portrait of a couple and their four children. The bride is wearing a white wedding dress, while the groom is in a grey suit and a kilt. Their four children are gathered around them. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;McGeoch Family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Ashleigh and her husband Robert took Delilah to hospital&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Without treatment about one in four children with Kawasaki disease get heart complications. This can be fatal in about 2 or 3% of cases.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However treatment for the disease involves taking intravenous immunoglobulin (IVIG) - a solution of antibodies. This can cause complications in children, meaning doctors wanted to rule out any other illness before diagnosing Delilah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"There isn't a test for it and the treatment can have risks as well, so they can't start giving it to young children unless they absolutely know it's Kawasaki disease," explains Ashleigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That meant Ashleigh and her husband Robert had to watch as their daughter suffered a range of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She had all of the symptoms, they came one after the other," said Ashleigh. "The high temperature came first, so I took her to the doctor and they thought it might be tonsilitis so gave her antibiotics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"By the Saturday she was getting worse and started getting golf ball sized lumps on her neck, so I took her to hospital. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She was also dehydrated and they thought it was a lymph node infection. They sent her home with antibiotics and some apple juice to drink." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e74e/live/0d90de80-f877-11f0-9bbf-e1d63eeffb0a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="McGeoch Family A young girl with blond hair smiles into the camera while wearing a bright white and light pink dress. She is leaning against a wall." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;McGeoch Family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Ashleigh feels Delilah is now much more like her usual self after receiving treatment &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ashleigh stressed she did not blame doctors at Glasgow's Royal Hospital for Children for not diagnosing Delilah's condition faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She believes it simply shows how hard it is to be sure a child has Kawasaki disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Delilah's other symptoms included bloodshot eyes, swollen fingers, skin peeling off her hands and feet, a rash, cracked lips and a swollen, red, bumpy tongue - known as strawberry tongue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"On the Monday she was really unwell and was admitted to hospital," says Ashleigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was just one thing after the other. When she was admitted to hospital they mentioned Kawasaki disease, but wanted to rule everything else out first. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We were getting frustrated as we couldn't understand why they couldn't start her on the treatment first. It was really hard watching her being poked with needles umpteen times a day, just really stressful for her and for us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Early diagnosis of Kawasaki disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Delilah soon improved after being given treatment, and Ashleigh remembers her daughter being more like her usual self within hours of taking IVIG.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She still has to undergo regular tests on her heart and has a weakened immune system, but otherwise has a clean bill of health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Ashleigh hopes that her family's experience can help other families to be aware of the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She is backing a new campaign called Light a Landmark, which will see buildings like the Glasgow Science Centre lit up in red across the country later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Professor Robert Tulloh, a paediatric cardiologist and the chairman of the charity &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.societi.org.uk/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;the Societi Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, said: "Early diagnosis and rapid treatment reduces the risk of children with Kawasaki Disease suffering from devastating heart damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Awareness of the signs and symptoms in the UK will help significantly with this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:08:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9wVDZLaWR5ZkJSYko3b0dGSS1Ja29pSzdPdHZrVjdrUEZXcVpXQl9ORHRJNG14TW9tYzRRMG5mQ194THdQVTdvcnkzUGViWUx6dXVOUHRPOVZjZw</guid></item><item><title>为什么我们早餐吃错了，吃早餐的最佳时间-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/diet/nutrition/healthy-breakfast-habits/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;Ultimately, exactly what you eat and when should be tailored to your routine. Here are their recommendations:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;How to approach breakfast if...&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-colour"&gt;You’re an early riser&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Kinross’s advice is simple: if you wake at 6am naturally, try to eat between 6.30 and 7.30am – and definitely before 8am.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hope mostly agrees: if you’re trying to stay full with a long day ahead, “it can be helpful to wait for about an hour, maybe an hour and a half” before you eat, to keep you going until lunch and make sure you’ve fully digested last night’s meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-colour"&gt;You struggle with mornings&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Should you not feel alert when you wake up, it’s tempting to reach for a big mug of coffee to help you get out the door, but Hope advises against this as doing so “can cause a big spike of cortisol, making you feel much more stressed”. Eating first slows the release of caffeine into your system, helping you to feel alert for longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugar is best avoided entirely. If you wake up groggy, a savoury breakfast will make sure you don’t crash later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-colour"&gt;You wake up ravenous&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Well done – it means you’ve likely fasted correctly and your circadian rhythm is in sync with your gut,” Dr Kinross says. Just bear in mind Hope’s advice that breakfast should make up about a fifth of your daily calorie intake, to leave room for two more square meals and some healthy snacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Aim to eat by satisfying your hunger without spiking your glucose,” Dr Kinross says, as “despite the urge to eat everything in sight, you need stable energy throughout the day”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-colour"&gt;You don’t feel hungry until the afternoon&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you consume any food, your body releases the hormone insulin to tackle it. The release of insulin can affect the release of other hormones in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So even if you don’t feel hungry, it’s best to eat something, even if small, particularly if you’re a woman, as “having something to eat soon after you wake is crucial to keeping the hormonal system stable”, Hope says. A handful of nuts and a few berries will do. “Never eat anything that comes in a bar form and don’t believe anyone who tells you that you can drink your breakfast,” adds Dr Kinross.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-colour"&gt;You exercise before work&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re planning to do cardiovascular exercise early in the morning, it’s wise to eat something relatively light but high in carbohydrates before you do, to fuel your body. Wong recommends “a banana and some peanut butter or a square of dark chocolate before your workout, followed by your full breakfast afterwards”.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPdjVTcGJCY253eUhvbm1wNXVHbGVSR3hCdkJOSHJPdklnc0p3VU5xVlBHcTJ5UG5QNV9sS0V4SDFHRXNSZW1nb2YtTS1HN3NiMlJuSTktZC0tQ01oVEZyOXg1U1V3RFQwbjF1aFlCQlE0OHA1OXJZSnF3Ykx0YjlkT3R1cFE4RUMtYWpB</guid></item><item><title>脂肪性肝病：您可能从未测试过的日益严重的威胁-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/health/fatty-liver-disease-the-growing-threat-you-have-probably-never-tested-for/articleshow/127521573.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fatty liver sounds harmless. But it isn’t. It’s a condition where excess fat builds up in the liver, and over time, it can mess up one of the hardest-working organs in your body. What’s worrying is how fast it’s spreading in India, and how little we talk about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decade or two ago, fatty liver was mostly linked to heavy drinking. That’s changed. Today, the bigger driver is lifestyle. Long work hours, sitting too much, food that’s quick but not great, and stress that never really switches off. And yes, alcohol still plays a role, but a large chunk of cases now fall under non-alcoholic fatty liver disease, or NAFLD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Fatty liver: What are the symptoms, risk factors? How to manage it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Fatty liver disease, now officially termed Metabolic Dysfunction-Associated Steatotic Liver Disease or MASLD, occurs when fat accumulates in more than 5% of liver cells in the absence of significant alcohol consumption," says Dr. Gagandeep Singh, MBBS, Founder – Redial Clinic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;India is seeing a strange mix right now. On one hand, rising incomes and urban living. On the other, less physical movement and diets packed with refined carbs, sugar, and ultra-processed snacks. So even people who don’t “look unhealthy” can have fatty liver. Thin outside, fat inside, as doctors sometimes say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The condition has reached epidemic proportions in India. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meta-analyses estimate that approximately one in three Indian adults now has fatty liver, a pooled prevalence of around 38.6%. In urban populations and high-risk groups such as those with diabetes or obesity, this figure exceeds 50%," says Dr Gagandeep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo   id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;So why don’t we hear about it more?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of the problem is that fatty liver is sneaky. In the early stages, it usually doesn’t hurt. No pain, no obvious symptoms, nothing dramatic enough to send someone to a doctor. Maybe some tiredness, a bit of discomfort. Easy to ignore. And because routine health checkups in India don’t always include liver imaging, many cases slip through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s also a mindset issue. Liver disease, for many people, still equals alcohol. So if someone doesn’t drink much, they assume their liver must be fine. Doctors do try to explain otherwise, but public awareness campaigns haven’t really caught up yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then there’s stigma. Talking about liver problems can feel awkward, like it automatically puts you in the “bad habits” box. So people avoid the conversation altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In order to clear confusion around fatty liver, Dr Gagandeep has answered a few common queries around the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo   id-r-component " data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why do many people with fatty liver have no symptoms at all?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Gagandeep Singh:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The liver is remarkably stoic. It has no pain receptors within its tissue, and it possesses extraordinary functional reserve, you can lose significant liver function before any symptoms appear. This is precisely what makes fatty liver so dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the early stages, simple steatosis, the liver compensates. Patients feel entirely normal. There's no pain, no jaundice, no obvious warning signs. Even standard liver enzymes like ALT and AST can remain within normal ranges despite substantial fat accumulation. Studies show that liver enzymes may be normal in a significant proportion of individuals even when there is considerable hepatic fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the time symptoms emerge, fatigue, right upper abdominal discomfort, unexplained weight loss, the disease has often progressed to inflammation (steatohepatitis) or even early fibrosis. The liver has been silently accumulating damage for years, sometimes decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is why I tell patients: the absence of symptoms is not the absence of disease. Fatty liver is diagnosed by looking, not by feeling. Without proactive screening in at-risk individuals, we're catching this condition far too late in its natural history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo   id-r-component " data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who is most at risk for fatty liver disease, even if they don't drink alcohol?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Gagandeep Singh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The obvious candidates are individuals with obesity, Type 2 diabetes, or metabolic syndrome. But here's what catches many patients and even physicians off-guard: lean individuals can absolutely develop fatty liver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research consistently shows that fatty liver occurs in individuals who are not obese, particularly in Asian populations. In India, studies have found that a substantial proportion of NAFLD patients have BMI below 25. The critical driver isn't total body weight, it's where the fat accumulates. Visceral adiposity, fat around the organs, matters far more than subcutaneous fat. An individual with a normal BMI but increased waist circumference and insulin resistance is at significant risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond metabolic factors, consider these high-risk groups: individuals with polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS), those with a family history of diabetes or fatty liver, people with sleep apnoea, and those with sedentary occupations. The IT sector workforce deserves special mention, recent research from Hyderabad found alarming MAFLD prevalence among IT employees, driven by prolonged sitting, irregular meal patterns, and high stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Age matters too, risk increases with age, though we're now seeing fatty liver in children and young adults, particularly those with childhood obesity. If you have central obesity, insulin resistance, or prediabetes, you should be screened regardless of your overall weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo   id-r-component " data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who should be screened? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Gagandeep Singh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone with Type 2 diabetes, obesity (especially central obesity), metabolic syndrome, PCOS, or persistently elevated liver enzymes. I wouldalso recommend screening for individuals with a strong family history of diabetes or liver disease, those with sleep apnoea, and anyone with unexplained fatigue alongside metabolic risk factors. Given the high prevalence in India, a case can be made for screening all adults over 40 with even one metabolic risk factor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo   id-r-component " data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What common diet habits silently worsen fatty liver?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Gagandeep Singh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several dietary patterns drive hepatic fat accumulation, often without patients realising the connection:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugar-sweetened beverages and fruit juices: These are perhaps the single worst offenders. Fructose, whether from table sugar, high-fructose corn syrup, or "natural" fruit juices, is metabolised almost exclusively by the liver. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Refined carbohydrates: White rice, maida-based products, processed snacks, these spike insulin levels repeatedly throughout the day, promoting fat storage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="82"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultra-processed foods: Beyond their refined carbohydrate content, these contain emulsifiers, preservatives, and industrial seed oils that may disrupt gut barrier function and promote inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="84"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sedentary lifestyle: This worsens body composition with more visceral fat and less muscle mass, and subsequently deranging overall metabolic profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inadequate protein: Without sufficient protein (I recommend 25-30 grams per meal), the body cannot maintain muscle mass. Sarcopenia, muscle loss, actually worsens fatty liver by reducing the body's capacity to handle glucose and triglycerides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo   id-r-component " data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Are liver detox drinks and supplements actually helpful or harmful?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Gagandeep Singh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let me be direct: liver detox products are, at best, a waste of money. At worst, they can cause the very liver damage they claim to prevent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The liver doesn't need external "detoxification". It processes toxins, medications, and metabolic waste continuously, 24 hours a day. The concept that toxins "accumulate" in the liver and require special juices or supplements to flush out has no proof in biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="98"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Johns Hopkins hepatologists, there are no clinical data supporting the efficacy of liver cleanses. More concerning, dietary supplements are increasingly recognised as a cause of drug-induced liver injury. Research from the Acute Liver Failure Study Group found that herbal-dietary supplements accounted for 16% of severe drug-induced liver injury cases requiring hospitalisation (&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S1542356525009425" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;DOI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="103"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specific concerns include green tea extract in concentrated supplement form (associated with hepatotoxicity at high doses), turmeric supplements containing piperine (case reports of significant liver injury exist — &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cureus.com/articles/405932-drug-induced-liver-injury-secondary-to-turmeric-supplement-containing-piperine-a-case-report" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;DOI&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;), and various proprietary "liver cleanse" formulations with undisclosed ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="107"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to support your liver, skip the supplements and focus on what actually works: dietary modification, exercise, weight management, and alcohol moderation. Your liver doesn't need a detox, it needs you to stop overwhelming it with excess calories and processed foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="111"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo   id-r-component " data-pos="112"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What are the top lifestyle changes you recommend to protect liver health?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Gagandeep Singh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;I approach liver health through what I call coordinated metabolic rehabilitation — addressing root causes rather than symptoms. Here are the interventions with the strongest evidence:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="115"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo   id-r-component " data-pos="116"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Time-restricted eating: After twelve years of practising intermittent fasting myself and implementing it with hundreds of patients, I've found that 14-16 hour fasting windows improve insulin sensitivity more reliably than calorie counting alone. During fasting, insulin levels drop, allowing the liver to shift from fat storage to fat oxidation. The key is consistency — pick an eating window that fits your lifestyle and maintain it.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Body recomposition, not just weight loss: I've stopped telling patients to simply "lose weight." The goal is losing fat while preserving or building muscle. Crash diets that sacrifice muscle for quick weight loss actually worsen long-term metabolic health. A 10-15% reduction in body weight, achieved gradually with adequate protein intake, produces more durable improvements than aggressive restriction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Resistance training: This is non-negotiable. According to PubMed research, resistance training is effective in reducing risk factors for metabolic syndrome and fatty liver by optimizing muscle and liver function (&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-031-88361-3_26" data-type="tilCustomLink" target="_blank"&gt;DOI&lt;/a&gt;). Aim for two to three sessions weekly, focusing on major muscle groups.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protein prioritisation: Every meal should contain adequate protein — 25-30 grams. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eliminate sugar-sweetened beverages: Replace sodas, packaged juices, and sweetened chai with water, black coffee, or unsweetened tea.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coordinated care: A physician adjusting medications and monitoring progress, a nutritionist customising meal plans within cultural preferences, and a fitness professional building sustainable exercise habits, this triangle of care succeeds where isolated dietary advice fails. Patients aren't lacking motivation; they're lacking a system.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="117"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The evidence is clear: fatty liver is not a life sentence. With early intervention and sustained lifestyle modification, reversal is achievable for many patients. But reversal requires action — and that action needs to start before symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="121"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Medical experts consulted &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="123"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="124"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="125"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article includes expert inputs shared with TOI Health by: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="127"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Gagandeep Singh, MBBS, Founder – Redial Clinic&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="129"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inputs were used to explain why fatty liver is not being talked about enough despite being a silently growing crisis in India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2gFBVV95cUxPenczb2swRXFBTmlHeG0tem9kdkpETjJrSUNzbGFUYV9hcld2UDlMM3VrN2NjV1k2bEhoVEJnaEQ5TnRBcnlETjZkWWY5dV9hQ2p6TW9qRkRPSl96ckNJa21TUGEzOTlGWUZjaXZSbEloUUZud1VyRDM4WXN6S29aSVZUQUhQMkdPdGNQRHhjZVJabGJaUHk4dFNyUGN5ekNyVzh0WEJqeWRMbUNHdU8za3BVVzdNNkhPR0F4LVQ2V3NLRTcwX2ZPYXlkeno0bnp1UE5oa3B5TE15QdIB3wFBVV95cUxOQzBUeE1wN2hrOEkyUEhfWWRpWl9pYmZjTnNULVNBQzJ3cHFtOGhLMjhidlc4ZFpnck1scTVMV0M2WFBtVk03TkFuQ0hKZHg0djc5LWI5Q2ViWHF0bkhvVUNsNmxQa2VfUjI3TmstUkpCNVZhWFpXM0pQYTN2N1JuWk82SHIzUzA3b0NVUk9qNGhPcnJzZUpXM1NRWjQ4UEJFT0dOclQ2eE1kSTRyMy1BSEt5MXZkSXNJLXNsREFxS3k4TFY3VHpGeUVuX2VOdUNWNEdkUTBDMHhFT25ZMkJZ</guid></item><item><title>根除天花的领导者William Foege博士去世- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/dr-william-foege-leader-smallpox-eradication-dies-129543666</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;ATLANTA -- &lt;/span&gt;Dr. William Foege, a leader of one of humanity's greatest public health victories — the global eradication of smallpox — has died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Foege died Saturday in Atlanta at the age of 89, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.taskforce.org/bill-foege-tribute/"&gt;according to&lt;/a&gt; the Task Force for Global Health, which he co-founded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The 6-foot-7 inch Foege literally stood out in the field of public health. A whip-smart medical doctor with a calm demeanor, he had a canny knack for beating back infectious diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He was director of the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention in the late 1970s and early 1980s, and later held other key leadership roles in campaigns against international health problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But his greatest achievement came before all that, with his work on smallpox, one of the most lethal diseases in human history. For centuries, it killed about one-third of the people it infected and left most survivors with deep scars on their faces from the pus-filled lesions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Smallpox vaccination campaigns were well established by the time Foege was a young doctor. Indeed, it was no longer seen in the United States. But infections were still occurring elsewhere, and efforts to stamp them out were stalling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Working as a medical missionary in Nigeria in the 1960s, Foege and his colleagues developed a "ring containment" strategy, in which a smallpox outbreak was contained by identifying each smallpox case and vaccinating everyone who the patients might come into contact with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The method relied heavily on quick detective work and was born out of necessity. There simply wasn't enough vaccine available to immunize everyone, Foege wrote in "House on Fire," his 2011 book about the smallpox eradication effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;It worked, and became pivotal in helping rid the world of smallpox for good. The last naturally occurring case was seen in Somalia in 1977. In 1980, the World Health Organization declared smallpox eradicated from the Earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"If you look at the simple metric of who has saved the most lives, he is right up there with the pantheon. Smallpox eradication has prevented hundreds of millions of deaths," said former CDC director Dr. Tom Frieden, who consulted with Foege regularly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Foege was born March 12, 1936. His father was a Lutheran minister, but he became interested in medicine at 13 while working at a drugstore in Colville, Washington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He got his medical degree from the University of Washington in 1961 and a master's in public health from Harvard in 1965.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He was director of the Atlanta-based CDC from 1977 to 1983, then held other international public health leadership roles, including stints as executive director at The Carter Center and senior fellow at the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In 2012, President Barack Obama presented Foege with the Medal of Freedom, the nation's highest civilian honor. In 2016, while awarding Foege an honorary degree, Duke University President President Richard Brodhead called him "the Father of Global Health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“Bill Foege had an unflagging commitment to improving the health of people across the world, through powerful, purpose-driven coalitions applying the best science available,” Task Force for Global Health CEO Dr. Patrick O’Carroll said in a statement. "We try to honor that commitment in every one of our programs, every day.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Jack Dura contributed to this report from Bismarck, North Dakota.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:22:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxPbnA1ZEE1TUcybEpVczRVVWRpTlUwVDZzMWdWX0Zfc1NCemN4UWNYMnNLRDZ2Mlktb25IMWw3Ymdpald6UF8temlzTHZaVmJTdDRZdl9IMjhXVHZtRFE5eHZVSl95TnJXV3JvZFhGdkpWWk4zbUt5YXRpUjJXQXRBbnlKbEtZeGNPMXloVXdOZXFRUFJlRlg2LVVnMVg4UGo10gGmAUFVX3lxTE5wTnNyT1JHVURWUFdyeVo5UzdYZHhnUWs2dVVpVHBmMnVuQUZRYlRXMmdiWWc3S1p1NVF5RjdDMnhnOTRiZ29wLTJ2aDgxbEExV3dpSmt4NzluUm1XcjBPNnNpVTNneGJMaVJrSkxvWXZzczhwR2k2VFpfVTV6cW03czRoOGVVN1RTMDZKOG5GZkhubktMSGV4VWJUY0JKM29DYzY3bWc</guid></item><item><title>医生无视新的联邦疫苗建议，坚持科学- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/26/health/vaccine-recommendations-cdc-aap</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrffriy000x26p77v68f0xs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The American Academy of Pediatrics on Monday released its updated recommendations for what vaccines children should get. It’s a routine revision, hardly different from last year’s recommendations, but it carries more significance this year: More states and doctors are relying on it instead of a controversial new schedule from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrpy4bv00033b6s31z7ozt1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The AAP’s newest recommendations include a new immunization against respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) and a few other minor adjustments — a stark difference from the sweeping changes abruptly made to the CDC vaccine schedule this month.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksq9pwd00013b6sp58ql1sw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Although the CDC schedule has long been the default guide to vaccination across the country, many doctors say they’re now choosing the AAP’s guidelines instead.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70006336po0aq7tw5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The science hasn’t changed,” said Dr. Claudia Hoyen, a pediatric infectious disease specialist and director of pediatric innovation at UH Rainbow Babies and Children’s Hospital in Cleveland. “We will continue to follow the science.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70003336pd2qqmt53@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The AAP continues to broadly recommend routine immunization against RSV, hepatitis A, hepatitis B, rotavirus, flu and meningococcal disease. Twelve major medical and health care organizations have formally endorsed its recommendations, including the American Medical Association, the National Medical Association and the American Academy of Family Physicians.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkst331000043b6swrnvdk62@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In contrast, the updated CDC schedule narrowed recommendations for protection against meningococcal disease, hepatitis B and hepatitis A to children who are at higher risk for infections. It also recommends that choices on vaccinations against flu, Covid-19 and rotavirus be based on “shared clinical decision-making,” which means people who want one must consult with a health care provider.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkslzh9l00003b6s6nq03rvw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “After an exhaustive review of the evidence, we are aligning the U.S. childhood vaccine schedule with international consensus while strengthening transparency and informed consent,” US Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. said after the vaccine schedule update. “This decision protects children, respects families, and rebuilds trust in public health.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrgx0330003336pq4kt2xtr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There were no safety issues or new research to suggest that the vaccines on the CDC’s previous schedule weren’t necessary.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70004336pwfwo7g2x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For now, unfortunately, we have to ignore everything about vaccines that is coming from our federal government,” said Dr. Sean O’Leary, chair of the AAP’s Committee on Infectious Diseases. “Parents should trust their pediatrician, trust the professional societies like the American Academy of Pediatrics.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70005336pku0unz2c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The half-dozen pediatricians who spoke with CNN they said they’ll stick with the AAP’s guidance.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70007336p1l18yxtr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Sarah Elizabeth DeRoo, a pediatrician at Children’s National in Washington, DC, says that she will continue to share “very candidly” with families about vaccines and that “we know they’re safe and effective.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksvg0fn000b3b6sm35p9dwi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When the CDC’s vaccine schedule changed this month, she said, it undermined some parents’ confidence.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70008336p76t2jpzt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We have families that come into our clinic that traditionally have been very accepting of vaccines and they want to know, ‘is this new recommendation, is this evidence-based, or do I need to think differently about these vaccines’ that they’ve accepted previously?” DeRoo said. “We’ve been giving messaging to our patients that we’re continuing to follow the recommended schedule by the American Academy of Pediatrics, which is an evidence- based schedule.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrso6q1000a3b6scfhomac4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The disconnect between advice from the CDC and from doctors has confused and even scared some parents.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70002336pj5zbjyga@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We are seeing the vaccine conversation come up more and more frequently because of&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;fear of this and general misinformation spreading online,” said Dr. Nina Alfieri, Continuity Clinic director with Lurie Children’s Pediatrics at Uptown in Chicago. “We always want families to feel welcome coming to clinic with their questions.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70009336p6xgky1u9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Adam Ratner, a pediatric infectious disease specialist at NYU, said he gets why parents are asking more questions.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksv4zcv00053b6sgnhd6yrb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We’ve had so many years of the CDC being a reliable source of information,” he said. “It’s understandable why families are confused.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000a336phoe299i5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Historically, states have followed CDC recommendations, but most say they will now follow AAP recommendations instead, &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/state-health-policy-data/state-recommendations-for-routine-childhood-vaccines-increasing-departure-from-federal-guidelines/" target="_blank"&gt;according to KFF&lt;/a&gt;, a health policy organization.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000b336p9inc8k93@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As of January 20, KFF found, 28 states were giving advice that deviates from federal guidelines for some or all childhood vaccines. Although it’s not clear how states will handle vaccine requirements for schools, what is clear is that there is a real blue/red divide on which vaccine advice to follow, according to Jen Kates, a co-author of the analysis.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000c336prcu8ic9f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            All states with Democratic governors have announced that they won’t follow federal guidelines. Only four states led by Republicans have done the same.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000d336phnzmyi44@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For the first time in our country, we’re going to have really varying laws, policies and attitudes about vaccines based on where people live,” Kates said. “It’s a major sea change in public health policy.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000e336p8ops78zy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Hoyen&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; of UH Rainbow Babies and Children’s, has been practicing medicine for 30 years and said she doesn’t want to go back to the pre-vaccine days. She remembers a colleague&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;who was deaf in one ear because of a childhood case of mumps and another in the same class who was deaf in one ear because of meningitis.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksv7ut000073b6saolln0i0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Meningitis was so common before the Haemophilus influenzae type b (Hib) vaccine came into use in 1987, she remembers, that pediatricians routinely kept spinal tap equipment on hand.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000f336p5xbeqzs5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “They’d do the taps in the office, give them a dose of penicillin or whatever and send them straight to the hospital,” Hoyen said. “There’s a reason why these vaccines were created. It’s to help kids thrive and not to have to worry about complications from these childhood illnesses.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000g336pcgyyhilg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            O’Leary also doesn’t want to go back to the pre-vaccine era. He trained to be a doctor in the 1990s, before there was a vaccine against rotavirus.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksvae9f00093b6s9ub0ul28@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We had three seasons. In the winter, we had influenza season, we had RSV season, and we had rotavirus season. Heaven forbid if they all hit at the same time, because we’d be overwhelmed. Now, we don’t have a rotavirus season, and we’re seeing a very big impact on RSV season with the new product,” O’Leary said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000h336pdv9s6b5c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            DeRoo, who has only been caring for children during what she called “the vaccine era,” says she’s been trying to refresh her knowledge of what vaccine-preventable diseases look like.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkstb4lj000c3b6s72fb2fl4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We have to rethink how we’re approaching people who walk in and are sick in the clinic, to make sure that we take all the appropriate precautions in the event that they may not be fully immunized,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000i336p36h6kzak@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Ratner said a measles outbreak in New York a few years ago was the first time many of his colleagues had ever seen a case.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkstbn7b000e3b6ss4msiw9e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I think, given the way that things are going in this country, that is likely to change,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000j336p1qe5s2w1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The idea of going backwards is horrifying because you don’t want to lose hard-won progress, but also because we’re not talking about something abstract,” Ratner said. “We’re talking about actual children and families.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:01:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE9hNS1uYUtOTkk1cGgzQWhGd2dlWVRLeE91N2UyM0hua3dqNUNyX2szWFNvUDltdDFTdE4yYThRNmFZSE5sU0FpMFR6dW1sXzFJUTZYdm1oczNuRkF3SFkxVk9KV29SUDJ2Z1BxS1FMYlc4U3N1bk41NA</guid></item><item><title>女性正在分享男性医生完全解雇她们的时间，这非常可怕- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/scarymouse/women-share-when-male-doctors-dismiss-them</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-22
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="140030743" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;Well, that was all a little heavy. Remember, everyone, the moral of the story is NOT to avoid seeing your doctor; it's to be clear and firm with your doctor, and make sure your needs are met. Stay safe and healthy, everyone!&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please note: some comments have been edited for length and/or clarity.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 01:31:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNOXlrME9fWTRuV25ZanQ3MjZkVG9HSm5MdWtBeGVBbU9aaUhhTlNXWVltWTg3elRtNlpONldpUEQxYTNSSEhmeHFxUkh1OUxVdXpDanVOeWlZaHViRUljeWJBNVg0VUFkYlFxWVRvNk91MmN4SkhMZGNQaklYdW4wLUpKSVA</guid></item><item><title>这是小RFK的疫苗故事不想让你听到-壁垒</title><link>https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div dir="auto" class="body markup"&gt;&lt;div class="captioned-image-container"&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/$s_!NtdN!,f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F12ba8ba3-6b12-420d-a4ea-30ba4e5b8362_2100x1500.jpeg" data-component-name="Image2ToDOM" rel class="image-link image2 is-viewable-img can-restack"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="image-caption"&gt;(Composite by Hannah Yoest / Photos: Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS ABOUT FIVE IN THE MORNING on April 1, 2025, when Antoine Archambault heard his four-month-old son, Isaac, fussing from the bedside crib inside their first-floor suburban Paris apartment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was more of a whimper than a wail, as Antoine recalls it, which was pretty typical for a baby even strangers said was unusually upbeat and given to giggling. Isaac was running a fever, but it was a mild one. Antoine gave him paracetamol (acetaminophen) and soon Isaac fell back asleep, seemingly at peace in his fuzzy sleep sack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antoine headed back to bed, hoping to get a little more rest before daybreak. But soon Isaac was up again, because the fever wasn’t going away. Claire Fauvet—Antoine’s partner and Isaac’s mother—had to take an early train to Strasbourg for work, so Antoine bundled up the baby for a short walk to a nearby medical clinic. Father and son arrived right as the doors opened at 8 a.m. and Antoine had no reason to think Isaac had anything more than a routine illness—until staff called an ambulance, for speedy transfer to the university children’s hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why, a panicked Antoine wanted to know. Because, a doctor told him, Isaac might have meningococcal disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nfid.org/infectious-disease/meningococcal/" rel&gt;Meningococcal disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is the ultimate nightmare for pediatricians, and for parents who know about it. It is caused by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Neisseria meningitidis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a bacterium that can invade the bloodstream, the spinal cord, or both. It is spread through close contact with respiratory or oral secretions, colonizing nasal and throat linings. Many people carry it harmlessly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But in rare cases it transforms into invasive disease, striking even healthy people with shocking speed. In a matter of hours, what seems like a routine, flu-like illness transforms into a full-body emergency of shock, blood clotting, and swelling of the brain. Between &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pinkbook/hcp/table-of-contents/chapter-14-meningococcal-disease.html" rel&gt;10 and 15 percent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; of those who get meningococcal disease will die, even with rapid treatment. Many more will suffer permanent &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.meningitis.org/meningitis-in-your-words-home/?types-of-meningitis=132&amp;amp;location-during-illness=&amp;amp;age-at-time-of-illness=&amp;amp;outcome-of-illness=&amp;amp;person-type=&amp;amp;after-effect=&amp;amp;search=1" rel&gt;physical or cognitive impairments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="captioned-image-container"&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/$s_!d82c!,f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fa65e03b6-062c-419e-9173-81e034c5da56_1200x1027.jpeg" data-component-name="Image2ToDOM" rel class="image-link image2 is-viewable-img can-restack"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="image-caption"&gt;Antoine and Isaac. (Courtesy Antoine Archambault and Claire Fauvet.)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Antoine knew a bit about the disease, he explained to me, because he remembered a documentary he had seen about a paralympic &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/05/sport/theo-curin-france-paralympics-spt-intl" rel&gt;swimmer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; who’d lost the outer parts of all four limbs as a child. Antoine also recalls thinking that Isaac was protected against it, because he and Claire were so diligent about getting Isaac his immunizations as soon as he was eligible. “I texted Claire, they suspect meningitis, but wasn’t he vaccinated?” Antoine told me. “And Claire was like, yes he is.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But France’s “schedule”—the list of vaccines required for public child care and school, and covered by national health insurance—had until recently excluded one of the two available meningococcal shots, each one being necessary for protection against different biological strains. A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.service-public.gouv.fr/particuliers/actualites/A17982?lang=en" rel&gt;new requirement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for the second version had taken effect on January 1, right after Isaac was born, and his appointment to get the vaccine was on the books. But it was not for another six weeks. That meant he remained at the mercy of the community around him, which—without widespread vaccination—included plenty of meningococcal carriers. Evidently one had given it to him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next few hours remain a blur, Antoine told me. “I lost my footing, I lost my step, my legs were shaking all day,” he said, reaching for the English words to capture a state of mind as much as anything physical. Less than twenty-four hours before, Antoine had been playing with Isaac at an outdoor café, drawing out the baby’s smile with a favorite stuffed monkey that played music when you squeezed it. When Claire had rocked Isaac to sleep by holding him close to her chest, in what had become their routine, he had seemed absolutely fine. Now doctors were putting him into a medical coma, which they said was his best hope for survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claire, who had rushed back to Paris by train, arrived at the hospital not long after that and for a while it looked like treatment might work. Isaac’s vital signs even improved for a bit. But the recovery was illusory and his condition deteriorated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His heart stopped three times. Doctors were able to revive him after the first two. They were not after the third. At 6:35 p.m., Isaac was gone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;EARLIER THIS MONTH, Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. announced the CDC would be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/05/childhood-vaccine-schedule-new-cdc-recommendation-11-shots/" rel&gt;removing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; several &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/cdc-childhood-vaccine-schedule-changes-diseases-history-data/" rel&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; from the list that it recommends for all American children. Among those CDC took off the list is the newer meningococcal vaccine, which has an excellent safety record and since its introduction had reduced the incidence of the disease in this country by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/vpd/mening/hcp/about-vaccine.html#:~:text=Immunogenicity%20and%20Vaccine%20Effectiveness,at%20risk%20for%20meningococcal%20disease." rel&gt;90 percent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Under the new guidelines, the agency recommends the shot only for high-risk groups (like people who are immunocompromised or college freshmen living in close quarters). For others, the agency suggests “&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/20/shared-decision-making-vaccine-guidance-twists-meaning-of-term/" rel&gt;shared clinical decision-making&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;,” meaning parents should discuss with their doctors whether the shots are advisable for their children.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exactly how much will change—and exactly when—is hard to say. Insurers will continue to pay for the vaccines, administration officials said, as will a government-run program that administers immunizations to low-income children. Decisions about whether to require shots for school will remain with states, as they always have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But physicians, state officials, and insurers all use CDC recommendations to guide their own decisions and advice. That’s one reason the recommendations &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/06/what-new-vaccine-schedule-means-doctors-parents-kids/" rel&gt;matter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; so much, including to people like Kennedy with long histories of hostility to vaccines. Another is that the guidelines make it possible for Americans without medical training to know what the nation’s most trusted scientists believe, based on their assessment of the latest and best available research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Or at least that’s how it is supposed to work. This month’s retrenchment on vaccine policy—arguably the biggest in American history—is not based on new data or research that’s suddenly become available. Rather, it is based on a reassessment &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/" rel&gt;ordered up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by Kennedy’s boss, President Donald Trump, that compared U.S. recommendations to those in peer countries around the world. “After an exhaustive review of the evidence,” Kennedy said in a statement, “we are aligning the U.S. childhood vaccine schedule with international consensus while strengthening transparency and informed consent.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Like so many other arguments Kennedy has made about vaccines, this claim about “consensus” is simply &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/09/childhood-vaccination-fact-check-denmark-not-america-is-the-outlier/" rel&gt;not true&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. In reality, vaccine recommendations vary across Europe, North America, and Asia, even among peer countries. Before the Trump administration issued its directive this January, the United States was at the high end of the spectrum, with a recommendation of immunization against seventeen diseases. Now it’s at the low end, with a recommendation for twelve—or just one more than Denmark, the European country with the fewest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/robert-kennedy-rfk-jr-denmark-vaccines-hhs-maga-trump" rel&gt;no coincidence&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Trump administration officials have said repeatedly that Denmark was their model, and arranged for a full presentation on the Danish recommendations during December’s meeting of the committee of outsiders that officially advises the CDC. The text of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/assessment-of-the-us-childhood-and-adolescent-immunization-schedule-compared-to-other-countries.pdf" rel&gt;assessment memo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; justifying the decision that the Trump administration released in early January cites “Denmark” or “Danish” authorities thirteen times—by far the most references for any country. A coauthor of the assessment is the same physician who gave the advisory committee presentation—&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/05/19/tracy-beth-hoeg-fda-advisor-marty-makary-vinay-prasad-vaccine-policy/" rel&gt;Tracy Beth Høeg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a sports-medicine specialist who spent part of her career in Copenhagen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/robert-kennedy-rfk-jr-denmark-vaccines-hhs-maga-trump" rel&gt;Denmark&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/12/26/nx-s1-5656214/childhood-vaccination-denmark-rfk-policy" rel&gt;an&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/morning-breakout/viewpoints-denmarks-vaccine-success-cant-be-copied-in-the-us-new-dietary-guidelines-dont-make-sense/" rel&gt;odd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/19/denmark-vaccine-schedule-vs-us/" rel&gt;choice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to be such a singular example given its relatively tiny population of six million people living in a quasi-socialist paradise. A truly “exhaustive” review of the evidence would have also considered some of the larger countries on the continent, especially anywhere the public has been arguing about vaccines or where officials recently changed recommendations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;France turns out to be one such country—and in the case of the vaccine for meningococcal disease, an especially useful one for understanding both the policy debate and very personal meaning it has for families like Antoine’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-attrs='{"url":"https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=share&amp;amp;action=share","text":"Share","action":null,"class":null}' data-component-name="ButtonCreateButton" class="button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=share&amp;amp;action=share" rel class="button primary"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Share&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE OBVIOUS REASON to consider France is that it simply looks a lot more like the United States than Denmark does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It has Western Europe’s third-largest economy, with a population of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statista.com/topics/5677/demography-in-france/?srsltid=AfmBOoqjCMvVTyaJSjkS0bWnfv4aNtMPVk2hjNKxln2OuRC1-QpvHR5p#editorsPicks" rel&gt;nearly 70 million&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that is literally ten times larger than Denmark’s. France doesn’t have the kind of economic inequality that you find in the United States, because no Western or Northern European democracy does, but its &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://worldpopulationreview.com/country-rankings/gini-coefficient-by-country" rel&gt;socioeconomic breakdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; looks more like America’s than Denmark’s. Even the French health care system is a better analogue to that of the United States. It delivers universal coverage through a mixed public-private system in which access can vary depending on insurance type and wealth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But there’s something else about France that makes its experience relevant. Like the United States, France has a vocal &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/01/14/956705043/france-has-1-of-the-highest-rates-of-vaccine-skepticism" rel&gt;anti-vaccination movement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, rooted partly in a political culture supportive of a strong central government but distrustful (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.truedem.eu/resources-and-deliverables/online-survey-2025" rel&gt;by European standards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;) of the people and institutions who run them. “I think we are one of the world champions when it comes to vaccine hesitancy,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://research.pasteur.fr/en/member/muhamed-kheir-taha/" rel&gt;Muhamed Kheir-Taha&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, who directs the invasive bacterial infections unit at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pasteur.fr/en" rel&gt;Institut Pasteur&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in Paris, told me. There’s &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S235239641630398X" rel&gt;survey data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to back that up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That tradition helps explain the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.doi.org/10.1016/j.vaccine.2018.02.095" rel&gt;evolution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.jle.com/en/revues/vir/e-docs/les_nouvelles_obligations_vaccinales_un_tournant_dans_la_politique_de_sante_publique_francaise_311395/article.phtml" rel&gt;French&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://infos.rtl.lu/news/frontieres/la-vaccination-obligatoire-interdite-en-droit-francais-pas-vraiment-1761203" rel&gt;vaccine laws&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. When the earliest vaccines for diseases like smallpox and polio became available during the early and mid-twentieth century, France made them mandatory, meaning they were a requirement for attending school. But as newer vaccines like the measles shot became available, French authorities merely “recommended” the vaccines—which meant, among other things, the national health system didn’t always pay for them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But agitation to change the policies reached a critical mass about twenty years ago, in part because physicians and public health experts worried vaccination rates for diseases like measles and pertussis would fall below herd immunity levels. French officials reacted by commissioning expert reports, and then convening public meetings so that the public had a chance both to hear the recommendations and offer feedback. The effort culminated in a 2017 law that added eight new vaccines to the mandatory list.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The newer meningococcal shot was initially not one of them, because for each vaccine French authorities were weighing the costs and benefits in the context of allocating money in the national health insurance system. They decided those other strains of meningococcal disease were too rare to justify the expense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But the disease turned out to be not so rare after all, with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.santepubliquefrance.fr/les-actualites/2024/infections-invasives-a-meningocoque-recrudescence-de-cas-en-france-en-2023" rel&gt;rising&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.santepubliquefrance.fr/maladies-et-traumatismes/maladies-a-prevention-vaccinale/infections-invasives-a-meningocoque/documents/bulletin-national2/infections-invasives-a-meningocoque-en-france-en-2024" rel&gt;caseloads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s12889-020-09487-7" rel&gt;outbreaks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in communal settings like schools. “We would get a lot of attention from the media for these, even when it was a single case, because they would be touching children or young adults in very good health, and then they may die within hours,” Taha said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;French authorities had a playbook for these situations: They would surge vaccination to the affected areas, aiming to protect people before they could get exposed and develop the condition, while rushing treatment to the afflicted. But meningococcal disease acts so quickly that the surges inevitably were too late for some.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The best way to avoid this disease—we told them—is to prevent the disease, not to treat it afterwards,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gpip.fr/organisation/" rel&gt;Hervé Haas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, president of the French pediatric infectious disease association, explained to me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once again, French authorities listened to the doctors and public health experts: In 2024, they added the second meningococcal vaccine to the mandatory list. The hope is that the requirement will dramatically improve uptake, which is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6607743/" rel&gt;what happened&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; with the vaccines that France made mandatory in 2017.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;THE STRATEGY THAT FRANCE ABANDONED—making the vaccine strictly voluntary, and then surging resources to stop outbreaks once they start—is similar to the one that Kennedy and the Trump administration just embraced. But if you look at that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/assessment-of-the-us-childhood-and-adolescent-immunization-schedule-compared-to-other-countries.pdf" rel&gt;assessment memo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that HHS released in January, you won’t find acknowledgement that the French recently adopted the meningococcal vaccine, let alone an explanation for why the authors believe the United States should be moving in precisely the opposite direction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, you won’t find any references to France—or any signs that memo’s authors seriously studied the experience of European countries other than Denmark. When I asked HHS about this explicitly—whether larger, more comparable nations like France, Germany, and the U.K. had been given the consideration that Denmark had—I got a boilerplate response: “Many peer nations achieve high vaccination rates without mandates by relying on trust, education, and strong doctor-patient relationships,” HHS Press Secretary Emily Hilliard wrote in an email, “and HHS will work with states and clinicians to ensure families have clear, accurate information to make their own informed decisions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hilliard also described the review as “thorough,” echoing what Kennedy has said, although it is a bit difficult to take that seriously when the entirety of the assessment is just thirty pages long. And because it’s a memo justifying decisions on several vaccinations, it gives only scant attention to each. The explanatory section on meningococcal disease is just four paragraphs, or barely 200 words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just for comparison, the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/pdf/rr/rr6202.pdf" rel&gt;document&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; the CDC used in 2013 when first recommending the newer meningococcal vaccine had roughly 18,000 words—on the meningococcal vaccine alone—with highly detailed reviews of research, projections of how different recommendations would play out in the real world, and other sorts of information you’d want officials to consider in making these kinds of decisions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That document is a reflection of the work that went into it—literally years of study and debating, with the CDC director ultimately making decisions after public votes by the outside committee of experts. Nothing like that happened this year, despite Kennedy’s promises of “radical transparency.” The CDC simply announced the decision one day, without warning, with the director signing off on a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/decision-memo-adopting-revised-childhood-adolescent-immunization-schedule.pdf" rel&gt;recommendation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; he got from the heads of three other government agencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Outside of a genuine emergency, our government should not be waking up in the morning, brushing its teeth, and abruptly announcing major shifts in longstanding policy,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/1781/joshua-m-sharfstein" rel&gt;Joshua Sharfstein&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a pediatrician and former deputy FDA commissioner now on faculty at Johns Hopkins University, told me. “The basis for changing course should be released well in advance, reviewed by independent experts, and modified as needed through careful consideration and explanation. It is a process with integrity that distinguishes thoughtful policymaking from a power grab.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-attrs='{"url":"https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=share&amp;amp;action=share","text":"Share","action":null,"class":null}' data-component-name="ButtonCreateButton" class="button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=share&amp;amp;action=share" rel class="button primary"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Share&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;TO RATIONALIZE ITS DECISION, the Trump administration memo cites a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/WER8647" rel&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; from the World Health Organization, which recommended society-wide vaccination only in countries where the case level is higher than it is in the United States. But the primary audience for WHO guidance is officials trying to make the most of scarce medical resources.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That’s not the way things work here, for better or worse depending on your perspective. The American system throws all kinds of money at saving lives—even for interventions that cost way more than vaccination—because that’s what &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://intuitionlabs.ai/articles/icer-vs-nice-drug-pricing-comparison" rel&gt;wealthier countries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; do when they want to prioritize health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Once you’ve seen a case of meningococcal disease, you are thinking my god, I never ever want to see a case like that again,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://advances.massgeneral.org/contributors/contributor.aspx?id=1818" rel&gt;Rochelle Walensky&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, the Harvard-affiliated pediatric infectious disease specialist and former CDC director, told me. “When you have seen a completely viable, young, vibrant person who suddenly obtunded [meaning barely responsive] with bacterial meningitis—and you know their life will never be the same—then the answer is that if there is anything I can do to prevent this, if I can prevent it safely, you’re going to do it.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;One other person who understands all too well the menace of the disease is Antoine. And he wants to do something about it. He and Claire have raised money to support research into the disease and to promote training for medical professionals, so they are better able to recognize it quickly. They’ve worked with local and national groups that are affiliated with the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.meningitis.org/como/" rel&gt;Confederation of Meningitis Organisations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a U.K.-based international organization trying to promote awareness and research worldwide.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They’ve also tried to do what they can to spread the word about the vaccine among friends and professional contacts. (Antoine is a consultant who works with banks on regulatory compliance, and Claire a lawyer.) Antoine told me he got “pretty pissed off” recently when he heard a friend got advice from a doctor not to get the shot, because they were not part of a high-risk group. “This is a big fight for us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before our video call ended, Antoine shared some photos, all of them with Isaac smiling in exactly the way I had been told. And when Antoine was done recounting that awful day last April, he told me about the quiet memorial service they held at the hospital—and the burial, with about a hundred family and friends present. Antoine said that he and Claire were careful to bundle Isaac in his favorite blanket with sheep and stars on it, and to make sure he had his beloved stuffed monkey with him. The cemetery is near their apartment. Antoine said he visits every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-attrs='{"url":"https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease/comments","text":"Leave a comment","action":null,"class":null}' data-component-name="ButtonCreateButton" class="button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease/comments" rel class="button primary"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leave a comment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Bulwark</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxQS1JnOURQelNqa19EQXNfaXVSSlhZMVdoR1pLM1hCNE9SRzRyUC14ZTlhcEhIXzdXdnk3dXJDMm9XYWJGQVRYMm9UTkI5QWFxZnM0ZktPZXR0RHNzaEYtZEpEeEFZMUxsSEJJUG1oWVlKenV2LU9DNFZDdFBTcnp6REItbHZxYnRuS0pVU2ZlNVhEblEwSDNiUXNxU1ljRC05ZHVUb0FtREVFa0Y3ZjB4dGRpSFd2ZWthTUE</guid></item><item><title>AHA表示，近90%的美国人患有无症状心脏病- NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/american-heart-association-cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic-syndrome/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 23:03:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOWHNCdy1oSUlvV1hnRzIxalBtclRuZzZfQ19vdnZxRElWTFREYmd2cDA2STg5NVBPVlc0amhJdXFNS3NiNjZHRUJvNW9lb1ljZWpmUWJOVDJxNkZEa1prSEpYZTdyN1UzSnlhVHppTUpmXzBFeGJWNmU3OUVhWV9SQ2JYdmZzd0szaDFOaUNhXzR3eFVidDJXQnVUeURKMVJQZnkwZkFOU1LSAa4BQVVfeXFMT25PZ3EwZHgwS3lRcjF6Vi1iSWhJa0hGUktoUUVpY185ZVY2VlBXR3ZjMGZ2MkFPVjhMNkVKLVd6RXJBUVpfOWlfX1VGNWdvZXNQNm9VUnJrUlhydW5sdnBuSTZpV0NaRTJHSVhoM19FRnpBa2xNSzJTVnRGR2F5R2RWWjh6WmVGUl9peEZGM3NmQkRkTnVfbWlmWEVCbnlJRk1ZTDYwWmV5V2Q1UDhR</guid></item><item><title>我的乳腺癌外科医生残害了我和数百名女性-泰晤士报</title><link>https://www.thetimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/article/ian-paterson-surgeon-victims-story-experience-scxs5c5dm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;It was 2006. I was 30 years old, running a small production company in Birmingham and life was good. But one night, when I was giving myself a routine breast check in bed, I found a large, hard lump in my right breast near the armpit. I froze.&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt; The lump wasn’t painful and I had no other symptoms but it was unmistakable. Breast cancer is a monster all women are terrified of. Even though I knew that the vast majority of breast lumps turn out to be benign I wasn’t reassured by the statistics. I didn’t sleep and in the morning I got an emergency appointment with my NHS GP. He examined the lump and said he wasn’t too worried about it but referred me for a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/comment/columnists/article/mammograms-must-stay-a-man-free-zone-mmqcq820z" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;mammogram&lt;/a&gt;, which he warned could take up to six weeks. My partner, who worked in logistics, reminded me that I was covered by his company’s private health insurance, so I called Bupa and it arranged an appointment that same week at the Spire Little Aston hospital with a consultant named &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/uk/healthcare/article/ian-paterson-breast-surgeon-refuses-leave-cell-2lrhxccw5" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;Ian Paterson&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Paterson was a strangely compelling man for someone who looked so ordinary. Average height, slightly overweight, impending baldness and yet he had a dynamism. I found him charming, reassuring and clearly competent. He didn’t patronise me, as so many doctors tended to do, and after examining the results of the mammogram and ultrasound Spire had undertaken the same day, he explained that he didn’t like the look of the lump so wanted to take a needle biopsy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="2.1"&gt;&lt;div id="281eea79-50f1-4880-ad64-54c5f51bbd98"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;Ian Paterson outside court in Nottingham in 2017&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;JOE GIDDENS/PA WIRE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/uk/healthcare/article/ian-paterson-breast-surgeon-refuses-leave-cell-2lrhxccw5" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ian Paterson: Jailed breast surgeon refuses to attend inquest&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;It hurt. A lot. He said, “It’s OK to swear,” something I later learnt he said to every patient. He said that breast cancer could strike at any age and that his youngest patient was a teenager. In hindsight, he was preparing me for the worst. A few days later I returned for the results. He told me “the boys at the lab” couldn’t agree on the severity of the problem but that it was clear the lump needed to be removed. I was terrified and began to cry. He offered me a tissue from the box on his desk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;My mental health collapsed. Paterson said the operation was urgent but I had a week’s holiday booked in Nice so we agreed he would operate when I returned. He told me to stay out of the sun because it increased my cancer risk so I spent the holiday in a state of paranoia and terror. I broke down in a French supermarket, overwhelmed by having to make small decisions about food. I kept thinking, what if I die while under anaesthetic? What if it was cancer and he needed to remove my breast? I was booked in for a “wide local excision” in which Paterson said he would remove just the lump, leaving a small scar, but he had warned me that there could be complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;After the surgery, in the private room at the expensive hospital, Paterson came in and told me and my partner that I had a “rare type of fibroadenoma that would quickly have turned into cancer” had he not removed it. This had the intended effect: cancer was a real danger but Ian Paterson was my saviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/uk/crime/article/butcher-breast-cancer-surgeon-ian-paterson-s2hdglxm7" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;I was mutilated by the butcher surgeon — and helped to jail him&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;I spent the next few years believing the danger might come back. While anyone can get breast cancer, there are some risk factors and I had none of them. No family history of the disease, no hormonal issues. I was physically fit, didn’t drink or smoke, had a healthy, balanced diet. But even though I was terrified that I was susceptible to this rare cancer, I could no longer bring myself to do a breast check. I didn’t want to touch the area where my scar was, didn’t want to experience that stomach-dropping moment of finding a lump again. I had to get my partner to do it for me, or a nurse at my GP surgery. It took me years to be able to do it myself (the NHS recommends doing it once a month).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;But life goes on. I had had a narrow brush with breast cancer but escaped with just a small scar to show I was ever under Ian Paterson’s knife. I moved to London to develop my career and tried not to think about it. In January 2011 my phone pinged. It was my sister, messaging to ask if I had seen the news about “that mad surgeon who has been operating on women for no reason”. It hadn’t occurred to either of us that it would be my doctor. I opened the link to the news site and with horror saw Paterson’s face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;He was being investigated for unnecessary surgery. What doctor would do that? He had been kind, clever and reassuring. It was impossible he could have lied to me. The next day I called the solicitors named in the article and they investigated my case. During a medical review with Spire and an independent surgeon, I learnt that I had never had any risk at all. The lump he had removed was simply a swollen lymph node and the results from “the boys at the lab” didn’t exist because Paterson had missed with the needle and failed to take a viable tissue sample. Everything he said had been a lie and I had never needed an operation. My medical saviour was not just a conman but a serial disfigurer of women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;There have been &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/uk/healthcare/article/the-jailed-breast-cancer-surgeon-and-the-650-deaths-being-investigated-hdqdqqnj5" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;hundreds, if not thousands, of victims&lt;/a&gt; — women who have had their breasts cut off for no reason and women with breast cancer to whom he gave unapproved “cleavage-sparing mastectomies” which left breast tissue behind, thereby increasing the risk of the cancer returning. He carried out his operations privately and in the NHS, and was praised for how quickly he could work, getting through a mastectomy in 30 minutes when it usually takes two hours. His theatres were known as especially bloody.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The story played out in the media as “butcher surgeon”. &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/best-law-firms/profile-legal/article/surgeon-ian-paterson-jailed-for-needless-breast-operations-0nklr2b7d" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;Paterson went to prison&lt;/a&gt;. I no longer lived in Birmingham and couldn’t face attending the trial because of trauma I experienced as a child but I followed it closely through the news and via friends. I felt a huge surge of relief when he was found guilty but also knew that put all of us into a whole new category. We were the victims of an evil surgeon imprisoned for his crimes. I tried not to think of my breast scar as “Paterson’s scar” and I felt a type of survivor’s guilt knowing that many of his patients had been through so much worse. I was furious on their behalf, for the needless pain and scarring and the mental anguish. Women no longer able to breastfeed or look at themselves the same way. It is a sacrifice to be made when it could save a life, not to satisfy the ego of a madman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In 2018 I decided to attend a coffee morning for victims of Paterson, which is where I first met Deborah Douglas. She was another patient of Paterson’s. I was aware of her campaigning work and admired her greatly. The continuing lawsuit was incredibly stressful and I still hadn’t worked out how to process any of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="2.15"&gt;&lt;div id="5f85c86d-fa73-405d-a05b-b5a5f5f96871"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;Deborah Douglas, another victim of Paterson’s crimes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;TOM JACKSON FOR THE TIMES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A few years later, in May 2023, Douglas contacted me to say she had written a book and could I help her to get it published? Ordinarily the answer is probably no — it is extremely difficult to get a literary agent and a book deal. (That much I knew. I had just had my memoir &lt;a href="https://timesbookshop.co.uk/learning-to-think-9781804991947/" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Learning to Think&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; published.) But I knew Douglas was an incredible campaigner with an amazing story so I told her to email her manuscript. She sent 100,000 words of research, plus details of her experiences of not only her cancer journey, the Paterson story and her tireless fight for justice, but the extraordinary family and background that make her the person she is today. There was so much more to the story than the public knew and I was gripped by her perspective. I forwarded her manuscript to my agent, who suggested she partner with a journalist. Douglas asked if I would do it. It took me a while to come round but I realised that it would be a privilege. And so it proved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Over the next two years I worked closely with her over Zoom or at her house in Birmingham. The more I learnt about the Paterson story, the more shocked I was. In reading the testimonies of other patients I discovered he had been using the same script over and over, including the lie about “a rare type of fibroadenoma”. I discovered exactly what Douglas had been up against for years — the infuriating failures in the NHS and the private sector, the missed opportunities to stop Paterson even when it was obvious he was doing something wrong, the brave whistleblowers who were ignored for years. While I had a job to do, it was impossible not to be affected by the story and I cried many times. I was blown away by how much work goes into Douglas’s campaigning and the determination she has to change the system to protect patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Paterson is due for release in 2027 after serving half of his 20-year sentence. Meanwhile, the Birmingham coroner is undertaking the largest inquest since Hillsborough to determine if any Paterson patients died as a result of his actions. So far 63 inquests have been opened and adjourned and the coroner is not expected to return a verdict until at least 2027. Douglas has launched a petition to stop Paterson being released while the inquests are in progress because of the distress this would cause to the families of the deceased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In 2025 we attended one of the inquest hearings together. I saw Paterson for the first time since he operated on me but this time he was attending online from the prison. He was angry, defiant and wretched. He has been described many times as a monster but I saw a man. There have always been people willing to exploit the most vulnerable and, without significant reforms to the culture and processes that allowed him to thrive, there will be more Ian Patersons, but at least this one faced justice. Sitting next to Douglas, I realised that in helping her to shape her story, I had also processed my own trauma and the man on the screen in front of me no longer held any power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;I have become good friends with Douglas and her amazing family. I discovered that although our lives were now very different, we had similar backgrounds. We grew up on council estates in Birmingham a stone’s throw from each other, albeit in different generations, had the same sense of humour, love of art and music, and shared the sort of grit and determination that had driven us both to succeed in our separate fields. The love and support Douglas has had from her family through what has been a nightmare most people can’t imagine is one of the most inspiring things I have witnessed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Nothing can make up for the evils committed by Paterson and those who enabled him but the Douglas family, Douglas’s tireless sacrifice in campaigning and supporting other victims of medical malpractice and her work as chair of a breast cancer charity give me hope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="last-paragraph" class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Cost of Trust &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;by Deborah Douglas with Tracy King&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;(HarperCollins £20) is published on February 12. To order a copy go to &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesbookshop.co.uk/the-cost-of-trust-9780008712938/?utm_source=timesandsundaytimes&amp;amp;utm_medium=online&amp;amp;utm_campaign=weekly" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;timesbookshop.co.uk&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;. Free UK standard P&amp;amp;P on orders over £25. Special discount available for Times+ members.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxQSW9SaTlpT1BNTVItRmcxY1JYUDVSc0kzRExDTDhSelpFRTRWMUhrYXY3SGVIRTZPWlJhdDhQaW0wVkxTUjUyT19ZRTZZQXYtZjl4S1BId3hhLTZLUDk3cXhmQkVBSlJ3WndjdGV6U1BXRi1yOExPR3J6bnVYOFFMaUZaSmhPeFRuWWlQU2wxczBwYnRlMDZRbmlmRFFJS2VUcndYSi0xZTRPaFRvMFE0OHlOSXg</guid></item><item><title>蛋白质去年就是这样。为什么光纤是下一件大事- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51438056/protein-is-so-last-year-why-fiber-is-the-next-big-thing</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK CITY — Move over, protein. Fiber is on pace to be the next "it" nutrient of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumers — particularly Gen Z — are fixated on stomach health, leading to the "fibermaxxing" trend taking hold on TikTok. As people try to maximize the fiber in their meals, major food companies are capitalizing on the trend with new, fiber-focused products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is a consumer need in terms of digestion and gut health, and that's something we've seen the last few years," said Sherry Frey, health and wellness thought leader at NIQ. The younger generation, she added, understands that digestive health is linked to better skin and improved cognitive function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dataessential, a food and beverage research firm, found that 52% of consumers were interested in trying "fibermaxxing" after learning about the trend and that 42% of shoppers think food labeled "high fiber" is healthier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiber builds on previous wellness-focused consumer trends, Frey told CNN. First was hydration, as seen with the rise of products like Liquid I.V. and Electrolit. Then protein, a trend that shows no sign of slowing down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The natural next step is for fiber," she said, calling the converging of trends a "perfect storm."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, fiber has been proven to trigger "a naturally occurring GLP-1 in our bodies," she added, referencing the appetite-suppressing hormone in weight-loss drugs like Wegovy that are flooding the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Big Food responds&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumers' desire for fiber is already evident on grocery store shelves. Whole Foods' &lt;a href="https://www.wholefoodsmarket.com/trends/the-next-big-things-our-top-8-food-trend-predictions-for-2026" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;forecast&lt;/a&gt; for 2026 said there are "more fiber-forward callouts on packaging" as well as more products with added fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thrive Market, a membership-based online supermarket, has seen fiber-related terms surge 30% over the past year with shoppers gravitating toward snacks, bars and supplements, a spokesperson told CNN.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major food companies have taken notice: PepsiCo CEO Ramon Laguarta said on its most recent earnings call in October that "fiber will be the next protein."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Consumers are starting to understand that fiber is the benefit that they need. It's actually a deficiency in U.S. consumers' diets, and that will be elevated," Laguarta told analysts. (More than 90% of women and 97% of men don't get their recommended daily intake of fiber, the U.S. government &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2020-12/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans_2020-2025.pdf" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; in 2020.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PepsiCo is already bolstering its soda portfolio with fiber-forward products. Last summer, it launched a gut-friendly soda following its purchase of Poppi with "Pepsi Prebiotic Cola," which includes added fiber. More products are on the way, including fiber-enhanced versions of its SunChips, Smartfood popcorn and Propel hydration packets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDonald's CEO Chris Kempczinski also recently predicted on his Instagram account that fiber "is going to be big" in 2026, perhaps signaling that the fast-food chain could dip its toes into the trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snacks, such as chips and puffed crackers, will be the battleground for fiber, Frey predicts, notably products made from legumes and beans. But taste is a factor, especially if it's made from plant-based ingredients.&lt;strong&gt;﻿&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Consumers are willing to make a trade, but they're not always willing to make the trade if the taste isn't there," Frey said. "Despite the economy, they're willing to pay a little more for these kinds of products."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's where private labels created by major grocery stores come in. They are also getting into the wellness sector with fiber-enchanced products, but without the premium prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aldi's recently relaunched in-house line includes knock-offs of "better for you" sodas and meal bars. Walmart is expanding its Bettergoods lineup, which encompasses several foods that have plant-based ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is this healthy?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recommended amount of fiber is 25 grams per day for adult women to 35 for adult males, according to medical experts, so "it's a generally good healthy trend," said Paul Kriegler, a registered dietician and senior director of nutritional products for Life Time Fitness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the prepackaged products hitting shelves are not a panacea for this deficiency. He would rather consumers gravitate toward the produce and vegetable section at the grocery store for their fiber needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. government's newly released dietary guidelines also urge people to prioritize "real food," including "fiber-rich whole grains," as well as curtail their intake of highly processed foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What I've taught clients for a long time is to eat a pile of vegetables the size of your head every day," Kreigler told CNN. "The irony is most of the foods that will help 'fibermaxxing' don't even have labels, and you have to go get them fresh."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 21:58:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPOUpkbVNRYVhJb3J3ZV9OMUFPLTNoX0FtYTN3aU9GSnE4MVI1TzBDNVFMaUpNcjdXRi02Tkh3RE0tWjJvZmJ5Ry1PS2g3SlFqdVlwa3V1YktNS0g2MjdwTjRUWmcxampNblhCR2dVWXdhTTR0SjhfN05SNmI1alF2aDY0aU1WcnpBZkFxa2U1U3BJcnhhUy04</guid></item><item><title>“拯救了数百万人的生命” ：来自华盛顿州的医学先驱William Foege在89岁去世- seattletimes.com</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/william-foege-medical-pioneer-who-helped-stamp-out-smallpox-has-died/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxNYUNwOXhEX3RkcmltQXVLR3ZRY3piVjcyY2JzSFU3SlZCMm05dXlyUFB3UUhZQkJuU0N2aDNzNmQ1a0tvNE9OeHlPRU1mdjFtYUFkWnlTYXhYOGJ6QTZxVTItSGp6cHQxekxueW1zNjZmRlVrdGlwOHZjTlRORjcteTk4MUVpU01sRzNneHh4Mk9zYWx6a1V1ZFRiYWZIQTZMVm5PbXAxUnVtRWFhSFVYcg?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;‘Saved the lives of millions’: William Foege, medical pioneer from WA, dies at 89&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;seattletimes.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxPbnA1ZEE1TUcybEpVczRVVWRpTlUwVDZzMWdWX0Zfc1NCemN4UWNYMnNLRDZ2Mlktb25IMWw3Ymdpald6UF8temlzTHZaVmJTdDRZdl9IMjhXVHZtRFE5eHZVSl95TnJXV3JvZFhGdkpWWk4zbUt5YXRpUjJXQXRBbnlKbEtZeGNPMXloVXdOZXFRUFJlRlg2LVVnMVg4UGo10gGmAUFVX3lxTE5wTnNyT1JHVURWUFdyeVo5UzdYZHhnUWs2dVVpVHBmMnVuQUZRYlRXMmdiWWc3S1p1NVF5RjdDMnhnOTRiZ29wLTJ2aDgxbEExV3dpSmt4NzluUm1XcjBPNnNpVTNneGJMaVJrSkxvWXZzczhwR2k2VFpfVTV6cW03czRoOGVVN1RTMDZKOG5GZkhubktMSGV4VWJUY0JKM29DYzY3bWc?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. William Foege, leader in smallpox eradication, dies&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxNZTJxT2plMVZwSjRVV0ZIZ0ptMjVId1JETVVzVzBZQUtWRGtlNlhVSUVaXzlVVEQtLWNqc0JTdnhJRUlSWEZETGlKSlhtRkZlVjBFamhLX2Y4cTJFdkM2SzJua2JPeDZtVTczeDlyNnJDV2VTTmtMbFR0R3FZZERIZTFpekVyXzJ1WXdCQ0NPaUNFRHYxUTRjU01uaGJrYXJUWHdRQzhyNA?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Lessons From William H. Foege, A Global Health Legend&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Forbes&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxOcFVHRkI5R212bG1EbzhCQTJWNFdEOHh4d0RxSHhMd3VNSndrSUZ6Q3pROFhkVFh3V0Q1cWJFUkpwUjlrMWN0Um9va0FEMWRoeXY3YzVoS1htNXNYa1RsMnI3VUpjdFEzdmpxSjNUUWRsXzF0TERYRjBVTGNMakhDazBFcUNOUzdoRlZfRU1lRnpfLXZWU0ZsbzJxZ09Td1ZHNUNNWTFn?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Opinion | Bill Foege’s optimism helped save the world from smallpox&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxQbmtTOHJyNGtxTFRHVDR6eEJpVVJ5MWNzYkQxMXpRT1d6QWpyQ1BVa0JtM3ZPZ1o0NGJXSWhtX0lzV0NCQk1zX2QxM1JwVU1ibEZrUmNTWVhtZDNkUks5a2oxT0NvOHY1ME0tcXBNWW1OeEtTd2t4VmVuUDhwMmY2Mkozb1ZLY0RqdTJ2QTBHZEFXQm5qNnk1eDhnbUhEWUxiQWtJWktR?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. William (Bill) H. Foege, Atlanta global public health giant, dies at 89&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ajc.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>seattletimes.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 21:25:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxNYUNwOXhEX3RkcmltQXVLR3ZRY3piVjcyY2JzSFU3SlZCMm05dXlyUFB3UUhZQkJuU0N2aDNzNmQ1a0tvNE9OeHlPRU1mdjFtYUFkWnlTYXhYOGJ6QTZxVTItSGp6cHQxekxueW1zNjZmRlVrdGlwOHZjTlRORjcteTk4MUVpU01sRzNneHh4Mk9zYWx6a1V1ZFRiYWZIQTZMVm5PbXAxUnVtRWFhSFVYcg</guid></item><item><title>这种被遗忘的癌症疫苗的结果在20年后被科学家们重新审视- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/this-forgotten-cancer-vaccines-results-were-so-unusual-scientists-revisited-it-20-years-later/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 21:19:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxPbXhIXzhlN3owMTJJdVUtUTNTbmcwLU9ERzMxOXpGVFl0V0JEdzZvNTIxNzUxcDV1LTVyM3lfMVhWb1A0OGdPNzdXUklFbHZQbkZBd3lveGtKQ3NGLUlJYS1XTVlSQWx4M04xTFRsWFJjYzdZck0tUVYyN3hBblpOMHdwRFMxVmstcXhUU2l3OEIyZzBkZkY3bmZQVWpEWFpkckZYYlc0cGkwZGdBbWw4S1FXWWwtSjdiWEFN</guid></item><item><title>Penarth妈妈“乞求”进行核磁共振检查，发现宫颈癌- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cd9eeklq93go</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Mum with cervical cancer begged for scan after years of being 'fobbed off'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Jessica Mason Jessica, who has curly blonde hair and pink highlights, with blue eyes, smiles as she sits in a car" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Jessica Mason&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jessica says women-specific health issues are too often dismissed&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A woman with cervical cancer who waited years to be diagnosed says she has "lost her faith in doctors".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica Mason went back and forth to her GP and hospital with swelling, bleeding and pain in her vagina but says she was "fobbed off" before "begging" for a scan which revealed cancer requiring urgent treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The 44-year-old believes she was only referred for an MRI because she "broke down in tears" to a doctor, adding: "I knew there was something wrong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A Senedd &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://laiddocuments.senedd.wales/cr-ld17744-en.pdf" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;health committee report &lt;/a&gt;into gynaecological cancer has found women have been "let down by the Welsh government's inaction". The Welsh government said it was working with the NHS to improve gynaecological cancer outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'I wasn't being believed'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica, from Penarth in the Vale of Glamorgan, was experiencing pain and vaginal bleeding which became serious in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I knew there was something wrong," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said doctors gave her ultrasounds which did not pick up any issues, and she was also given various diagnoses including a cyst, endometriosis and prolapse, for which she was advised to perform pelvic floor exercises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was so confusing because you trust in the doctors and you think if it was something serious they would have known," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Jessica Mason Jessica, who has long blonde hair, smiles in a selfie with her husband Dan, who is wearing a black jumper and has short silvery hair and stubble. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Jessica Mason&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jessica with her husband, Dan&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica said a smear test six months before she was diagnosed also picked up nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It was only in May 2022 when she went to the University Hospital of Wales in Cardiff for the results of an ultrasound that she broke down in tears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They said there was something on the lining of the womb but it all looked OK," said Jessica, who begged them to do something more to check what could be causing her symptoms as she felt she "wasn't being believed".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was only at that point they offered me an MRI," she added, which she said was offered as a way to give her "peace of mind".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The results came back a couple of weeks later in June 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Cancer didn't cross my mind to be honest, I thought it would be something like an infection, I didn't think it was going to be that serious."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In fact the doctor told her that she had stage 1 B3 cervical cancer and needed to start treatment urgently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica started a programme of chemotherapy and radiotherapy in August 2022 for five weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Jessica Mason Jessica wearing a hospital gown, lies in a hospital bed with nasal tubes attached. Her blonde hair is tied back. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Jessica Mason&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jessica says cancer treatment caused her to have an early menopause&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica said the treatment took its toll on her 13-year-old son and also pushed her into early menopause, meaning she had to give up her plans to have another child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I couldn't cook and couldn't clean, I couldn't even iron my son's uniform or take him to school," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica believes she should have been referred for an MRI sooner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The cost of the MRI is probably just as much as the amount spent on treatment, GP and doctor appointments," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But that wasn't the end of Jessica's ordeal, after a further MRI in February 2023 found the tumour was still there and meant she needed to have a hysterectomy in July 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I lost my faith in the doctors," said Jessica. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's horrible because obviously I'm not a medical expert and you've got to put your faith in them but I'm always questioning them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica used to work full time but said she could now only manage three days a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It took over our lives. My body is wrecked from everything I've been through but mentally too, my friends, my family, my home life, everything just revolves around that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica said she still experienced bleeding occasionally and will need further biopsies, describing the situation as "never-ending".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I've always got this worry in the back of my head, what if they miss something again and this time I don't survive it?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She has accused the health board of "dragging their heels" over sharing her medical records while she considers whether to take legal action against them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"A lot of women-specific issues are just not recognised [quickly] enough. They just dismiss it as 'your time of the month' or 'women's issues'," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A spokesperson for Cardiff and Vale University Health Board said: "We are sorry to hear about Jessica's experience while in our care and acknowledge the challenges surrounding her cancer diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"As it would be inappropriate to comment on an individual patient case, and due to ongoing legal proceedings, we are unable to comment further."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'Critical failures'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A recent Senedd health committee report into gynaecological cancer care in Wales found that women were "still being let down by the Welsh government's inaction".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The report found a failure to deliver on a number of recommendations made in December 2023 as part of a landmark report uncovering "critical failures".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It said despite accepting the majority of the committee's 2023 recommendations, the Welsh government had not allocated specific ring-fenced funding for gynaecological cancer services or published measurable NHS targets for improving outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It also found that Wales had fallen short on waiting times, with only 41% of patients starting treatment within the 62-day target in October 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cancer charity Tenovus said it was "deeply concerning to see in black and white just how little progress has been made".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Welsh government said: "We are committed to working with the NHS to improve access to timely diagnosis and treatment for women with gynaecological cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We have made changes to support earlier referrals and we are investing in new equipment and new treatments to improve women's outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The current performance against the 62-day target is simply not good enough and must improve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The Women's Health Plan is driving real change in women's healthcare in Wales."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 21:02:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBZV0RtakcybGhlaFVCQlNhdmc1N0Fqcmg1ZmdOOUhQWDMzZ1pTajhQTUdRcnBPVDI2NkpPM2xwSFpxVWc5bHJIcjhKTk1aeVEzVEk1Szhtd3hxUdIBX0FVX3lxTE5Td1c5YllhTks2UUxicG1mSjI3d3FRaTI4ejkyUFhfYWx5OHdXR29PeFF0MC1hbkRhMTVPTkphWDhuQXVKblJyWERMcEZDVnBFQ0V5Y1NOc1l3X2RIcUFj</guid></item><item><title>边缘性人格特质与手指敲击任务期间协调性降低有关- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/borderline-personality-traits-are-associated-with-reduced-coordination-during-a-finger-tapping-task/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p class="instaread-player-slot"&gt; &lt;instaread-player publication="psypost" playertype=""&gt;&lt;/instaread-player&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An experimental study conducted in Italy found that individuals with pronounced borderline personality traits tended to show greater asynchrony with a virtual partner in a finger-tapping task. They also perceived lower synchrony and reported more negative affect during the interaction. In other words, they both coordinated less effectively with a virtual partner and experienced the interaction as less coordinated. The paper was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1037/per0000684"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Personality Disorders: Theory, Research, and Treatment&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Borderline personality traits are a pattern of emotional, interpersonal, and behavioral characteristics associated with borderline personality disorder but present to varying degrees in the general population. These traits include intense emotional reactivity, rapid mood shifts, and difficulty regulating negative emotions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individuals high in borderline personality traits tend to form unstable and intense interpersonal relationships in which they frequently shift between perceiving the other person as entirely positive and perfect or entirely negative and worthless. Fear of abandonment and heightened sensitivity to rejection are common features of these individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Identity disturbance, such as an unstable or unclear sense of self, is frequently reported. They may act impulsively in areas such as spending or substance use and may show a heightened proneness to risky behavior. Many individuals with borderline personality traits experience chronic feelings of emptiness or inner instability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study author Camilla Gregorini and her colleagues note that individuals with high borderline personality traits might show difficulties in social cognitive processes that require them to align and coordinate their actions with other people and to functionally modulate their emotions. When humans do something together, they coordinate their movements, behaviors, and even physiological processes. This is called interpersonal synchronization, and it is one of the key mechanisms underlying the human ability to cooperate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These authors conducted an experiment in which they used a finger-tapping task to explore whether high borderline personality traits might affect a person’s ability to synchronize with a partner. Coordinating with others requires a person to be able to flexibly plan and monitor one’s own and others’ actions and create a good balance between oneself and the partner. Study authors hypothesized that the emotional dysregulation and interpersonal instability of individuals with high borderline traits would produce difficulties in anticipating the actions of the partner and adapting to the partner’s actions, regardless of when and how the partner adapted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study participants were 206 individuals recruited from the general population in Italy. Of these participants, 130 were women. Their average age was 24 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants completed an assessment of borderline personality traits (the Personality Assessment Inventory – Borderline Scale). They also completed an experiment in which they interacted with a virtual partner with several levels of adaptivity in a finger-tapping task. The task required participants to tap the space bar on a keyboard so that they synchronized with tones played by the virtual partner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depending on the setting, the virtual partner adapted the timing of its tones to reduce the asynchrony produced by the participant’s taps. In that way, the virtual partner modulated the synchrony between itself and the participant. There were 5 levels of virtual partner adaptivity, ranging from non-adaptive to overly adaptive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the end of each condition, participants evaluated their perception of synchrony (“How much did you feel in sync with the virtual partner?”). They also evaluated their affect using the International Positive and Negative Affect Schedule Short Form. Additionally, study authors derived an objective measure of asynchrony between participants and their virtual partners as the time mismatch between each tap and each tone. Participants were not informed that their virtual partner had different adaptivity settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results showed that individuals with more pronounced borderline personality traits tended to show greater asynchrony with the virtual partner. They also perceived lower synchrony and reported more negative affect. In other words, these individuals both coordinated less effectively with their virtual partner and experienced the interaction as less coordinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our results reveal that the interpersonal disturbances and emotional dysregulation related to individuals with high BPD [borderline personality disorder] traits might interfere with the social cognitive processes implicated in coordination processes. Consequently, such impairments might lead to higher asynchrony and a negative experience of synchrony,” study authors concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study contributes to the scientific understanding of social interactions of individuals with pronounced borderline personality traits. However, it should be noted that the study utilized an interaction with a virtual partner, not a real person. Findings about interactions with real people might differ. Additionally, study participants were recruited from a nonclinical population; therefore, it is likely that, on average, their borderline personality trait levels were low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1037/per0000684"&gt;Stable Asynchrony? Association Between Borderline Personality Traits and Interpersonal Asynchrony&lt;/a&gt;” was authored by Camilla Gregorini, Pietro De Carli, Laura Parolin, Marco Petilli, Ivana Konvalinka, and Emanuele Preti.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 19:12:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPWXl5RHRIN1Q0a3EwT1VtWm5xVWh0eHJtcDZLcUlScVQxYWVMVGVxeFp4QzIzMFl3TGVMd1ZaaGJneVlZdWRjSXJNOUF6eDdMRUJmaWJhOUs3TkxTV3ZoRGE4YnlJeHJwbEY4cV81ZTkwNGk3bHZCaXFkY0ZnU2hHeXFEQ3RzQmc0aEJhbk40M3lNTXJRYTlSOWtKM0RZd0ZtWFY5UUFjenF0V0RrSXFjMHhobC1jSExSZklBcFRBRS1KZw</guid></item><item><title>房客专栏|我是营养师。这就是为什么您不应该将食物标记为“好”或“坏”的原因。’-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2026/01/25/nutrition-healthy-eating-good-bad-foods/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="D4EFSZFECFHIDPSODJK7UUW6ZA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Eat this, avoid that. This one food will cure everything. But this one you should NEVER eat. You can eat these foods, but &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; during strictly controlled times of day. Statements like these are all over social media, gyms and even health care offices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNTy1DemY2QU1sSktpLTVteFRPTl8zTExsc1AtZS1GNVpoSy1MOFJFYTE4MkpjZ3dfbjhsXzlwYjR6NHhyN043SzZCNDUxZmtNYm1FeHRaNDdZR09oYlZtelBhWkZnX2p1ampNUjJIak1mSEZFSGI5eXhQbGhNcy1YQzlIVVNYNXpONkpHMHkxVjVob2REWHc</guid></item><item><title>科学家说前进，继续前进-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/scientists-gooning</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;Adult content has never been as accessible as it is now, thanks to the internet. Hell, online smut &lt;a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/porn-behind-internet-technologies-2017-5" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;played a major role&lt;/a&gt; in the rise of the web itself in the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;With that glut of porn, some have voiced concerns that some people are &lt;a href="https://www.apa.org/monitor/2014/04/pornography" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;consuming too much&lt;/a&gt; of the stuff or even becoming addicted, which they claim could have consequences like regulating emotions or impaired sexual functioning.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;But as &lt;a href="https://www.psypost.org/frequent-pornography-use-does-not-always-indicate-a-problem-new-study-suggests/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;PsyPost&lt;/em&gt; reports&lt;/a&gt;, these concerns may be overblown. Researchers at the University of Pécs in Hungary have found that it doesn’t matter how frequently one watches porn; the reasons why somebody indulges in the stuff are far more predictive of their sexual health.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;As detailed in a &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/19317611.2025.2605517" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;new paper&lt;/a&gt; published in the &lt;em&gt;International Journal of Sexual Health&lt;/em&gt;, the researchers found that positive motivations, such as “enhancing sexual pleasure, exploring fantasies, or deepening intimacy,” were “associated with frequent but non-problematic pornography use and with adaptive sexual regulation.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;However, those with “negative motivations,” such as “stress reduction, emotional escape, or avoidance of discomfort,” were strongly linked to “sexual system hyperactivation, emotion regulation difficulties, and impaired relational functioning.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The study involved  890 adult participants in Hungary, including 600 individuals assigned female at birth and 290 assigned male at birth. The participants submitted answers anonymously through an online survey.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“A major gap in the literature is that pornography use is often evaluated mainly by how frequently people use it, even though frequency alone tells us very little about whether use is actually harmful,” University of Pécs psychology professor Norbert Meskó told &lt;em&gt;PsyPost&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“We were interested in whether these different motivations are linked to different patterns of sexual and emotional functioning,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Most strikingly, the researchers found that participants who reported frequent pornography use were less likely to experience problematic outcomes. However, those who primarily used it for coping and managing stress were more likely to experience symptoms of problematic use, indicating that frequency isn’t the main indicator of whether it’s actually harmful.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“One somewhat surprising finding was that frequent use, when driven by positive motivations, was linked to less sexual deactivation — meaning less emotional withdrawal from sexuality,” Meskó told &lt;em&gt;PsyPost&lt;/em&gt;. “In contrast, only problematic use — not frequent use — was associated with these kinds of disengaged or avoidant sexual patterns.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Importantly, problematic use showed much stronger links to difficulties in sexual and emotional functioning than simple frequency did,” he added. “This suggests that from a practical standpoint, it is more useful to look at whether someone feels out of control or distressed by their use than at how often they watch pornography.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Of course, as the researchers note in their paper, there are some limitations to their research. For one, the self-reported nature of their data may not be reliable, as it relies on memory. It also may not be generalizable to a broader population as a result.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Multiple motivations for pornography use may also overlap — for instance, seeking pleasure while also distracting from stress — meaning that some cases may not neatly fit into either positive or negative motivations. One category may also quickly shift to another, further complicating the picture.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“We would caution against thinking of pornography as either simply ‘good’ or ‘bad,'” Meskó told &lt;em&gt;PsyPost&lt;/em&gt;. “For some people, it may be part of healthy sexual expression, while for others it may function as a way to avoid emotional problems or relationship difficulties.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on pornography:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/future-society/grok-violence-women"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Grok Is Being Used to Depict Horrific Violence Against Real Women&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZkFVX3lxTE9BNFJwSHJ6YXUwdmJZOVZ6Z3d2QXhnZnMxdkhvbzk3Sm54d3lPdFBIVUtlc3R4cFhzdE1ObEJGY3FuUnRGUDdjaElxaUxWT0Y1cENFaUVqUi1MbGR1R3dyRU54alp6Zw</guid></item></channel></rss>