<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>根据新研究-每日邮报，戒掉抗抑郁药并避免残酷副作用的最佳方法</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15419207/come-antidepressants-avoid-effects.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Coming off antidepressants is notoriously difficult, with many experiencing horrendous side-effects including stomach problems, irritability and insomnia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And with some seven million Britons estimated to be taking the mood balancing drugs, knowing exactly how to stop this powerful drugs of class is paramount—but has eluded experts for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But new research, published in &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpsy/article/PIIS2215-0366(25)00330-X/abstract"&gt;The Lancet Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;, has suggested the best way to come off the pills is to slowly reduce dosage, with the support of a trained mental health professional, such as a psychiatrist. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This, researchers say, could prevent relapse in 20 per cent of patients, enabling them to live more freely and not be reliant on prescription medication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Our findings suggest that while antidepressants are effective in preventing depressive relapses, they do not need to be a long term treatment for everyone,' study co-author, Dr Debora Zaccoletti, said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Antidepressants are not only used to treat &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/depression/index.html" id="mol-23dc1570-e4a8-11f0-8f57-c7d8fe898dbf" class=""&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;, but a number of mood disorders including anxiety, obsessive compulsive disorder (OCD) and post-traumatic stress disorder (PTSD). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors (SSRIs), one of the most widely prescribed types of the drug, work by increasing the amount of available serotonin—dubbed the happiness hormone—in the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, as Christine Villelongue, co-head of the France Depression Association, explained: 'As soon as an antidepressant is changed or reduced, it is a source of anxiety for the person. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-module-version="1.17.6" data-dataset-id="2057" data-mol-fe-xpmodule-newsletter-sign-up data-newsletter="configurable" data-form-action-url="https://link.news.dailymail.com/s/Health" data-environment="production" data-newsletter-id="Health" data-newsletter-channel-colour="health" data-watermark="uk" data-image="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/i/pix/2025/10/27/Sign_UpModule_Image_Health.png" data-title="Sign up for our free Health newsletter" data-subtitle="Transform your health every Tuesday with expert guides, real-life stories and advice from top doctors"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The powerful drugs — taken by millions — have long been known to potentially trigger symptoms including dizziness, headaches, insomnia and nausea when coming off them&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'However, there are no real guidelines: When medication is stopped, there is no follow up.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To assess the health impact of overprescribing, experts from the World Health Organisation's (WHO) Collaborating Centre for Research and Training in Mental Health and Service Evaluation, cross-examined over 75 studies to work out the best way for a patient to come off the medication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Analysing medical records from over 17,000 individuals, the researchers found the most effective method is gradually lowering the dosage alongside seeing a therapist. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to the researchers, this could help prevent relapse in one in five patients, helping dramatically reduce the number of patients unable to get off of antidepressants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients were followed for around a year, with those who abruptly stopped taking their medication found to be at a 40 per cent risk of relapse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those who gradually came off antidepressants, whilst seeing a psychiatrist, however reduced their risk of relapse by nearly 50 per cent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This, the study found, was almost as effective as continued drug usage without psychological support. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers concluded that guidelines on coming off antidepressants should 'promote individualised deprescribing with gradual tapering and structured psychological support.' &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Professor Giovanni Ostuzzi, study co-author also from the University of Verona, added: 'Continuing with or without psychological support, slow tapering with the psychological support and continuing at the antidepressant at reduced doses had similar benefits in preventing relapse within the first year after stopping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Abrupt stopping or fast tapering carried the highest risk of relapse.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers hope that their study will pave the way for more personalised prescribing practices and help more patients come off the drugs sooner. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Our new review clarifies the scientific evidence about the most effective way to come off antidepressants for individuals successfully treated for depression and could change how coming off antidepressants is managed globally,' Prof Oztuzzi added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'These findings highlight the need for clinical guidelines to be updated to promote regular treatment reviews and individualised deprescribing with gradual tapering and structured psychological support for patients with depression who are feeling better and wish to come off their medication.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But, experts who were not involved in the current study have expressed concern over patients coming off medication too quickly, without the support of their doctor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Jonathan Henssler, MD, an expert in evidence-based mental health, stressed: 'The best patient outcomes were achieved with strategies that maintained antidepressant therapy.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He added that currently both pharmaceutical treatment and psychotherapy are limited in their curative capacity- meaning that for effective usage, both need to be used in adjunct, which is not always feasible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox health" data-version="2" id="mol-5e8755b0-e4b0-11f0-b285-a1098cd4136c" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15419207/come-antidepressants-avoid-effects.html"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;What are antidepressants? &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Antidepressants are medicines that treat depression symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are around 30 different types that can be prescribed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The NHS says that most people who have moderate or severe depression notice improvement when they take antidepressants. But it notes that this isn't the case for everyone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Side effects vary between different people and antidepressants but can include nausea, headaches, a dry mouth and problems having sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Antidepressants aren't addictive but patients may have withdrawal symptoms if they stop taking them suddenly or miss a dose. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These can include an upset stomach, flu-like symptoms, anxiety, dizziness and vivid dreams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other experts highlighted the the follow-up period of the study was relatively short, meaning it is difficult to make long-term conclusions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, Dr Alberto Oritz Lobo, a leading psychiatrist at La Paz University, welcomed the findings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He said: 'This is a crucial study given the alarming increase in antidepressant prescriptions and the need to consider strategies for reducing their use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The usual clinical reality is that, after people improve, antidepressant treatment is often continued for months, years, or indefinitely, leading to chronic adverse effects of the medication, exposure to its risks, and brain neuroadaptation that makes stopping the medication difficult. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He added that gradually reducing the dose helps support changes in the brain.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Continuing, he said: 'Psychological support provides confidence and security in this process, in which the person regains their agency and autonomy, reappropriates their emotions and stops delegating their well-being to a medication.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Latest NHS data shows a record 8.8million people in England are now on the mood-boosting drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Common SSRIs prescribed in the UK include citalopram, fluoxetine and sertraline, sometimes known by brand names Cipramil, Prozac and Lustral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But their use has been linked to long-term and even permanent sexual dysfunction by researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The NHS has warned that side effects such as a loss of libido and achieving orgasm, lower sperm count and erectile dysfunction 'can persist' after taking them — and patients have described feeling 'carved out', relationships wrecked, from their use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Most medics, and the NHS, consider the use of SSRI for depression, particularly persistent or severe cases, as worthwhile given the debilitating nature of the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 14:09:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxObHIyODlrMk5zdUd3ZEpnYW93LTYxdTNJaVU2cTNLSWw0WHVnQVk2T05McDNwWVl0TU5QWnR2WjJXZHZYb3FKQW9qakZHTDBvZ3p1ek5BclpvTjhuZ2xGSE5iQXA2RmdSdU90N05PdGg2cDdmaXZDN3BMYllyT2ZFUjFFRXp2VkZJVHVRNTVhRlZDT3lnOWfSAZsBQVVfeXFMTXZfTFdkQ080dnJmNm5vVk1PZGUyVldJbnRxN0dBMHdUaVdiMlFSUE9kM0FfUEJncEhuaXNOU2RRdjZKZUYzbjkyMVJZd2duM09fMDBSc0xzS3BFNW1kekp4NktaOGpLY0ljWHIwVHlrbGxheDJUUHRjaHg1VGw1Y0pMUEMtX2J0NE9CcXR5Y19sMFY3ZlJGaGFZX3c</guid></item><item><title>想在2026年改善您的健康状况吗？简明扼要-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/wellness-influencers-politics-fiber-protein-longevity-9969ef29b9cf29fe5fded67637351c7c</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;The new year is a time when many try to start new good habits and commit to improving health and wellness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But resolutions, lofty as they may be, can turn daunting quickly with all the advice and sometimes contradicting information coming at you from news reports, advertisers, influencers, friends and even politicians. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But they don’t have to be. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year, The Associated Press got the downlow on all manner of health and wellness claims and fads. The good news is that the experts mostly say to keep it simple. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As 2026 arrives, here’s what you can skip, what you should pay attention to and how to get credible information when you are inevitably faced with more confusing claims next year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Protein and fiber are important, but you probably don’t need to pay more&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to your diet, experts say most people can skip the upcharge. If you’re eating enough, you’re &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/high-protein-muscle-food-nutrition-e3bd1ddb197139bdf7fe67a09fcdf32e"&gt;probably getting enough protein&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and don’t need products that promise some big boost. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And it’s true that most people could use more fiber in their diets. But, please, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/fiber-fibermaxxing-digestion-wellness-730bdd5f68f448fe979f4ebd598e2340"&gt;ditch the “fiber-maxxing” trend&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Instead, eat whole foods such as fruits, vegetables, beans and whole grains.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;A good skin care routine is not expensive or complicated&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;That 20-step skin care routine and $200 serum some TikToker sold you on? &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/skin-care-retinol-red-light-therapy-beef-tallow-16ce2a56462995c41054fdf147814d7e"&gt;Dermatologists say&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you really don’t need it. Stay away from the beef tallow and slather on a good sunscreen instead (yes, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/sunscreen-for-dark-skin-tones-cccd4a0c1cea4e4a5ca6a67c00a5b5c5"&gt;even if you have darker skin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ), they say. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the same rule for simplicity applies to that hourlong “everything shower.” The best showers are simple and short, dermatologists say, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/shower-basics-tiktok-social-media-dermatologist-8a96743d7b86c329703f7736a7306961"&gt;no “double cleansing” required&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Infobox" data-module data-gtm-region="This article is part of AP's Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. Read more Be Well." data-align-center&gt;
    
    &lt;div class="Infobox-items RichTextBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This article is part of AP’s Be Well coverage, focusing on wellness, fitness, diet and mental health. &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/hub/be-well"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read more Be Well.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;There are many simple ways to get that workout in&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the gym and all its equipment feel intimidating, you can drop the illusion that a good workout requires either. This year, the &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/calisthenics-exercises-fitness-body-weight-c9f2f9c44c36a3078f5ffeb744c094d2"&gt;comeback of calisthenics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; put the focus back on no frills, bodyweight workouts you can do in the comfort of home. Research shows calisthenics helps with muscle strength and aerobic conditioning. You may eventually need weightlifting or other equipment, but it is a great place to start to build consistency and confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;h2&gt;Be wary of wellness fads and treatments — they are often too good to be true&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if you imbibe too much this New Year’s Eve, doctors say you can do without “ &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/retail-iv-therapy-drip-hydration-e335f09bc013739aa69fa43d92bc4945"&gt;IV therapy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; ” which have vitamins you can get more easily and cheaper in pill form — if you even need more, which is unlikely if you have a balanced diet. You’re pretty much just paying for “expensive urine,” one doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Same for “wellness” focused products like &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/gut-health-test-microbiome-probiotics-diet-f61947edfc591616639253eeb7a8c3e0"&gt;microbiome testing kits&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that generate information that doctors can’t actually act on. And if you don’t have diabetes, there’s scant evidence that you need &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/continuous-glucose-monitor-cgm-diabetes-75469f79bc649cab0d831e6ec52758a7"&gt;a continuous glucose monitor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;To improve your health, go back to the basics&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of a panacea pill, product or routine can be enticing. But science already knows a lot about how to improve mental and physical health, and they are tried and true:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These lifestyle changes don’t just make you feel better in the moment. Research shows they impact your life for years to come, by &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/brain-health-dementia-exercise-diet-33fe2ed685acc30452005e53eba11410"&gt;lowering the risk of dementia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and many other health issues.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Don’t know who to trust? Start with your doctor&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be tough to know who to listen to about your health, faced with compelling personal stories on social media from people who swear something worked from them, or clever marketing and advertising from companies that scare you or promise an easy fix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doubts have been raised this year about established medicine, including the safety of &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/synthetic-dyes-red-3-artificial-colors-ef5af10b3aca66d0033d3f239546f1aa"&gt;food dyes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/fluoride-treatment-dental-teeth-78371f76118a1c7b8bf954d19b641d26"&gt;fluoride dental treatments,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/hepatitis-b-vaccine-acip-a6032868d6025e2c527c574222fcabf3"&gt;hepatitis B shot&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for newborns, and &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/hormone-therapy-estrogen-hot-flashes-fda-5b1f29a73553c142f67b1f88b6656428"&gt;hormone therapies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the medical system is not perfect, your doctor remains the best person to talk to about prevention, health concerns and potential treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you can’t get to a human doctor and turn to Dr. Google instead, be sure to &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/google-internet-medical-advice-9d4c56da3e598e694b2cf99b4eb5b71b"&gt;follow these tips and never use it to diagnose yourself&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. When you do get that doctor’s appointment, you can &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/doctor-visits-checkup-questions-primary-care-3fcde5b5c927734429818bd0ed1c6680"&gt;make the most of it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; by bringing a list of written questions — and don’t hesitate to ask for any clarification you need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;___&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 13:38:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQWk10ZlpoOVBTN2lZYlNEQzQ5bjFVcTlJdFFtdFZfWm13Q2l4ZUdBSlk5UUhDV0hEanVqWklaRFJsdXFzdU44MzlabEdZVTFVLUNlazREZkdSN1BveGJBalY4RTc5QWVYR1h3VVhhVUJuclRiUXYtdUJFTDcxRjFaMkxiQ2VNOEszYmRGOGl2ZjNKQ1dnQkpaS21HUWlSUmY5cU83dW5mclN5QnlYb1ZWaEE4NA</guid></item><item><title>酒精、咸味食物可以触发“节日之心” ：您需要了解的信息- NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/mosaic/2025/12/alcohol-salty-foods-can-trigger-holiday-heart-what-you-need-to-know.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2WPRPUWFURFZHIR4X2SKLKTIP4"&gt;When Dr. David Feingold felt his heart surge into a chaotic rhythm 15 years ago, he knew instantly what was happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YPY2HONL5NG4DPEJBZTLYFATPI"&gt;“I was drinking five or six Red Bulls a day, and I had a bad cold, and I was spraying myself with Afrin nose spray,” he recalled. “I went into atrial fibrillation. I felt it. I knew it.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UWATSP4YYFDGDNGT5O4UDSDVTU"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/atrial-fibrillation" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/atrial-fibrillation"&gt;Atrial fibrillation (AFib&lt;/a&gt;) is an irregular, rapid heart rate. AFib causes the heart’s upper chambers to beat erratically and out of sync with the lower chambers, which can lead to poor blood flow, according to the American Heart Association.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BTU2MMQCYFGDTCUXWNKS7TZB7Y"&gt;The condition is informally known as &lt;a href="https://www.laspalmasdelsolhealthcare.com/healthy-living/blog/recognize-holiday-heart-symptoms-to-stay-healthy-during-the-holidays" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.laspalmasdelsolhealthcare.com/healthy-living/blog/recognize-holiday-heart-symptoms-to-stay-healthy-during-the-holidays"&gt;“holiday heart syndrome”&lt;/a&gt; because it can be triggered by binge drinking, stress, overeating or dehydration common during the holidays, as well as factors like those that affected Feingold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MT5CZFLCJVD53BTBL3L2H7TRO4"&gt;His AFib episode was treated with a cardioversion — a controlled electrical shock to reset his heart. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DGNDE5JD45HBJG5LKITG5DSH6M"&gt;“Thank God,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AHZCU6ZTBJFRZDCGE7XMA564RA"&gt;“I haven’t had atrial fib in 15 years,” Feingold added. “But it was caused by the same mechanism that causes ‘holiday heart’: toxins.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XEXP6CYLKZEZ5I3U77RJJFEGK4"&gt;While New Jersey doesn’t track AFib-specific data, the national picture is sobering: AFib affects an estimated 10.5 million Americans and contributes to &lt;a href="https://search.cdc.gov/search/?query=Atrial%20fibrillation%20cases%20by%20state&amp;amp;dpage=1" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://search.cdc.gov/search/?query=Atrial%20fibrillation%20cases%20by%20state&amp;amp;dpage=1"&gt;more than 232,000 deaths,&lt;/a&gt; annually, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="R53LC53PGVAZHAPMABGXAHFDSI"&gt;Black and brown individuals have a lower overall incidence of AFib than white individuals, despite a higher incidence of risk factors such as hypertension and diabetes, according to the National Institutes of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XYSFT4XQ7RE3ZGCPZ6YYQJHDII"&gt;Yet when AFib does occur, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12173103/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12173103/"&gt;research indicates &lt;/a&gt;that people of color experience significantly worse outcomes, including nearly double the rates of stroke, heart failure, and death. Contributing factors may include disparities in health care access, diagnosis and socioeconomic conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;What ‘holiday heart’ means&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IEP3RGDIGFDAHKRC74KF3G667Q"&gt;Feingold, a longtime cardiologist and chief of cardiology at Hackensack Meridian JFK in Edison, said his experience is a reminder of how far cardiac care has come and how vulnerable people still are to preventable triggers. He offers realistic tips to stave off cardiac events during the holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="226HV53XIVHPPD2Q5Q6275757Q"&gt;The term may sound lighthearted, but Feingold said “holiday heart” can be dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="H5G4KG2JYRBJ3HLNVU5Z2TTXWE"&gt;“It’s a colloquial way of expressing a toxic episode that occurs with the heart,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CM52GAZQV5HCZPCFEFLI2I6JRU"&gt;Most cases, he said, involve people who don’t drink regularly but take a large amount of alcohol during the holidays triggering atrial fibrillation — an irregular heartbeat that can lead to stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CV3J2AAV6VFWLFVW5362PG5QUY"&gt;“If there’s a clot in there, it goes forward into your head,” Feingold said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2V2NOVMUOVHGLASTJOTNTEJU6I"&gt;Doctors now typically start patients on blood thinners immediately to prevent that risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="S7OOEE5ZSNFPDMFU63GGHUJLG4"&gt;He said alcohol isn’t the only culprit. Heavy holiday foods, especially salty dishes, which pull fluid into the heart, can also trigger symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;His holiday advice: Moderation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4PPHBQBCSFC4VNUMYCGLX2YGBI"&gt;As the season approaches, patients often tell him they can’t control their eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ME4IXUS33JCAJHGLSOKTNP2TEI"&gt;“They say, ‘Doc, the holidays are coming,’” he said. “I say to them, there’s Thanksgiving, there’s Christmas Eve, Christmas, maybe New Year’s. That’s four days. That’s no excuse.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MKBWILEW4JF3BIMRAHLCGKDUCU"&gt;He said holiday food stirs emotions for many people, bringing us back to our childhood and to our ethnic backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N4CBYJGSSBANRIM2YQZJCWDKD4"&gt;But he urges small portions, lighter swaps, alternating alcoholic drinks with water, and eating something before drinking to help slow absorption. For those who insist on dessert, he suggests, “Have a bite or two. That’s it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="R4IPLC7CTZGL3CJSAQ4QEBAF2Y"&gt;He also urges people to move around — take a short walk — and pay attention to symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KT7ZGSLFBZDLRJYJWBPXHDQ6IM"&gt;“If you feel fluttering in the chest or any discomfort, immediately stop,” he said. “If it persists, call a doctor or head to the ER.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Heart care has evolved&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="C2F5OESKLRG2BISUJKYFNAYJ3Q"&gt;Feingold said the good news is that the treatment of heart conditions has evolved since he entered cardiology 43 years ago when options were drastically limited. He said when a patient came in with a heart attack, you sat by their bed, and you gave morphine and maybe some nitroglycerin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AIWYIGSP4BD6BAIIA6MPXSGPNQ"&gt;“They either died or lived” he said. “You didn’t know.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-28" data-gaid="inarticle-28"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZR7B2CRYC5DKJAUVYHFJLYUKMM"&gt;If a patient survived, he said treatment options were limited and only the wealthy had access to bypass surgery in either Texas or New York, which had hospitals offering the latest in heart care technology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-29" data-gaid="inarticle-29"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PI5EOUSN7BGJTISS4LXSBZAZCY"&gt;Today, the landscape is unrecognizable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-30" data-gaid="inarticle-30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WNLALIZ27BAJLN4YNC6DW3XJ64"&gt;“Now you come in with a heart attack, we give drugs that prevent worsening of the heart attack,” he said. “We put new heart valves in from the skin. We put defibrillators in. Heart disease has become a chronic disease and not an acute killer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-31" data-gaid="inarticle-31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SAXGIAFB5RFSPPTKF46FK4HYB4"&gt;He also noted that early pacemakers were the size of a deck of cards and sometimes had to be recharged through the skin, which could cause the skin to heat up or even burn. Today, he said, pacemakers are about the size of a half dollar — or even smaller.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-32" data-gaid="inarticle-32"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Modern monitoring tools&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-33" data-gaid="inarticle-33"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="B7KU5RMEAFG6JOUSATDD4E2VSE"&gt;Thanks to new technology, patients can now monitor their own rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-34" data-gaid="inarticle-34"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7MXSAKI4FNFTVI4JNXS4UBON3M"&gt;“The new Apple watches actually give you a printout,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-35" data-gaid="inarticle-35"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IADE6JB7FZBQLOWHH6TTQN5IC4"&gt;A small device called Kardia also works, but he cautions that risk still depends on the individual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-36" data-gaid="inarticle-36"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5DXDXGZ3IVHJPMJCOUX5ABD4QU"&gt;“Someone older with hypertension or diabetes needs more urgent evaluation than a 20-year-old with no cardiac history,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-37" data-gaid="inarticle-37"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="H65E3EU6RNA3TAQD34M3DAFIZI"&gt;Feingold has seen the long-term effects of alcohol too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-38" data-gaid="inarticle-38"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RC6OOTV4UJB3LGHJAHNTQG6UE4"&gt;While holiday heart is temporary, chronic heavy drinking can weaken the heart muscle itself, causing cardiomyopathy — the deterioration of the middle muscular layer of the heart wall responsible for the heart’s contraction and relaxation. This condition is not reversible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-39" data-gaid="inarticle-39"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="T6DT4UYEIZEXBI5YHG5Y43FRMU"&gt;His message for the holidays is simple: listen to your body; enjoy responsibly; and respect what the heart can — and can’t — endure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-40" data-gaid="inarticle-40"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:KTZGL2NEJNCFROIVGC4CG7AAN4" data-fusion-component="KTZGL2NEJNCFROIVGC4CG7AAN4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:KTZGL2NEJNCFROIVGC4CG7AAN4" data-fusion-component="KTZGL2NEJNCFROIVGC4CG7AAN4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-41" data-gaid="inarticle-41"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNZFBiRkJKYkdQYUVYRUt3TW1SSkM0bTlnRmpsaTJITGFxUzVqME05RnpUUE9Mc0s3Rk8wUldIX0NSSHRnLXdLZDlXS1NFTVp2Vm1GQW9IUXp2V09nWDY2eWk3U1JodVdMbjJaNFMyWEl0aXc2TnZxWVZfaXg2YjNvblptYjJ4dmQ4by1CYjRVQTJfZVVlcENPNmxLbmN6Rmk4cWlpOVo3NzZ2Z9IBvgFBVV95cUxPNnpnaHIteU9zaTlTV2NCQTlQWUVHTUJzdHpUTmdsNFdERlBHTTRRVnh2QlB5cTJFZEppY2J5N0pLSWx6Qk1HWUF6QmxvT1dZMGJraTRRcGdSa1ZRZ3piMFFTV1pTRVZKUld3NlFYVDJwcWtuR1ItVFJSZHktdzJkQjJ0YVFJNnduWUZuVjg5OWoyUndTbWtlQWRVZnhybUQ2bl93LVoxRnNqdUZuZDlLaW10OFVOQTRhYjM0Mmhn</guid></item><item><title>有一种非常简单的方法可以去除饮用水中的微塑料- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/theres-a-surprisingly-easy-way-to-remove-microplastics-in-drinking-water</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Tiny fragments of plastic are making their way &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-found-in-every-human-placenta-tested-study-finds"&gt;deep inside&lt;/a&gt; our bodies in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-infiltrate-every-organ-including-brain-study-in-mice-shows"&gt;concerning quantities&lt;/a&gt;, particularly through &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microwaving-safe-plastics-can-release-billions-of-particles-scientists-warn"&gt;our food&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/bottled-water-is-packed-full-of-up-to-100x-more-microplastic-than-expected"&gt;and drink&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2024, scientists in China found a simple and effective means of removing them from water. The team ran tests on both &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Water_softening"&gt;soft water&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hard_water"&gt;hard tap water&lt;/a&gt; (which is richer in minerals).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They added in nanoplastics and microplastics before boiling the liquid and then filtering out any precipitates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-food-packaging-is-shedding-microplastics-into-every-meal-study-reveals"&gt;Your Food Packaging Is Shedding Microplastics Into Every Meal, Study Reveals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Tap water nano/microplastics (NMPs) escaping from centralized water treatment systems are of increasing global concern, because they pose potential health risks to humans via water consumption," &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.4c00081"&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the researchers &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.4c00081"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below for a summary of the findings:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some cases, up to 90 percent of the NMPs were removed by the boiling and filtering process, though the effectiveness varied based on the type of water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course the huge benefit is that most people can do it with what they already have in their kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This simple boiling water strategy can 'decontaminate' NMPs from household tap water and has the potential for harmlessly alleviating human intake of NMPs through water consumption," &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.4c00081"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; biomedical engineer Zimin Yu from Guangzhou Medical University and colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A greater concentration of NMPs was removed from samples of hard tap water, which naturally forms a buildup of limescale (or &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Calcium_carbonate"&gt;calcium carbonate&lt;/a&gt;) as it is heated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commonly seen inside kitchen kettles, the chalky substance forms on the plastic's surface as changes in temperature force the calcium carbonate out of solution, effectively trapping the plastic fragments in a crust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our results showed that nanoplastic precipitation efficiency increased with increasing water hardness upon boiling," the team &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.4c00081"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For example, from 34 percent at 80 mg L&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; to 84 percent and 90 percent at 180 and 300 mg L&lt;sup&gt;−1&lt;/sup&gt; of calcium carbonate, respectively."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even in soft water, where less calcium carbonate is dissolved, roughly a quarter of the NMPs were snagged from the water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any bits of lime-encrusted plastic could then be removed through a simple filter like the stainless steel mesh used to strain tea, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S004565352030686X"&gt;Past studies&lt;/a&gt; have measured fragments of polystyrene, polyethylene, polypropylene, and polyethylene terephthalate in potable tap water, which we're consuming daily in varying quantities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144609" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144609" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AbstractGraphicRemovingNMPFromTapWater.jpg" alt="Graphic depicting boiling water to remove NMPs" class="size-full wp-image-144609" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AbstractGraphicRemovingNMPFromTapWater.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AbstractGraphicRemovingNMPFromTapWater-600x257.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144609" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;This simple boiling water strategy can 'decontaminate' NMPs from household tap water. (Yu et al., &lt;em&gt;Environ. Sci. Technol. Lett&lt;/em&gt;., 2024)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To put the strategy to the ultimate test, the researchers added even more nanoplastic particles, which were effectively reduced in number.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Drinking boiled water apparently is a viable long-term strategy for reducing global exposure to NMPs," &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.4c00081"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; Yu and team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Drinking boiled water, however, is often regarded as a local tradition and prevails only in a few regions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists hope it might become a more widespread practice as plastics continue to take over the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-seem-to-be-in-every-kind-of-animal-except-one"&gt;Microplastics Seem to Be in Every Kind of Animal… Except One&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tiny pieces of plastic are an increasingly big problem. &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-expert-explains-the-real-dangers-of-microplastics-to-human-health"&gt;Microplastics&lt;/a&gt; originate from clothing, kitchen utensils, personal care products, and countless other everyday objects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their durability makes them persistent in the environment – including in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-could-accumulate-in-our-brains-more-than-in-kidneys-and-livers"&gt;human bodies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_145098" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-145098" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/NMPConsumptionByCountry.jpg" alt="A graphic showing NMP consumption per country" class="size-full wp-image-145098" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/NMPConsumptionByCountry.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/NMPConsumptionByCountry-337x415.jpg 337w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/NMPConsumptionByCountry-600x739.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-145098" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Human exposure to NMPs through drinking water consumption. (a) World map of drinking water hardness. (b) Daily consumption of NMPs through boiled and tap water in 67 regions. (Yu et al., &lt;em&gt;Environ. Sci. Technol. Lett.&lt;/em&gt;, 2024)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only are many people on Earth already &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-found-deep-inside-human-bones-scientists-warn"&gt;contaminated by microplastics&lt;/a&gt;, but we're also still being exposed every day, as there is minimal regulation of these insidious specks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-persist-in-drinking-water-despite-treatment-plant-advances"&gt;According to a 2025 literature review&lt;/a&gt; from The University of Texas at Arlington, a significant portion of our microplastic exposure may come from drinking water, as wastewater treatment plants are still not effectively removing microplastics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roughly &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s44296-024-00024-w"&gt;9 billion metric tons&lt;/a&gt; of plastic have been produced globally since plastic production began, much of which has progressively degraded into ever-smaller fragments without truly breaking down, forming a fine plastic dust that now pervades the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wastewater treatment plants actually do remove a lot of these small particles, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.scitotenv.2025.178818"&gt;the new review&lt;/a&gt; indicates, but not enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/glass-bottles-actually-contain-more-microplastics-scientists-find"&gt;Glass Bottles Actually Contain More Microplastics, Scientists Find&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it's still not certain exactly how damaging this &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-are-infiltrating-your-brain-what-are-the-effects"&gt;plastic is to our bodies&lt;/a&gt;, it's clearly not the healthiest of snacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144611" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144611" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PlasticsInOcean642.jpg" alt="Plastic waste in water" class="size-full wp-image-144611" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PlasticsInOcean642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PlasticsInOcean642-533x415.jpg 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PlasticsInOcean642-600x467.jpg 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144611" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Plastics continue to take over the world. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAFTVTour4A/"&gt;mbala mbala merlin/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plastics have already &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0147651323002415"&gt;been linked&lt;/a&gt; to changes in the gut microbiome and the body's antibiotic resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team behind this study wants to see more research into how boiled water could keep artificial materials out of our bodies – and perhaps counter some of the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/microplastics-infiltrate-every-organ-including-brain-study-in-mice-shows"&gt;alarming effects&lt;/a&gt; of microplastics that are emerging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our results have ratified a highly feasible strategy to reduce human NMP exposure and established the foundation for further investigations with a much larger number of samples," Yu and colleagues &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.4c00081"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;a href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.4c00081"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Environmental Science &amp;amp; Technology Letters&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in March 2024.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 12:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNazR3dktocGJMdFhvTXBwV0VYUmtwRk5yYzlLbS0wT2g5bjg1WnVObXoyaW43VjFWNlRlUFRZRUtwbEhNQURZUU1kb3NpVC03VzV6SHVJbzdFN2R0X2lZMUpVcW9ZZE5OMGZEM2xDUm1PWE9rUTdIakVmQVJmX2VlZ1M4S2RYOEszcEc4X29DNVJmWGlkcDFNSDB0ZUhnbXlmNS0w</guid></item><item><title>我以采访营养学家为生–以下是他们都同意的饮食建议-《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/best-diet-tips-fat-loss-nutrition-experts-b2883459.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;here is a lot of diet advice on the internet – some good, some not so good, some terrible. As &lt;em&gt;The Independent&lt;/em&gt;’s&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;senior fitness writer, I interview experts weekly in an attempt to cut through this noise and bring readers accessible, effective tips that benefit their &lt;a href="/news/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No matter which expert I’m speaking to, there are several underlying features of a nutritious adult &lt;a href="/topic/diet"&gt;diet&lt;/a&gt; that remain largely undisputed: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-kk992l-0 sc-1k7glnk-1 dDVXDN irZnNR"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eat a wide variety of plant-based foods including plenty of vegetables&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choose wholefoods where possible &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Focus on hitting fibre requirements – at least 30g per day &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consume adequate protein from lean sources&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay hydrated&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Foods with excessive saturated fat and added sugar should form only a small portion of your diet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Consume an appropriate number of calories for your build and activity levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you were to follow this advice consistently, chances are your health would be in a pretty positive place. Add regular &lt;a href="/topic/exercise"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt; into the mix and you’re running in the right direction. But there are other key tips that have stayed with me in 2025 – which I have compiled for you below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Prioritise nutritious foods you can add to your diet &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Appetite is finite,” &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="http://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?tsid=3658&amp;amp;platform=independentcouk_web&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.co.uk%2FEverything-Fat-Loss-Definitive-Bullsh%2Fdp%2FB0BT733QD8%3Fascsubtag%3DIN%7C2883459%7CB0BT733QD8%7Cindependentcouk_web"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Everything Fat Loss&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; author and experienced trainer Ben Carpenter tells me. “I like focusing on adding nutritious foods into your diet because they tend to displace other foods.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, one study Carpenter cites found that children encouraged to eat more apples – a food rich in nutrients and high in fibre – actually lowered their daily caloric intake. The fruit had elbowed other less nutritious, energy-dense food out of the picture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He says most people have a good idea what is meant by nutritious food, but adds that opting for items that “tend to be slightly less processed” is a good rule of thumb to follow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For example, fruits and vegetables, lean proteins [white fish, white meat, soy, tofu], beans, lentils and wholegrains,” Carpenter lists. “Even things like rice and oats as opposed to donuts, pancakes and waffles.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/bold-bean-co-gut-health-recipes-b2842333.html"&gt;How fibremaxxing became the secret to better gut-health and easy recipes to use now&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="7" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bHmhpR"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/08/20/8/43/iStock-2150137406.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/08/20/8/43/iStock-2150137406.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/08/20/8/43/iStock-2150137406.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Incorporating more nutritious foods in your diet can displace more energy-dense, less nutritious alternatives" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-519624"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Incorporating more nutritious foods in your diet can displace more energy-dense, less nutritious alternatives&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Balance wins over ultra-extreme every time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From carnivore to keto, extreme diets will continue to grab headlines – yet the definition of diet isn’t something short-term, but rather the foods you habitually eat. By this logic, it makes sense to stick with something sustainable and health-promoting, rather than following an unmanageably restrictive regime for a few weeks before inevitably falling back into old habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rather than being ultra-extreme, focus on balance,” advises &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/live-well/eat-well/how-to-eat-a-balanced-diet/eating-a-balanced-diet/"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; GP Dr Radha Modgil. “One of the big things we can all do is look at how many fruits and vegetables we’re eating each day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They don’t have to be fresh, they can be canned, dried or frozen, but the evidence shows that if we at least eat our five a day, we have a lower risk of heart disease, stroke and some cancers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Modgil points to the NHS’s Eatwell Guide as an example of how to structure a balanced diet. It recommends that a third of the food we eat should be fruit and vegetables, another third should be starchy foods high in fibre such as wholegrains, then the remainder should comprise items such as beans, pulses, lean protein sources and dairy (or dairy alternatives). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foods such as chocolate, cakes, biscuits, sugary soft drinks, butter and ice cream are non-essential additions to your diet, “so should be eaten less often and in smaller amounts”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="7" class="sc-awdjp1-0 kSPTgz"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2016/05/22/15/eatwell-guide.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2016/05/22/15/eatwell-guide.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2016/05/22/15/eatwell-guide.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="NHS GP Dr Radha Modgil says the Eatwell Guide provides a good template for constructing a healthy meal and wider diet" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-519625"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;NHS GP Dr Radha Modgil says the Eatwell Guide provides a good template for constructing a healthy meal and wider diet&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Public Health England)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/how-to-reduce-diabetes-risk-b2878819.html"&gt;What the shape of your buttock muscles might mean for your future health – and how to change it&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Alter your food environment &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The human body and brain like to take the path of least resistance, particularly when your schedule becomes hectic. If you can make healthy options more practical, you drastically increase your chance of choosing them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many ways to do this. Preparing your lunches in advance is the most obvious, stopping you from splashing the cash on fast food during office days. But there are other quick things you can do that will push your eating habits in a positive direction. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cooking up a lean protein source like a chicken or block of tofu at the start of your week, then having it in your fridge, can make it easier to whip up nutritious meals when you’re short on time in the evenings. Having fruit on your desk in the office can encourage smarter snacking, while placing nutritious snacks such as carrots and hummus in compartments at the front of your fridge or cupboard means you can mindlessly graze on these nourishing foods with minimal effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One final tip is omitting products high in saturated fat and added sugars – such as crisps and chocolate – from your weekly food shop, meaning you have to leave the house and buy them if you want to eat them. Putting an extra hurdle between you and the action you’re looking to cut back on makes you less likely to do it, and if you do pop to the shops you’ll be adding a bit of extra movement into your day – a win-win. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/exercise-snacking-workouts-heart-health-b2859776.html"&gt;The science-backed two-minute daily workouts for improving heart health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="7" class="sc-awdjp1-0 dywRpZ"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/03/14/14/iStock-883982334.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/03/14/14/iStock-883982334.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/03/14/14/iStock-883982334.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Preparing nutritious meals in advance can make healthy choices easier to take later in the week" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-519626"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Preparing nutritious meals in advance can make healthy choices easier to take later in the week&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Focus on fibre as well as protein &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Both protein and fibre are essential,” says Dr Karan Rajan, a surgeon and author of &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="http://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?tsid=3658&amp;amp;platform=independentcouk_web&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.co.uk%2FThis-Book-Save-Your-Life-ebook%2Fdp%2FB0BY1R4D7V%2Fref%3Dsr_1_1%3Fascsubtag%3DIN%7C2883459%7CB0BY1R4D7V%7Cindependentcouk_web"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This Book May Save Your Life&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. “There are plenty of foods and meal combos where you can get both, but if I had to over-index on one, it would be fibre. I’d say the average person probably consumes enough protein and nowhere near enough fibre.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/national-diet-and-nutrition-survey-2019-to-2023/national-diet-and-nutrition-survey-2019-to-2023-report"&gt;National Diet and Nutrition Survey&lt;/a&gt;, 96 per cent of UK adults are falling shy of their 30g daily fibre requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When it comes to human physiology, there [aren’t many processes that] fibre isn’t involved in, either directly or indirectly,” Dr Rajan continues. “Its benefits include regulating hormones, metabolism, appetite, the gut microbiome, mood, bowels and more.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fibre can be found in plant-based foods such as lentils, beans and peas, as well as wholegrains such as oats and barley, fruits, vegetables, nuts and seeds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protein is also important, playing a role in many bodily processes such as building and repairing tissues (including, most notably, muscle) and supporting immune function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The recommended nutrient intake for protein in the UK is 0.75 grams per kilogram of body weight,” says &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://researchportal.bath.ac.uk/en/persons/javier-gonzalez"&gt;Professor Javier Gonzalez&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of nutrition and metabolism at the University of Bath’s Centre for Nutrition, Exercise and Metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are some good arguments that a little higher than this – up to 1.2g/kg – may have additional benefits for muscle health and weight control. The requirements of athletes can be even higher than this – up to around 1.8g/kg.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most experts I speak to argue that the majority of people are already consuming enough protein. However, as Dr Gonzalez explains above, those who exercise may benefit from a slightly higher daily intake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this reason, Nichola Ludlam-Raine, a specialist registered dietitian and author of &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="http://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?tsid=3658&amp;amp;platform=independentcouk_web&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.co.uk%2FHow-Not-Eat-Ultra-Processed-life-changing%2Fdp%2F1529940117%2Fref%3Dasc_df_1529940117%3Fascsubtag%3DIN%7C2846584%7C1529940117%7Cindependentcouk_web"&gt;How Not to Eat Ultra-Processed&lt;/a&gt;, recommends aiming to include both protein and fibre in your snack choices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Think apple and cheese, berries and yoghurt, carrots and hummus, or nuts and dried fruit,” she says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/life-style/food-and-drink/features/ultra-processed-food-lancet-medical-journal-b2868062.html"&gt;The five ultra-processed food ingredients to avoid on packaging – and what to buy instead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="7" class="sc-awdjp1-0 laKbvU"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/10/30/09/houmous.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/10/30/09/houmous.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/10/30/09/houmous.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Dietitian Nichola Ludlam-Raine recommends aiming to include both fibre and protein in your snacks – for example, carrots and hummus" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-519627"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Dietitian Nichola Ludlam-Raine recommends aiming to include both fibre and protein in your snacks – for example, carrots and hummus&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Eat your CAP&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/gut-health-nutrition-diet-b2789919.html"&gt;Gut health&lt;/a&gt; is a buzz term in the fitness industry right now. Fermented items such as kimchi, &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/kombucha-drink-health-benefits-scoby-equinox-b2848346.html"&gt;kombucha&lt;/a&gt; and sauerkraut are widely seen as the key to a more settled stomach – something that plugs into a huge range of systems in the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Johnny Drain, a fermentation expert and author of &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="http://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?tsid=3658&amp;amp;platform=independentcouk_web&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.co.uk%2FAdventures-Fermentation-Culinary-Frontiers-Exploration%2Fdp%2F0241699134%2Fref%3Dasc_df_0241699134%3Fascsubtag%3DIN%7C2765194%7C0241699134%7Cindependentcouk_web"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Adventures in Fermentation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, says his golden rule for gut health is to “eat your CAP” – an acronym for “colourful array of plant-based foods”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are associations between a more diverse gut microbiome and improved mood and cognition, improved mental health, improved immune function and improved digestion,” Dr Drain explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Humans are essentially a tube – you put something in at the top and other stuff comes out of the bottom. The game is getting as many nutrients from it as possible in the process.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microbes in our gut help us extract nutrients from the food we eat. Research, such as this 2023 study from the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.ox.ac.uk/news/2023-12-15-study-shows-diverse-gut-bacteria-communities-protect-against-harmful-pathogens"&gt;University of Oxford&lt;/a&gt;, suggests improved gut microbiome diversity is associated with better health outcomes, and vice versa. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People that have some diseases, such as metabolic diseases, might have a less diverse microbiome,” explains Dr Drain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American Gut Health (or Microsetta Initiative) study showed that consuming 30 or more different plant foods per week can increase gut microbiome diversity, and consequently gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These foods include fruits, vegetables, whole grains, beans, lentils, nuts, seeds and even herbs and spices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The inclusion of fermented foods with live cultures such as kefir, live yoghurt, sauerkraut, kimchi and miso has also been associated with positive impacts on gut health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/best-healthy-habits-every-day-b2837119.html"&gt;Do these five things daily for 90 days to see a ‘profound difference’ in your health, fitness and energy levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="7" class="sc-awdjp1-0 gFcOVD"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/16/17/25/iStock-2233021362.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/16/17/25/iStock-2233021362.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/10/16/17/25/iStock-2233021362.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Fermented foods such as kimchi can contribute to a more diverse gut microbiome and improved gut health" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-519628"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Fermented foods such as kimchi can contribute to a more diverse gut microbiome and improved gut health&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Know where to find polyphenols&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polyphenols are plant-based dietary compounds found in a wide variety of foods and drinks, from berries to green tea to dark chocolate. They overlap heavily with fibre, although emerging research points towards these compounds having health perks in their own right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Rajan, they have anti-inflammatory properties, they can improve cardiometabolic function and they support endothelial function (related to the lining of the blood vessels). Polyphenols may also aid lipid modulation and directly impact gut microbiome health, he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A review article, published in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1568163725000790"&gt;Ageing Research Reviews&lt;/a&gt; journal in 2025, also pointed towards polyphenols having anti-ageing effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So where can you find them? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-kk992l-0 sc-1k7glnk-1 dDVXDN irZnNR"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Berries – especially blueberries, blackberries and strawberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cocoa and dark chocolate – 70 per cent cocoa or higher&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Green tea and coffee &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Grapes and red wine – “Though alcohol obviously has downsides for gut health and it is more generally linked to increased risk of cancers, so grapes are better,” says Dr Rajan &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apples and pears &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Turmeric – curcumin is the active compound – and other herbs and spices &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Olive oil &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nuts such as almonds or walnuts &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Onions and garlic &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than targeting specific polyphenols in the supermarket, Dr Rajan recommends shaping your wider diet to include several sources. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A Mediterranean-style diet is naturally rich in polyphenols,” he says. “Small daily choices, like opting for black coffee, snacking on a couple of squares of dark chocolate, eating some mixed berries and having olive oil with meals, will add up over time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/diet-and-exercise-advice-for-longevity-b2833750.html"&gt;Scientists reveal the small lifestyle changes that can reduce your risk of heart disease and add 10 years to your life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="7" class="sc-awdjp1-0 eFcuEG"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/10/22/14/iStock-1337021714.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/10/22/14/iStock-1337021714.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/10/22/14/iStock-1337021714.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Blueberries, almonds and dark chocolate all contain polyphenols" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-519629"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Blueberries, almonds and dark chocolate all contain polyphenols&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Prioritise wholefoods&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultra-processed food (UPF) is another phrase that has hit the mainstream in recent years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professor Chris van Tulleken, a professor of global health and infection at University College London, and author of &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="http://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?tsid=3658&amp;amp;platform=independentcouk_web&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.co.uk%2FUltra-Processed-People-Stuff-That-Isnt%2Fdp%2F1529900050%3Fascsubtag%3DIN%7C2883459%7C1529900050%7Cindependentcouk_web"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ultra-Processed People&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, applies the working definition: “If the packaging you are reading has an ingredient that you don’t typically find in a domestic kitchen, like an emulsifier or a flavouring, then it’s very likely to be an ultra-processed food.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The concept of UPF continues to stir up debate, but a systematic review published in &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.thelancet.com/series-do/ultra-processed-food"&gt;The Lancet&lt;/a&gt; medical journal this year detailed a link between UPF consumption and non-communicable diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you can find a way of eating real food, we’re very sure that’s better for you,” says van Tulleken. “You don’t have to believe any of the evidence around ultra-processed food to say that’s true – that’s established in nutrition.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To achieve this, he recommends asking yourself a simple question before you buy or eat any food and drink. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Was this food prepared with the purpose of protecting my health and nourishing me? If the answer to that question is no, then I think you should contemplate if you want to eat it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Count your drinks in your diet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What we drink is often seen as separate diet, but everything we put in our body will have some sort of impact – large or small, positive or negative. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Water is always the healthiest option of any drink,” says Dr Modgil. “Our brains are nearly 80 per cent water, so it’s something we obviously need to stay healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s important to drink regularly throughout the day and avoid sugary drinks.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This includes the usual suspect such as energy drinks and fizzy drinks, as well as limiting fruit juices and smoothies to one small glass per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Even though there is fruit in there, they are still quite high in sugar,” Dr Modgil explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other small changes you can make include adding less sugar to your tea and coffee, and drinking alcohol in moderation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The current guidelines are 14 units per week,” says neuropsychopharmacologist and &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="http://redirect.viglink.com/?cuid=xid:fr1765816255343fda&amp;amp;u=https%3A%2F%2Fsentiaspirits.com%2Fpages%2Fabout&amp;amp;articleId=b2846549&amp;amp;key=5b1a6400a3c0d931ed2037885e1a27a3"&gt;Sentia&lt;/a&gt; co-founder Professor David Nutt. “If you can stick within those, the harms of alcohol are relatively minor. Most people who stick within these limits will not experience significant harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-us-premium-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The advice we give is, if you do drink, always have at least two days a week where you don’t drink at all because that allows your liver and heart and blood vessels to recover. And don’t stockpile. If you’re going to try and stick to the 14 units, don’t take them in one go because that’s going to be more deleterious to your brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/life-style/food-and-drink/features/food-inflation-rising-why-climate-change-meat-price-b2868901.html"&gt;Inflation is down – so why is your food shop getting even more expensive?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:58:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQWUNQUmlwR2QwY01UbFpOeHJzV2FYVngxQVg0Qm0weHhFYnZ2WURLMGI2QkNUV1c0ZXJfVlJxQWNISmdzQTBiTEw3Njg1eDZtVnFVYzF0WWFPMkRvT051RGE0UXBySXlWV25aY2k2OFF1RUlYcTFkbFByR1lGNk1lNEhoS3FSRVF0X0R3dnRLUUVOLWYxZ0QzOUpwbks2ZHlQQ2h5YjN1WQ</guid></item><item><title>专家质疑丹麦的疫苗计划是美国的典范--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/29/world/europe/denmark-vaccine-schedule-rfk.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 10:01:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPQ285OFRBTWFqUmZXVU96T21kcWFjNXhzdHVBQUNGUmxZNndIRXZVZE5WOGh3ZmVhSjY1R1JXUTJvOHRaS3NJVTJFYWpMNVZMQ0s3eGp6cHFsaERmbkQ5clRyOFlzWEtDNVY4MmFuRmlQLVVqcnhNQUVBN29JTlZac0x2RkhFY2VK</guid></item><item><title>Kratom和7-OH产品可广泛使用。它们也是公共卫生辩论的核心。：短波- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/29/nx-s1-5633323/kratom-fda-drug-addictive-opioids</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resnx-s1-img-5866695" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Kratom and 7-OH products are available in many smoke shops. Some people use them instead of opioids. Others say they're addictive – and should be better regulated.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    somnuk krobkum/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        somnuk krobkum/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Kratom and 7-OH products are becoming increasingly popular in the United States. They're available in many smoke shops, but the &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/news-events/press-announcements/fda-takes-steps-restrict-7-oh-opioid-products-threatening-american-consumers" target="_blank"&gt;Food and Drug Administration says&lt;/a&gt; certain products are highly addictive — and could lead to the next wave of the opioid epidemic.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;This isn't the first time kratom has come under scrutiny.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Nearly a decade ago, the Drug Enforcement Administration, or DEA, &lt;a href="https://www.dea.gov/press-releases/2016/08/30/dea-announces-intent-schedule-kratom" target="_blank"&gt;wanted to classify&lt;/a&gt; the active ingredients in kratom in the same category as heroin. That meant products would have gone from being widely available to highly&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;restricted.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Following the announcement, there was a massive wave of protest from advocates and lawmakers — including people who said they used kratom products to wean themselves off opioids.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The DEA decided not to move forward.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Today on the show, we dive into what could happen with the FDA's scheduling change, and what researchers do – and don't – know about kratom and 7-OH.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Interested in more of the science behind drugs and supplements? Email us your question at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:shortwave@npr.org" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;u&gt;shortwave@npr.org&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen to every episode of Short Wave sponsor-free and support our work at NPR by signing up for Short Wave+ at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://plus.npr.org/shortwave" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;plus.npr.org/shortwave&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Listen to Short Wave on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://n.pr/3HOQKeK" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Spotify&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; and &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://n.pr/3WA9vqh" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This episode was produced by Rachel Carlson and Hannah Chinn. It was edited by Rebecca Ramirez. Tyler Jones checked the facts. The audio engineer was Jimmy Keeley.   &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOR1ZfcklscnA1b2xxREJmaGtadGpOeF80Uk5raDVWc0I1MVlLN3BseTdkbE8yT054blFacGdEOGNUdkxXNzFDeVc2bndsdm1lTnB6Q2FGdWhFYVBrWHBoQTJQbWRrWjFRSG5ZUld5bUlDaGNQcEpwM05lM2xISDlKd0lMSVg</guid></item><item><title>如何及早发现动脉阻塞？心脏病专家揭示动脉粥样硬化是“无声的杀手” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/how-to-detect-blocked-arteries-early-cardiologist-reveals-atherosclerosis-is-a-silent-killer-101766979986636.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/how-to-detect-blocked-arteries-early-cardiologist-reveals-atherosclerosis-is-a-silent-killer-101766979986636.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-shares-life-saving-tips-for-heart-attacks-you-can-follow-in-first-few-minutes-101766502781253.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Heart attacks"&gt;Heart attacks&lt;/a&gt; are one of the major causes of death globally, and clogged arteries are the underlying reasons behind most of them. As per the &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.who.int/health-topics/cardiovascular-diseases#tab=tab_1" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="World Health Organization"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, an estimated 17.9 million cardiovascular deaths (CVD) occur worldwide each year. And four out of five CVD cases are due to heart attacks and stroke.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/29/550x309/heart_1766980254101_1766980254261.jpg" alt="One needs to take precautions to prevent artieries getting clogged up. (Pexels)" title="One needs to take precautions to prevent artieries getting clogged up. (Pexels)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/29/550x309/heart_1766980254101_1766980254261.jpg" alt="One needs to take precautions to prevent artieries getting clogged up. (Pexels)" title="One needs to take precautions to prevent artieries getting clogged up. (Pexels)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;One needs to take precautions to prevent artieries getting clogged up. (Pexels)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-warns-of-high-heart-attack-risks-after-menopause-shares-5-signs-neck-pain-irregular-heartbeats-fatigue-101757385613811.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Cardiologist warns of high heart attack risks after menopause; shares 5 signs: Neck pain, irregular heartbeats and more"&gt;Cardiologist warns of high heart attack risks after menopause; shares 5 signs: Neck pain, irregular heartbeats and more&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Narrowed or blocked arteries are one of the main reasons for these life-threatening medical emergencies. So it is critical to identify it early, right during the process of artery blockage. Let's take a closer look at a related condition called atherosclerosis, where plaque builds up inside the arteries. This subsequently leads to blocked arteries, which reduce or stop blood flow.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Saurabh Juneja, Director &amp;amp; HOD, Cardiology, ISIC Multi-Speciality Hospital, shared with HT Lifestyle how one can detect it early.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He explained the condition, “&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Atherosclerosis is a formidable and often silent adversary, a chronic condition characterised by the gradual hardening and narrowing of arteries due to the build-up of plaque.” This condition is progressive in nature, and the cardiologist noted that the initial stages are usually asymptomatic.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He also shared how this condition leads to blocked arteries, “&lt;span&gt;Atherosclerosis is a progressive disease that typically begins with damage to the inner lining of an artery. The damage initiates an inflammatory response, leading to the accumulation of plaque. As plaque continues to grow, it stiffens and narrows the arteries, impeding the smooth flow of blood.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why is atherosclerosis a ‘silent killer’?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Juneja flagged this condition as a ‘silent killer' as it can grow slowly in the body for years without showing any visible symptoms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Later on, it appears only after significant damage has already occurred, often without the individual being aware. The cardiologist warned of major emergencies such as heart attacks, strokes and severe cardiovascular conditions. This happens as eventually the artery becomes narrowed or completely blocked. It is alarming, as Dr Juneja remarked, one can live for decades without any symptoms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Risk factors and vulnerable groups&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some lifestyle and pre-existing factors that make a person more likely to develop this condition. Dr Juneja listed the risk factors:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;High blood pressure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;High cholesterol (particularly high LDL, "bad" cholesterol)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Smoking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Diabetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Obesity and physical inactivity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unhealthy diet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Likewise, certain groups of people are more vulnerable to developing atherosclerosis. Dr Juneja outlined these groups, making it important for individuals in them to be especially vigilant about presentation and early detection:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Individuals with metabolic conditions:&lt;/strong&gt; Those diagnosed with hypertension, dyslipidemia (high cholesterol), or diabetes are at a substantially elevated risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Smokers&lt;/strong&gt;: Tobacco use is one of the most potent risk factors, directly damaging arterial walls and accelerating plaque formation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Individuals with unhealthy lifestyles: &lt;/strong&gt;Sedentary habits and diets rich in saturated/trans fats, cholesterol, and sodium contribute significantly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Older age: &lt;/strong&gt;The risk of atherosclerosis increases with age, typically becoming more prevalent after 45 for men and 55 for women.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Family history:&lt;/strong&gt; A strong family history of early heart disease or stroke indicates a genetic predisposition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chronic inflammatory conditions: &lt;/strong&gt;Conditions like chronic kidney disease and certain autoimmune diseases can also heighten susceptibility.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Tests&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Since this condition is asymptomatic in its early stages, it is vital to stay on top of your health and undergo regular tests. Dr Juneja recommended these tests, especially for those with multiple risk factors, a family history of heart diseases or for people over the age of 40:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blood tests:&lt;/strong&gt; Cholesterol panel (lipid profile), blood sugar, and C-reactive protein (CRP) levels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blood pressure monitoring: &lt;/strong&gt;Regular checks are essential for identifying hypertension.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ankle-Brachial Index (ABI):&lt;/strong&gt; A simple test comparing blood pressure in the ankle to that in the arm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carotid ultrasound: &lt;/strong&gt;Visualises plaque buildup in the neck arteries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Coronary Artery Calcium (CAC) score: &lt;/strong&gt;A CT scan measuring calcium deposits in heart arteries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TMT (Treadmill Test) / Stress Echo: &lt;/strong&gt;These tests assess heart function under stress to detect blockages in coronary arteries that might not be apparent at rest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 04:55:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8wFBVV95cUxQZjBlSW5OZ25aYjl4a1V2ZWVuVWtsYUx6WnlobHc4Z0pSUlVSZ293Z2VIdkJPaHBTYjNxc045OHVtdEhzYndNclRuMTVwOHpxWlgyQTNyQ2x2b2NucHY5STd0OGdJU0F1M2VBYjlkczNCVUlnaUNQcHFRQk1vNnhTN1JBTHBBNHZ3dE1FRWpRZmVoN0tveE8yREFkUW5JMXJFS01tbW84RV81Z0MzZjFLNVQ2M2dldnhtY1dCTWhISTJxUzByZEVUU2lvdkVpMDRhUmNvRmM1LWlYQnNhc3lva0F1ZXJXS2ItelVEbG9UV2tSTHfSAfgBQVVfeXFMTlE1M0N4eG1OWUx6TkFWaTVUYVVSYWo1NnlheE0ybTZCZk5IaHE5OUhQUXcwNll0elBfNW1RRWZ2Tl9oWmpxMmFKd05nR3dCeS1ENFF3SzlneGRfRTl6N0lyakoxUEJBQU1kNGx4WDF1UElaMGRUaDI3SENFUWxCZkVRd2pJU0tUcVhieTNGOUhLenJia0RDSWdKdzd2VTFJTW9LVmpRaHlERWZja0gyS1NLNUxtcjAyWlpwX2xzTXBhOWhxa3RpTDlNMWlYc3BvZVdoRm5JdWtWU0hrVFlrVG1DTU1ZRjdacl9BWXNxaTZaZUJlQTVyWFc</guid></item><item><title>新的抗体治疗重新唤醒免疫系统以对抗胰腺癌- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/new-antibody-treatment-reawakens-immune-system-to-fight-pancreatic-cancer/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 02:11:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxPZjdESTFMV3l3UklXQ1NmLUhuLVQydmRXME1TdFFlQ0lFRDlHYWZxanVLQTlhUWtTa2VScEZPN1BRcXlZekNVRnFoeTJQd0d4bXI5bUoyMTFFd0xZUGQ2YTZCdDlRT0FUSFZTekR3cXRPR29xdXJIbjBzazlRTDVHRFRtZUlud0F1NjlUbDVzVmxCT3V2Q3ZkV1JmWjlCaFBT</guid></item><item><title>奶酪确实与降低痴呆风险有关，但有一个问题- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/cheese-really-is-linked-to-lower-dementia-risk-but-theres-a-catch</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A large Swedish &lt;a href="https://www.neurology.org/doi/10.1212/WNL.0000000000214343?url_ver=Z39.88-2003&amp;amp;rfr_id=ori:rid:crossref.org&amp;amp;rfr_dat=cr_pub%20%200pubmed"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; reported a lower risk of dementia among middle-aged and older adults who consumed higher amounts of full-fat cheese and cream. The findings may sound like welcome news but they need careful interpretation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study followed 27,670 participants for 25 years, during which 3,208 developed &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/dementia-283"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among people without a known genetic risk for  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="186945" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease, eating more than 50 grams of full-fat cheese per day was associated with a 13%–17% lower risk of Alzheimer's. No such reduction was seen among people who carried genetic risk factors for the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-drug-stalls-alzheimers-development-in-breakthrough-trial"&gt;New Drug Stalls Alzheimer's Development in Breakthrough Trial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consuming more than 20 grams of full-fat cream per day was linked to a 16%–24% lower risk of dementia overall. No associations were found for low-fat or high-fat milk, fermented or non-fermented milk, or low-fat cream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings are notable given longstanding public &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/live-well/eat-well/food-types/milk-and-dairy-nutrition/"&gt;health advice&lt;/a&gt; to choose low-fat dairy to reduce cardiovascular risk. This matters because heart disease and dementia share many risk factors, including high blood pressure,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="186945" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, and obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When evidence from previous studies is combined, analyses suggest that cheese consumption may also be linked to a lower risk of heart disease, and that full-fat dairy does not necessarily increase cardiovascular risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several other studies have explored whether similar patterns apply to brain health, but the results are mixed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186949" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186949" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/TwoPeopleDrinkingTakeawayCoffeesorMilkshakes-642x361.jpg" alt="Two young adults enjoying takeaway drinks on a bench outdoors" class="size-medium wp-image-186949" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/TwoPeopleDrinkingTakeawayCoffeesorMilkshakes-642x361.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/TwoPeopleDrinkingTakeawayCoffeesorMilkshakes-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/TwoPeopleDrinkingTakeawayCoffeesorMilkshakes-600x338.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/TwoPeopleDrinkingTakeawayCoffeesorMilkshakes.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186949" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;No need to add extra cream… (FatCamera/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evidence &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38043604/"&gt;overall&lt;/a&gt; suggests that studies conducted in Asian populations are more likely to report benefits of dairy consumption for cognitive health, while many European studies do not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One possible explanation is that average dairy intake tends to be much lower in Asian countries, meaning modest consumption may have different effects than higher intakes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, one Japanese study reported a reduced dementia risk among people who ate cheese, but overall consumption levels were very low and the research was sponsored by a cheese producer. In contrast, another &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37335358/"&gt;Japanese study&lt;/a&gt; funded by government grants found no protective effect of cheese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some long-term European studies have also reported benefits. In a Finnish &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00394-022-02834-x"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; of 2,497 middle-aged men followed for 22 years, cheese was the only food associated with a lower dementia risk, reduced by 28%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumption of milk and processed red meat was linked to poorer performance on cognitive tests, while fish consumption was associated with better outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11357-022-00615-2"&gt;UK study&lt;/a&gt; following nearly 250,000 people found that eating fish two to four times a week, fruit daily and cheese once a week was associated with lower dementia risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, these studies have important limitations. What people eat is usually self-reported, and changes in memory can affect both eating habits and how accurately people remember what they have eaten. To deal with this, the Swedish researchers took two extra steps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, they excluded anyone who already had dementia when the study began. Then they repeated the same calculations after removing people who went on to develop dementia within the first ten years of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This did not mean starting the study again or recruiting new participants. It simply meant re-checking the results using a smaller group of people who remained dementia-free for longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason for doing this is that the early stages of dementia can subtly change behaviour long before diagnosis. People may eat differently, lose their appetite, or struggle to recall their usual diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By focusing on participants who stayed cognitively healthy for many years, the researchers reduced the chance that these early changes were influencing the results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another important question is whether substitution played a role. Some of the apparent benefits may reflect replacing red or processed meat with cheese or cream, rather than an effect of dairy itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Supporting this idea, the Swedish study found no association between full-fat dairy and dementia risk among participants whose diets remained stable over five years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, foods should not be considered in isolation. Dietary patterns matter more than individual ingredients. Diets such as the &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11357-022-00615-2"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;, which is consistently associated with lower risks of both dementia and heart disease, include cheese alongside vegetables, fish, whole grains, and fruit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186951" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186951" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/HealthyFoodDisplay-642x361.jpg" alt="Flatlay of various fresh healthy foods" class="size-medium wp-image-186951" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/HealthyFoodDisplay-642x361.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/HealthyFoodDisplay-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/HealthyFoodDisplay-600x338.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/HealthyFoodDisplay.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186951" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Eating a healthy, varied diet can help protect brain health. (AlexRaths/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Swedish study, people who consumed more full-fat cheese and cream were also more educated, less likely to be overweight, and had lower rates of conditions linked to dementia, including heart disease, stroke, high blood pressure, and diabetes. All of these factors independently reduce dementia risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This suggests that higher cheese intake tended to occur within healthier overall lifestyles, rather than alongside excess calorie consumption or poor metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-identify-6-key-depression-symptoms-that-predict-dementia-risk"&gt;Scientists Identify 6 Key Depression Symptoms That Predict Dementia Risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, the evidence does not support the idea that full-fat dairy causes dementia, nor that fermented milk products reliably protect against it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Full-fat cheese contains several nutrients relevant to brain health, including fat-soluble  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="186945" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamins&lt;/a&gt; A, D, and K2, as well as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="186945" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamin&lt;/a&gt; B12, folate, iodine, zinc, and selenium. These nutrients play roles in neurological function and may help support cognitive health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, the data do not justify eating large amounts of cheese or cream as protective foods against dementia or heart disease. The most consistent message remains that balanced diets, moderation, and overall lifestyle matter far more than any single item on the cheese board.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/272138/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/eef-hogervorst-1283596"&gt;Eef Hogervorst&lt;/a&gt;, Professor of Biological Psychology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/loughborough-university-1336"&gt;Loughborough University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/can-eating-high-fat-cheese-and-cream-reduce-dementia-risk-as-a-new-study-suggests-272138"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:12:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPM3hiaFA0VFZWdFQta1FDZDJMVGdqNzlBSWNMdjdlREZXU29Ta1NpbmExUlZBbDhNMXlmSlNzVXBBcFo0bHZRNDlXZ1UxNmtnWTQyeVBqTF84Q0g0Wkllc1BrcEpqV1Vib3hyeTk2cWRzY0R3YkhCdUVnX3E3T2lGejFlbmhFQW1HcG8wNzd1YUNYV1IxaF85ZmlR</guid></item><item><title>他汀类药物为什么会受伤？科学家解开30年的谜团-SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/why-do-statins-hurt-scientists-solve-30-year-mystery/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 01:01:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNVkktdUpRZzM5RU9HV0hKTF81ZWtSNUR1N0s1Qjc3UXBHeWtuZVdPbm1ERTR3ZXU3RXhjbnZzSG5zV3FxcnZhekhfOWNSRVBNMC0zZm9iVzg2MlVCYWZNSXlzVnUzWmFkWXZBRVpFemdBd21JUU83WGFrRERoV05mSmdqb3Q</guid></item><item><title>根据健康专家的说法，深度睡眠的最佳夜间零食- REAL SIMPLE</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/healthy-nighttime-snacks-for-better-sleep-11874584</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-article-intro_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-intro mntl-block article-content__description"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--summary realsimple-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Snacking before bed is fine—if you pick sleep-friendly foods like nuts, yogurt, oats, or tart cherries that curb hunger and support restful sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nutrients like fiber, magnesium, tryptophan, and melatonin can boost sleep quality while keeping you satisfied.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Skip sugar, alcohol, caffeine, and heavy or spicy foods at night, as they can disrupt sleep and digestion.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It’s all too common to feel &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/stop-late-night-cravings-11836290" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nagging hunger pangs&lt;/a&gt; in the hours between dinner and bedtime. Unfortunately, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/heart-healthy-snacks-for-late-night-cravings-11777163" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;nighttime snacks and drinks&lt;/a&gt; often have a not-so-healthy reputation—it’s easy to reach for the most convenient (and crave-worthy) options after a day of making nutritious choices. While those late-night treats may be delicious, some can interfere with sleep quality and leave you feeling unsatisfied. That’s a frustrating double whammy, especially since good sleep is a cornerstone of overall health and wellness.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The good news? Needing a snack before bed isn’t a problem—with the right choices, a nighttime snack can be both satisfying and nourishing. Here, experts share some delicious, healthy options that curb hunger and support restful sleep.
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-optimal-nutrients-for-healthy-nighttime-snacks"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Optimal Nutrients for Healthy Nighttime Snacks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Foods with these nutrients aren’t just healthy for you, but also support a good night’s rest—so they’re perfect healthy night snacks. When midnight hunger comes knocking, reach for:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Fiber &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-much-fiber-do-you-need-a-day-7564730" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Fiber supports optimal health&lt;/a&gt; by regulating the blood sugar response, lowering cholesterol levels, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-to-help-you-poop-11769125" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;encouraging healthy digestion&lt;/a&gt;, increasing satiety after eating (ideal for evening snacks!), and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/best-foods-for-gut-health-11833113" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;supporting the gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt;. A thriving gut microbiome supports the immune system, brain health, and several other body systems. And interestingly enough, a &lt;a href="https://pubs.rsc.org/en/content/articlelanding/2022/fo/d2fo01178f" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;2022 study&lt;/a&gt; showed that fiber’s positive impact on the microbiome may be linked to better sleep by supporting the gut-brain axis and reducing symptoms of several sleep disorders. &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/high-fiber-foods-11690551" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;Fiber is found largely in plant-based foods&lt;/a&gt; including fruits, veggies, whole grains, nuts, seeds, and legumes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Magnesium &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One of the most common dietary supplements for those with sleep troubles is magnesium. “Magnesium, found in nuts, seeds, spinach, and tart cherry juice, may improve sleep quality so that you feel more rested and may help you fall asleep faster,” says Bianca Tamburello, RDN. A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35184264/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;2023 review&lt;/a&gt; on this key mineral supports these benefits. Though further research is warranted, &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/foods-high-in-magnesium" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;magnesium-rich foods&lt;/a&gt; are undoubtedly healthy additions to your after-dinner snack, too, as they promote better bone, heart, and metabolic health.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Vitamin D &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Ever elusive &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-to-get-more-vitamin-d-11807401" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;vitamin D is essential&lt;/a&gt; for optimal immune, heart, metabolic, and bone health, but emerging research is also finding it to be &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/vitamins-for-better-sleep-8660402" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;super beneficial for sleep&lt;/a&gt;. This is thanks to a handful of proposed mechanisms, including: 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vitamin D’s role in serotonin and melatonin production that are essential to healthy circadian rhythms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vitamin D receptors on the brain stem that play an important role in sleep.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vitamin D’s impact on certain pain disorders (like &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/endocrinology/articles/10.3389/fendo.2022.994545/full" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;restless leg syndrome&lt;/a&gt;) that may negatively impact sleep.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These impacts have been found in a multitude of studies, but are well summarized in this &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8912284/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;2022 systematic review&lt;/a&gt; published in Nutrients. Some great dietary sources of vitamin D include cod liver oil, salmon, swordfish, tuna, sardines, beef liver, egg yolk, fortified orange juice, fortified dairy and plant milks, and fortified cereals.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Omega-3 Fatty Acids &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Research shows that omega-3 supplementation &lt;a href="https://www.nutraingredients.com/Article/2021/01/28/Study-says-omega-3-supplements-improve-sleep-in-people-with-low-fish-consumption" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;may improve sleep&lt;/a&gt; for those eating few omega-3 rich foods,” Tamburello says. This could be thanks to the fatty acid’s role in melatonin regulation. “Eating more &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/healthy-fats-8740244" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;foods high in omega-3 fats&lt;/a&gt; like salmon, walnuts, and chia seeds, may improve sleep by promoting higher melatonin levels,” she adds. Plus, omega-3s promote heart, brain, and immune health, among many other impressive benefits.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Antioxidants &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Antioxidant-rich micronutrients like plant compounds, vitamin E, and vitamin C are also food additions to a bedtime snack. They help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/anti-inflammatory-foods-11684448" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reduce inflammation&lt;/a&gt;, promoting overall health and immunity, while also aiding in pain alleviation that may interfere with quality shut-eye. Foods especially high in antioxidants include berries, citrus fruit, leafy greens, beets, nuts, seeds, and whole grains—though most plant-based foods contain at least some.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Tryptophan &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; We’ve all heard the common trope that the &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/tryptophan-foods-6823810" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;tryptophan found in turkey&lt;/a&gt; is to blame for the Thanksgiving nap many of us take after the big meal. And as it turns out, some of this may be true. “Tryptophan, which is often associated with turkey, but also found in dairy, chicken, and fish, can help &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/mind-mood/mood-boosting-foods" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;boost serotonin&lt;/a&gt; levels to &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33942088/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;positively impact sleep&lt;/a&gt;,” Tamburello explains.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Melatonin &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Melatonin is a hormone produced naturally by the body to promote sleep, but can also be found as a supplement and in foods including tart cherry juice, walnuts, almonds, oats, and grapes,” Tamburello says. And there’s plenty of evidence to back this up, with research pointing to its role in improving symptoms of &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36064286/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;sleep disorders&lt;/a&gt;, while also helping you to fall asleep faster and stay asleep longer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-healthy-sleep-promoting-snacks"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Healthy Sleep-Promoting Snacks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Reach one of these healthy, sleep-promoting snacks if you're feeling hungry before bed.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc__content_1-0" class="comp list-sc__content realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="list-sc-item_1-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-handful-of-walnuts-or-almonds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Handful of Walnuts or Almonds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Walnuts are packed with sleep-promoting &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-high-in-omega-3-11695043" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;omega-3 fatty acids&lt;/a&gt;, while both almonds and walnuts are filled with fiber, antioxidants, melatonin, and magnesium—plus a bit of plant protein, too. These nutritional perks will encourage overall health, satiety, and sleep. Plus, if you opt for lightly salted nuts, it can help to curb your salty cravings after dinner.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@1a804d21" data-item-index="1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_2-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-mini-smoothie-bowl-with-tart-cherries"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Mini Smoothie Bowl With Tart Cherries &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The satisfying sweetness of a smoothie bowl is perfect after dinner. Smoothies are also an ideal vehicle for sleep-inducing additions like &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/tart-cherry-benefits" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;tart cherries&lt;/a&gt; (or tart cherry juice), frozen berries, grapes, and even oats.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@486174b1" data-item-index="2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_3-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-smoked-salmon-on-whole-wheat-crackers"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Smoked Salmon on Whole Wheat Crackers &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The unctuous fattiness of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/smoked-salmon-recipes-8387772" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;smoked salmon&lt;/a&gt; will not only help curb your nighttime hunger and salt cravings, but it may also promote better sleep. This is due to its omega-3 fatty acids and vitamin D. Salmon from Chile is especially beneficial in this regard as it is &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25108414/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;particularly high&lt;/a&gt; in omega-3s. Smoked salmon is nothing short of a *chef’s kiss* when served on whole wheat crackers with a swipe of cream cheese and a sprinkle of fresh dill.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@3175b41a" data-item-index="3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_4-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-overnight-oats-with-chia-seeds"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Overnight Oats With Chia Seeds &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Overnight oats can save the day at night—not just at breakfast time. They contain omega-3 fatty acids, melatonin, magnesium, fiber, and antioxidants found in ingredients like oats and chia seeds. Top with berries and a splash of milk to help with those sugar cravings.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@70838e4" data-item-index="4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_5-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-turkey-roll-ups"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Turkey Roll-Ups &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The tryptophan found in turkey (and chicken!) will help you have a more complete night’s sleep, making turkey roll-ups the perfect slightly salty nighttime snack. Roll up nitrate-free, low-sodium deli turkey with lettuce, tomato, your condiments of choice, and maybe a slice of cheese.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@1ff98461" data-item-index="5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_6-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-yogurt-with-fruit-and-granola"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Yogurt With Fruit and Granola &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A bowl of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/easy-ways-to-add-greek-yogurt-to-your-diet-11810883" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein- and calcium-packed yogurt&lt;/a&gt;, topped with fruit, granola, or some chopped nuts, is always a satisfying snack, and even more so with a sprinkling of omega-3-rich chia seeds or hemp hearts. The tryptophan and vitamin D found in yogurt, especially, will also promote healthy sleep.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@5cfeafd3" data-item-index="6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_7-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-fresh-veggies-and-cottage-cheese-dip"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Fresh Veggies and Cottage Cheese Dip &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Crunchy foods are a common craving in the hours after dinner. High-fiber popcorn and protein-filled edamame are excellent choices, but don’t sleep on fresh-cut veggies and a satisfying dip. Dip them in vitamin D and tryptophan-rich cottage cheese to promote sleep and add an irresistibly savory bite. I top my cottage cheese with everything bagel seasoning for extra flavor. If you’re really not a cottage cheese fan, hummus, yogurt dip, or guacamole are delicious, savory, filling options too!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@40371532" data-item-index="7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_8-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-popcorn"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Popcorn &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you need something truly zero-fuss—just a light, airy, crunchy bite—reach for a few handfuls of plain or lightly salted popcorn. This snack is technically a whole grain that'll provide a bit more fiber than other late-night, bagged snacks like potato chips or pretzels. Try a pre-bagged option from the grocery store that's easy on the sodium levels, made with little to no oils, and doesn't have any or much added sugar.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@63ecac8" data-item-index="8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_9-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-herb-and-cheese-crackers"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Herb and Cheese Crackers &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Believe it or not, cheese one of the simplest—and most delicious—ways to induce sleep when you're snacking before bed. Cheese contains tryptophan&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, an amino acid that carries sleep-regulating properties. Additionally, the calcium found in cheese mixes with tryptophan to produce melatonin—the sleep-inducing hormone. Seriously, think about all those times you felt a bit lethargic after eating from a cheese board; you weren't just imagining it!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@55b78ce2" data-item-index="9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_10-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-scrambled-eggs"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Scrambled Eggs &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Scrambled eggs are packed with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-high-in-vitamin-d-8781864" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt;, protein, and even melatonin. If you happen to be up late and your stomach's aching for a snack, consider whipping up an egg or two to satiate you (and lull you to sleep). Plus, it's a relatively easy meal to make when you're short on time and energy!
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@7c9e21b0" data-item-index="10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-article-outro_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-outro mntl-block"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-foods-to-avoid-before-bed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Foods to Avoid Before Bed &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; On the other side of the coin, there are certain &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/foods-you-should-never-eat-before-bed-11684466" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;foods you should avoid before bed&lt;/a&gt; because they can disrupt nightly sleep or leave us still-hungry and lacking satisfying nutrients.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alcohol, high-sugar products, ultra-processed foods: &lt;/strong&gt;These include alcohol, ultra-processed foods, and added sugars. As pro-inflammatory agents, these foods can hurt sleep quality, potentially causing stomach upset, interfering with normal sleep patterns (as is the case with &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/sleepadvances/article/3/1/zpac023/6632721" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;alcohol&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://mana.md/sugar-and-sleep/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;added sugar&lt;/a&gt;), or promoting spikes in energy, which added sugar tends to do.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Caffeine:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/should-you-drink-coffee-before-bed-7255700" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Caffeine-rich drinks&lt;/a&gt; and foods—certain teas, coffee, energy drinks, and &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/how-much-caffeine-in-chocolate-8383422" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt;—should also be approached with caution post-dinner, as caffeine is a stimulant that promotes stamina and wakefulness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spicy foods and high-saturated fat foods: &lt;/strong&gt;“Additionally, spicy foods and hard-to-digest high-fat foods can cause acid reflux if eaten too close to bedtime, interfering with healthy sleep patterns” Tamburello adds. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-more-healthy-nighttime-snacking-tips-and-considerations"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; More Healthy Nighttime Snacking Tips and Considerations &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “If you feel that you’re ravenous soon after dinner, it’s possible that you’re restricting too much,” Tamburello says. “For maximum nutrition and filling power, aim to make half your plate a fiber-rich veggie, a quarter of your plate a lean protein, and a quarter of your plate a whole grain or complex carbohydrate.” This winning combination of nutrients should &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/most-satiating-foods-8424198" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;leave you feeling satisfied&lt;/a&gt; well after you’ve finished your meal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/healthy-eating/why-am-i-craving-sugar" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;sugar cravings&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/health/nutrition-diet/why-do-i-crave-salt" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;salt cravings&lt;/a&gt; hit you at night, it’s important to look at the whole picture of your daily life—these cravings can be brought on by stress, habitually consuming higher amounts of these foods regularly, dehydration, and (ironically) poor sleep habits. The healthy snacks highlighted above should help to curb some of these cravings, while &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.realsimple.com/mindfulness-activities-7555756" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;practicing mindfulness&lt;/a&gt; can be beneficial, too. The practice of mindfulness helps us tune into our bodies to determine whether we’re actually hungry, experiencing an empty craving, snacking out of a behavioral habit, or actually have another need, like drinking more water.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-whats-the-best-time-for-a-nightly-snack"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What’s the Best Time for a Nightly Snack? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In terms of when the best time for a nighttime snack is, “some research suggests that eating &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC9092657/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;four to six hours&lt;/a&gt; before bed is best to prevent digestion from interfering with sleep, while &lt;a href="https://www.sleepfoundation.org/nutrition/is-it-bad-to-eat-before-bed" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;other experts recommend&lt;/a&gt; eating up to 2 hours before bed,” Tamburello says. In other words, there are several schools of thought, and it really depends on you, your appetite, and other contextual factors. “The bottom line: If you’re hungry, you should eat something,” she says.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQVjJWZ0lJMHF1U0x4LXFRV1VyLXFkdE54OXUzbnEzYUU0R3lFZWxValZKbzZlU19uRUhIckgzTmJtbk01Mm51YnN2bHFLNW9jcmJVUldoVENmajFuRVZQVjRxSHRMcEcwUlZka0J2QlJ0bHdMNWpIN0lmWmlNOEY2U3ZRcw</guid></item><item><title>我每天走一万步。这是我用来保持动力和无痛的装备- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/cnn-underscored/health-fitness/essentials-walking-10000-steps-a-day</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 22:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNMjlDcGxnSThTcjRmUUl3ZlB6ZjdYeW4xVUtES0dkWDd6bEF1S0xLTXlxOGJuWVNLQko4REdocGN1QmVFbllNNTNwOXhoOVgxdTVBOFh5V25hU0VCTWxzUExSbFdWeVZZczFmRjBoUi1sVmJvY2k4U0doeUI5NlVNY19ONE1SbVVycmxleDRuYm7SAZYBQVVfeXFMTTk4ZDBhUW5WOVBXWjl0aTVUNHQzMFBPY1pydDlRa2JVV214N21IcUNjbTRCWEF4MkVlRHJFeFRIQm9RZVNKSVA1ZHdaNjdKMDZXaXcyRDkzX1pkcmFKaG1DTE40WDRfNlN5bUNZN2xlQkpUSWlLZXhjeGhWMmxIRWxTN01HRjNtUWxJbVc2MUJ0Nzk3Vnln</guid></item><item><title>心理疲劳有心理触发因素-新的研究表明具有挑战性的目标可以阻止它- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/mental-fatigue-has-psychological-triggers-%E2%88%92-new-research-suggests-challenging-goals-can-head-it-off/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you ever feel spacey, distracted and worn down toward the end of a long work-related task – especially if that task is entirely a mental one? For over a century, psychologists have been trying to determine whether mental fatigue is fundamentally similar to physical fatigue or whether it is governed by different processes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.actpsy.2003.11.001"&gt;researchers have argued&lt;/a&gt; that exerting mental effort depletes a limited supply of energy – the same way physical exertion fatigues muscles. The brain consumes &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1037/0022-3514.92.2.325"&gt;energy in the form of glucose&lt;/a&gt;, which can run low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1037/h0069511"&gt;Other researchers&lt;/a&gt; see mental fatigue as more of a psychological phenomenon. Mind-wandering means the current mental effort is not being sufficiently &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.brainresrev.2008.07.001"&gt;rewarded&lt;/a&gt; – or opportunities to do other, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1017/S0140525X12003196"&gt;more enjoyable activities are being lost&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?hl=en&amp;amp;user=JGWPdcMAAAAJ"&gt;My&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?hl=en&amp;amp;user=1fv9jBIAAAAJ"&gt;colleagues&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?hl=en&amp;amp;user=I5HWMl8AAAAJ"&gt;I&lt;/a&gt; have been &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3758/s13414-023-02803-4"&gt;trying to resolve this question&lt;/a&gt;. Our research suggests mental fatigue is in large part a psychological phenomenon – but one that can be modified by setting goals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Vigilance is hard to sustain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We began by reviewing the science related to mental fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Psychologists in the World War II era studied why soldiers monitoring radar were losing focus during their shifts. Psychologist Norman Mackworth designed the “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/17470214808416738"&gt;clock test,&lt;/a&gt;” in which military participants were asked to watch a large “clock” on a wall for up to two hours. The second hand ticked at regular intervals. But rarely and unpredictably, it would jump twice the usual distance. The task was to detect those tiny variations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within the first 30 minutes, the subjects’ performance dropped dramatically – and then continued to decline more gradually. Psychologists named the necessary mental focus “vigilance” – and concluded it was fundamentally limited in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1037/0033-2909.117.2.230"&gt;Decades of research&lt;/a&gt; since has confirmed that vigilance is difficult to maintain, even over brief intervals. In studies, people report &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/00187208211011333"&gt;feeling stressed and fatigued&lt;/a&gt; following even a brief vigilance task. In 2021, one study even showed a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/00187208211011333"&gt;reduction of blood flow through the brain&lt;/a&gt; during vigilance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My colleagues and I wondered: Are all forms of mental work like vigilance? Surely, there are instances where people can engage with mental work without feeling fatigued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Setting goals&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We decided to study whether &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1037/mot0000127"&gt;goal-setting&lt;/a&gt; could improve mental focus and ran &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3758/s13414-023-02803-4"&gt;three experiments&lt;/a&gt; to test this idea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the first experiment, we showed 108 undergraduate students at the University of Oregon a screen with four empty white boxes against a gray background. Every one to three seconds, an X appeared in one of the four boxes. Their task was to indicate where that symbol appeared as quickly as possible. After each response, the participant was given feedback about both their accuracy and their speed, such as “Correct! Reaction time = 400 milliseconds.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Periodically during the 26-minute test, we also asked participants to rank their mental state as task-focused, distracted or mind-wandering. This gave us data about how they felt, in addition to how they did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We randomly gave half of them a specific goal: Keep their reaction times under 400 milliseconds while staying as accurate as possible. We gave no goal to the other half.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3758/s13414-023-02803-4"&gt;Our results&lt;/a&gt; were mixed. People who were given a goal did not experience as many slow reaction times, but having goals didn’t increase their top speed. It also didn’t change how often people reported feeling distracted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Setting increasingly harder goals&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We decided to tweak the test for our second experiment. Again, we randomly assigned a goal to half of the 112 fresh participants and no goal to the other half. But this time, as the experiment progressed, we increased the difficulty of the goal from a 450-millisecond reaction time to 400 milliseconds and then to 350 by the final block. Setting these harder-over-time goals had a huge effect on performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared with the participants assigned a set goal in the first experiment, the participants assigned increasingly more difficult goals in the second experiment had faster reaction times by an average of 45 milliseconds – about a 10% improvement. Participants in the second experiment also reported fewer instances of mind-wandering and showed no slowing of reaction times throughout the experiment. In other words, they showed no signs of mental fatigue. And we didn’t have to make the task easier. In fact, we made it harder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our first two experiments were conducted online because of shutdowns related to COVID-19. Our third study – a repeat of our second study – was conducted in person. We got the same results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings, combined with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1037/xhp0001148"&gt;other recent work&lt;/a&gt; we’ve conducted, have changed the way my colleagues and I consider mental fatigue. It’s clear that when people strive for specific and hard-to-reach goals, they report feeling more motivated and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1037/mac0000141"&gt;they do not report feeling as drained&lt;/a&gt; by mental work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re wondering how to implement these findings in your life, make simple, direct and specific goals for yourself. Mark when you complete the goals – the feedback can help you keep going. If you’re feeling particularly drained, take short breaks. Even &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cognition.2014.10.001"&gt;brief rests&lt;/a&gt; of less than two minutes can restore capacity for mental work.&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/219057/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img class="lazyload" decoding="async" src="" data-src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/219057/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/mental-fatigue-has-psychological-triggers-new-research-suggests-challenging-goals-can-head-it-off-219057"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 21:07:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxNSk9sSTBzaXV0UzRwSzBoelpKVGY0dDg1Wm5RS1N3Q3UyN0g5NDVndFQ3Y0xiaGVwcUhqTzNVdHF0VGU4cWlrb3pJYUdQU0NFeFpxSVhNaVctcUtvbnB5a1ljMGVPazc5bmhKYkk2T1N0eWZYLTU3cDdtSm5COE5TM2JJOHdQdUo4TG84Y3BkTEhNWDFtYWZIdlpXU25sUHpZUWNYX0VhQ01DYWtaWTBPVm5MdVdFZUlkUmxVVFNROXBreDNGNlRPRXNzVG0</guid></item><item><title>美国各地出现“超级流感”病例：须知- NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/super-flu-cases-what-to-know/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 20:22:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTFBHcDBjN21XSnhaVTRmY3J3czFpMmx3YTM3SDlCcjNIM0ZvZnpNc3A0a3VILWkxQS1TQ0p6WTY1bmVxQVpDVENNSDVscjFQTXhId2xCUnVwRHVBZENLZ3dSbGF2ejd0WEh5UkdvaEtTVG42RjdH0gF6QVVfeXFMUDJ4aHhwdHFsTkJNWUZMdlpaZXFTTG53MUtPb1NfQWZwcldtaEpEVkFBZVEzY01pYlVQUGRWQXU5c1p6Z1FJQ2tLX0FlQUtXX0lGWV9oQmFZZDh3LVhzUGVzVnN0MFdSNmdKM3VOYTYtM3lTZ3gyM3RxdGc</guid></item><item><title>将这种药物与咖啡相结合实际上可以提高其效果- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/combining-medication-coffee-actually-boost-155000218.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would be great if medications worked ASAP, making you feel better literally as soon as you took them. If your symptoms have reached the point where you’re turning to medication to feel better, you’re likely feeling pretty lousy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it’s often important to give the body the rest it needs to recover, other times, you just need the pain to go away so you can power through your day. After all, there’s probably a lot you want to get done. In these moments, you’re likely relying on your &lt;a href="https://parade.com/living/good-morning-memes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:morning;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;morning&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-happens-when-you-drink-coffee-every-day" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cup of coffee;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;cup of coffee&lt;/a&gt; even more to help energize you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, not all medications are designed to work instantly, and most of us have been told again and again not to expect immediate relief. Many pain relievers, allergy meds, and even everyday supplements can take a while to absorb, which only adds to the frustration when you’re already dragging yourself through the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s why people get curious about anything that might make their medication kick in faster—whether it’s timing your dose with food, taking it on an empty stomach or pairing it with hydration. And since caffeine is already part of so many morning routines, it’s natural to wonder if that daily cup could give you a lift in more ways than one. Maybe you’ve even noticed moments where medication seems to “hit” you harder after your &lt;a href="https://parade.com/food/coffee-jokes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:latte;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;latte&lt;/a&gt; or espresso, making you question whether there’s something actually happening there instead of pure coincidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ready to hear the best news ever? According to three doctors we talked to, sometimes, taking your medication with &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1354797/elizabethnarins/types-of-coffee/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:coffee;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt; can make it work even better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/stethoscope" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🩺;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;🩺&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/healthy-now-2" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/pill" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:💊;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;💊&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Grace Cary&amp;amp;sol;Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;It’s Helpful To Take This Medication With Coffee&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://health.usnews.com/doctors/fawad-mian-1236522" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Fawad Mian, MD,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Fawad Mian, MD,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a neurologist and founder at &lt;a href="https://prolohealing.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ascend Regenerative;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Ascend Regenerative&lt;/a&gt;, taking &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-happens-to-your-body-if-you-take-advil-every-day" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ibuprofen;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;ibuprofen&lt;/a&gt; with coffee can boost the medication’s pain-relieving powers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Caffeine works by blocking adenosine, which is one of the chemicals in pain and fatigue. It tightens up blood vessels in the head. Ibuprofen works by blocking prostaglandins, which drive pain and &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/how-to-reduce-inflammation" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:inflammation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt;. In combination, they are synergistic in reducing pain,” he says, adding that his patients who get &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1115926/kaitlin-vogel/migraine-home-remedies/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:migraines;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;migraines&lt;/a&gt; often combine ibuprofen and coffee when they get a &lt;a href="https://parade.com/1134949/hollypevzner/get-rid-migraine-fast/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:migraine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;migraine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Family physician &lt;a href="https://www.dralexamieses.com/about" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Alexa Mieses Malchuk, MD, MPH,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Alexa Mieses Malchuk, MD, MPH,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; agrees that taking ibuprofen with coffee can be effective. “In some research studies, around 100 milligrams of caffeine plus ibuprofen has been shown to work better for pain management than ibuprofen alone,” she says, adding that this is roughly the amount of caffeine in a cup of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-happens-when-you-drink-coffee-every-day" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Here's Exactly What Happens to Your Body When You Drink Coffee Every Day;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Here's Exactly What Happens to Your Body When You Drink Coffee Every Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To her point, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6481458/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:scientific research shows;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;scientific research shows&lt;/a&gt; that people who took ibuprofen with 100 milligrams of caffeine experienced 50% more reduction in pain than people who took ibuprofen on its own. Dr. Mieses Malchuk explains that caffeine likely enhances ibuprofen’s ability to stop pain signals in the brain, and may specifically help ibuprofen work more quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1093169757/sarah-m-bobker" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Sarah Bobker, MD,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Sarah Bobker, MD,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a clinical associate professor in the NYU Grossman School of Medicine’s Division of Headache Medicine, says that it isn’t just coffee that can have this effect; anything with caffeine can. So if you’re not a coffee drinker, you can take your ibuprofen with caffeinated tea instead and get a similar result, although Dr. Bobker says that coffee has more caffeine than tea, so the impact won’t be as dramatic. She also points out that many pain relievers are formulated with caffeine, so taking one of these medications is another way to get the boosted benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/best-starbucks-protein-coffee-order-according-to-dietitian" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:'I'm a Registered Dietitian—Here's My Go-to Starbucks Protein Coffee Order';elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;'I'm a Registered Dietitian—Here's My Go-to Starbucks Protein Coffee Order'&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Does Food Impact Ibuprofen's Effectiveness?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In terms of how other foods and drinks can impact ibuprofen, all three doctors say that there aren’t any specific foods that make the medication more or less effective. However, you may want to avoid taking it after a big meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Food does not specifically make ibuprofen less effective, but it may slow down ibuprofen's absorption. After a big meal, for example, it will take your stomach more time to digest everything inside. This can delay the positive effects of ibuprofen on your pain,” Dr. Bobker says. Dr. Mian says this too, explaining that fatty meals can especially make ibuprofen take longer to reach peak levels, meaning it would take longer to feel the effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, ibuprofen can be tough on your stomach, especially if taken regularly. Taking ibuprofen with food can help mitigate these effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The One Drink You Shouldn’t Take Ibuprofen With&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is one drink in particular that all three doctors warn against taking with ibuprofen: alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Taking ibuprofen with alcohol significantly increases the risk of bleeding from the gastrointestinal tract,” Dr. Mieses Malchuk says, explaining that common signs of a GI bleed include vomiting blood, black, tarry stools and maroon-colored blood streaked on your stool or from your rectum. If you are experiencing any of these symptoms, you should see a doctor ASAP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/never-combine-these-over-the-counter-medications-according-to-doctors" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:2 Over-The-Counter Medications You Should Never, Ever Combine, According to Doctors;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;2 Over-The-Counter Medications You Should Never, Ever Combine, According to Doctors&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to increasing the risk of a GI bleed, Dr. Mian says that taking ibuprofen with alcohol puts added stress on the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/normal-pain-that-could-signal-kidney-issues" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:kidneys;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;kidneys&lt;/a&gt;, which can be especially dangerous for older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you find yourself taking ibuprofen frequently, Dr. Mieses Malchuk recommends seeing your healthcare provider to make sure there isn’t a more serious underlying problem. While it’s okay to take ibuprofen occasionally, it shouldn’t be a regular habit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, there’s nothing the body needs more than rest, and trying to power through your symptoms is only going to prolong your illness. But when it’s a headache, muscle aches, menstrual cramps or minor joint pain holding you back, taking ibuprofen with coffee may be just the trick to feeling better as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Up Next:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/medications-to-never-mix-with-multivitamins" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: 5 Medications You Should Never, Ever Mix With Your Multivitamins Without Talking to Your Doctor;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Related: 5 Medications You Should Never, Ever Mix With Your Multivitamins Without Talking to Your Doctor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sources:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://health.usnews.com/doctors/fawad-mian-1236522" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Fawad Mian, MD,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Fawad Mian, MD,&lt;/a&gt; neurologist and founder at &lt;a href="https://prolohealing.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ascend Regenerative;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Ascend Regenerative&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dralexamieses.com/about" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Alexa Mieses Malchuk, MD, MPH,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Alexa Mieses Malchuk, MD, MPH,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/1045384/marynliles/family-quotes/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:family;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;family&lt;/a&gt; medicine physician at Geisinger in Bellefonte, Pennsylvania&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1093169757/sarah-m-bobker" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Sarah Bobker, MD,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Sarah Bobker, MD,&lt;/a&gt; clinical associate professor in the NYU Grossman School of Medicine’s Division of Headache Medicine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Derry, S., Wiffen, P.J., Moore, R.A. (2015). &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6481458/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Single dose oral ibuprofen plus caffeine for acute postoperative pain in adults.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Single dose oral ibuprofen plus caffeine for acute postoperative pain in adults. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cochrane Database of Systematic Reviews. &lt;/em&gt;2015(7):CD011509.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally published by &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/combining-this-medication-with-coffee-can-boost-its-effects" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt; on Dec 28, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Health &amp;amp; Wellness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Health &amp;amp; Wellness&lt;/a&gt; section. Add Parade as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=parade.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:07:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNSGkwR0dBbXYxbnAzS2RycVVaS3JLWHpqNXNDMGVPRmxVRXE5eTh6cElteGpQT2R6S1ZrUmM4NkFMcHpjdGlaR1RGWXY5d3pTWjJ5M3pLNDBoWFFHb0NjMk5MWV9JVVVucFNtLUZlT0pDT2NKczY4VHVGYzlYMlFsSjE4WGRPRFp4LTAtenJJZw</guid></item><item><title>男孩， 11岁，死于严重的流感病例： “杰斯甚至从来没有打开过他的圣诞礼物” -雅虎新闻加拿大</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/boy-11-dies-severe-case-190057922.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Alabama boy Jace Watkins, 11, died on Dec. 27 after being hospitalized due to complications from the flu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A GoFundMe page for Watkins stated that he suffered a seizure days after falling ill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sabrina Parsons, his aunt, wrote on Facebook, “Jace never even got to open his Christmas gifts ... What do we even do now?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;An 11-year-old boy in Alabama died after a severe case of the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Jace Watkins died on Saturday, Dec. 27, after being hospitalized due to complications from the flu, according to &lt;a href="https://www.fox8live.com/2025/12/28/11-year-old-boy-dies-after-battling-severe-case-flu-family-says/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Fox 8;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Fox 8&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The boy received treatment from the Children’s of Alabama intensive care unit. During his illness, he suffered seizures and had trouble breathing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Earlier in the week, his family said he was not receiving enough oxygen to his brain due to swelling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Watkins' aunt, Sabrina Parsons, said he had no underlying health issues, per Fox 8. "He was a premature baby, but other than that, he’s had inhalers and stuff, but that’s been years ago," she said. "He was telling everybody he was fine, he felt fine. And then, I guess he started throwing up that night and had a seizure."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Watkins was a fifth-grade student at Hueytown Intermediate School. The school’s principal Cari McClellan shared an emotional statement in honor of the boy via &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/share/p/1DL7MSj2fK/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Facebook;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; on Dec. 28, writing, "Our hearts are broken this morning. ... Jace Watkins passed away last night after a brief and sudden illness. There really aren’t words to adequately describe what we’re feeling right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;McClellan continued, "Jace was a bright light to everyone who knew him. His sweet genuine smile will be missed by all.  Please continue to pray for his family, and our school family, as we all work to navigate this unimaginable loss."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A family friend organized a community prayer vigil for the boy on Dec. 23, the school shared in a previous &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/share/p/1DQUnMBixA/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:statement;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;gofundme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Children's of Alabama hospital&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/prayers-and-support-for-jaces-critical-battle" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:GoFundMe;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/a&gt; created for Watkins and his family has raised more than $6,000 so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The description for the page stated that Watkins fell ill and visited a doctor the following day. He was told, at the time, that his "lungs sounded clear." Days later, he had a seizure and was taken to the hospital where he was diagnosed with the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The page said, at one point, Watkins was placed on a ventilator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sabrina made an emotional &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/share/p/1DPnM6A6VL/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Facebook;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; post on Dec. 28, writing, "I just want to say.. Jace never even got to open his Christmas gifts ... What do we even do now?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She continued: "This will forever weigh over our family."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Watkins' grandmother, Joann Clayton Parsons, also paid tribute to the boy and thanked the community for their support. "I just want to think each and every one of you for all the sweet kind words and the prayers for my sweet great grandson Jace Watkins," she wrote in a &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/share/p/1aZuDJGCcy/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Facebook;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"He was so loved by everyone [and] our hearts are [broken], but you will never know what it meant to us for y’all to show so much love to us and to Jace," Joann said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk: PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/why-is-this-year-flu-season-so-bad-11874366" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cases of the flu continue to be on the rise;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cases of the flu continue to be on the rise&lt;/a&gt; in the United States, with the most recent data from the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-50.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:U.S. Centers for Disease Control;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;U.S. Centers for Disease Control&lt;/a&gt; showing a 14% increase in hospitalizations and a 4% increase in visits to a medical care provider for respiratory illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Two pediatric deaths from the flu were also reported, the agency said. Per the &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/aapnews/news/33978/Health-care-professionals-urge-vaccination-as-flu?searchresult=1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Academy of Pediatrics;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;American Academy of Pediatrics&lt;/a&gt;, last year’s flu season hit a tragic milestone as the most fatal for children, with 288 kids dying from influenza.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/alabama-boy-11-dies-after-severe-case-of-the-flu-jace-watkins-11876722" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:00:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE15bm1zaWszenhBUGFCMTZXdUFLd3hIbXR2VzlsLU1GUmhjck5reTkybnM3V2F0bDhidlV2WWNCYVlacVBNdXp2MVg0OHd4LVU5U05VWE5rTUJjbTRlSnpFUVlyUGZYOWJpWmxVNy1VTlVBZw</guid></item><item><title>男孩， 11岁，死于严重的流感病例： “杰斯甚至从来没有打开过他的圣诞礼物” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/boy-11-dies-severe-case-190057922.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Alabama boy Jace Watkins, 11, died on Dec. 27 after being hospitalized due to complications from the flu&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A GoFundMe page for Watkins stated that he suffered a seizure days after falling ill&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sabrina Parsons, his aunt, wrote on Facebook, “Jace never even got to open his Christmas gifts ... What do we even do now?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;An 11-year-old boy in Alabama died after a severe case of the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Jace Watkins died on Saturday, Dec. 27, after being hospitalized due to complications from the flu, according to &lt;a href="https://www.fox8live.com/2025/12/28/11-year-old-boy-dies-after-battling-severe-case-flu-family-says/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Fox 8;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Fox 8&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The boy received treatment from the Children’s of Alabama intensive care unit. During his illness, he suffered seizures and had trouble breathing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Earlier in the week, his family said he was not receiving enough oxygen to his brain due to swelling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Watkins' aunt, Sabrina Parsons, said he had no underlying health issues, per Fox 8. "He was a premature baby, but other than that, he’s had inhalers and stuff, but that’s been years ago," she said. "He was telling everybody he was fine, he felt fine. And then, I guess he started throwing up that night and had a seizure."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Watkins was a fifth-grade student at Hueytown Intermediate School. The school’s principal Cari McClellan shared an emotional statement in honor of the boy via &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/share/p/1DL7MSj2fK/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Facebook;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; on Dec. 28, writing, "Our hearts are broken this morning. ... Jace Watkins passed away last night after a brief and sudden illness. There really aren’t words to adequately describe what we’re feeling right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;McClellan continued, "Jace was a bright light to everyone who knew him. His sweet genuine smile will be missed by all.  Please continue to pray for his family, and our school family, as we all work to navigate this unimaginable loss."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A family friend organized a community prayer vigil for the boy on Dec. 23, the school shared in a previous &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/share/p/1DQUnMBixA/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:statement;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;gofundme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Children's of Alabama hospital&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/prayers-and-support-for-jaces-critical-battle" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:GoFundMe;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/a&gt; created for Watkins and his family has raised more than $6,000 so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The description for the page stated that Watkins fell ill and visited a doctor the following day. He was told, at the time, that his "lungs sounded clear." Days later, he had a seizure and was taken to the hospital where he was diagnosed with the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The page said, at one point, Watkins was placed on a ventilator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Sabrina made an emotional &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/share/p/1DPnM6A6VL/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Facebook;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; post on Dec. 28, writing, "I just want to say.. Jace never even got to open his Christmas gifts ... What do we even do now?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She continued: "This will forever weigh over our family."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Watkins' grandmother, Joann Clayton Parsons, also paid tribute to the boy and thanked the community for their support. "I just want to think each and every one of you for all the sweet kind words and the prayers for my sweet great grandson Jace Watkins," she wrote in a &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/share/p/1aZuDJGCcy/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Facebook;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"He was so loved by everyone [and] our hearts are [broken], but you will never know what it meant to us for y’all to show so much love to us and to Jace," Joann said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk: PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt; PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/why-is-this-year-flu-season-so-bad-11874366" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cases of the flu continue to be on the rise;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cases of the flu continue to be on the rise&lt;/a&gt; in the United States, with the most recent data from the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-50.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:U.S. Centers for Disease Control;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;U.S. Centers for Disease Control&lt;/a&gt; showing a 14% increase in hospitalizations and a 4% increase in visits to a medical care provider for respiratory illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Two pediatric deaths from the flu were also reported, the agency said. Per the &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/aapnews/news/33978/Health-care-professionals-urge-vaccination-as-flu?searchresult=1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Academy of Pediatrics;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;American Academy of Pediatrics&lt;/a&gt;, last year’s flu season hit a tragic milestone as the most fatal for children, with 288 kids dying from influenza.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/alabama-boy-11-dies-after-severe-case-of-the-flu-jace-watkins-11876722" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:00:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5KQTBldGhNalNlYUt4RmJYX3ZSc2lGQlRlbHNvLTV6SnZVYTlSVWsxQ21hMVA5QVR1ekFZWk5UUkpSeDhrVlVuM3dhdjB2U3VOZ0tWanZjYlNvOWtFRFltZUZxYnlsWDFaVmdIUWtUOEQ3UFREUG5mWVJROW1lQms</guid></item><item><title>关于古希腊和罗马科学家提供的错误信息的5课-对话</title><link>https://theconversation.com/5-lessons-about-misinformation-from-ancient-greek-and-roman-scientists-270941</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="grid-ten large-grid-nine grid-last content-body content entry-content instapaper_body inline-promos" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Ancient scientists can be easy to dismiss. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greek philosopher &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thales_of_Miletus"&gt;Thales of Miletus&lt;/a&gt;, often described as the West’s first scientist, believed the whole Earth was suspended on water. Roman encyclopaedist &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pliny_the_Elder"&gt;Pliny the Elder&lt;/a&gt; recommended entrails, chicken brains, and mice cut in two as topical remedies for snakebite. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The lone ancient Greek thinker who believed Earth orbits the Sun – &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aristarchus_of_Samos"&gt;Aristarchus of Samos&lt;/a&gt; – was universally dismissed by his contemporaries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Because these scientific beliefs are so different from our own, it may seem we have nothing to learn from long-dead scientists. However, thinkers 2,500 years ago already faced many problems that are today amplified by social media and artificial intelligence (AI), such as how to tell truth from fiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are five lessons from ancient Greek and Roman science that ring surprisingly true in the face of misinformation in the modern world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;1. Start with observations&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost every ancient scientific text offers advice about observing or collecting data before making a decision. For example, in a &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Astronomica_(Manilius)"&gt;1st century CE text&lt;/a&gt; about astronomy, author &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Marcus_Manilius"&gt;Marcus Manilius&lt;/a&gt; explains that his scientific predecessors learned via detailed, long-term observations. He says&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;they observed the appearance of the whole night sky and watched every star return to its original place […] by doing this repeatedly, they built up their knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ancient astronomers, Manilius says, would look around and gather evidence before drawing any conclusions. Greek and Roman scientists wanted their readers to do the same, and to be suspicious of any claims that are not backed up by data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;2. Think critically&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ancient scientists insisted their readers think critically, encouraging us to analyse the claims made by other people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://penelope.uchicago.edu/Thayer/E/Roman/Texts/Aetna/text*.html"&gt;Aetna&lt;/a&gt; is an anonymous text that explains how volcanoes work. Its unknown author warns readers about two potential sources of misinformation: other authors and other people. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether these groups intend to mislead their audiences or are simply misinformed, the book urges us to scrutinise their claims carefully and think about whether they are consistent with the evidence of our own senses and &lt;em&gt;ratio&lt;/em&gt; (the Latin term for the powers of reasoning).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ancient scientists encourage us to think critically about information we read or hear, because even well-meaning sources are not always accurate. Writers like the Aetna author want us to think before accepting other people’s claims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;3. Acknowledge what you don’t know&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another skill ancient scientists encourage is acknowledging our limits. Even Greek and Roman scientists who claimed to be experts in their field frequently admitted they didn’t have all the answers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="http://files.libertyfund.org/files/2242/Lucretius_1496_Bk.pdf"&gt;On the Nature of Things&lt;/a&gt;, Roman philosopher &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lucretius"&gt;Lucretius&lt;/a&gt; proposed three different explanations for solar eclipses:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the Moon passing in front of the Sun &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;some other opaque body passing in front of the Sun, or &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the Sun’s light temporarily growing dim for some reason. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lucretius says he cannot determine which is more likely without additional evidence. In fact, he says it would be “unscientific” to eliminate any of these theories just for the sake of appearing more certain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Multiple explanations seem unsatisfactory to us because they make ancient scientists’ theories seem less precise. Yet writers like Lucretius should be praised for their honesty in admitting they simply don’t have all the answers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greek and Roman scientists knew that people who claim they have no doubts can be very persuasive. However, as Lucretius demonstrates, a source that acknowledges its limits may actually be more trustworthy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;4. Science is part of culture&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An ancient medical text from the school of Hippocrates called &lt;a href="https://classics.mit.edu/Hippocrates/sacred.html"&gt;On the Sacred Disease&lt;/a&gt; sought to explain the causes of epilepsy. Contrary to what the title might lead us to expect, the author argues vehemently that there is nothing “sacred” about epilepsy or any other illness, and is determined to discover its physical causes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ancient Greek doctors were divided on the causes of disease, and on whether they were supernatural or not. A patient might be given very different answers and advice depending on the perspective of the person they consulted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ancient thinkers understood that science was part of culture rather than separate from it, and that an individual’s beliefs and values will have a significant impact on the information they promote as “factual” or “truthful”. Greek and Roman scientists remind us about this because they want readers to think about where information is coming from.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;5. Science is for everyone&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our Roman astronomer Manilius says the only essential for students of science is “a teachable mind”. In other words, the ability to acquire new knowledge is all about interest and willingness to learn, rather than possessing any innate skill. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The anonymous Aetna author says something similar: “Science is no place for genius.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ancient scientists understood the importance of deferring to specialists and listening to expert advice. However, they were also keen for their readers to understand where scientists acquire knowledge and how scientific facts can be verified. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These hard-won lessons about how to figure what’s true and what’s not helped build the foundations of modern scientific knowledge – and they can still help us navigate a world where truth is just as slippery as it was for ancient Greeks and Romans.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

        

        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Conversation</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 18:02:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPSDk3Y0o4eHdUT0VZSGh5ckNWX0xJQV9fWEpKVlQtam15SHJ0Y2w4TnpTd3l6N2J3OGFCeUg4bzU3c3BlR1dGdjBTSlBZM1hDNDJuak1uSWw3VjJmVl9BejJjaXN4MVBzQm9NUHNZWUFwRm4zcFQ2ODNuN3Boam1XaWM0Mnk4UmpxUWJmM1YxVnpQNWMzQWpEU2U5LWhTS2t4dzdsc3lsUDY</guid></item><item><title>专家警告：世界正沉睡在禽流感中- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/the-world-is-sleeping-on-bird-flu-expert-warns</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;There's an unwritten rule in publishing, or so I've been told: Don't write about COVID. Our collective attention span has been saturated by those endless months holed up in attics and cramped corners of apartments, staring out at a world we could no longer take part in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the worst of it passed, we felt an urge to close that chapter, to padlock it behind a heavy latch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in doing so, we also tuck away the hard-won lessons of that time: how quickly systems buckle, how two decades of &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/coronavirus-5830"&gt;coronavirus&lt;/a&gt; warnings &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ejim.2022.07.009"&gt;accumulated without adequate preparedness&lt;/a&gt;, and how the very mechanisms we rely on for safety can become the scaffolding of a next disaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/worlds-first-death-from-h5n5-bird-flu-strain-reported-in-us"&gt;World's First Death From H5N5 Bird Flu Strain Reported in US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This matters now as another threat is taking shape: highly pathogenic avian  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt;, known as bird  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bird flu still poses a low‑probability threat of sustained human transmission. But that doesn't make the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; harmless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The H5  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt; are &lt;a href="https://www.dw.com/en/virus-has-killed-almost-9-million-birds-and-counting/a-74972319"&gt;brutally lethal&lt;/a&gt; to birds – 9 million have died outright, and hundreds of millions have been culled to contain the spread. &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/h5n1-bird-flu-cases-spike-in-europe-how-worried-should-we-be-269962"&gt;Alarming&lt;/a&gt; is the virus's expanding reach into mammals. So far, at least 74 mammal species, from elephant seals to polar bears, have suffered die‑offs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The individual cases are situated within a broader shift. Dense poultry farms create opportunities for the virus to hop species. Over a &lt;a href="https://www.avma.org/resources-tools/animal-health-and-welfare/animal-health/avian-influenza/avian-influenza-virus-type-h5n1-us-dairy-cattle"&gt;thousand US dairy herds&lt;/a&gt; have tested positive in the past two years, and viral fragments have even been detected in milk – &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/11/06/nx-s1-5600125/bird-flu-risk-outbreak-trump-administration"&gt;a worrying route&lt;/a&gt; of spillover. Every jump is a probe for new footholds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Europe is &lt;a href="https://www.efsa.europa.eu/en/news/avian-influenza-europe-enhanced-surveillance-and-strict-biosecurity-needed-detections-surge?"&gt;seeing a surge too&lt;/a&gt;. From early September to mid-November 2025, 1,444 infected wild birds were found across 26 countries: a quadrupling compared with the year before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human cases remain rare: only &lt;a href="https://cdn.who.int/media/docs/default-source/influenza/h5n1-human-case-cumulative-table/cumulative-number-of-confirmed-human-cases-for-avian-influenza-a(h5n1)-reported-to-who--2003-2025ac90dee8-f1c4-4ff6-b891-f92e0df414cb.pdf?sfvrsn=447db8c4_3&amp;amp;download=true"&gt;992&lt;/a&gt; confirmed H5N1 infections worldwide since 2003, though with a near‑50% fatality rate. But the numbers are increasing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Americas have logged 75 cases since 2022, and in November, the US recorded its &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/391/bmj.r2480"&gt;first H5N5 death&lt;/a&gt; in a patient with existing health problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186710" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186710" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm-642x361.jpg" alt="Multiple cows on a dairy farm" class="wp-image-186710 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm-642x361.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm-600x338.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CowsOnADairyFarm.jpg 1200w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186710" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;More than 1,000 US dairy herds have tested positive in the past two years. (TinaFields/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;And although no human cases have been reported in Europe, the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control &lt;a href="https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/sites/default/files/documents/Zoonotic_influenza_pre_pandemic_scenarios_SARMS%20FINAL%20VERSION2.pdf"&gt;warns&lt;/a&gt; that the widespread animal circulation raises the risk of spillover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My research focuses on how warnings collapse before catastrophe, from geopolitical shocks to intelligence failures and industrial accidents. The pattern is often the same. Frontline observers spot something early, but the signal fades as it moves upward, diluted by bureaucracy, competing interpretations, or institutional forgetfulness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recent Hong Kong fire is yet another tragic example: residents at Wang Fuk Court &lt;a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/graphics/2025-hong-kong-fire/"&gt;had raised multiple alarms&lt;/a&gt; about the styrofoam boards that ignited with a lighter, the uncertified netting and the pattern of ignored safety notices long before the blaze, yet those concerns never gained traction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The failures I study share recurring blind spots: weak signals drowned out by noise, bureaucratic habits that slow or soften uncomfortable messages, and the political instinct to downplay problems that threaten established narratives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you see warning as a chain running from detection to decision, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/isr/article/27/1/viaf009/8109154"&gt;collapse is often partial&lt;/a&gt;. Some links hold. Others jam at the moment they are most needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bird flu now sits inside that kind of chain. The technical ability to detect change is there: veterinarians, virologists and surveillance systems are picking up signals, sequencing viruses and logging outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the infrastructure meant to catch the virus in its early stages is &lt;a href="http://npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/11/06/nx-s1-5600125/bird-flu-risk-outbreak-trump-administration"&gt;fraying&lt;/a&gt;. The agencies that once charted the terrain of emerging  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pandemic" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73047" data-postid="186706" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;pandemic&lt;/a&gt; threats have been hollowed out – budgets trimmed, staff evaporated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Surveillance falters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study of 31 European nations warned that COVID exposed a &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurpub/article/34/2/402/7603330"&gt;"critical gap in preparedness"&lt;/a&gt; and urged standardised indicators and open data as the foundation for any future response. The EU's freshly launched &lt;a href="https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/scenarios-pre-pandemic-zoonotic-influenza-preparedness-and-response"&gt;pre-pandemic plan&lt;/a&gt; is a good step, but it cannot mask the gaps in day-to-day monitoring and response that still leave countries exposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across the Atlantic, &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/12/01/nx-s1-5619764/months-of-tumult-and-waves-of-staff-cuts-take-a-toll-on-the-cdc"&gt;cuts&lt;/a&gt; have left the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention scrambling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American scientists warn that federal reporting has slowed: the United States Department of Agriculture &lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2024/04/23/health/h5n1-usda-gisaid-genetic-sequences"&gt;shared&lt;/a&gt; too little genetic data on the outbreak in cattle and other affected animals, released it late, and in formats researchers could not use. It left scientists unable to track how the virus was evolving or spreading across herds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.midlandfarmer.co.uk/2025/12/04/uk-poorly-prepared-for-animal-disease-outbreaks/"&gt;the UK&lt;/a&gt;, domestic surveillance capacity has equally faced strain, with reduced access to European disease intelligence and chronic vet shortages weakening early detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the signal dims within institutions, it dims for the public as well. And a weak warning rarely travels far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent &lt;a href="https://ajph.aphapublications.org/doi/10.2105/AJPH.2025.308080"&gt;poll&lt;/a&gt; shows this clearly: most Americans don't even register bird flu as a credible threat. What doesn't help is that symptoms in humans can be so mild that they slide past notice. A &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/insights/2024/05/bird-avian-flu-h5n1-cows-pandemic-threat.html"&gt;case&lt;/a&gt; in a dairy worker earlier this year looked like nothing more than conjunctivitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this means a new pandemic is imminent. Health authorities still say the chance of an efficient human-to-human outbreak &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bird-flu-poses-risk-pandemic-worse-than-covid-frances-institut-pasteur-says-2025-11-27/"&gt;is low&lt;/a&gt;. These viruses rarely make that leap. And we're not helpless. We're &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/insights/2024/05/bird-avian-flu-h5n1-cows-pandemic-threat.html"&gt;better prepared&lt;/a&gt; than we were before COVID: We have vaccine candidates, clearer protocols and agencies that learned painful lessons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spikes-of-bird-flu-in-cats-could-be-a-warning-of-a-future-pandemic"&gt;Spikes of Bird Flu in Cats Could Be a Warning of a Future Pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But low isn't none. And if it were to occur, the consequences could be catastrophic. Most people have some immunity to the seasonal flu strains. We probably have &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/bird-flu-poses-risk-pandemic-worse-than-covid-frances-institut-pasteur-says-2025-11-27/"&gt;none&lt;/a&gt; to H5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And influenza doesn't restrict itself to the frail in the way COVID often did; past flu epidemics killed healthy adults in large numbers. Adding to the concern, health expertise itself &lt;a href="https://www.apha.org/topics-and-issues/public-health-under-threat"&gt;has come under attack&lt;/a&gt;, weakening the very authority that should turn signals into action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we avert our eyes from the bird flu threat because our systems have grown inattentive, underfunded and unprepared, we risk repeating that same pattern. And the next alarm will arrive too late for anyone to claim they didn't see it coming.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/271765/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/nikki-ikani-346615"&gt;Nikki Ikani&lt;/a&gt;, Assistant Professor Intelligence &amp;amp; Security, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/leiden-university-935"&gt;Leiden University&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/kings-college-london-1196"&gt;King's College London&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/bird-flu-warnings-are-being-ignored-ive-seen-this-pattern-before-271765"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 18:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQODBwWFM4YlJpR0s5aVZwYkpVYmJMNXc0YmxRT1RfbWdiWFZ3TUlJR0F6NDBCbWkyN01KTno4Wjk2RDgwQm81VU9jNzZSSEtSNDdIZllLTkgtaHBKbERnVkcxdUxlMEs2Um9fWFhISjhUeGRLZ0cxdExKTm55UGZZZw</guid></item><item><title>意识科学： 2025年涉及神经科学和思维的最有趣的发现-汇报</title><link>https://thedebrief.org/science-of-consciousness-the-most-intriguing-discoveries-in-2025-involving-neuroscience-and-the-mind/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;
																										&lt;p&gt;Questions about the nature of &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/category/consciousness/"&gt;consciousness&lt;/a&gt; remain among the most perplexing areas of modern &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/category/science/"&gt;scientific research&lt;/a&gt;, with implications for neuroscience and &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/lost-in-thought-how-meditation-can-sometimes-unsettle-the-mind/"&gt;the human mind&lt;/a&gt;, as well as our broader &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/darpas-inspire-program-seeks-to-revolutionize-our-understanding-of-how-the-brain-constructs-reality/"&gt;concept of reality&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2025, many new thresholds in this complex area of study were crossed, with empirical inquiry into our questions about the nature of consciousness occurring within fields such as &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/category/neuroscience/"&gt;neuroscience&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/category/psychology/"&gt;psychology&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/category/health/"&gt;medicine&lt;/a&gt;. Many advancements in this area over the last year have also challenged long-held assumptions about where and how consciousness originates, how widespread it may be, and how profoundly &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/study-finds-mindfulness-training-may-induce-altered-states-of-consciousness/"&gt;altered states&lt;/a&gt; can reshape human perception.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s a look at just a few of the major stories involving consciousness, the mind, awareness, and the science behind it all that &lt;em&gt;The Debrief &lt;/em&gt;has covered in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Did ‘Universal Consciousness’ Exist Before the Big Bang? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among the year’s most provocative work about consciousness, one controversial peer-reviewed paper published in &lt;em&gt;AIP Advances &lt;/em&gt;proposed that “&lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/new-study-claims-universal-consciousness-existed-before-the-big-bang-and-still-shapes-our-reality/"&gt;universal consciousness&lt;/a&gt;” may have existed before the Big Bang, functioning not as a byproduct of matter but as a foundational feature of reality itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_27271" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-27271" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="wp-image-27271 lazyload" data-src="https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/consciousness.jpg" alt="Consciousness" data-srcset="https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/consciousness.jpg 2324w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/consciousness-300x182.jpg 300w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/consciousness-1024x621.jpg 1024w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/consciousness-768x466.jpg 768w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/consciousness-1536x932.jpg 1536w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/consciousness-2048x1243.jpg 2048w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/consciousness-770x467.jpg 770w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2024/08/consciousness-1400x849.jpg 1400w" data-sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" src=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-27271" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(Image Credit: Pixabay)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Such claims are nothing new and remain hotly debated by researchers, although they reflect a growing willingness among scientists to explore questions about consciousness, whether it is purely emergent or could play a deeper role in shaping the universe. The result has been a reignition of discussions long relegated to philosophy, now increasingly framed through modern cosmology and theoretical physics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consciousness May Be Far More Widespread Than Previously Believed &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Closer to Earth, neuroscientists and cognitive researchers have increasingly argued that consciousness may be far older and more widespread than traditionally believed. Studies examining simple organisms, brain networks, and evolutionary pathways this year, undertaken by researchers at Ruhr University Bochum, suggested that rudimentary forms of awareness &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/scientists-say-consciousness-is-far-older-and-more-widespread-than-we-ever-realized/"&gt;could predate complex nervous systems&lt;/a&gt; throughout the animal kingdom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rather than being the apex of the human evolutionary process, the researchers argue in a pair of papers that appeared in &lt;em&gt;Philosophical Transactions of the Royal Society B,&lt;/em&gt; consciousness “rather represents a more basic cognitive process, possibly shared with other animal phyla.” This reframing has major implications not only for how scientists define consciousness but also for how humans understand their relationship to other life forms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Psychedelic Therapy and Related Discoveries  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the most tangible advances came from renewed interest in altered states of consciousness, particularly through psychedelic research. Multiple studies in 2025 demonstrated that psychedelic compounds &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/psychedelics-can-quickly-reorganize-our-brain-functions-offering-promise-for-lasting-therapeutic-approaches/"&gt;can rapidly reorganize brain networks&lt;/a&gt;, temporarily dissolving rigid patterns of thought associated with depression, trauma, and addiction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_39629" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-39629" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="wp-image-39629 lazyload" data-src="https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/magic-mushrooms.jpg" alt="psilocybin" data-srcset="https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/magic-mushrooms.jpg 800w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/magic-mushrooms-300x199.jpg 300w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/magic-mushrooms-768x509.jpg 768w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/magic-mushrooms-360x240.jpg 360w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/magic-mushrooms-770x510.jpg 770w" data-sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" src=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-39629" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(Image Credit: Pixabay/CC0 Public Domain)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the same time, scientists explored non-drug pathways to similar states, such as research into &lt;a href=""&gt;ancient breathwork techniques combined with modern neuroscience&lt;/a&gt; that suggests altered states resembling psychedelic experiences could be induced through controlled breathing alone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, long-term studies also continued to examine the social and spiritual dimensions of psychedelic experiences. Decades of research now suggest that such states often produce a heightened sense of connection—to other people, to nature, and to perceived transcendent realities. In 2025, &lt;a href=""&gt;experiments involving participants from diverse religious backgrounds&lt;/a&gt; highlighted how profoundly personal belief systems shape the interpretation of these experiences, even when the underlying neurochemical mechanisms are shared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pitting Consciousness Theories Against Each Other &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, researchers &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/i-think-therefore-i-am-study-pitting-top-theories-of-consciousness-against-each-other-reveals-its-findings/"&gt;made rare progress on a long-standing scientific impasse: competing theories of consciousness&lt;/a&gt;. Chris Plain, reporting for &lt;em&gt;The Debrief&lt;/em&gt; in May on a 2025 Allen Institute study, described Integrated Information Theory (IIT) and the Global Neuronal Workspace Theory (GNWT), a pair of differing approaches to consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_42888" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-42888" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="wp-image-42888 lazyload" data-src="https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/consciousness.jpg" alt="consciousness" data-srcset="https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/consciousness.jpg 1600w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/consciousness-300x164.jpg 300w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/consciousness-1024x559.jpg 1024w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/consciousness-768x419.jpg 768w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/consciousness-1536x838.jpg 1536w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/consciousness-770x420.jpg 770w, https://thedebrief.b-cdn.net/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/consciousness-1400x764.jpg 1400w" data-sizes="(max-width: 650px) 100vw, 650px" src=""&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-42888" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(Image Credit: Ashley Batz/Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The resulting research revealed functional connections between neurons within the visual areas of the brain and the brain’s frontal areas, which the researchers behind the study say helps them “understand how our perceptions tie to our thoughts” while also reducing the typical emphasis on “the importance of the prefrontal cortex in consciousness, suggesting that while it’s important for reasoning and planning, consciousness itself may be linked with sensory processing and perception.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;University of Virginia Researchers Study Support Gaps for NDE Experiencers &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, 2025 saw increased attention to near-death experiences (NDEs) as a legitimate area of study. Researchers at the University of Virginia &lt;a href="https://thedebrief.org/university-of-virginia-researchers-identify-support-gaps-for-people-recovering-from-near-death-experiences/"&gt;identified significant gaps in psychological and medical support for people who report NDEs&lt;/a&gt;, many of whom struggle to integrate these experiences into their lives. While interpretations of NDEs vary widely, the research emphasized a growing consensus: regardless of cause, such experiences can be deeply transformative—and ignoring their impact may carry real mental health consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Taken together, these stories reveal a year in which consciousness research moved decisively out of the shadows. Whether probing the origins of awareness in the early universe, mapping its neural signatures, or exploring its therapeutic potential, scientists in 2025 treated consciousness not as an unspeakable mystery—but as a frontier worth confronting directly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Micah Hanks is the Editor-in-Chief and Co-Founder of The Debrief. A longtime reporter on science, defense, and technology with a focus on space and astronomy, he can be reached at&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:micah@thedebrief.org"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;micah@thedebrief.org&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Follow him on X &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.twitter.com/MicahHanks"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;@MicahHanks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;, and at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.micahhanks.com/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;micahhanks.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Debrief</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:13:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPUGJnOXJuV0VmaDZfU0VTdHJqdm04ZThnTzhaSXJiSzdYT3k5cnRPdHE2ampJSjBfN2VmelhjYXVfWHdmcmJSd0FjNFljWU5xU1I4Y2xKMzlrMWhSWW5wc1QxMjR4LWFxcGg0bHNSclVyaS0zbkl1dzBFZ09CdWtOUWpfdmZ1YmQ2dERQWnBQTGp3NzBVUVFHUmNfRWsweU9uU2VyMXduSThlUmdudk9RWmt6NmdWYjhBYlc5N0YzTnYtUQ</guid></item><item><title>我非常想尝试团体性爱。一个又小又可怕的东西在阻挡我。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/group-sex-advice-threesome-feeld-orgy-alone.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna3a7g009n63mc72vw6sp2@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjnacyxc00363b78kk4ov2kh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="156" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93js001n3b78set17ghu@published"&gt;I have always been curious about group sex. I’ve dabbled in the world of Feeld lately, and have received some interest from hot men for potential threesomes/more and have been tempted to try it but something keeps holding me back. I’m so afraid of feeling like the odd one out or the less enticing person in the party. It’s an insecurity I would say I have in many areas of life beyond sex—I often feel like the one who gets left out in the friend group or the social gathering and I’m so afraid of feeling rejected in that way in a sexual context. Is there a way to protect against that? Am I completely off base to even worry that someone would inevitably get left out, and that someone would be me? I just don’t want to walk away from something that was supposed to be really hot, feeling like I didn’t get picked again.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93my001o3b78kx685v31@published"&gt;—Group Project&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93r1001p3b78j5ptzsbs@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Group Project,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="153" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93us001q3b786d0sx1ub@published"&gt;The fear of being left out is so common it must be up there with fears of heights and snakes. This can be especially pronounced in vulnerable situations like sex, when rejection feels that much more personal as a result of what has been revealed (your body, your desires, etc.). However, when it comes to pursuing sex, rejection is always a possibility, and that’s how it has to be. People must have the ability to revoke consent at any moment for whatever reason, and the hurt feelings of those who are denied is merely collateral. It can suck, but you know what makes it suck less? Being rejected! You get used to it. You see that it’s not really a big deal, that it’s often not personal, and that you’ll live to see another dick. It can actually be character-building and I think it would be a good thing for you to experience.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="64" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna93yi001r3b78cm748l37@published"&gt;If you can’t bear the thought of being rejected, I don’t think you should be on Feeld or any app for that matter—it’s just a matter of time before you find yourself enormously disappointed. Working through this fear of rejection via means other than exposure could also benefit you. For example, you may want to talk to a therapist about your strong feelings here.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="205" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna942b001s3b78acegjfrt@published"&gt;However, I do think that your fear in the context you wrote about is somewhat overblown. You are afraid of being left out of group sex that you will have coordinated. While it is true that interacting on apps and in person are two very different modes of communication, you can assume that people are going to be showing up because you have attracted them via what you look like, what you’re offering, and your overall vibe. When people leave their house to have sex (or open their home to host it), they want to have a good time. No one is joining in this group with the objective of leaving you out—that would contradict the point of getting together in the first place. You can help safeguard against being left out, though, by enlisting only straight guys to participate. I don’t think it would be wrong of you to say that you want to be the focus and so all action should involve you. I know gay bottoms that take this approach to group sex/gangbangs and it works out for them. This is one situation where it’s really OK to express your selfishness. I think a lot of guys will just find that hot.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjnabva2002i3b788w3r6e5c@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmjnabyuk002l3b78671lmnl2@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjnac4me002p3b78gbw89bpu@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna945q001t3b78qvl8y8sq@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="49" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna949i001u3b78ssh6imbi@published"&gt;I am a 48-year-old man, and for the last year I thought I was suffering from ED, but it turns out that I just can’t get it up for my wife anymore.  When it comes to porn, I’m back in business. What can I do to rekindle the flame with her?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="8" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94cq001v3b78ch45e36l@published"&gt;—Rising to Every Occasion but the Right One&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="9" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94fw001w3b78y3ano819@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Rising to Every Occasion but the Right One,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="70" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94jl001x3b78p7z2suxf@published"&gt;Your assessment sounds right—usually when erectile dysfunction is situational (that is, you can get hard in some situations but not others), it’s regarded as being a psychologically rooted issue (as opposed to a physiological one as a result of, say, diabetes). That said, you are 48 and it’s likely that your testosterone levels aren’t what they used to be. If you aren’t regularly seeing a doctor/getting bloodwork, now’s the time.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="193" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94nm001y3b78c39txzum@published"&gt;Rekindling could look like a lot of things. If you are having wood issues with your wife, she must be noticing and so a conversation may be useful. It’s common in long-term relationships for desire to wane—Esther Perel’s &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Mating-Captivity-Unlocking-Erotic-Intelligence-ebook/dp/B000UODXP0/ref=sr_1_1?crid=2KFLDW9XS3D4&amp;amp;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.9TBgqJH8OXaXJ6KF-p0h2kiUlcEoJVKlMs9LiYHOqbmj3Ltj7tID5mjXlzIy3vFrG-ffA-RkeZjl5zQROs7-3kM8mUhqQUWNxRLL3FauXHkiHYn8o8qVtOT_87IekJCsF76G9rzN0dgy_WDoRNyLXuy62WJsygbNVXDhP6yrk2mODHIW0D6GwNKpTZH-ZlPyxA09WKWnURyMj5NUW4QmHLe1hhXeCS78p77v1q5h6S0.CEYYxaVRazv_Twik-AToMJu7pLXiTSTRs2ZBbnKTNlI&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;keywords=mating+in+captivity+esther+perel&amp;amp;qid=1766454898&amp;amp;sprefix=mating+in+ca,aps,137&amp;amp;sr=8-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mating in Captivity&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (my go-to recommended read for these types of situations) explores how closeness is often at odds with eroticism. It wouldn’t be surprising at all if your wife were having similar issues. If you can have an honest (but considerate!) conversation about the underwhelming state of your sex life, you can begin a collaboration to get things back on track. This might mean trying things (like kink, toys, and roleplay) that you’ve been curious about but have been too timid to ask for. It might mean exploring consensual non-monogamy. It might mean putting into practice some of the distancing techniques that Perel writes about (such as moving your sex outside of your home to, say, a hotel with some kind of regularity). It might mean something as simple as enjoying porn together instead of watching it alone. It might mean ongoing conversations and/or enlisting the help of a couples counselor or sex therapist/coach.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="64" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94qn001z3b784gyxx4uv@published"&gt;Your letter is phrased as though this is your issue that you want to resolve yourself. It’s noble to take responsibility, but you aren’t in this alone and in fact, you’re going to have a much better shot at success if you work with your wife here. The initial conversation may not be easy, but the process should be much smoother with her participation.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjnac9d4002s3b78c33tblbs@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmjnacdgl002v3b78c1z8xzvx@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="36" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjnacj0c002z3b786n67spoa@published"&gt;The columnists behind our advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjnacnai00333b78hffkytb8@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94tq00203b78e8dt1d7a@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="68" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94wr00213b78o24s2u3u@published"&gt;I got my lower right leg amputated almost three years ago (diabetes). Well, they might as well have cut off another organ. My erections are much less frequent and not the same as they used to be. I don’t think I can get hard enough for penetration (haven’t tried). Pills do nothing. Yet I still think about sex a lot, so the drive is there. Is this normal?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna94zv00223b78tbko02z1@published"&gt;—Lost a Leg and a Dick&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna953u00233b78zlq40y5m@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Lost a Leg and a Dick,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="186" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna957f00243b78uqk3s12y@published"&gt;Sexual dysfunction is common in people who have undergone limb amputation. In a 2015 &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26030200/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; of people with a limb amputation in the Netherlands, the intro/review of previous literature points out that post amputation, people “may be confronted with a variety of sexual problems, such as problems with arousal and/or orgasm, due to both the physical and/or psychological consequences of a limb amputation.  Furthermore, depression, (sexual) performance anxiety and an altered body image may influence the amputee’s sexual adjustment. Moreover, pain related to the amputation and medication use (to treat this pain) may also affect both sexual interest and activity.” There is a lot stacked against you, and one of the findings of this study’s survey was that there was very little discussion of sexuality during the rehabilitation process. Again, this was a study of Dutch subjects, but it’s hard to believe that elsewhere is doing much better to support these patients. In this study, 56 percent of participants reported at least one sexual problem and 20 percent reported sexual dysfunction(s). The problems included sexual desire (31 percent), sexual arousal (25 percent), and orgasm (21 percent).&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="69" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna95cg00253b780lu1x163@published"&gt;A more recent &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28359182/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; from 2018 of only people with lower limb amputations found that only half were sexually active, and of that group, about 60 percent were sexually dysfunctional. The study’s authors highlighted the need for psychological and psychosexual assessment and intervention after amputation. “Depression, anxiety and body image issues were significantly associated with sexual dysfunction in the current sample of individuals with lower limb amputation,” they wrote.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="143" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna95fr00263b78eeuuqsbk@published"&gt;So yes, it’s hardly surprising that your erections aren’t what they used to be. Diabetes, also, can have detrimental effects on erection quality. You have tried pills, but you may need to look into other options like injectable ED meds (like Trimix) or even an implant. Have you been to therapy or sex coaching regarding your amputation and/or sexual dysfunction? That might also be helpful. You should search for a provider who specifically deals with amputation that is near you or otherwise reachable. You may also want to think about expanding your definition of sex to incorporate things that don’t require an erection—toys, roleplay, forms of BDSM and kink, dressing up, even talking dirty. Don’t give up on your search for a reliable erection, but this is an opportunity to think beyond that and to enter a realm that many take for granted.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="57" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjna95j400273b78r3c1sas6@published"&gt;In the meantime, some community may help. There are subreddits like &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/amputee/"&gt;r/amputee&lt;/a&gt; that would allow you to share your issues and hear from others who have gone through the same thing. (Here is &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/amputee/comments/cqr2ct/being_an_amputee_affecting_sex_life/"&gt;one such thread&lt;/a&gt; about the effect of amputation on one’s sex life.) You shouldn’t be dealing with this alone, nor do you have to.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjnaapdr002b3b78ckw4ek2q@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmjna3a7g009q63mcq7zjjfo2@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOY19qX2hLdXZhV0FiZ2xFdmxRakwxYl91c1ZpNy02MlVzblRoSXJjbGxnM0dGR1pqcmpjMTkyazFYQ2RfVndtenAxQkY2QmljWDZaLXk5dDFrODRwam5KVE16OENlY0FrTkpxVmk0ajZYdXBIWXVBRzRNMHFZcS1hTEcyNW9aME9i</guid></item><item><title>这种常见疫苗可能会减缓甚至预防痴呆症的进展-雅虎加拿大新闻</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/common-vaccine-may-slow-progression-170000003.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The shingles vaccine may slow the progression of dementia or offer protection against developing it&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Research published in the medical journal &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt; shows that the vaccine “slows or prevents disease progression across the entire disease course … of dementia”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“We’re much more confident that what we’re actually looking at here is cause and effect,” the study’s senior author said&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://people.com/health/shingles-vaccine-shingrix-what-to-know/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:shingles vaccine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;shingles vaccine&lt;/a&gt; may show the progression of dementia and “prevent early memory decline.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers looked at health records from more than 300,000 people in Wales between 2013 and 2022, and found that the herpes zoster (HZ) vaccine (the medical term for shingles) “slows or prevents disease progression across the entire disease course … of dementia,” according to new research published in the medical journal &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674%2825%2901256-5?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0092867425012565%3Fshowall%3Dtrue" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cell.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The researchers found that for those living with dementia, the vaccine reduced their risk of death by 29.5%; For those who had not been diagnosed, the vaccine lessened the likelihood of being diagnosed with cognitive impairment by 3%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Stock image of a doctor preparing a vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“The effect of HZ vaccination — both on reducing new diagnoses of MCI and deaths due to dementia— was larger among women than men,” the study noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“That means that the vaccine doesn’t just have a preventive potential, but actually a therapeutic potential as a treatment, because we see some benefits already among those who have dementia,” &lt;a href="https://profiles.stanford.edu/pascal-geldsetzer" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Pascal Geldsetzer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dr. Pascal Geldsetzer&lt;/a&gt;, assistant professor of medicine at Stanford University and senior author of the new study, told &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/02/health/shingles-vaccine-dementia-progression-study-wellness" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CNN;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;CNN&lt;/a&gt;. “To me, this was really exciting to see and unexpected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-puzzler-8620185" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The shingles vaccine is a two-dose series of shots given at age 50, or to immunocompromised adults once they turn 19, the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/shingles/vaccines/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:U.S. Centers for Disease Control;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;U.S. Centers for Disease Control&lt;/a&gt; explains. One in three adults will develop shingles, which causes an itchy rash on one side of the body and significant, often long-term, nerve pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It’s caused by the same virus as chickenpox, the CDC explains — but even if you’ve had chickenpox, you should be vaccinated as the “virus stays dormant (inactive) in the body. It can reactivate years later and cause shingles.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Stock image of an older adult with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://forms.dotdashmeredith.com/people-news-inline" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers accounted for eligibility requirements for the shingles vaccine in Wales and explained they were able to compare groups who were eligible with those who were not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“We know they should have similar physical activity level, diets, et cetera,” Geldsetzer said. “So, we’re much more confident that what we’re actually looking at here is cause and effect, rather than just correlation.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/this-common-vaccine-may-slow-the-progression-of-dementia-11862390" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOYUpKQVVBTFVhWE5iZm0yLTlzbGc2dnptSFY4aDFndTBub2hKQWtjeUt0TDFyWEtDZ0FHZ1NlMXVMVFkzbHJvazhuWjhTTmhWeE55eXB0S2d2b0lTZ0E3YUpVMWlLQTNIVHJ0U0c2d3pST3VYaG1LSVJvZlZ2OExicFZn</guid></item><item><title>儿童不再能够参观SC最大的医院团体之一。原因如下-州政府</title><link>https://www.thestate.com/living/health-fitness/article314012092.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="primary-content" class="paper story-body"&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="trinityAudioPlaceholder trinity-player-iframe-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting this week, one of the largest health care groups in South Carolina will restrict children from visiting its hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Dec. 26, Prisma Health announced that it &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://prismahealth.org/patients-and-guests/news/prisma-health-to-temporarily-restrict-children-from-visiting-hospitalized-patients"&gt;won’t allow anyone 15 and younger to visit&lt;/a&gt; patients in its hospitals because of increased rates of the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The temporary visitor restriction will go into effect on Tuesday, &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://prismahealth.org/"&gt;Prisma Health&lt;/a&gt; officials said in a news release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-101" class="zone zone-el" index="2" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decision was made to protect patients, doctors, nurses and other staff members “during this time of higher-than-normal flu infection rates,” officials said. It’s believed that the measure will also protect vulnerable patients from infection by measles, which is still surging in the Upstate, according to the release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By taking this proactive step, we can help ensure our hospitals remain safe places for our patients to receive high-quality care,” Jacie Volkman, executive director of Prisma’s Department of Infection Prevention, said in the release. “Exceptions may be allowed for circumstances such as the imminent death of a loved one.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More suggestions to prevent and protect against the flu, and other respiratory viruses, include frequent handwashing, and staying home or away from others while sick, according to the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://dph.sc.gov/"&gt;South Carolina Department of Health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any visitors who feel sick should not visit hospitals. Additionally, it’s recommended that all visitors wear masks to help avoid the spread of respiratory illnesses, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;Flu season&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seasonal flu activity is increasing in most areas of the country, including South Carolina and Tennessee, where Prisma has hospital locations, according to the release. Nationwide, the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.cdc.gov/"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt; estimates that there have been at least 4.6 million illnesses, 49,000 hospitalizations and 1,900 deaths from flu so far this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current flu season started Sept. 28, according to the South Carolina Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://dph.sc.gov/diseases-conditions/infectious-diseases/flu"&gt;Symptoms can include&lt;/a&gt; a sudden onset of fever, cough, headache or muscle aches, tiredness, sore throat and nasal congestion or stuffiness, the S.C. Department of Public Health said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://dph.sc.gov/sites/scdph/files/2025-12/2025-Flu-Watch-MMWR-WK-51.pdf"&gt;seven flu-related deaths&lt;/a&gt; this season in South Carolina, according to the state Department of Public Health. The Palmetto State has reported more than 6,100 cases of the flu, and has exceeded 700 hospitalizations, S.C. Department of Public Health data shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-106" class="zone zone-el" index="11" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;Prevention&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both the CDC and S.C. Department of Public Health recommend that everyone 6 months of age and older get vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccination to prevent flu is particularly important for people who are at increased risk of complications from flu, including young children, adults aged 50 years and older, pregnant women and people with certain chronic medical conditions, Prisma officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu vaccines offered at Department of Public Health clinics are available by appointment. To make an appointment, call 855-472-3432, or go to the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://dph.sc.gov/diseases-conditions/infectious-diseases/flu/flu-vaccine-clinics"&gt;Department of Public Health website&lt;/a&gt; to find the nearest location.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-107" class="zone zone-el" index="15" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We look forward to returning to our normal visitation guidelines once the illness levels of our communities subside,” Volkman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://prismahealth.org/locations?searchType=location"&gt;Prisma has 18 hospitals&lt;/a&gt; in South Carolina, including seven in Columbia and the Midlands. Prisma said it serves more than 1.6 million patients per year in South Carolina and Tennessee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="transparency"&gt;    &lt;h3&gt;         BEHIND THE STORY     &lt;/h3&gt;            &lt;a class="more-link expander" role="button"&gt;            MORE        &lt;/a&gt;                &lt;div class="question"&gt;        &lt;h3&gt;This is a breaking news story&lt;/h3&gt;        &lt;div class="summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a breaking news situation, facts can be unclear and the situation may still be developing. The State is trying to get important information to the public as quickly and accurately as possible. This story will be updated as more information becomes available, and some information in this story may change as the facts become clearer. Refresh this page later for more updated information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="zone grid"&gt;&lt;div class="related-stories story-module"&gt;
        &lt;h5&gt;Related Stories from  The State in Columbia SC&lt;/h5&gt;
        
        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="story-module"&gt;&lt;div class="author-card "&gt;
        
        
        &lt;div class="author-description"&gt;

            &lt;span&gt;Noah Feit is a Real Time reporter with The State focused on breaking news, public safety and trending news. The award-winning journalist has worked for multiple newspapers since starting his career in 1999.&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://thestate.com/subscribe"&gt;Support my work with a digital subscription&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-16" class="zone-el"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The State</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 16:44:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFBNblZUZ2duNWVyV3dOQkx2VXVrVXRQdnVGX1ZGWTd4dlNidmZoRjA1cGRlNnZOOUJzVkdGUWhfdWR3el9XSF8wSzlEZEhCd29GSUthTTNpemltdXZ0c2psT0taOXpEbkx3SDZUbGNGcnE3R1BNNmJ30gF3QVVfeXFMTUpZOXpDUDlwQ3plSWdZakRId2MyYUlMT0N2RUt1amZRcUdaRmhTbmJGMWoxdGFqSEc3R0Z3ZTg3eEc0Vi1rOE5rOTF6LXd5VUV2cVJlZDFYOXEzQ2JWZXgxRlZzc1Z2Tlk0QWdCeFlpc0tKbHU4alU</guid></item></channel></rss>