<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>新研究发现，近二十年来，美国儿童变得越来越不健康-美联社新闻 | American kids have become increasingly unhealthy over nearly two decades, new study finds - AP News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxPc2g1NVo5Y2FmT012UklQYXhqZWZzVkJSa1hPWGVpbzZiZlJDQmczVnd0RVphT2F4N184Y1ZPNFZJeUdxdzE0SkhHZ3ExOHRmVUV4clh1cWhpbGtvRG9nVE4zQTBxeWtKN0Z4MzBMb2JJSFJvM1liZ1R1bWJ0M2NOaFdjd1lMWEhHUlA4WWlESVBxQ09STjFN?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 15:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPc2g1NVo5Y2FmT012UklQYXhqZWZzVkJSa1hPWGVpbzZiZlJDQmczVnd0RVphT2F4N184Y1ZPNFZJeUdxdzE0SkhHZ3ExOHRmVUV4clh1cWhpbGtvRG9nVE4zQTBxeWtKN0Z4MzBMb2JJSFJvM1liZ1R1bWJ0M2NOaFdjd1lMWEhHUlA4WWlESVBxQ09STjFN</guid></item><item><title>育儿建议：我想帮助我的家人度过医疗紧急情况。但不是这样的。-石板 | Parenting advice: I want to help my family through a medical emergency. But not like this. - Slate</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxNYmpyUktPWDdMbkt4dWx6Nl9zcTRNQlRTd2YxUFpFNEY0NVJGTHpQLVJ3X1hwb0c5YU8zZlVzaHlnVzdGZnNhSjJQYWp3enhQWnFHMFdnUmZPb01NUFRhdFRlVmZyZTN5bGtSNGFXLWJsT3Nob2E5QUNOTjh6NkhHUXRvUFd6dw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="54" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmcnxc0dd004otcm9x7y9hioz@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Hi Advice readers! Have you ever thought about writing into Care and Feeding? Now’s the time—our inbox is in need of more questions! Conundrums big and small are welcome, and of course, it’s anonymous. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeI516MVbV7en9S-8krL2zppY_GWq-qad7K_P7iUvxcD7t6vA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Submit your family and parenting questions to Care and Feeding here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;. (Or your questions about anything else to our &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://slate.com/life/2023/06/advice-columns-submit-questions.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;other columns here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmcnxfr03001j3b6hnelu9e7k@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="89" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7ulgu00093b76z4u1jomq@published"&gt;My brother and his wife live nearby, and our kids get along well. We definitely have different parenting styles, but we talk through them. We’re comfortable with this, and we often host each other’s children for the day. There’s one major difference: Our kids (ages 3 and 5) are sleep trained, but my brother and sister-in-law never sleep trained their 5-year-old son, “Pete.” They’ve mentioned having to get up with him several times a night. Pete seems fine otherwise, and since it was their choice, I left it alone.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="70" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7unw9000f3b768lo9gelc@published"&gt;But now that’s changing. They’ve asked us to take Pete for a while when his baby brother is born, and we haven’t really said “yes” because we’re trying to figure out how to handle it. My SIL is in her third trimester and found out that the birth will be complicated. Their baby will, at minimum, spend time in the NICU. It’s scary, and we’re all hoping everything goes well.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="123" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7ur8j000l3b76dvnywvi8@published"&gt;It feels cruel to tell them to sleep train a 5-year-old in the last months of a difficult pregnancy, or else we can’t babysit him. But it also won’t get easier once the baby is born. If it were only two or three nights, we’d manage, but we’re probably going to be caring for Pete for longer stretches in that first month, unless the birth goes miraculously well. My husband’s work shifts mean sleep is precious in our household. I’m usually the nighttime parent, and I cannot be getting up multiple times every night, outside of emergencies and regular parenting stuff.&lt;br&gt;All this will already be a series of hard transitions for Pete. How do we approach the conversation with my brother and SIL?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7uuy9000r3b764uuwjlr9@published"&gt;—(Not) Up All Night&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7uwwg000x3b76n85xctci@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Not Up, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="96" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7v0fq00133b76qtgl0poa@published"&gt;As tricky as this is, your brother and his wife are in an emergency medical situation they neither asked for nor planned for. This is a time when you need to step up. You don’t have to turn your own life totally upside down, but you should be prepared to make some adjustments or concessions. By asking questions and setting expectations now, you can help make the transition smoother for everyone. So, go ahead and say yes, but ask for a chat about the specifics of what caring for Pete might actually look like. For example:&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;ul data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-list/instances/cmco7v4pm00193b76fn9vqvdw@published" class="slate-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are they willing to let you set boundaries around Pete’s nighttime waking? Are they open to using tools like an OK-to-Wake clock, or placing a nightly limit on how many times he can get out of bed?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If any of those boundaries lead to sleep training Pete—whether inadvertently or intentionally on your part—are they OK with that?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the waking is due to bedwetting, what kinds of interventions (mattress pads, special pajamas, wetness sensors) have they tried, or would they be open to you exploring?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;How long do they anticipate this arrangement lasting? What happens if they need to extend it? And what happens if they need more time, but you can’t accommodate it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the nighttime waking becomes too much and you need help, are they willing to contribute financially to a solution, like hiring a nighttime nanny or flying in a grandma to give you a respite? (I truly hope this isn’t necessary for a 5-year-old, but covering all bases here.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="55" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmcnxfvqf001o3b6hamhvoq8t@published"&gt;Let’s also acknowledge that Pete might do &lt;em&gt;great &lt;/em&gt;in a new environment, simply because you aren’t his parents and his routine will be different. He also might regress. Either way, knowing ahead of time what kind of freedom you’ll have to manage any challenges will allow you to be nimble in the moment. Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmco7yh0m003h3b76rxq2c1n5@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSeI516MVbV7en9S-8krL2zppY_GWq-qad7K_P7iUvxcD7t6vA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmco7yqgr003p3b7635tnbf5n@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmco7ynfk003l3b76a14bszor@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmcnxfwyz001u3b6hwm5hakna@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="111" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7wvh2001g3b76xdl57hqk@published"&gt;My mother has bipolar disorder and has spent the past decade and a half in and out of treatment facilities. My parents divorced when I was 8 because my dad simply couldn’t deal with her erratic behavior anymore. (Some of her episodes involved chaining herself to a traffic light and threatening to jump off the roof of our house.) He was awarded sole custody of my sister and me. My mother was unable to hold a job and couldn’t pay child support. Her (supervised) visits eventually stopped, even before she was admitted for inpatient treatment. My sister was less than 2 years old when our mom dropped out of our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="99" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7wxkv001k3b76iaz2iwp4@published"&gt;Now, our mother has contacted us out of the blue, saying she wants a relationship. I am convinced she’s looking for a place to crash, someone to support her, or both. I have refused contact—I have two kids under 5 and no desire to put them in physical or emotional danger. My sister, however, is very excited over the prospect. She was too young to remember how unstable and terrifying our mom’s presence was, and I’m extremely concerned she’ll get hurt if she lets our mom back into her life. How can I get my sister to face reality?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7wzjh001o3b762g49mr8q@published"&gt;—Take Off the Rose-Colored Glasses&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7x1el001s3b76tgzu7vio@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Glasses, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="127" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7x37n001w3b76v7b9yax2@published"&gt;This is a situation where you might need to get out of your sister’s way, while still helping her stay as safe as possible. As you said, she doesn’t have any memories from when things with your mom were really bad, and there is a big difference between hearing about it and experiencing it firsthand. Even at your most persuasive, I wonder whether your accounts of the past would be enough to convince her to walk away now; it’s very possible that your sister has been fantasizing about this kind of reunion for years. And though you may be right about your mother’s motives, it’s also conceivable that you are wrong—so I’m not sure forbidding your sister from finding out for herself is in anyone’s best interest.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="87" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7x62000203b76kbkh6idu@published"&gt;All that aside, it is absolutely appropriate for you to set your own boundaries and be skeptical about your mother’s motives. Focus on equipping your sister with the knowledge she needs, so she doesn’t go into the meeting with rose-colored glasses. Discuss your concerns, identify warning signs to look out for, and make a plan for the boundaries your sister will maintain. For example, maybe she promises not to give your mother money. If your mom asks for any, then you and your sister can discuss it together.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="54" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7x81r00243b7614yg6191@published"&gt;Mental illnesses like bipolar disorder can be devastating for a family, but it is possible to learn how to manage and mitigate their impacts. I think there is a way to protect yourself and your sister while remaining open to the possibility that your mom has made progress. Good luck with whatever you decide.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmco7yddo003d3b76k4es6h8d@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmco82vq8004c3b761a8obg43@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Your Questions to Good Job!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="34" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco82vnu004b3b768p063yxh@published"&gt;Laura Helmuth and Doree Shafrir want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmco7z8k6003u3b768ommb0a5@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7x9aw00283b762wlkkr8c@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="115" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7xhni002d3b76dsuo2ywk@published"&gt;My wife “Anling” has a fear of germs that borders on irrational. She keeps our 3-year-old son “Joseph” meticulously clean and won’t allow him to do normal kid things like roll around in the grass or play in the sand at the park. (My parents even bought him a kiddie sandbox, but Anling made me give it back to them.) She vacuums the entire house every single day and insists on changing Joseph’s clothes and bathing him every time they return from running errands. I don’t go along with any of this when I’m caring for our son on my own, but if Anling sees even a smudge of dirt on him, I get blasted.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="54" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7xjqf002h3b764sbt8tp4@published"&gt;Last week, we took a trip to a seaside town. The birds there (pigeons and seagulls) are very habituated to people, so I gave Joseph some popcorn to feed the pigeons while we waited for Anling to come back from the restroom. The pigeons ate right out of Joseph’s hands, and he was delighted.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="73" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7xljc002l3b768fdk6wb4@published"&gt;The fun ended when my wife returned. She came running over, shouting and waving her arms to scare the birds away, then took hand sanitizer from her purse and slathered it all over Joseph’s hands and arms while he cried. Anling then caused a scene, berating me and calling me a “moron,” and said it would be my fault if our son got bird flu. She made us leave for home that day.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="79" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7xpj1002p3b76edykwcxa@published"&gt;Anling has always been a “clean freak,” but things really went into overdrive after Joseph was born—and my patience with her hypochondria has run dry. Beyond depriving our son of normal childhood experiences and making him anxious, I’m concerned she is setting him up for allergies and a weakened immune system, since he’s never exposed to anything. I’m ready to give Anling an ultimatum: Either she eases up, or we go our separate ways. Is that the right approach?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7xr54002t3b76033j320k@published"&gt;—Dad of the Boy in the Bubble&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7xsyu002x3b762vwi99n4@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Dad, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="82" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7xv7e00313b76nj1hxqgj@published"&gt;I am not going to attempt any kind of diagnosis here (and I’m unclear on whether your wife has already been diagnosed with hypochondria, or whether that’s hyperbole from you), but according to the &lt;a href="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/statistics/mental-illness#:~:text=Serious%20mental%20illness%20(SMI)%20is,experience%20disability%20due%20to%20SMI."&gt;National Institute of Health&lt;/a&gt;, mental illnesses are considered serious when they “substantially [interfere] with or [limit] one or more major life activities.” It sounds like you feel this is where your family is at right now, which is a valid reason to ask your wife to seek help.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="75" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7xxww00353b7649cm3dia@published"&gt;If she is resistant, show her a list of characteristics for “illness anxiety disorder” (also known as hypochondria) and use that as a conversation tool. The goal isn’t to prove that she is “broken,” but to gently demonstrate how her behaviors are impacting you and your son.&lt;br&gt;If she acknowledges there’s a problem, the next step isn’t her “easing up” as you put it, but seeking individual and family therapy to learn some new coping skills.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmco7y1dy00393b76jpqihl9x@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Allison&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmcnxfzlr00213b6h30o1wc3r@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Parenting Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="102" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmcnxgjk200293b6hmfsk0wet@published"&gt;I have a 14-year-old stepson whom I first met when he was a toddler. He spent weekends with his father and me until he was 7, when he moved in with us because his mom moved out of state and we were awarded physical custody. When we got married several years ago, I asked him what he wanted to call me, and he said “Mom.” He is smart, bright, funny, and generous, and he has a heart of gold. He deserves to have present, loving parents as much as every single kid out there does. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2019/02/stepson-love-care-and-feeding.html"&gt;And yet, I do not love him.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmcnxc0dd004rtcm928nl9sgc@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;The latest sex, parenting, and money advice from our columnists delivered to your inbox three times a week.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNYmpyUktPWDdMbkt4dWx6Nl9zcTRNQlRTd2YxUFpFNEY0NVJGTHpQLVJ3X1hwb0c5YU8zZlVzaHlnVzdGZnNhSjJQYWp3enhQWnFHMFdnUmZPb01NUFRhdFRlVmZyZTN5bGtSNGFXLWJsT3Nob2E5QUNOTjh6NkhHUXRvUFd6dw</guid></item><item><title>专栏|我是一名胃肠病学家。这就是我告诉我的病人吃这种水果的原因。-《华盛顿邮报》 | Column | I’m a gastroenterologist. Here’s why I tell my patients to eat this one fruit. - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxPVjE1NjNadDVubGNvbGZDV1JuTXlHeEVZdE4yX2pQWXVXNGNTNEYyelZGQkF5VGNpU2NZT0pBSkV5MDVhM0tfLUNTVG1ma29qamFWQk1LLWE3MF83N1pwTTIxQzQxbWpPYTJwN1JQQVZFcDFkOG5pU0xHaF9PdWkyVUc5TGQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YVDJ3WHKAJB5BHR4X5FQASBETE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Is there something I can eat to help with constipation? A lot of high-fiber foods and supplements make me bloated, but I don’t want to take a laxative.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HKLD2GFURJBQBLJU7PNUFWU2O4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I get this question often in my gastroenterology clinic. Gut symptoms like bloating and constipation are &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31917991/" target="_blank"&gt;incredibly common&lt;/a&gt;, affecting up to a third of the population. Many people don’t want to take medication if there are more natural ways to help. But I also know that simply recommending people &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/06/09/healthier-food-diet-advice/" target="_blank"&gt;increase their fiber intake&lt;/a&gt; is vague and not always useful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GFOXN2HO4RFHFIPSCHNM45JGYU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;That’s why&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;I’ve been “prescribing” a dose of two kiwis a day to my patients for years now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4IZ5ZIXYYVGBFFRCBQ6C36OZM4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A small but mighty green or gold fruit, kiwis are &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/media/77434/download" target="_blank"&gt;bursting with nutrients&lt;/a&gt;: A single kiwi contains 80 percent or more of an adult’s daily vitamin C requirement and packs two to four grams of &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/04/13/legume-pasta-edamame-low-carb/" target="_blank"&gt;fiber&lt;/a&gt;. In addition to vitamins E and K and other beneficial antioxidants and phytochemicals, one of the kiwi’s most important properties is an enzyme called actinidin. Actinidin is present in only a few dietary sources besides kiwis (including mango and pineapple), and it can help break down proteins, aiding in our digestion. Actinidin is so powerful that it’s used commercially as a meat tenderizer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YBSCQRCWDBAKXPMRPTRBJ67CP4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;So how does this help your gut? Let me fill you in on the findings of a randomized controlled trial that electrified gastroenterologists everywhere. The study was funded by a kiwifruit marketer, but its methods were rigorous and showed clear measurable outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UKVVHWV64BCKDM2C5ZPCC6TJRE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In the 2022 &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10226473/" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;, scientists from three countries — New Zealand, Italy and Japan — found that eating two green kiwis per day for four weeks helped people have more complete bowel movements. On average, people pooped between one and two more times each week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SFK4Y3XBFJG5ZNQ7IJZ3NBLQNI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;For people with constipation at baseline, kiwis improved symptoms such as abdominal pain, indigestion and straining during &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/01/16/poop-frequency-color-meaning/" target="_blank"&gt;bowel movements&lt;/a&gt; — often even more so than &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/01/06/psyllium-supplement-how-much/" target="_blank"&gt;psyllium&lt;/a&gt;, a type of fiber sold in powders and capsules over-the-counter. These people also reported an improvement in overall quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RUWEPREMTNDMPGDFCN4A42DNI4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Consuming a diversity of plants is always the overarching goal for a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2022/09/20/gut-health-microbiome-best-foods/" target="_blank"&gt;healthy microbiome&lt;/a&gt;, and I tell patients that kiwis can be a great addition to that approach. I’ve seen the benefits firsthand in my patients and even my own family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="OIRPOLEWZNF3RO74IKQGDUN3EQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="OIRPOLEWZNF3RO74IKQGDUN3EQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;The power of fruits and vegetables&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UQ6V4U3QPFEHHAXBJMGSQZC5HI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Besides fiber, the benefits of eating a diet rich in &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2022/10/13/food-hacks-help-you-eat-more-fruits-vegetables/" target="_blank"&gt;vegetables and fruits&lt;/a&gt; like kiwis are commonly attributed to their antioxidants. These compounds are known to protect against &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002916522030064" target="_blank"&gt;cancer, cardiovascular diseases&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://diabetesjournals.org/care/article/27/2/362/28291/Dietary-Antioxidant-Intake-and-Risk-of-Type-2" target="_blank"&gt;diabetes.&lt;/a&gt; But — and this is a big one — it’s an effect that mainly appears to occur through a healthy diet — and not through antioxidant supplementation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="A4NIAVRXEJFU3IOQ4KIO5L4P7A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;As is often the case with other &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/03/31/supplements-benefits-research-science/" target="_blank"&gt;supplements&lt;/a&gt;, when you try to distill the compound of interest into a capsule or pill, that &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17327526/" target="_blank"&gt;beneficial health effect&lt;/a&gt; of antioxidants vanishes — and may even be potentially harmful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UJHZZUKM4FF6VL2R3C7HBGEPAI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Scientists suspect that the kiwi’s antioxidants, like vitamin C, synergize with its other naturally occurring phytochemicals to boost its protective power — something we lose when we distill these nutrients into a commercialized supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="5ZBJXROZRNHUVEKAWO4COUB6FA" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="5ZBJXROZRNHUVEKAWO4COUB6FA" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Kiwi’s benefits may go beyond the gut&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RXYZ5QQLFNCJFFRVT7JPNXP2XQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In 2011, Norwegian researchers randomized healthy volunteers to a month of eating either one or two &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/21586177/" target="_blank"&gt;gold kiwis daily&lt;/a&gt;. When the scientists analyzed DNA samples, they found fewer DNA strand breaks — a sign of improved fortitude that can theoretically reduce opportunities for cancerous growth. And indeed, after one month, the volunteers’ DNA had become about 30 percent more resistant to a kind of injury called oxidative damage that can lead to dangerous mutations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PA57FX423RBU3DHSDOFD2VUUFQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Besides studying DNA, researchers also looked at plasma triglycerides, a kind of fat circulating in the bloodstream that increases &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/01/08/apo-b-cholesterol-test/" target="_blank"&gt;heart attack risk&lt;/a&gt;. At the end of the month, triglycerides had decreased by about 13 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XGLRYG5JTBE3TMEQT22AJ3OSVQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Though not a perfect study design, a 2023 &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10198059/" target="_blank"&gt;meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; of retrospective studies of kiwi and other fruit consumption found that people who ate more kiwis had a 13 percent decreased risk of &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/05/19/why-colorectal-cancer-rising-young-people/" target="_blank"&gt;colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TPPGM2FVBNGPBOGX324TKMZZFM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;More research needs to be done to fully understand kiwi consumption and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/08/05/how-to-prevent-cancer/" target="_blank"&gt;cancer risk&lt;/a&gt; — but the scientific groundwork has been laid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="2CTRDRDGKZH6HKIUSDZG3YOIEM" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="2CTRDRDGKZH6HKIUSDZG3YOIEM" data-testid="article-header"&gt;What are other natural ways to help with constipation?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IAEROMHC75DQHLF2RMPG4MSTZ4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Supplementing with psyllium husk fiber has long reigned as queen in the gastroenterology world: Psyllium is specific, easy to take and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/01/06/psyllium-supplement-how-much/" target="_blank"&gt;does wonders for the body&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N5PHBQ6CYFH4NB7DIAIG7XFOEA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Prunes have been hailed for their laxative properties, but, if I’m being honest, have you ever tried to tell a college student with constipation to go buy some prunes? Trust me, it won’t happen. And for many people, prunes can actually make bloating &lt;i&gt;worse &lt;/i&gt;due to high levels of sorbitol, a naturally occurring sugar that gets fermented by your colon’s microbiome. That’s why I tend to recommend kiwis instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="F3YEZYTGZ5C43D7QOBWNPOG2VQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="F3YEZYTGZ5C43D7QOBWNPOG2VQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;What I want my patients to know&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XVT6XTIS6BEMLNSXNSECE6VXRU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;No, you don’t have to eat the kiwi’s peel. Plenty of studies have found notable health benefits &lt;i&gt;sans&lt;/i&gt; peel. But if you feel so inclined, go on, have a little nibble on the skin. It’s totally edible and packed with fiber. Just be sure to keep your doctor in the loop about your gut issues. For lots of people, the underlying condition causing their symptoms is past the point of a simpler dietary intervention. It’s why it’s important to find a doctor you trust who can consider multiple angles in approaching your health concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-raw_html" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-cbTFcs wpds-c-cbTFcs-iPJLV-css" data-qa="raw-html"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;
  
  &lt;p class="wpds-c-joLgjs"&gt;
    This content was created independently by The Washington Post and is not influenced by the advertiser and their affiliates. The advertiser had no involvement in the reporting, writing, or editing of this article or video.
  &lt;/p&gt;
 
  
  &lt;div&gt;
    &lt;span&gt;
      Presented by
    &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;img src="//logotyp.us/file/one-medical.svg" alt="One Medical"&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 13:47:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPVjE1NjNadDVubGNvbGZDV1JuTXlHeEVZdE4yX2pQWXVXNGNTNEYyelZGQkF5VGNpU2NZT0pBSkV5MDVhM0tfLUNTVG1ma29qamFWQk1LLWE3MF83N1pwTTIxQzQxbWpPYTJwN1JQQVZFcDFkOG5pU0xHaF9PdWkyVUc5TGQ</guid></item><item><title>与营养不良相关的新生儿死亡，生长缓慢增加-《华盛顿邮报》 | Newborn deaths related to malnutrition, slow growth increased - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxPOEp6QkFsSERFUjhXZ2k0NmpBRkdCWC1iSE9yMlpGODZoSUliVUxQMGl3a0Q2RnhUVmN0b19LVTBqb0NzSEtyZVlDeVZ3OElxNVRlcE03TjNmYUJXemd6Y2hDcS01bTZZOXJOM2tya0RXN0h2SDhhbmRaTVJ6S3pNWm12dGFhLUlDc3BtbHdQZGFQXzhUTnow?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="5UU6DNLPX5BLRAZXOKITRWSEHU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;While U.S. neonatal deaths have generally decreased in recent decades, mortality because of slow fetal growth and malnutrition increased annually by almost 2 percent from 1999 through 2022, according to a &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamapediatrics/article-abstract/2835097" target="_blank"&gt;research letter&lt;/a&gt; published in JAMA Pediatrics in June.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CVDCTNXGJVF2XJUFQVIYLPNDEQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Using data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, researchers reported that over 280,000 newborn infants — 283,696 — died of perinatal complications from 1999 to 2022 in the United States. Researchers said over half of those who died were male, which the study suggests was because of differences in their lung development and immune response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IYHQ7HSNQJFM5B53TOEIHEHY74" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Most leading causes of neonatal deaths declined over the two decades studied by the researchers, but a 1.91 percent rise in fetal growth and malnutrition deaths annually raised concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3YMEVVGJ3RAZXMGSWUT6E6OPE4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“The rising mortality due to slow fetal growth and malnutrition is concerning,” Muzamil Khan, a research fellow at George Washington University School of Medicine and Health Sciences who was an author of the study, wrote in an email to The Washington Post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IET3TMK5UFES7E6PFVLO32NEKE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“It points to persistent gaps in prenatal nutrition and maternal care,” Khan added. “Our findings emphasize the need for targeted interventions — especially focused on nutrition and delivery practices — to further reduce preventable neonatal deaths.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UMNQRLFAWFEK7MAU45HRKOYAKU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The research paper cited disorders related to short gestation and low birth weight as the top cause of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EVINFUZ5E5BFVM3PV2J5XQPHS4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;After that, the nine next leading causes of death were maternal complications; complications of placenta, umbilical cord or membranes; bacterial sepsis; atelectasis, or a partial or total lung collapse; intrauterine hypoxia and birth hypoxia, or oxygen deprivation; neonatal hemorrhage; newborn necrotizing enterocolitis, a gastrointestinal disease; pulmonary hemorrhage; and respiratory distress. The top 10 causes accounted for 79.8 percent of total deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="H4OXOM3O4VDHXGLC5BYCNQIGDE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In addition, children who were delivered vaginally had a mortality rate three times higher than that of cesarean deliveries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HIPFFWJC7FDXNGP64UO25U4PAM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article is part of The Post’s “Big Number” series, which takes a brief look at the statistical aspect of health issues. Additional information and relevant research are available through the hyperlinks.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 13:17:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPOEp6QkFsSERFUjhXZ2k0NmpBRkdCWC1iSE9yMlpGODZoSUliVUxQMGl3a0Q2RnhUVmN0b19LVTBqb0NzSEtyZVlDeVZ3OElxNVRlcE03TjNmYUJXemd6Y2hDcS01bTZZOXJOM2tya0RXN0h2SDhhbmRaTVJ6S3pNWm12dGFhLUlDc3BtbHdQZGFQXzhUTnow</guid></item><item><title>维生素D缺乏可能导致的5种严重疾病-印度时报 | 5 serious diseases Vitamin D deficiency can cause - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi4gFBVV95cUxPbURRVmpjZ2NLdmNQaVFvb3ZHRm0wT1VRa1RFRlRNbWlDYVRBMmx4djd4ZDdTbll2c19zUXFJZG1ORDdvcF9qc2VzbHdueWl6dElFYVVpVVVSWjVkaWhtakVUdFVBUHlSRUZ0aTJOUVVQRWdmTlFqM3ZJR1NMbVVWR09Qenp6UUlEeWRjeFZjbmtJSDN1S0tnVjg4SmFSVHVRNjFHczRHaTVhMFo3TW1Pd29wWjNyNzlaanpuVUVwVi1aaklwel9fZEZDUElEeXI2REpVY0w3VV9tcFo4cGhJQ25R?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin D is much needed for bone health, supporting immunity, regulating mood, and inflammation-- thus making it important for our overall health and well-being. Apart from getting it from foods, Vitamin D is also synthesised in the body when exposed to sunlight and hence it is also called the "sunshine vitamin". However, a large number of people across the world suffer from Vitamin D deficiency, often without even knowing it. This deficiency is mainly due to poor diets and limited sun exposure, and it can lead to more than just fatigue or low mood— it’s been linked to several serious health issues, some of which can be long-term or even life-threatening if ignored. Here we list some serious diseases Vitamin D deficiency can cause:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 12:44:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4gFBVV95cUxPbURRVmpjZ2NLdmNQaVFvb3ZHRm0wT1VRa1RFRlRNbWlDYVRBMmx4djd4ZDdTbll2c19zUXFJZG1ORDdvcF9qc2VzbHdueWl6dElFYVVpVVVSWjVkaWhtakVUdFVBUHlSRUZ0aTJOUVVQRWdmTlFqM3ZJR1NMbVVWR09Qenp6UUlEeWRjeFZjbmtJSDN1S0tnVjg4SmFSVHVRNjFHczRHaTVhMFo3TW1Pd29wWjNyNzlaanpuVUVwVi1aaklwel9fZEZDUElEeXI2REpVY0w3VV9tcFo4cGhJQ25R</guid></item><item><title>戒酒后，我的体重激增。以下是我最终戒掉两种毒瘾的方法--《每日电讯报》 | My weight ballooned after I gave up drinking. Here’s how I finally quit both addictions - The Telegraph</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiigFBVV95cUxQa1FydVhIQTQ1VkN5T2I4NkN0N0NJREZZaVd0LURWYWcxUElyM1ltRmM0QWFfSG9xUXMya3pVNG5wZ3NWU0x4dGpjeHFrdWdoUTAyZGRHRkdseXpWRVBYYlFjNVJaLXhSaHRmeXItVGk5YmlUaTdNclk4TG41ZHY2UGNuWTlVa01WcWc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Yet my personal life was in tatters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;But while all that was taking off, behind closed doors my personal life was slowly falling apart. Admittedly, there were already cracks in my six-year-old marriage when I was drinking. Midlife marriages can be complicated; I had&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;four step-children and my ex-wife had undergone cancer – more than once. I can’t have been easy to live with, and fundamentally we were cut from different cloth. Stopping drinking wasn’t a miraculous cure-all. My issues (a complicated childhood, a turbulent relationship which led to me constantly getting absolutely plastered, sleeping rough for four nights on the beach and culminated in the pain of my mum’s death in 2018) were all still there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once sober I started seeing life in full 4K, realising what I did and didn’t want. So by 2022 my marriage was over and we’d separated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I packed my bags and left our London house, we both knew it was for the best. But it was unsettling, especially without alcohol as my trusty crutch any more, and with all the financial stress divorce brings. After moving around in-between rentals and hotels for the next year or so, I eventually bought my own place in the East Midlands. But I didn’t have many friends there, so apart from work (I now coach people online as well as give talks in schools, companies and for the Blue Light professions) life could sometimes feel fragile. I’d take Rosie, my dog, out for long, lonely walks thinking about life. But here’s the truth – while I’d remained sober throughout an emotional roller-coaster, I’d secretly swapped the booze addiction &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/wellbeing/mental-health/life-with-food-addiction/"&gt;for a sugar one&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one admits that swapping one addiction for another is incredibly common. Whether it’s food (like me) or shopping, work, exercise, social media – we all reach for something, people I meet in recovery circles all say the same thing. We’re all a bunch of hypocrites because we’re all human!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;I swapped my beer gut for a food belly&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portion control was a problem, I thought I was being healthy having a weighty bowl of granola and Greek yoghurt in the morning, but I’d ladle on so much honey that breakfast alone was probably 700 calories. The bowl would weigh a tonne. Or I’d eat cinnamon buns, or wholemeal toast but slathered with peanut butter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lunch might be four chicken thighs with jacket potato and salad (and I’d polish my halo), then I’d tuck into a huge steak and chips for dinner – enough to feed an entire rugby team. I wasn’t a bad cook, it wasn’t like I’d left all that to my wife during marriage, but I was naive about portion sizes and nutrition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the evenings, I’d come home from a long day talking to people about alcohol addiction and scoff a family-sized apple crumble with vast amounts of ice cream&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; nipping back for more until – ah, f--k it – I’d finish the lot. “I’m allowed treats, I’ve stopped boozing,” I’d tell myself. But just like my drinking had stopped being something sociable by the end, so too had my eating. It was something I’d privately binge for a dopamine hit, along with a huge dollop of shame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I ballooned back up to 19st 8lb through comfort eating, yet all the while I was out there giving talks, helping people get sober. I felt like a greedy fraud.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 12:41:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQa1FydVhIQTQ1VkN5T2I4NkN0N0NJREZZaVd0LURWYWcxUElyM1ltRmM0QWFfSG9xUXMya3pVNG5wZ3NWU0x4dGpjeHFrdWdoUTAyZGRHRkdseXpWRVBYYlFjNVJaLXhSaHRmeXItVGk5YmlUaTdNclk4TG41ZHY2UGNuWTlVa01WcWc</guid></item><item><title>心脏病和BMI与绝经后妇女乳腺癌风险增加相关- Scimex | Heart disease and BMI linked with increased breast cancer risk in postmenopausal women - Scimex</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxNQWlWcmRwdnJRQUN6Uzc5amN1cHZhMzFncUtvVFBtMGk5M0loQzk2SS1CVkZhRzRicEIySm9tVkhCbFVLNHJ4WTU3M3p1dkJLbUtob1ZBX2RaOFVadk9RbjJiRjY5T0kxem9oQnd4eG44S19kZXBhMGxaY2YzbTFObVYxZjRkTmI1VE5PVHl6V1Q3Q00wVE90OG5UTE56ZDU3T2t4S1FETTdGN205eVowelB2WQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story-summary"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="story-summary-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In postmenopausal women with heart disease, excess weight could be linked to an especially high risk of developing breast cancer, according to international researchers. The team looked at data from over 168,000 postmenopausal women who did not have type 2 diabetes and cardiovascular disease when they agreed to participate. After a follow-up of around 10 years, over 6,000 developed breast cancer, and the team found that in women who developed cardiovascular disease during the study, each 5 point increase in BMI was associated with a 31% higher risk of breast cancer when compared to women without cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                  
                

                
                &lt;div class="story__notes"&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Journal/conference:&lt;/strong&gt; CANCER&lt;/p&gt;
               
                  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/cncr.35911" target="_blank"&gt;Paper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  
                  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organisation/s:&lt;/strong&gt; The International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC), World Health Organization&lt;/p&gt;
                  
                                  &lt;/div&gt;
                  
                  

                  &lt;div class="story-content"&gt;
                                            &lt;h2&gt;Media release&lt;/h2&gt;
                    
&lt;strong&gt;From:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt; Wiley

                                        
                    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does body mass index affect breast cancer risk in postmenopausal women with and without cardiovascular disease?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysis shows that weight-associated breast cancer risk is higher in women with cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New research reveals that excess weight is linked to an especially high risk of developing breast cancer in postmenopausal women with cardiovascular disease. The findings are published by &lt;a href="https://zwly9k6z.r.us-east-1.awstrack.me/L0/https:%2F%2Fwww.wiley.com%2F/1/01000197cb39c7fe-8757bfab-e5e9-498d-a8c0-092e46891925-000000/ar_rreNj0Y8xYzsWyvyAKaqESzY=433"&gt;Wiley&lt;/a&gt; online in &lt;a href="https://zwly9k6z.r.us-east-1.awstrack.me/L0/https:%2F%2Facsjournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com%2Fjournal%2F10970142%3Fdmmsmid=73865%26dmmspid=22624228%26dmmsuid=1961220/1/01000197cb39c7fe-8757bfab-e5e9-498d-a8c0-092e46891925-000000/dJyVq8jWm3Qmy5Q9R1Pd5vB3IZw=433"&gt;CANCER&lt;/a&gt;, a peer-reviewed journal of the American Cancer Society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although higher body mass index (BMI) is a known risk factor for breast cancer in postmenopausal women, it’s unclear whether this risk differs among women with and without cardiovascular disease or type 2 diabetes. To investigate, a team led by Heinz Freisling, PhD, of the International Agency for Research on Cancer (the specialized cancer agency of the World Health Organization) analyzed data from the European Prospective Investigation into Cancer and Nutrition (EPIC) and UK Biobank on 168,547 postmenopausal women who did not have, type 2 diabetes, and cardiovascular disease when they agreed to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a median follow-up of 10.7 years in EPIC and 10.9 years in UK Biobank, 6,793 postmenopausal women developed breast cancer. In a pooled analysis of both studies, each 5 kg/m&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt; increase in BMI was associated with a 31% higher risk of breast cancer in women who developed cardiovascular disease during follow-up and a 13% higher risk in women without cardiovascular disease. The development of type 2 diabetes did not seem to affect breast cancer risk: women with or without type 2 diabetes had a similarly elevated breast cancer risk related to higher BMI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The combination of overweight (BMI≥25 kg/m&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;) and cardiovascular disease was estimated to lead to 153 more cases of breast cancer per 100,000 people per year than expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The findings of this study could be used to inform risk-stratified breast cancer screening programs,” said Dr. Freisling. “This study should also inspire future research to include women with a history of cardiovascular diseases in weight loss trials for breast cancer prevention.”&lt;/p&gt;

                  &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Scimex</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:41:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxNQWlWcmRwdnJRQUN6Uzc5amN1cHZhMzFncUtvVFBtMGk5M0loQzk2SS1CVkZhRzRicEIySm9tVkhCbFVLNHJ4WTU3M3p1dkJLbUtob1ZBX2RaOFVadk9RbjJiRjY5T0kxem9oQnd4eG44S19kZXBhMGxaY2YzbTFObVYxZjRkTmI1VE5PVHl6V1Q3Q00wVE90OG5UTE56ZDU3T2t4S1FETTdGN205eVowelB2WQ</guid></item><item><title>吃什么来保护衰老的肌肉-《华盛顿邮报》 | What to eat to protect your aging muscles - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxQN1ZsUFQ2a0ZRS2luMmtFTXlzUjN3M0RJZ0hvYVdOM2QzTTdXc0JrdTRiNDFHZFpUcGhHWG95THJnNmJ3U3RudHh2Wl8xQ2ZyNlhwTThTQnJocG9FM1MxdUlHdmIzbXRIc3l2WXU3cjZVRE95ZlRzUUNhY254eHpYMUt1Y3FQMWpJSEJYWGdB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VGH2W2CZRRCELDS66TNLXGPQHQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Consumer Reports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; has no financial relationship with any advertisers on this site.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HZ65C7ZJVNDWRJG42ZRTQPSNBA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Have you found yourself feeling a little weaker than you used to? Are you having trouble climbing stairs or carrying groceries? The reason may be reduced muscle mass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2U62Z4LKXBHNBDSAO56OBTTLBA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;With age comes some decline in muscle, and for many people that’s accompanied by a drop in strength and function. Severe muscle loss, known as sarcopenia, can increase the risk of illness and even death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WNR4OFYXRFBMVGKN7IDZN7XLEY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Although you can’t prevent all age-related muscle loss, you can slow it down significantly and even boost your strength level in the process. You’ve probably heard that exercise, especially weight training, can help you build and maintain muscle. What isn’t discussed as often is the role that diet plays in keeping your muscles in good shape. “You can’t get stronger without eating properly, so diet is essential,” says Elizabeth Klingbeil, an assistant professor in the department of nutritional sciences at the University of Texas at Austin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4H4DJGMYNBH3TJOWSLUP2MO45Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Follow these eating tips to fuel muscle growth and feel stronger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="3LFVGOBZ4JGZXLVNOIISFQVNHM" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="3LFVGOBZ4JGZXLVNOIISFQVNHM" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Bump up your protein&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="T57RJ4CAXJH4HDK6EDJEMNXNUE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Protein is core to building muscle and, even more so, maintaining it, Klingbeil says. The National Academy of Sciences recommends that adults eat 0.36 grams of protein per pound of body weight per day. But an &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s12603-019-1174-1" target="_blank"&gt;analysis of data from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey&lt;/a&gt; found that 42 percent of men and 50 percent of women over age 70 don’t get that much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZBDPN3YSSJAXLD2WTHH6OSUXA4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Some experts recommend even more protein for older adults to compensate for muscle loss and the fact that building new muscle becomes harder with age, Klingbeil says. Aim for 0.45 to 0.59 grams per pound per day — that’s 72 to 94 grams for a 160-pound person. (But if you have kidney disease, check with your doctor about your protein intake because too much can tax your kidneys.) Dietitians generally recommend spreading protein throughout the day because that may help your body absorb it better, but Klingbeil says that getting enough is the most important thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YDDEDAEALRBLDEND2P6Q6IUGTA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The source of protein isn’t super important for building muscle, says Travis Masterson, the principal investigator of the Health, Ingestive Behavior, and Technology Laboratory at Pennsylvania State University. &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/healthy-eating/how-red-meat-can-fit-into-a-healthy-diet-a3360518260/" target="_blank"&gt;Animal foods&lt;/a&gt; tend to have more per serving than plant sources. But for other aspects of your health, it’s best to get at least some of your protein from plants, such as beans, nuts and tofu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IRDQYIYNQRADVN33ET622RPCSA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A plant-based diet that includes mostly whole foods is good for your heart and brain, and it lowers your risk of certain cancers. “It also appears to be gentler on the kidneys than a diet high in animal protein as we age,” says Judy Lester, a clinical dietitian at the University of North Carolina Health Care System in Chapel Hill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GH2FAXJWWBAZRD7IUXPWZ2N2JM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There are 20 grams of protein in a cup of tofu; about 18 grams in a cup of lentils, white beans or edamame; 8 grams in a cup of quinoa or whole-wheat pasta; and 7 grams in an ounce of peanuts. Beef and chicken breast have about 24 grams in 3 ounces. A 5.5-ounce serving of plain nonfat &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/yogurt/healthy-yogurts-that-taste-great-too-a1114386696/" target="_blank"&gt;Greek yogurt&lt;/a&gt; has 16 grams, a cup of low-fat milk has about 8 grams, and an egg has 6 grams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="ZK4XCWDUMFAJ3ITFWG4HWXFO3Q" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="ZK4XCWDUMFAJ3ITFWG4HWXFO3Q" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Get enough calories&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BSOR7IS6WZDDDOGXPMEKFMTYPM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“If you’re not getting enough calories, your body will break down muscle,” Klingbeil says. Calorie needs vary based on height, weight, gender and activity levels, but eating somewhere between 1,800 to 2,400 calories per day is probably adequate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="TWVS7NA4JNGBXOYJQIGUBT24JE" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="TWVS7NA4JNGBXOYJQIGUBT24JE" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Choose quality carbs&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4HLP2AP2TNAFNKCC5MXNOHELNY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Carbohydrates fuel your muscles, so they can help you feel stronger. The best sources are whole grains, &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/canned-foods/best-tasting-canned-beans-a6489833691/" target="_blank"&gt;legumes&lt;/a&gt;, fruits and vegetables. Refined carbs like white bread, crackers, soda and desserts can boost short-term energy, but unlike high-quality carbs, they don’t have the advantage of being rich in fiber and other nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N6ONHD5KMVEHBAJ6XW6J6I33BQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Research shows that fiber may help build or preserve muscle mass, possibly because it increases the level of healthy bacteria in the gut that produce short-chain fatty acids. These compounds are involved in muscle development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="3FNHAQMUYVBQBHPGNURK34JYWY" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="3FNHAQMUYVBQBHPGNURK34JYWY" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Check your vitamin D&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WWMN4HG46ZHJHCLGQCGQ5CM52Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Some studies show a connection between vitamin D levels and muscle strength, although it’s not clear whether getting more vitamin D from your diet or a supplement will help you become stronger. Still, we know that the vitamin is important for bone, muscle and overall health, Klingbeil says, so getting the recommended 20 micrograms (800 IU) per day is smart. New guidelines from the Endocrine Society don’t recommend regular vitamin D testing for healthy adults, so ask your doctor what’s right for you given your particular health picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="KRXJGKPPORF3LMBN4RULB7XRXE" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="KRXJGKPPORF3LMBN4RULB7XRXE" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Add omega-3s&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BKKYM6XZBJHNRFONVSUNDH5PLU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;These fats, found in fish, may help protect from normal age-related declines in muscle. In a 2020 &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7071242/" target="_blank"&gt;review of research on sarcopenia published in the journal Nutrients&lt;/a&gt;, researchers noted that eating fatty fish was linked to increases in muscle mass and better performance on muscle-strength tests. Other studies have shown similar benefits for people who took omega-3 supplements, but the science isn’t conclusive. For now, aim to eat two servings of fatty fish like salmon or sardines per week, which is the American Heart Association’s recommendation for heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="3OMT3BM3TREURCJBIUXZG7Y4DE" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="3OMT3BM3TREURCJBIUXZG7Y4DE" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Stay hydrated&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AWSQBKKSIZGC7FGU5ZXELUELOU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Getting plenty of fluids is important for overall health and preserving muscle, Lester says. Muscle is 70 to 75 percent water, and insufficient water content inside muscle cells has been linked to changes in muscle strength and the ability to do daily activities, as well as a higher risk of frailty in older adults. Drinking water is obviously helpful, but you can also get fluids from other healthy beverages (coffee, tea and milk, for instance) and eating fruits, vegetables and soup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="27RN3PBZ6ZHQXEEXMNXSKMZB7I" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="27RN3PBZ6ZHQXEEXMNXSKMZB7I" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Ask your doctor about creatine&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZGWRCV2EIRAR3EQS6T5VAC7NGU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;This compound in muscle tissue is found in meat and seafood, and your body also makes it. But taking it in pill or powder form may be helpful for some people. “Creatine in the muscle is used for producing energy, especially in that initial onset of a contraction, the first one to two seconds,” Masterson says. “The more creatine you can get into the muscle, the more effective that first bit of contraction is going to be.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VQTOXJB2GBHX5KYLJJ4B2OO6CE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Creatine is often used by athletes looking to improve exercise performance, but some research suggests that older adults may benefit from it, too. A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6518405/" target="_blank"&gt;review published in 2019 in the Journal of Clinical Medicine&lt;/a&gt; found that creatine — in combination with regular &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/dumbbells/strength-training-using-adjustable-dumbbells-a3150717795/" target="_blank"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt; — may help reduce the risk of sarcopenia and falls. (Muscle is important for balance, too.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XEJOXQIGZZGEVKU4PSOFP4NWDQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“I’m pretty anti-supplement overall,” Masterson says. “But creatine is one where there are no known side effects, and it’s pretty cheap. Will it drastically change someone? No, but it could give you more energy for exercise or even provide more oomph as you’re trying to get out of a chair.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="IE7DIX3Y5JHS7GHE2JWWDYXWM4" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="IE7DIX3Y5JHS7GHE2JWWDYXWM4" data-testid="article-header"&gt;The importance of strength training&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UIXS4T3OTJG6TG26T7KBGMDTCY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There’s no getting around the fact that exercise is crucial for your muscles. But that doesn’t mean you have to take up bodybuilding to get stronger in your 60s, 70s and beyond. Activities like walking and simple &lt;a href="http://cr.org/4strength" target="_blank"&gt;strength-training&lt;/a&gt; moves such as chair squats (repeatedly sitting and standing) and wall push-ups — and just being active and moving more in general — are a good way to preserve muscle and keep bones and joints strong, Masterson says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KVHCJMREWFCDJEQKMKIJQX6PQM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If you want to go further, you can find weight-focused classes that use dumbbells or other simple equipment at gyms or community recreation centers, or online. (Check out the &lt;a href="http://youtube.com/@nihaging" target="_blank"&gt;workout videos from the National Institute on Aging&lt;/a&gt;.) Try to time your workouts so you’ll be having a meal or snack within a few hours afterward, Masterson says. Both exercise and eating protein stimulate muscle development, so combining them will lead to greater effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p id="MX42FHQYCNA47FRI3ZJH4W7M4Q" class="wpds-c-esEUdQ wpds-c-esEUdQ-hqvHjm-isBold-false wpds-c-esEUdQ-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="MX42FHQYCNA47FRI3ZJH4W7M4Q" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Copyright 2024, Consumer Reports Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NGIOUE72HRGJHDJS2MZ36HBWDU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Consumer Reports is an independent, nonprofit organization that works side by side with consumers to create a fairer, safer and healthier world. CR does not endorse products or services, and does not accept advertising. Read more at &lt;a href="http://www.consumerreports.org/"&gt;ConsumerReports.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:40:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQN1ZsUFQ2a0ZRS2luMmtFTXlzUjN3M0RJZ0hvYVdOM2QzTTdXc0JrdTRiNDFHZFpUcGhHWG95THJnNmJ3U3RudHh2Wl8xQ2ZyNlhwTThTQnJocG9FM1MxdUlHdmIzbXRIc3l2WXU3cjZVRE95ZlRzUUNhY254eHpYMUt1Y3FQMWpJSEJYWGdB</guid></item><item><title>随着疫情蔓延，美国麻疹病例达到33年来的新高--《华盛顿邮报》 | U.S. measles cases reach 33-year record high as outbreaks spread - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE9FRG16Q1huYnZOeHE5ZGVlcUtaMmx4M09NeFlkdERTLWhZa1NnMngyWTNXR1ZwV3VyRVRCRHZoU0M1b21QQVF5Sk5pSFlPU201dkxRZ0pTSGh4VE5rVC02UzhVXzJFdlRVQmtoQ3RaRVg5YTI3Ul92b0hsRjV2U00?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TUMTDIR4INADZPOTBGMDJGGIEE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The United States has reached its highest annual measles case tally in 33 years, hitting at least 1,277 confirmed cases across 38 states and the District of Columbia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YUX2HRFOKRD4LHDZVLA5RJ7JVY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The milestone marks a public health reversal in defeating a highly contagious, vaccine-preventable disease as the anti-vaccine movement gains strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4BNSIPRQORC35LFHUYC3YFFHZY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The nation surpassed infections reported in&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2019/04/29/us-officials-say-measles-cases-hit-year-record/" target="_blank"&gt; 2019,&lt;/a&gt; reaching the largest number of cases since &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;1992,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;when officials recorded more than&lt;a href="https://washpost.arcpublishing.com/ellipsis/#!/edit/GL3L5OPSSBENDLNKJIFCV42LDA/"&gt; 2,100&lt;/a&gt; infections, according to &lt;a href="https://cori.centerforhealthsecurity.org/resources/measles-outbreak-response" target="_blank"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; published Friday&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from the Johns Hopkins University Center for Outbreak Response Innovation (CORI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IIUQXZCV4JFTVEOR62HTLW6Y6M" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“It’s devastating,” said Claire Hannan, executive director of the Association of Immunization Managers, a national organization of state and local immunization officials. “We worked so hard to eliminate the threat of measles and to keep it at bay.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CTOXBKSGEVDB7ML4D6BVYMZNMI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Authorities said at least &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;155 people have been hospitalized &lt;/a&gt;and three people have died of measles-related complications this year. The dead include &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/06/measles-texas-death-outbreak-vaccine/" target="_blank"&gt;two otherwise healthy children &lt;/a&gt;in Texas and a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/03/06/measles-death-outbreak-new-mexico/" target="_blank"&gt;man in New Mexico,&lt;/a&gt; all of who were unvaccinated. In contrast, only three measles deaths were reported between 2001 and 2024, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CCMWQ5NIWJDQJDORYT3SBJ2MGI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;About 92 percent of measles cases in 2025 were in people who were either unvaccinated or whose vaccination status was unknown, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JP66LFKCVJEJ3NXF6S7SMPA6BA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Data from the CDC does not yet reflect the record as it is updated weekly on Wednesdays, while the Johns Hopkins’ site validates data every weekday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DZDKRATFOBFJBI2IFXIQR54DSI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The largest outbreak has been in West Texas, where officials have recorded more than 750 cases since late January and believe the true toll is much higher. Data shows that outbreak has slowed, but that it has spread to surrounding states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="B2DIVDW6KFCYXNO7ZIEHLZR6XA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Unrelated clusters of cases emerged elsewhere, usually originating with an unvaccinated person who traveled abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-image subtype-StaffPhoto" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="A26FIGIMSJDAJPPLUTIFOKI2GU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Measles was &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html"&gt;officially eliminated from the U.S. in 2000&lt;/a&gt; with high vaccination coverage&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and rapid outbreak response. Cases still popped up periodically. But in recent years, large outbreaks with 50 or more cases have become more frequent, especially in close-knit communities with low vaccination coverage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RJ7C6RHGGVFQHOTG3PCLXJC72Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Public health experts say the U.S. is on track to lose the elimination status if there is continuous spread of linked measles cases for more than 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XLTSLTOXNVGERIZ6ERL3M45I7E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“It’s a harbinger of things to come,” said Eric Ball, a pediatrician who heads the California chapter of the American Academy of Pediatrics. “Once we see a resurgence of measles, we know that other diseases are going to come behind it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="Q3LXJSWL35CPDLDUML4KRDPAYQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="Q3LXJSWL35CPDLDUML4KRDPAYQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Consequences of vaccine distrust&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XSE4UUHLJRBB3LGE2BMHSPE4BE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/antivaxxers-go-viral-in-communities-battling-measles/2019/05/20/a476417c-78d7-11e9-bd25-c989555e7766_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;Misinformation &lt;/a&gt;about the safety and effectiveness of the measles, mumps and rubella vaccine fueled the 1,274 cases recorded in 2019, according to public health officials and researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="S4CLA7EOU5DR7HJMGOJRBNTBX4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The outbreaks that year were concentrated in &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/new-york-city-vaccination-order-shines-spotlight-on-insular-jewish-community/2019/04/11/fd59b098-5bc3-11e9-a00e-050dc7b82693_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;ultra-Orthodox Jewish communities &lt;/a&gt;in New York, highlighting the risks in tight-knit communities where vaccine distrust takes hold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BF737NVPJVAWND3BFIAPWMHRO4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Confidence in public health measures, especially vaccines, has fallen since then, and is sharply divided along political lines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="23IOQE4B5FAJ3HP7EIHS7OJ4ZQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The national rate for MMR vaccination among kindergartners was slightly above 95 percent in 2019, the level of community protection scientists say is needed to prevent measles outbreaks. But that rate is now &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/73/wr/mm7341a3.htm" target="_blank"&gt;under 93 percent and falling, &lt;/a&gt;according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="O7SW2JKJONADNMGKBBI7MJXPEI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Even in states with high vaccination coverage, pockets of unvaccinated people tend to cluster together. Measles is so contagious that a person without immunity exposed to the virus is highly likely to be infected and to spread it days before they develop symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="W7TW4BAVEVBL3OYR7NCKRCUOFI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A recent study showed that if U.S. vaccination rates continue to decline, the nation could &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/24/measles-cases-deaths-vaccine-rates-rfk-jr/" target="_blank"&gt;face millions&lt;/a&gt; of cases over the next 25 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WZGOXF73QZBBXGJ3QVHGVPFSVE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A&lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/poll-amid-multi-state-measles-outbreak-79-of-americans-support-routine-childhood-vaccine-requirements/?utm_source=chatgpt.com" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/poll-amid-multi-state-measles-outbreak-79-of-americans-support-routine-childhood-vaccine-requirements/?utm_source=chatgpt.com" target="_blank"&gt;poll conducted in March&lt;/a&gt; by the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health and the de Beaumont Foundation found that 79 percent of adults say parents should be required to have children vaccinated against preventable diseases such as measles, mumps and rubella to attend school. Support was stronger among Democrats, 90 percent, than among Republicans, 68 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TNYGNRFW7ZEVVGVR4TEPR4TFN4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Five years after the start of the coronavirus pandemic, less than half the public says it has at least some confidence in federal health agencies to carry out core public health responsibilities, according to a &lt;a href="https://connect.kff.org/e3t/Ctc/RB+113/c1ThL04/VVK5501sYLjFW6bKZXX6WMnh3W5j5c_V5wcn3yN1vWRrn5nR32W5BWr2F6lZ3mWW8wtK6h4-m88gW5SkMMf5MZX2XW1VyVdt2bfDssW7GLKwD7mRPV9W4KnxR68MGwJCN8hDdQ5SWLx2VJVgQK2wk2NJW5bq1Ds3vKdmQW1LXb9x8GMkknW4xb2pD7ysxY8W4P3Qgz8JKw-kW6zzrjG19ZL7gW4v9zXY6Rq2WSN67wxcV16S16W7BwWvs6vYcVmVxd6N87Y9YJ6N2QJRGtBWsRNW4nTtxj8BsCmxN1fkBfzT84w-W1FqQW25PGwsMW5QTqPf1GJKwKW7jj4y97HrfG5W1kcNjg5q16PPW2bVG5j8_Lxz2W3N6slZ5WJtHnVD1j2H1K4V2wW4pj-_f7SvTjlW7wb13P3NJ2sgW1PqX3b5JgWt1W6_5CBH2yyXdsW66Pvl62kSpVvW8f2Wll26Q712W5ZZqV_1tTdxwW2QNyz65NGMxQf60bwLb04" target="_blank"&gt;poll conducted in April by the health care think tank KFF. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RZM4SUND7BGQ7CNKHDBICERWOY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a longtime anti-vaccine activist who ascended to&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;be the top U.S. health official, has offered &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/05/11/vaccines-measles-rfk-jr-health/" target="_blank"&gt;mixed messages&lt;/a&gt; about measles and the vaccine to prevent it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="K654CNPIJBBKBCQZTP2PWH3UZY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;He initially &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/02/26/measles-texas-unvaccinated-death/" target="_blank"&gt;downplayed the seriousness of the Texas outbreak&lt;/a&gt; after the first child died, saying: “We have measles outbreaks every year.” He accompanied his calls for vaccination with caveats, raising concerns about the shots that public health experts called unfounded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LV76A2NLSNAYLKSPNXKGMQBLDY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Nola Jean Ernest, a pediatrician in rural southeastern Alabama, said many of her patients trust others who share their political views more than her when it comes to vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6JWCF3D2DRAJZAHY3NJ23KB5ZA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;She now sees patients who vaccinated older children refuse to vaccinate their infants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Y7GMRUGIXJBOVMSKM3WLY6Z7CI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“I’ve had several conversations in the last few months where they will say, ‘We still trust you, we just don’t trust the vaccines,’” Ernest said recently. “That really breaks my heart.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="YBUTKDDX4RAPNOFA4MYXHY3WOQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="YBUTKDDX4RAPNOFA4MYXHY3WOQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Anatomy of an outbreak&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UVIT3NA7TVGBVMFBJO4UKLGGFQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In Texas, infections in late January &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/03/02/measles-outbreak-texas-vaccine-hesitancy-death/" target="_blank"&gt;spread quickly&lt;/a&gt; within Gaines County’s Mennonite community, some of whom educate their children at home or at private schools without vaccine mandates. The county had among the lowest kindergarten MMR vaccination rates in Texas, about 82 percent, according to state immunization data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3NCTWUJSXZFCRCVV32SWLU6C7Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Public health officials said they faced challenges in controlling the outbreak because many people were not getting tested or vaccinated for measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NN22J4SY3JCPDCSRLNQUPAFR5E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Anti-vaccine groups mobilized quickly on the ground. Many Mennonite families turned to a prominent anti-vaccine doctor who offered unproven alternative treatments. Kennedy praised that doctor and his methods in a visit to the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BDWEDEWYRRFYZGSKW2LYVZFBVU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Children’s Health Defense, an anti-vaccine group founded by Kennedy, interviewed the parents of a 6-year-old girl who died of measles, blaming her death on medical error rather than vaccination status. The organization did not immediately return a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3SJMB7YJJZD7ZDWLLHZA2AGQ3E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Eventually, 36 Texas counties reported measles cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N6T7LSAV65CHRFIEKMGDUWUMIA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Young adults from El Paso who work in oil fields close to Gaines County were among those infected this spring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SUPIOULXYBB5BKAAFLLXLP75FA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;El Paso went from five cases to 53 in a month, said Hector Ocaranza, director of the city and county health authority. Ocaranza said his community was vulnerable because a growing number of young adults, listening to what they see and hear on social media, are not getting vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LDTO4BBLMBGTDPMXKMILHNWRMU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lara Anton, a spokeswoman for the Texas Health Department, said last week that the reporting of new measles cases has slowed, crediting rising population&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;immunity from infections and increased vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2AZ7MRVB3BEOBKQHVIRIWQM5ZQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But the outbreak is not over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YZSSD6VMTRFNPM2JZOZ5FLWQNU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Transmission is continuing in Gaines County, as well as Lamar County, in northeast Texas bordering Oklahoma, according to health department data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AU7ROGVAHFERHIPMEVWFJNLIQQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In Chihuahua, Mexico, which borders Texas and New Mexico, a child who visited Texas in February started a large measles outbreak that now exceeds 2,400 cases and eight deaths as of last week, according to &lt;a href="https://www.paho.org/en/documents/epidemiological-update-measles-americas-region-1-july-2025" target="_blank"&gt;data &lt;/a&gt;from the Pan American Health Organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="RRL4D7GJDNALVFZ4QZEUZ5QSR4" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="RRL4D7GJDNALVFZ4QZEUZ5QSR4" data-testid="article-header"&gt;A costly disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KYL3ETR64ZE3RPCKSW3TRXC2E4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Measles outbreaks require vast personnel, time, dollars and messaging, public health experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AQDCXNBYX5FEXEMX3VUKX2GOPA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The 2019 outbreak cost New York City $8.4 million with 550 staff involved in the response, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1912514" target="_blank"&gt;2020 report &lt;/a&gt;in the New England Journal of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TSREL5YMSRAVDBES2XTEOGMAWI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Funding for state and local public health agencies, including immunization programs, has been slashed after increasing during the pandemic. Public health workers have been laid off because of &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/01/hhs-senior-leaders-put-on-leave-nih/" target="_blank"&gt;widespread budget cuts &lt;/a&gt;across the federal health agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WQFEDRCAMZGMDF5EJYH4RWH4VM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Because of the decreased funding, Texas&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;had to &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/16/texas-measles-response-funding-cuts/" target="_blank"&gt;pull resources&lt;/a&gt; and staff from other parts of its health department to respond to the outbreak, David Sugerman, a senior CDC scientist, &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/02/20/cdc-vaccine-advisory-panel-meeting-postponed/" target="_blank"&gt;told a committee&lt;/a&gt; of agency vaccine advisers in April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QUFY5QQ2J5FWXFMCBZTUEIWMBY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In Dallas, which has had one measles case this year, health officials had to lay off 16 immunization staff because of federal cuts, said&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Philip Huang, director of the county’s &lt;a href="https://www.dallascounty.org/departments/dchhs/" target="_blank"&gt;health and human services &lt;/a&gt;department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BTAMU3QEIVBTHJKMUIGYBGZ5LU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“The fact that this is occurring at the same time that we are seeing more measles cases in Texas than we have seen in more than 30 years makes absolutely no sense,” Huang said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 10:04:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE9FRG16Q1huYnZOeHE5ZGVlcUtaMmx4M09NeFlkdERTLWhZa1NnMngyWTNXR1ZwV3VyRVRCRHZoU0M1b21QQVF5Sk5pSFlPU201dkxRZ0pTSGh4VE5rVC02UzhVXzJFdlRVQmtoQ3RaRVg5YTI3Ul92b0hsRjV2U00</guid></item><item><title>新英格兰正在经历多年来最糟糕的蜱虫季节之一--《波士顿环球报》 | New England is seeing one of its worst tick seasons in years - The Boston Globe</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxOX3NST2hpbnF4c19IRWdxZW8xd2VXb25fM0pVd3FrSE8xUTFwTk0wMnRSQmtYa2dvQ2NJUVdOZElVWVNwaWlPZTI2UWhFWjRTaHpyOS1ZR0ZPWHE2dUNXazlyRjdoZHlTV0YwWmJWN0lGb29OQ2VMcWNZNldyd01fTmVxbll4RDM2SVVyZHlB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;New Englanders are used to dealing with a vast assortment of ticks, including Lone Star ticks, deer ticks that carry Lyme disease, and American dog ticks that can transmit Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever. But this season is shaping up to be a particularly bad one, with a surge of tick-borne diseases and tick exposures across the country, especially in the Northeast. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;In June, visits to emergency rooms for tick bites reached their highest levels in at least five years in New England and other nearby states, according to data from the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/data-research/facts-stats/tick-bite-data-tracker.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/data-research/facts-stats/tick-bite-data-tracker.html"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. Last month, 233 out of 100,000 ER visits in the Northeast were for tick bites, nearly double the national average of 118. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The trend is similar in Massachusetts. According to monthly records published by the state’s department of public health, &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/lists/monthly-tick-borne-disease-reports#2025-" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mass.gov/lists/monthly-tick-borne-disease-reports#2025-"&gt;more than 0.6 percent&lt;/a&gt; of visits to an emergency department in May were for tick exposure, up from around 0.4 percent from 2022 to 2024. Visits typically peak in July. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Massachusetts State Epidemiologist Dr. Catherine Brown said that although the data doesn’t capture visits to urgent care and primary care providers for tick exposure, it points to a real increase in interactions between ticks and humans in the state. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“This year is definitely an outlier for us,” Brown said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Thomas Mather, director of the University of Rhode Island’s Center for Vector-Borne Diseases, said that higher levels of tick-borne diseases in New England are mostly caused by higher numbers of blacklegged, or deer tick, nymphs. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The nymphs are around the size of a poppy seed, and about 20 percent of them in the New England region carry Lyme, Mather said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;They thrive in humid weather. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It’s not related to how warm it is in the winter … if it’s dry in the early spring when they first emerge, they start dying,” Mather said. “Whenever there were low-humidity episodes early in the season in late May and early June, we always had fewer ticks and fewer disease cases.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;All in all, New England is seeing more humidity in the spring and summer now compared to the previous two decades, said Ken Mahan, the Globe’s lead meteorologist.&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;This is a direct result of a warming atmosphere because warmer temperatures hold more moisture. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“When dew points push above 65, that’s when a big change in available moisture can be felt,” said Mahan. “[There has been an] increasing trend in the number of 70-degree dew point days across Boston over the years.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Deer tick populations are also positively correlated with the populations of small rodents and deer, the animals that serve as their most important food sources.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Mather said that the migration of Lone Star ticks, which were formerly common only in the South, over the past five years has been the biggest change in the trend of tick-borne diseases in New England. Mather runs an &lt;a href="https://web.uri.edu/tickencounter/tickspotters/submit/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://web.uri.edu/tickencounter/tickspotters/submit/"&gt;online project called TickSpotter&lt;/a&gt; where people across the country can send in photos of ticks they encounter so that his team of scientists can identify what kind of tick it is. Data from TickSpotter showed a more than 300 percent increase in people encountering these ticks in the past three years. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Rhode Island and Southeastern Massachusetts are right on the edge of the northward expansion of these ticks … Martha’s Vineyard and Narragansett Bay are completely infested with them,” Mather said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Allison Cameron Parry, a professional bodybuilder and mother of two who lives on Martha’s Vineyard, said that almost everyone in her family has Alpha-gal. After giving up meat and dairy, she has had to work harder to supplement those nutrients, which are necessary for her athletic training. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Cameron Parry also said she was worried about her 3-year-old son playing outside. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Long grass literally gives me anxiety … We use a natural spray in our yard, because I have a young child. Unfortunately, the smaller the child, the bigger the risk, because they don’t know to stay out of the bush,” Cameron Parry said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;At a virtual panel held by the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health last week, experts from Harvard and Boston University spoke about preventing tick-borne diseases. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Richard Pollack, senior environmental public health officer at Harvard University, recommended that people treat their clothes with permethrin, an EPA-registered tick repellent derived from an ingredient&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;found in chrysanthemums. Pollack also advised people to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/after-a-tick-bite/index.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/after-a-tick-bite/index.html"&gt;pull ticks off of their skin&lt;/a&gt; as soon as they notice them, because ticks attached for 24 to 36 hours can transmit the infection that causes Lyme disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“You don’t necessarily need to go to the emergency room to have somebody pull the tick off. You might be sitting for six hours, in some cases, before you’re actually seen,” Pollack said. “So just pull the tick off, save it, and then you can delve into what it was later.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Dr. Daniel Solomon, infectious disease specialist at Mass General Brigham, recommends that people take the antibiotic doxycycline within 72 hours of removing a tick that was attached to their skin. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“By the book, the CDC would say that the tick needs to be attached for 36 hours or more [for a patient to take the antibiotic], but we don’t know when ticks attach,” Solomon said. “So if there’s a tick attached, it’s plausible that it could have been on there for a day or more, so take a single dose of doxycycline.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Brown, the state epidemiologist,&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;said the increase in tick exposure should not discourage people from enjoying the outdoors. She recommended people use tick repellents, wear light-colored, long-sleeved clothing so it’s easier to spot and remove ticks, and put their clothes in the dryer on high heat after returning home to kill ticks that are hard to see.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;For pets, Pollack said that there were oral medications for dogs as well as topical ointments that can be applied at the back of the neck once a month to prevent tick bites. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Patrick and Lily Marvin of Topsfield have three golden retrievers and have noticed more ticks on their dogs this summer when they go for hikes in Beverly. Two summers ago in Nantucket, one of the dogs, Kevin, contracted Lyme disease despite wearing a medicated collar. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“He was lethargic, didn’t want to eat, and would cry whenever we gave him antibiotics,” Patrick said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;He has since recovered, and the Marvins have been proactive about giving their dogs chewable tablets to keep them safe from ticks. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The speakers at the panel also noted that there are vaccines in the works to fight tick-borne diseases. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/about/lyme-disease-vaccine.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Lyme disease vaccine developed&lt;/a&gt; by Valneva and Pfizer is in late-stage clinical trials. The University of Massachusetts Medical School’s MassBiologics has also developed an antibody designed to be used as pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) for Lyme disease, but human trials haven’t begun yet. A Lyme disease vaccine called LYMERix had been approved by the FDA in 1998 but was discontinued in 2002 because of a lack of consumer demand. There isn’t a prophylaxis being developed for Alpha-gal yet, though &lt;a href="https://che.engin.umich.edu/2024/08/12/tick-borne-red-meat-allergy-prevented-in-mice-through-new-nanoparticle-treatment/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://che.engin.umich.edu/2024/08/12/tick-borne-red-meat-allergy-prevented-in-mice-through-new-nanoparticle-treatment/"&gt;University of Michigan scientists&lt;/a&gt; tested a nanoparticle treatment that successfully reduced allergies in mice bitten by Lone Star ticks. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;This is welcome news to McCormack. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Ticks are scary because they’re so small and they carry such life-altering diseases,” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Angela Mathew can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:angela.mathew@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;angela.mathew@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 10:02:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOX3NST2hpbnF4c19IRWdxZW8xd2VXb25fM0pVd3FrSE8xUTFwTk0wMnRSQmtYa2dvQ2NJUVdOZElVWVNwaWlPZTI2UWhFWjRTaHpyOS1ZR0ZPWHE2dUNXazlyRjdoZHlTV0YwWmJWN0lGb29OQ2VMcWNZNldyd01fTmVxbll4RDM2SVVyZHlB</guid></item><item><title>更有效、更合法的大麻将一些人送往医院：纽约市中心在急诊就诊中处于领先地位- Syracuse.com | More potent and legal cannabis sends some to hospital: Central NY leads state in ER visits - Syracuse.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizwFBVV95cUxQZENvd0p3eDl3OV9vWi1ab0V5eHRaeWN6bktfUjJFa1IxSVVBSUVpdWV6am91UU9KZXhoc3lzRFFxMUh5LWJ4X0VsUURrdFBZVnNST3k3Z09TWU8xRldEZnR2VEJtOGhSUHhBLTdNOVg2ck93anpiV0tDbDhtVDJyQWN4NzBENllka1dKV1YtTWgtQWF2Y2wtb09INXZHUVMtOWF3S2licVktbzYzWUdhcWZLTFZMN05pc1hrR1gwLVhKZ0hha29hYlBURDNKLUHSAeMBQVVfeXFMT3dFTmZudFRpRmU4RDNySkh0UVlsTHhOVUFxNk5QZmhnUUI4SDRBMHlwR3otMm5FRldZemtKcFByV3RCVWc5TTFZX2Nsd3BiMzUxVlEwa29mSXNOWVZqUlV4OTBYbGs4aDFoR0RPc2lPNWdVc2MtbG9POVpCV0d0V1I2T2JzeWVidkNMRE5pY3duZF9mUGhoaUhsU0hmUmVkS1RDcmg2RFdDMzI1ek56TmtHMjU0ejFKcjlxb0hfWnd1elFhVlNrT0g3VXNGeU9uRDZsWktIcUJPU3dzb2t2cHI5aTg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="arc-COY5EMNYQJF6VOVT6F3YA5HSLM" class="article h-entry" data-type="article"&gt;&lt;div class="multimedia-main"&gt;&lt;figure class="article__image"&gt;&lt;div class="article__image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source media="(max-width: 500px)" srcset="https://www.syracuse.com/resizer/v2/JG32KNUPFVCTRJA6PSZNCP2CZE.jpg?auth=99c1bfe32c06b174eef0935633ddd696e4e62ffe7acd6655177ae96fb04170c5&amp;amp;width=500&amp;amp;quality=90 500w"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="https://www.syracuse.com/resizer/v2/JG32KNUPFVCTRJA6PSZNCP2CZE.jpg?auth=99c1bfe32c06b174eef0935633ddd696e4e62ffe7acd6655177ae96fb04170c5&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;quality=90 800w"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://www.syracuse.com/resizer/v2/JG32KNUPFVCTRJA6PSZNCP2CZE.jpg?auth=99c1bfe32c06b174eef0935633ddd696e4e62ffe7acd6655177ae96fb04170c5&amp;amp;width=1280&amp;amp;quality=90 1280w"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.syracuse.com/resizer/v2/JG32KNUPFVCTRJA6PSZNCP2CZE.jpg?auth=99c1bfe32c06b174eef0935633ddd696e4e62ffe7acd6655177ae96fb04170c5&amp;amp;width=500&amp;amp;quality=90" sizes="50vw" fetchpriority="high" loading="eager" alt="Cannabis injuries addressed by Upstate Medical doctor" decoding="async" class="article__image-content"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="article__image-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="article__mm-image-caption-text"&gt;Dr. Deborah Mann, Assistant Professor of Emergency Medicine at Upstate Medical University, has seen scores of people in the ER after consuming too much cannabis. Photo taken on Wednesday, June 11, 2025. (N. Scott Trimble | strimble@syracuse.com)&lt;span class="article__mm-image-credit"&gt;N. Scott Trimble | strimble@syracuse.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   paywall"&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XMRLOOQGJRB53AHD4HPVWPDXOA"&gt;Syracuse, NY – Since New York legalized recreational cannabis, emergency rooms are treating thousands more people for endless vomiting, a racing heart and belief they are dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HPAREY5TGRFILLB3HF5U3P3H34"&gt;Cannabis-related ER visits statewide topped 135,000 in 2023, nearly double the cases from before legalization two years earlier. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content-blocker-piano " id="content-blocker-piano"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Syracuse.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizwFBVV95cUxQZENvd0p3eDl3OV9vWi1ab0V5eHRaeWN6bktfUjJFa1IxSVVBSUVpdWV6am91UU9KZXhoc3lzRFFxMUh5LWJ4X0VsUURrdFBZVnNST3k3Z09TWU8xRldEZnR2VEJtOGhSUHhBLTdNOVg2ck93anpiV0tDbDhtVDJyQWN4NzBENllka1dKV1YtTWgtQWF2Y2wtb09INXZHUVMtOWF3S2licVktbzYzWUdhcWZLTFZMN05pc1hrR1gwLVhKZ0hha29hYlBURDNKLUHSAeMBQVVfeXFMT3dFTmZudFRpRmU4RDNySkh0UVlsTHhOVUFxNk5QZmhnUUI4SDRBMHlwR3otMm5FRldZemtKcFByV3RCVWc5TTFZX2Nsd3BiMzUxVlEwa29mSXNOWVZqUlV4OTBYbGs4aDFoR0RPc2lPNWdVc2MtbG9POVpCV0d0V1I2T2JzeWVidkNMRE5pY3duZF9mUGhoaUhsU0hmUmVkS1RDcmg2RFdDMzI1ek56TmtHMjU0ejFKcjlxb0hfWnd1elFhVlNrT0g3VXNGeU9uRDZsWktIcUJPU3dzb2t2cHI5aTg</guid></item><item><title>专家无法忍受的10个更年期神话-《纽约时报》 | 10 Menopause Myths the Experts Can’t Stand - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMibEFVX3lxTE5HazVwWlBjeGdfUE1aVVdyOWh1VVZTRFduZllrR2diaXpZRUJsTnpIY3BSZ1BkUDBfUTBpbnZxd0s3MVFqdnp3cTROTVpFOVNQRUttRTRpdGdseDBwWDBfeG9Ia21ySm9DUHFaTw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 09:00:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibEFVX3lxTE5HazVwWlBjeGdfUE1aVVdyOWh1VVZTRFduZllrR2diaXpZRUJsTnpIY3BSZ1BkUDBfUTBpbnZxd0s3MVFqdnp3cTROTVpFOVNQRUttRTRpdGdseDBwWDBfeG9Ia21ySm9DUHFaTw</guid></item><item><title>脂肪肝在脸上出现的4种方式-印度时报 | 4 ways fatty liver disease can show up on your face - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi5gFBVV95cUxOQ2VjN0pZbm1WQU91Q29Ob1FmZFUyQ3c0ZFJlSE01N1J1ZDUtSnVsODhidW9HYkY5VUI0ZFg2TlZ3MVdNMzhjVTBSZWtzRmRmYWttRVFPcngwcTJpWDJ3OVRyMmtCMEZVZ0g1U2xlZVI2djVxU3JhNlJ5REhjMTVzekItbDJqNGdfVnBXeXlfb2plbEdETXdXd3pKY01UWE00OUFPWTgxZkdRN1ZRS25ibWZtVGNZTlFLSTA4U1NfZmhRc0Z2MGhwTEw3M1JiSFRGajhIRnNndUdubzcwWlctZ3Y5eUp1UdIB6wFBVV95cUxQTmV1Yk11U3ZLQXdUM0k0RFgxc09YLUkwQlZSbF9HbnFicDY4MTJ6QjVSNmlCN3JKR3dPam9FNjdMM0pSa1NDb1M2dnMzb2pSaGh3RTdraGVjR190bHREaFR1cW90VUNVMlJzbVZyTnBRN05fem9YTWEtbF9xRFhSdzN2YXZ4SHBOMUduQjhmZV9weTJWUk1NV3F5Smw5U0NkM2xZLVdGOGlsWVE1UENDRXVvenBDRGtLS1ZpUDZEekVTUHFWenpsZzdMSkRUX0c3QlV1VENoRGFTbk9wY0NnV3Z2SGZ3OFVlcXVz?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fatty liver disease, particularly Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease (NAFLD), is a growing health concern, affecting an estimated 30.2% of the world's population. Prevalence varies by region, with rates above 40% in the Americas and Southeast Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease (NAFLD)?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-alcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD) is a condition where excess fat builds up in the liver, not caused by heavy alcohol consumption. It's often linked to obesity, type 2 diabetes, and metabolic syndrome. NAFLD encompasses a spectrum of conditions, from simple fat buildup (NAFL) to more serious inflammation and scarring (NASH).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Often termed the "silent epidemic," NAFLD is often symptomless in its early stages. However, the liver’s strained function can manifest surprisingly on your face. Subtle signs like puffiness, discoloration, dryness, and rashes may seem cosmetic, but they often signal deeper metabolic or inflammatory processes. Recognizing early indicators of fatty liver disease allows you to read the warning signals and seek timely medical attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Puffiness and swelling around the face&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What you might notice:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A consistently swollen or bloated appearance – especially around the cheeks and under the eyes – sometimes referred to as “fluid retention puffiness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Why it matters:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; As liver function deteriorates, its ability to maintain proper protein synthesis and fluid balance diminishes. This results in capillary leakage and fluid buildup, causing puffiness, particularly around the eyes and cheeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Health note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; If puffiness persists despite normal sleep, low salt intake, and good hydration, consider checking liver function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Skin discoloration: Yellowing, dark circles, and spider veins&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Yellow tint (Jaundice)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A yellow hue in the skin or the whites of your eyes. This is known as jaundice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Underlying cause:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Bilirubin, a breakdown product of red blood cells, accumulates when the liver cannot process it effectively – a hallmark of advanced liver dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Dark circles and hyperpigmentation&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Persistent dark under‑eye circles or dusky patches, even with adequate rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Possible cause:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Toxin accumulation and impaired blood filtration due to liver strain can manifest as persistent dark circles. Insulin resistance – a common feature of NAFLD – can also cause acanthosis nigricans in skin folds like the neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Spider veins and rosacea&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Small red lines (spider angiomas) across the cheeks or nose, or facial redness that’s blotchy and persistent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Why it shows:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Impaired estrogen breakdown in liver disease increases blood flow to superficial vessels, causing spider veins. Additionally, inflammatory conditions like rosacea are linked to fatty liver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Acne, oiliness, and mouth rashes&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Unexpected adult acne, oilier skin, especially around the chin or jawline, and rashes or bumps around the mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Connection:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Acne and oily skin:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; When the liver’s detox and hormone regulation falter, androgen and toxin levels build up, leading to hormonal acne.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Perioral rash:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Chronic zinc deficiency – common in NAFLD – can trigger dermatitis around the mouth, visible as small fluid- or solid-filled bumps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Itching, dryness, and an itchy rash&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Constant itching or dryness on the face and facial skin rashes that don’t resolve with usual skincare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="82"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Medical insight:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Itching (pruritus) is often due to bile salt buildup when liver excretory function is compromised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dry red patches/rash:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Linked to both nutrient deficiencies and toxin retention. Zinc deficiency may also worsen skin dryness and itching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="89"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why your face reflects your liver:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The liver is our primary detox and metabolic organ. When overwhelmed – by fat, toxins, or insulin resistance – its inability to filter effectively shows externally. Facial skin, highly visible and sensitive, becomes an early signal. Recognizing these signs allows for proactive intervention through diet, exercise, and medical evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your face is more than the reflection of your beauty – it can forewarn about your liver. Listen to your skin’s signals, get evaluated, and embrace lifestyle changes early. Early recognition can prompt action – medical guidance, lifestyle adjustments, and targeted nutrition – that often reverses fatty liver and restores both internal health and skin vitality. So, next time you take a close look standing in front of the mirror, listen to your skin – it might be protecting your liver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="96"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt; This article is for informational purposes only and does not substitute professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult a qualified healthcare provider before making any decisions based on this content. If you experience persistent facial changes or health concerns, please seek medical attention promptly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="99"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="100"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;7 Ways to check for fatty liver at home&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="102"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="103"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5gFBVV95cUxOQ2VjN0pZbm1WQU91Q29Ob1FmZFUyQ3c0ZFJlSE01N1J1ZDUtSnVsODhidW9HYkY5VUI0ZFg2TlZ3MVdNMzhjVTBSZWtzRmRmYWttRVFPcngwcTJpWDJ3OVRyMmtCMEZVZ0g1U2xlZVI2djVxU3JhNlJ5REhjMTVzekItbDJqNGdfVnBXeXlfb2plbEdETXdXd3pKY01UWE00OUFPWTgxZkdRN1ZRS25ibWZtVGNZTlFLSTA4U1NfZmhRc0Z2MGhwTEw3M1JiSFRGajhIRnNndUdubzcwWlctZ3Y5eUp1UdIB6wFBVV95cUxQTmV1Yk11U3ZLQXdUM0k0RFgxc09YLUkwQlZSbF9HbnFicDY4MTJ6QjVSNmlCN3JKR3dPam9FNjdMM0pSa1NDb1M2dnMzb2pSaGh3RTdraGVjR190bHREaFR1cW90VUNVMlJzbVZyTnBRN05fem9YTWEtbF9xRFhSdzN2YXZ4SHBOMUduQjhmZV9weTJWUk1NV3F5Smw5U0NkM2xZLVdGOGlsWVE1UENDRXVvenBDRGtLS1ZpUDZEekVTUHFWenpsZzdMSkRUX0c3QlV1VENoRGFTbk9wY0NnV3Z2SGZ3OFVlcXVz</guid></item><item><title>一位培训师说，您所需要的只是您的体重和每天一分钟来建立健康的锻炼习惯-她的新锻炼挑战今天开始- Fit&amp;Well | A trainer says all you need is your bodyweight and one minute per day to build healthy exercise habits—her new workout challenge starts today - Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAJBVV95cUxQOFp3bXlDZy1fbFVKLW4tUGRUWEV1NFRSdVVNSEdDQ0lzME9scURndlhldjI1QXpfM2t2dDhYZ1doenFfUllPZWR1VlhoWHhkeHY0dlJwUC1Ta1RSYlhOQ0JPbTJEcURIZlVmUzZsZDJqVmcyWU9RNUk4ckZ5R1JPTVJ6MldtN2xXME9BdG1lV3dRRHRVT05aZHBUSWNNcmZqckxXQVpLSTJkdzNGTnNfcThnaTBtVC1sZjcyZUxLV0FkeWwxSHI5VDlrY0diMDZ4N3F6N3FBMllzN24yT0NnR3djcE1EM3ZYQzVtVURjaEdSUGZVT2dLbmdaV0JtaWdXTkVUb0dJeHR5YnljQ0VjbzNnNi1TT3hDc0RfZDdZV2FidHVU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Convenience and accessibility are two essential ingredients in any effective workout regimen, ensuring you’re able to stay the course and see long-term benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that’s exactly what online trainer Rachael Sacerdoti is serving up with her new 14-Day Mini Movement Challenge launching on Monday, July 7 on &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.instagram.com/itssosimple_rs" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.instagram.com/itssosimple_rs" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;her Instagram channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She’ll be sharing a quickfire workout every day for two weeks to help you build consistent, sustainable habits with nothing more than your bodyweight. Each routine takes just 60 seconds—and can be done while waiting for the kettle to boil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This 14-day challenge is perfect if you’re short on time but want to feel stronger, more energized and more in control of your day,” she tells &lt;em&gt;Fit&amp;amp;Well&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No gym. No equipment. Just you and one minute of movement.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One minute of daily exercise might not transform your physique and fitness overnight, but research suggests that even short bursts of vigorous movement can lead to serious long-term health results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's according to a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/59/5/316?rss=1" target="_blank" data-url="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/59/5/316?rss=1" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published earlier this year in the &lt;em&gt;British Journal of Sports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;, which found ultra-short doses of vigorous physical activity—between an average of 1.5 to 4 minutes a day—can be enough to halve cardiovascular risk in middle-aged women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-vPnb2YHgunXhpvV9FzfL46" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-vPnb2YHgunXhpvV9FzfL46 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-this-60-second-fitness-challenge-builds-good-habits"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How this 60-second fitness challenge builds good habits &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sacerdoti is keen to stress that this challenge isn’t about quick fixes and shortcuts. Instead, she says, it’s about consistency, confidence and momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Life is full. Most of us are juggling work, family and everything in between,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The idea of carving out 45 minutes for a workout can feel impossible some days. But movement doesn’t have to be all or nothing and this challenge is here to prove that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are multiple benefits, she adds, but primarily the challenge will build and reinforce healthy habits that you can sustain without relying on motivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“[Each workout will] also give your brain and body an instant energy and mood boost, while building confidence through movement repetition, helping you perfect your form.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day one features four moves: a squat to punch, jumping jacks, standing cross-body crunches and high knees. Perform each move for 15 seconds and you’re done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For added accountability, Sacerdoti encourages you to invite a friend or housemate to join you in the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As we’re all about keeping things simple, this challenge is here to help people move their bodies daily in a way that feels doable,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you can find just 60 seconds while your coffee brews, you can start building a habit that sticks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:22:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAJBVV95cUxQOFp3bXlDZy1fbFVKLW4tUGRUWEV1NFRSdVVNSEdDQ0lzME9scURndlhldjI1QXpfM2t2dDhYZ1doenFfUllPZWR1VlhoWHhkeHY0dlJwUC1Ta1RSYlhOQ0JPbTJEcURIZlVmUzZsZDJqVmcyWU9RNUk4ckZ5R1JPTVJ6MldtN2xXME9BdG1lV3dRRHRVT05aZHBUSWNNcmZqckxXQVpLSTJkdzNGTnNfcThnaTBtVC1sZjcyZUxLV0FkeWwxSHI5VDlrY0diMDZ4N3F6N3FBMllzN24yT0NnR3djcE1EM3ZYQzVtVURjaEdSUGZVT2dLbmdaV0JtaWdXTkVUb0dJeHR5YnljQ0VjbzNnNi1TT3hDc0RfZDdZV2FidHVU</guid></item><item><title>一位步行专家说，这是您每天保持健康的最少步数（远低于10,000步） - Fit&amp;Well | A walking expert says this is the minimum number of steps you should take every day to stay healthy (and it’s a lot lower than 10,000) - Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgJBVV95cUxQaE41b0F3a0F5VjJhUWNWOEY3aUtGZzJQeXREbmNsczBSWUJQMEpub2x0dDZXZUdhSmtkeFB1TWxiOVlXek9ZV3hVMm82LURrV2tkT1dSRDF3OWhmSHZ2ZEIwbmtrVldQdDlnNEdmNEh1QXowRUpJV3h6MmJPR2kzdEExQ01IWkRhekN2am1Ib2hVRTBpSUdGQXhnVUtZcjdxYUQ0ZzU5bm12ZEg0Vk5mQUpnNGtlOHVMMkF3aEJENEp2Y2t1VlBfOVJiZnZOaVRJbVJfQkd6NVF3Vkp4a045NmNoN0ZXZEpZbU5IYWo3bHRZVXpTSlhEOVQySk9YRWVTVXZWeHRn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all know that regular walking is good for us, but information around step count goals can sometimes be confusing. Most people have heard of the 10,000 steps a day target by now, but a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpub/article/PIIS2468-2667(21)00302-9/fulltext" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpub/article/PIIS2468-2667(21)00302-9/fulltext" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2022 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; found that you can get significant health benefits from fewer steps a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which may leave you wondering, is there a lower limit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, there are walking experts like Milica McDowell, a doctor of physical therapy, exercise physiologist, and VP of operations for &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://gaithappens.com/" target="_blank" data-url="https://gaithappens.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Gait Happens&lt;/a&gt;, who are more than happy to share their expertise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDowell outlined the figures for me and explained why you should be worried if you’re walking fewer than 2,500 steps a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDowell’s advice is based on findings from a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2023 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; that appeared in the &lt;em&gt;European Journal of Preventive Cardiology.&lt;/em&gt; The research collected data from more than 250,000 participants over multiple years, meaning the findings can be reliably used to make informed recommendations by experts like McDowell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this information motivates you to walk more to regularly hit that minimum, that’s great, but just make sure to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/how-do-you-increase-your-step-count-safely-an-exercise-physiologist-weighs-in" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/how-do-you-increase-your-step-count-safely-an-exercise-physiologist-weighs-in"&gt;increase your step count safely&lt;/a&gt;—building up slowly over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-why-2-500-steps"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why 2,500 steps?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; mentioned above explains that you need to walk a minimum of 2,500-4,000 steps a day to see a reduction in the risk of all-cause mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-GgGtB3NtSUZj35XNFS3srY" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-GgGtB3NtSUZj35XNFS3srY slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;From 2,337 steps a day, the risk of cardiovascular mortality specifically begins to reduce, so McDowell rounds that up to a more memorable 2,500 steps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiovascular mortality encompasses all deaths caused by diseases of the cardiovascular system—your heart and blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re walking fewer than 2,500 steps a day, your risk of heart disease, stroke and cardiovascular events is increased. Over 2,500 steps, those risks begin to decrease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“2,500 is the utter basement. If you’re lower than that, you are at risk for all sorts of horrible things,” says McDowell. “So, please get above 2,500. Most people take about 100 steps per minute, so 2,500 is roughly 25 minutes of walking per day.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember that all steps count—even getting something from another room—and this ambient walking, as it known, quickly adds up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-many-steps-should-you-aim-for"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How many steps should you aim for?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / sdominick)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="3-000-to-4-000-steps-3"&gt;3,000 to 4,000 steps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If 2,500 is the absolute basement and you increase by 500 steps per day to 3,000, your risk of dying goes down 7%,” says McDowell. “If you go up 1,000 steps a day, from 2,500 to 3,500, you reduce your risk of dying by 15%.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; states that from around 3,867 steps a day, the risk of mortality from all causes&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;begins to reduce. This includes deaths from any illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="5-000-steps-3"&gt;5,000 steps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anything under 5,000 steps a day is considered sedentary, with 5,000 to 7,500 classed as low activity. Other benefits kick in at 5,000, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We know that when we hit that 5,000 step mark, it’s very good for managing depression symptoms,” says McDowell. “So if you have a family history or if you’ve struggled with those conditions in the past, there are prescriptive amounts of walking that can reduce the symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://publichealth.jmir.org/2024/1/e48355/" target="_blank" data-url="https://publichealth.jmir.org/2024/1/e48355/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2024 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;JMIR Public Health and Surveillance&lt;/em&gt; found that walking can be used as “an evidence-based intervention for reducing anxiety and depression.” You might not be able to add walking to your list of medications, but a higher step count could make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That’s an important message because we know that anxiety, depression, and a lot of mental health disorders impact people’s longevity,” says McDowell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="6-000-to-8-000-steps-3"&gt;6,000 to 8,000 steps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re older than 60, you should be aiming for between 6,000 and 8,000 steps a day for optimal health and longevity, after which the benefits stop increasing with the number of steps you walk. This recommendation is based on data from a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpub/article/PIIS2468-2667(21)00302-9/fulltext" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpub/article/PIIS2468-2667(21)00302-9/fulltext" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2022 &lt;em&gt;Lancet &lt;/em&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; exploring the benefits of walking for longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When you hit around the 7,000 mark, it’s good for reducing your risk of developing depression in the first place,” says McDowell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="8-000-to-10-000-steps-3"&gt;8,000 to 10,000 steps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are under 60 years old, the point of diminishing returns mentioned earlier is slightly higher, between 8,000 and 10,000 steps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking 8,000 steps at a moderate pace (about 3mph) will take you about 90 minutes to walk, depending on your stride length.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember, you don’t have to do that 90 minutes all in one go: you can break it up into smaller chunks like three 30-minute walks or three 20-minute walks and one 30-minute walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-to-walk-more"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to walk more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I asked McDowell for her top tip to squeeze more steps into a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I encourage people to do micro walks,” she says. “They can go out for five minutes because most people walk at 100 steps per minute. So even five minutes can make a significant difference. And if we get them to add 10 minutes a day consistently, we’re looking at a significant impact on their longevity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-if-i-do-other-cardio-should-i-still-walk-for-health"&gt;&lt;span&gt;If I do other cardio should I still walk for health? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of my colleagues do other forms of exercise, and I wondered if doing more cardio exercise means you can skip hitting your steps that day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rowing, biking and swimming are all good for you, but they don’t provide the specific &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/what-are-the-benefits-of-walking" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/what-are-the-benefits-of-walking"&gt;benefits of walking&lt;/a&gt;. They surely provide other benefits, but your body needs a certain number of steps per day to achieve optimal health,” says McDowell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-shop-walking-shoes"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Shop walking shoes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're in need of a new pair of walking shoes, our guide to the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/buying-guides/best-shoes-for-walking" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/buying-guides/best-shoes-for-walking"&gt;best walking shoes&lt;/a&gt; can help. Are are the top three picks in brief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="product-container hero-product-container product-block-no-wrap"&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="c4e09e1b-da08-4334-9e27-0da7195a6174"&gt;
&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1920-80.jpg.webp 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1600-80.jpg.webp 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1280-80.jpg.webp 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1024-80.jpg.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-768-80.jpg.webp 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-415-80.jpg.webp 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-360-80.jpg.webp 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-320-80.jpg.webp 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK.jpg" alt="Brooks Glycerin Max" class="featured_image" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1920-80.jpg 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1600-80.jpg 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1280-80.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-768-80.jpg 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-415-80.jpg 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-360-80.jpg 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-320-80.jpg 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)" loading="lazy" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK.jpg"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label hero__label"&gt;Best Overall&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="6adbf704-d76c-4c12-bdf4-ce16e9ca5822"&gt;
&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1920-80.jpg.webp 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1600-80.jpg.webp 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1280-80.jpg.webp 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1024-80.jpg.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-768-80.jpg.webp 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-415-80.jpg.webp 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-360-80.jpg.webp 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-320-80.jpg.webp 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL.jpg" alt="Columbia Konos TRS Hiking Shoe" class="featured_image" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1920-80.jpg 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1600-80.jpg 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1280-80.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-768-80.jpg 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-415-80.jpg 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-360-80.jpg 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-320-80.jpg 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)" loading="lazy" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL.jpg"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label hero__label"&gt;Best on a budget&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="93dbdbc6-1654-49d5-9ddb-b1160f324e02"&gt;
&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1920-80.jpg.webp 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1600-80.jpg.webp 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1280-80.jpg.webp 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1024-80.jpg.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-768-80.jpg.webp 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-415-80.jpg.webp 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-360-80.jpg.webp 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-320-80.jpg.webp 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM.jpg" alt="Hoka Clifton 9" class="featured_image" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1920-80.jpg 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1600-80.jpg 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1280-80.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-768-80.jpg 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-415-80.jpg 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-360-80.jpg 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-320-80.jpg 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)" loading="lazy" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM.jpg"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label hero__label"&gt;Best for Concrete&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxQaE41b0F3a0F5VjJhUWNWOEY3aUtGZzJQeXREbmNsczBSWUJQMEpub2x0dDZXZUdhSmtkeFB1TWxiOVlXek9ZV3hVMm82LURrV2tkT1dSRDF3OWhmSHZ2ZEIwbmtrVldQdDlnNEdmNEh1QXowRUpJV3h6MmJPR2kzdEExQ01IWkRhekN2am1Ib2hVRTBpSUdGQXhnVUtZcjdxYUQ0ZzU5bm12ZEg0Vk5mQUpnNGtlOHVMMkF3aEJENEp2Y2t1VlBfOVJiZnZOaVRJbVJfQkd6NVF3Vkp4a045NmNoN0ZXZEpZbU5IYWo3bHRZVXpTSlhEOVQySk9YRWVTVXZWeHRn</guid></item><item><title>拯救我们的孩子免于滚动到死-福音联盟 | Saving Our Kids from Scrolling to Death - The Gospel Coalition</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMie0FVX3lxTE5YVTdDa0VjeXhpb0xKR0Vob2QzR0wwNUpVRVJLZUY1azBteHZTUmx4cHdPLXV2X2cyYzdXYkFzYm85TU1mZzRSOTdGY0txOWtNLWlVTXd5eGdKYVVoNEQwSUtPbmh0b3JUSUpWVm5MQktBZVZzd0hXNzJ1MA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content_container"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;It’s no secret that kids today are not all right. Youth rates of &lt;a href="https://www.usnews.com/news/health-news/articles/2024-11-07/rates-of-anxiety-depression-rising-among-americans-especially-the-young" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;anxiety and depression&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/news/articles/2024/12/eating-disorders-among-kids-are-on-the-rise" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;eating disorders&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/changing-america/well-being/mental-health/3806794-most-teenagers-exposed-to-online-pornography-by-age-13-survey/#:~:text=The%20average%20age%20of%20exposure%20to%20online%20pornography%20was%2012.&amp;amp;text=iStock." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;pornography exposure&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://medicine.yale.edu/news-article/youth-suicide-is-on-the-rise-yale-aims-to-save-lives/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;suicide&lt;/a&gt; remain shockingly high. Inside and outside the church, we’ve falsely believed that the dangers posed to developing brains by smartphones and social media can be overcome with occasional conversations or the latest parental controls, or by a “mature” teenager.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the past decade has demonstrated that our current methodologies—however well intentioned—aren’t working to slay the digital beast.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What&lt;em&gt; will&lt;/em&gt; work? Are these dangerous devices simply a necessary evil in our kids’ lives? Or are there more effective ways we can mitigate their influence?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Digital Dope&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Writing in her new book, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Tech-Exit-Practical-Freeing-Smartphones/dp/059373629X/?tag=thegospcoal-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Tech Exit&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Clare Morell documents how technology is like second-hand smoke: “The teen mental health crisis today is due not only to negative effects of digital technologies for individuals but also to the group social dynamics that smartphones and social media have created.” This echoes the question recently asked by Trevin Wax: “&lt;a href="https://www.thegospelcoalition.org/blogs/trevin-wax/scrolling-become-new-smoking/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Could Scrolling Become the New Smoking?&lt;/a&gt;” With &lt;a href="https://www.psypost.org/passive-scrolling-linked-to-increased-anxiety-in-teens-study-finds/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;studies showing&lt;/a&gt; increased levels of anxiety for teens who are passive scrollers, it’s time we age-restrict tablets, smartphones, and social media until adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s time we age-restrict tablets, smartphones, and social media until adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jonathan Haidt’s &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Anxious-Generation-Rewiring-Childhood-Epidemic/dp/0593655036/?tag=thegospcoal-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;i&gt;The Anxious Generation&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt; documented many of the dangers. Countries such as Australia and Sweden have responded boldly. Australia raised the &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c89vjj0lxx9o" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;minimum age of social media use&lt;/a&gt; to 16, and &lt;a href="https://www.government.se/articles/2024/02/government-investing-in-more-reading-time-and-less-screen-time/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Sweden took necessary steps&lt;/a&gt; to reduce the presence of tablets and computers in schools. A year ago in my home state of Virginia, governor Glenn Youngkin introduced a measure to prohibit phone use by students during the school day. It’s going &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/02/us/school-cellphone-ban-virginia" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;remarkably well&lt;/a&gt;, with fewer discipline issues and happier, more connected students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While many people have compared smartphones to cigarettes, Patrick Miller is perhaps more accurate when he writes in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://store.thegospelcoalition.org/product/9781433599446/scrolling-ourselves-to-death-paperback" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Scrolling Ourselves to Death&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, “Your phone is a digital syringe.” Nicotine addiction may cause cancer after decades of use, but “digital dope” is leading to deaths of despair for teens and 20-somethings &lt;i&gt;now&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Miller goes on to say, “Ninety-five percent of teens between thirteen and seventeen are using digital dope, and most parents can’t bring themselves to tell them to stop, even though social media’s dangerous and addictive effects are now widely known.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We can improve the mental health crisis among youth, but only if we’re willing to speak the truth. We must be bold and declare that smartphones and social media aren’t for minors. We can no longer put forward the narrative that just a little bit of digital dope is OK, so long as our kids make good grades and still attend youth group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We shouldn’t blame or ridicule parents, but we do need to call them to a higher standard. The church must be willing to say that parental controls are a red herring and that the social internet is simply incapable of replacing the goodness of in-person community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Protect Children&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recently, I spoke with a mom who relies on internet controls to safeguard her son’s smartphone. She had prohibited him from downloading apps rated ages 17+. As a well-educated, actively engaged parent, she was unaware that some apps rated ages 4+ can still include pornography and eating disorder information.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;App stores aren’t tethered to any real standards and lack appropriate regulations. Utah’s &lt;a href="https://ifstudies.org/blog/utahs-app-store-accountability-act-what-you-need-to-know" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;App Store Accountability Act&lt;/a&gt; aims to rectify this, as does &lt;a href="https://www.click2houston.com/news/local/2025/05/28/governor-abbott-signs-bill-mandating-stricter-controls-for-online-app-stores-parents-and-kids-react/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;recently passed legislation in Texas&lt;/a&gt;. But the other 48 states have no such laws, leaving millions of children less protected than their parents believe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;We can no longer put forward the narrative that just a little bit of digital dope is OK, so long as our kids make good grades and still attend youth group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An &lt;a href="https://www.ic3.gov/PSA/2025/PSA250306" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;FBI warning on the “764 network”&lt;/a&gt; documents how minors are targeted by a crime ring of bad actors who “manipulate or coerce victims to produce Child Sexual Abuse Material (CSAM) and other videos depicting animal cruelty and self-harm.” The FBI notes that posting photos and videos of minors puts the subjects at risk of becoming victimized. No amount of “likes” is worth this risk, not even on a church’s social media feed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn’t a new problem, though. Forty years ago, Neil Postman wrote in &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Amusing-Ourselves-Death-Discourse-Business/dp/014303653X/?tag=thegospcoal-20" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Amusing Ourselves to Death&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, “As a television show, and a good one, &lt;em&gt;Sesame Street&lt;/em&gt; does not encourage children to love school or anything about school. It encourages them to love television.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the same way, Instagram doesn’t encourage children to love community. YouTube doesn’t encourage a love of serving others. TikTok doesn’t encourage creativity. They all encourage children to love consuming content on Instagram, YouTube, and TikTok. We don’t have to be against the internet in its entirety to be against minors being preyed upon by addictive, algorithm driven apps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, it’s not enough to say yes to a smartphone and no to social media. An internet-connected device in your son’s or daughter’s pocket allows too much, too soon. Research shows that the earlier minors receive a smartphone or tablet, &lt;a href="https://sapienlabs.org/data_gallery/?report=3901" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;the worse their mental health&lt;/a&gt; will fare into early adulthood. Waiting until after high school graduation is the prudent response.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This approach isn’t without precedent. We have age requirements on purchasing cigarettes, alcohol, and guns and on entering strip clubs. Minimum age restrictions exist for getting a driver’s license or riding in the front seat of a car. We’ve collectively agreed that some things aren’t safe for children and teens. Until our laws catch up with our needs, the church should stand in the gap and protect children.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;How You Can Take Action&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A group in Maryland has done as much by &lt;a href="https://www.frontporchrepublic.com/2023/08/postman-pledge/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;signing the “Postman Pledge,”&lt;/a&gt; agreeing to restrict smartphone and social media access for their children and teens. Instead, they commit to creating “deep bonds of community . . . to foster friendship among our families in the natural, traditional ways human cultures have always done.” They aren’t doing something new, but they are doing something good.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;We don’t have to be against the internet in its entirety to be against minors using the social internet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My family has chosen to &lt;a href="https://open.substack.com/pub/dearchristianparent/p/landline-phones-because-vintage-is?r=3huc9s&amp;amp;utm_campaign=post&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;showWelcomeOnShare=false" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;install a landline phone&lt;/a&gt;, as have a handful of our friends. My sons use the landline to make plans with their buddies or clarify the evening’s homework assignment. Parents of their friends are accustomed to fielding calls from my children and often praise their communication skills. As some of my sons’ friends have gotten smartphones, our landline is still an effective means of communication. And I never have to worry that an app update will undo parental controls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Internet culture’s negative influences have seeped into our homes and our churches, despite our best efforts. The narrative that we must teach kids how to use these devices well hasn’t produced much fruit. Rare is the adult who claims a healthy relationship with his or her smartphone. As followers of Christ, we must be brave enough to stand up for children and say that smartphones, tablets, and social media aren’t for minors.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our kids are scrolling themselves to death, but this can end. The church can fight for children. After all, if we don’t, then who will?&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
																			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Gospel Coalition</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE5YVTdDa0VjeXhpb0xKR0Vob2QzR0wwNUpVRVJLZUY1azBteHZTUmx4cHdPLXV2X2cyYzdXYkFzYm85TU1mZzRSOTdGY0txOWtNLWlVTXd5eGdKYVVoNEQwSUtPbmh0b3JUSUpWVm5MQktBZVZzd0hXNzJ1MA</guid></item><item><title>为什么你的心喜欢步行10分钟甚至超过10公里-印度时报 | Why your heart loves a 10-minute walk even more than a 10k run - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi7wFBVV95cUxQT1hMckotMUI4QUJiQ2pwYWo5U2lnTUhHLWVmNW9hZkdFdE5BLUN2b3otd0dlNVF3M3BhV2s1cE1wZUZmT0x4TVlUTm1ENEF3ZEU3azJIZl9zbC1SM0VRbDlyaFByTk1ZT2dkTVJpV3FmaXdsYzZOeXpzcTdhbFFTLVYxdkJia3NqeS03eWdKSUVLM3FmbmNDTzAtUTh5aExqQ0ZFMmRLV3I4UWxJWVpfdWpFcEhLNHVxTFJfS2lJTWhOVDJCa2VxeWlRdmhCUHpBUU1sOXczVVB4SDJRdWh0NU1jeUJDczZnajY4MGNWOA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever scrolled through fitness Instagram and felt a pang of guilt for not running marathons, power-lifting, or doing bootcamps at 5 a.m., take a deep breath—and go for a 10-minute walk. That’s it. No sweat-drenched t-shirts. No interval timers. Just ten minutes of walking. Because, as surprising as it sounds, your heart might prefer it that way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to protecting your heart, short, consistent walks may be just as powerful, if not more so, than an occasional 10K run. Here’s why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The myth of “go hard or go home”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, the fitness industry has glorified high-intensity workouts. While there’s no denying the benefits of vigorous activity (especially for endurance and metabolic boost), the idea that you must suffer through sprints or long-distance runs to support heart health? That’s outdated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What happens to your heart in just 10 minutes?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The beauty of walking lies in its immediate impact. The moment you start moving, even at a casual pace, several things happen:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood vessels dilate. That means improved circulation and better oxygen delivery throughout the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your heart rate rises slightly—but safely. You’re not maxing out; you’re nudging your heart just enough to stimulate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Endothelial function improves. The &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/19757859/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;endothelium &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;(lining of blood vessels) becomes more efficient, which helps prevent atherosclerosis (hardening of the arteries).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood pressure drops. Yes, even a 10-minute walk can lead to modest reductions in blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stress hormones reduce. Cortisol levels dip, and mood-lifting neurotransmitters like serotonin and dopamine kick in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add that up across 5 or 6 walks per week, and you’re looking at a cumulative effect that’s seriously heart-protective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The longevity link&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2021 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2783711" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;published in JAMA Network Open found that walking for just a few minutes a day (even broken into smaller chunks) reduced the risk of cardiovascular events by up to 50%. That’s on par with many cholesterol-lowering drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even more eye-opening? The biggest heart-health gains were seen in people who went from no movement to just a little. It wasn’t the marathon runners who saw the sharpest drop in risk—it was the couch potatoes who started taking short strolls after lunch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why running isn’t always the winner&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s not demonize running—it’s a powerful cardiovascular activity and brings benefits to many. But for some people, especially those with joint issues, high blood pressure, obesity, or chronic stress, running can actually be counterproductive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;It spikes cortisol. High-intensity workouts temporarily raise stress hormones. That’s fine occasionally—but in already stressed individuals, it can strain the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;It increases injury risk. Shin splints, knee pain, plantar fasciitis—these are all common in recreational runners, which can lead to complete inactivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s unsustainable for many. You’re more likely to stick to something that doesn’t leave you breathless and sore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s where walking shines: it’s kinder, gentler, and easier to stick with. For people over 40, especially, walking can be a gateway to sustainable heart health without the strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The secret sauce? Frequency and joy&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your heart doesn’t just respond to effort—it responds to regularity and emotion. A 10-minute walk taken daily with your dog, your spouse, or even a podcast you love? That’s medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking after meals also brings added benefits. Postprandial (after-meal) walks can blunt blood sugar spikes, ease digestion, and reduce blood pressure. All of these are gold for cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Japan, where heart disease rates are significantly lower, it’s common to see office workers walking after lunch. It’s not seen as “fitness”—it’s just a lifestyle. That mindset shift might be the real win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What if you can’t find ten minutes?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then find five. Seriously. A recent &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sydney.edu.au/news-opinion/news/2024/11/07/five-minutes-of-exercise-a-day-could-lower-blood-pressure.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;out of the University of Sydney found that people who did three short 5-minute walks a day—morning, lunch, and evening—saw improvements in blood pressure and VO₂ max, a marker of heart fitness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What the heart really wants&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s cut to the chase. Your heart wants:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular, gentle movement&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Calm instead of chaos&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oxygen-rich blood&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Low inflammation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A consistent routine&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Time outdoors, preferably under a tree or near a bird&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking offers all of that. And when it’s done regularly, especially in green spaces, it turns into a meditative ritual that benefits not just your heart, but your entire nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So yes, run if you love it. But don’t for a second believe that running is the only path to heart health. If all you can offer today is 10 quiet minutes with the pavement, your heart will thank you—quietly, efficiently, and over the long haul.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s something deeply rebellious about choosing simplicity in a world obsessed with extremes. And when it comes to your heart, the data is clear: you don’t need to conquer mountains. You just need to step out your front door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether it’s walking your kid to the school bus, strolling through your building's corridor, or circling your kitchen island with a podcast playing—those 10 minutes are no joke. They’re cardiac gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So lace up. Not to chase a record or beat a personal best, but to remind your heart that you’re in it for the long run—the slow, steady, 10-minute-at-a-time kind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and does not constitute medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new exercise routine, especially if you have existing heart conditions or health concerns. Individual fitness needs may vary, and what works for one person may not be suitable for another. The content is based on current research and expert opinion, but should not replace personalized guidance from your doctor or cardiologist.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt; Use discretion and prioritize safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 02:17:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7wFBVV95cUxQT1hMckotMUI4QUJiQ2pwYWo5U2lnTUhHLWVmNW9hZkdFdE5BLUN2b3otd0dlNVF3M3BhV2s1cE1wZUZmT0x4TVlUTm1ENEF3ZEU3azJIZl9zbC1SM0VRbDlyaFByTk1ZT2dkTVJpV3FmaXdsYzZOeXpzcTdhbFFTLVYxdkJia3NqeS03eWdKSUVLM3FmbmNDTzAtUTh5aExqQ0ZFMmRLV3I4UWxJWVpfdWpFcEhLNHVxTFJfS2lJTWhOVDJCa2VxeWlRdmhCUHpBUU1sOXczVVB4SDJRdWh0NU1jeUJDczZnajY4MGNWOA</guid></item><item><title>传染病更新2025年7月6日-每日科斯 | Infectious Updates 7/6/2025 - Daily Kos</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxQWklSUTBYcHN2S0pETFExRVR3bmxtSWQ1ZGxqemt3YVVKUVNUNUFSQXJBLXM2ekJNYlRkZTViM1JNQm9TWEthOVMwalgtcnZtWjk2bnRndlVNOWcxTndXTTJwN2dBU1RmbHVZOU1IUzJpNEFLaVJFYU9CQ3FpRk1oSlpKRFI?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story__text"&gt;
          &lt;p&gt;Well, we did it.  Yay. Also whoopee.  We have broken our own 2019 record for measles cases, and the year is only half over. 1,277 cases as of Saturday. &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/measles/more-measles-outbreaks-put-us-total-within-single-digits-modern-day-record" target="_blank"&gt;See how fast totals get outdated?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Giving a pregnant woman a flu shot protects her &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/influenza-vaccines/maternal-flu-vaccine-protects-newborns-vaccination-kids-also-effective-studies" target="_blank"&gt;baby, too, for a few months.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/avian-influenza-bird-flu/cambodia-confirms-2-more-h5n1-avian-flu-infections" target="_blank"&gt;Cambodia continues to have H5N1 cases&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/avian-influenza-bird-flu/cambodia-confirms-12th-h5n1-avian-flu-infection-year" target="_blank"&gt;Up to 12 this year, many fatal or very serious.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vinay Prasad restricted Covid boosters &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/covid-shots-fda-trump-kennedy-fda-overruled-3ac51f93225aa5f20d5840468fff8b02" target="_blank"&gt;Contrary to scientific advice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Moderna's mRNA flu vaccine showed very good efficacy &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/influenza-vaccines/moderna-announces-promising-efficacy-results-mrna-flu-vaccine-trial" target="_blank" title=""&gt;in Phase 3 trials.&lt;/a&gt; They would also like to combine flu and Covid in a single shot. Under this administration, I wish them luck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;..&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table align="center" class="basic-table"&gt;
	&lt;tbody&gt;
		&lt;tr&gt;
			&lt;td&gt;
			&lt;div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/groups/Infectious%20Information" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infectious Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is a DK group for collecting diaries on all things infectious, both basic educational material and breaking news updates.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;p&gt;Given the precarious state of public health agencies under the Orange Menace, it is my hope that the information &lt;em&gt;itself&lt;/em&gt; can be infectious, spread widely to all your contacts, in the hope of promoting self-defense from disease. Knowledge is the best inoculation against misinformation!&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;

			&lt;div&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/users/strawbale" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Kosmail&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for an invitation if you want to join and have info to contribute, or&lt;a href="https://www.dailykos.com/groups/Infectious%20Information" target="_blank" title=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt; follow the group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to get these posts automatically in your activity stream.&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/td&gt;
		&lt;/tr&gt;
	&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p class="is-empty-p"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Kos</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 00:57:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxQWklSUTBYcHN2S0pETFExRVR3bmxtSWQ1ZGxqemt3YVVKUVNUNUFSQXJBLXM2ekJNYlRkZTViM1JNQm9TWEthOVMwalgtcnZtWjk2bnRndlVNOWcxTndXTTJwN2dBU1RmbHVZOU1IUzJpNEFLaVJFYU9CQ3FpRk1oSlpKRFI</guid></item><item><title>科学家解释为什么随着年龄的增长，时间似乎移动得更快并“飞逝” - Earth.com | Scientists explain why time seems to move faster and 'fly by' as we age - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirwFBVV95cUxPNTNRaXFET2w2MkRxWHRsLTU1Qjl4QllUeWZvQzE2NVJyOElIUE1jUnI5VmlmSDVRV0t6endfZEtLbExDWHJxYnFsVHNQa2FYT1ZGSktFbC1VSlB0R2N6dVV2cE9NdnFBdmNfR2ZHeDhUUlAyRFV6NDVHakc2eXNCUk5wN05LYmpsNTQ3VFdmNU5OQ3dwVXMyd1N4WTN3Skt0bk1JSjBmdUZZc3NaV3Jv?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of us have heard a parent or grandparent say, “Time goes by faster every year,” while shaking their head at how quickly July 4 seems to roll around. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re twelve, however, the brain has a different perception of time – the wait for summer vacation feels endless, and a single school day can feel as slow as a traffic jam in August heat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That gap between the child’s long afternoon and the adult’s lightning-fast month isn’t just storytelling, it’s how our brain’s perception of time changes, altering the way it measures all of the moments that make up our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-first-vs-fresh-experiences"&gt;First vs. fresh experiences&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children cram their days with firsts: a first dive into the pool, a first try at long division, a first sleepover away from home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These fresh experiences swarm the brain with new images to file away, stretching the subjective length of a single afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adults, by contrast, tend to replay &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/extreme-heat-impacts-our-daily-routines-and-transportation/"&gt;familiar routines&lt;/a&gt;. With fewer novel snapshots to store, the days collapse into something closer to a highlight reel than a feature film.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to psychologist Marc Wittmann at the Institute for Frontier Areas of Psychology and Mental Health &lt;a href="https://igpp.de/en/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;(IGPP&lt;/a&gt;), the feeling that time accelerates is tightly linked to how much new material our brains record each day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He points out that &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/memory-clutter-speeds-up-aging-in-the-brain/"&gt;memory&lt;/a&gt; and time perception sit on the same neural bench; when one slows, the other shrinks. “Newness” holds the key to this phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-human-brain-and-time-perception"&gt;Human brain and time perception&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whenever a brain encounters something it has never processed before, a quick surge of attention flags the event as worth keeping. The more flags raised, the thicker the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/human-brains-use-storage-trick-to-keep-your-memories-in-sequential-order/"&gt;memory log&lt;/a&gt; becomes, and the longer that span later feels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kids, still green to nearly everything, throw flags left and right. A lunchroom joke, a new word in science class, or a game of tag – each registers as its own small chapter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adults often glide through copy-and-paste days that differ only by the date on the calendar. With fewer chapters recorded, the book of any given week reads as a short story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research using immersive virtual reality in 2024 showed that older volunteers underestimated simple time intervals by roughly 15 percent, highlighting how novelty &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S096800042300302X" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sharpens the inner clock&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Routine doesn’t just compress the past; it also drains the present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies tracking holiday seasons in several countries found that people who stuck to predictable daily rhythms felt that Christmas or Ramadan arrived sooner every year, while those who sprinkled in new activities reported a slower march toward the festivities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-brain-processing-speed-linked-with-time"&gt;Brain processing speed linked with time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every sensation has to travel from eye or ear to cortex. In youngsters, those &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/speech-pattern-wfd-that-is-a-clear-indication-a-person-is-in-cognitive-decline/"&gt;neural highways&lt;/a&gt; are short and well-paved. As bodies grow, the routes lengthen, and the conduction speed though still quick can’t match its earlier zip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add natural age-related slowing of signal processing and the brain starts sampling the world less often each second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fewer samples mean fewer “ticks” on the subjective stopwatch, so a morning meeting seems to vanish faster for a forty-year-old than for a fourth grader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This sampling &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-link-pupil-dilation-to-brains-working-memory-levels/"&gt;shows up in the eyes&lt;/a&gt;. Our eyes jerk from point to point in rapid saccades, pausing in brief fixations while the brain grabs a visual frame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young, rested eyes squeeze in more fixations per minute. Older or fatigued eyes lag, offering the brain fewer still frames to stitch together. With a thinner film strip, the projection of the day speeds along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists studying eye movements liken perception to a flipbook. Each fixation is a page; flip them fast enough and you see smooth action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When fixations slow, the flipbook loses pages. Motion still appears, but the storyline gets choppy, and, in recall, it shortens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-sleep-and-alertness"&gt;Sleep and alertness&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A single night of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/sleep-can-boost-memory-in-a-surprising-way/"&gt;good sleep&lt;/a&gt; can pull the brake on runaway days. When neurons are well-rested, they fire faster, notice more, and form clearer memories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Athletes know the flip side: stepping onto the field after too little shut-eye makes the whole match blur. The plays happen, but the mind records only a highlight or two before the final whistle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Students grinding through an all-nighter meet the same fate – an exam that seems to finish moments after it starts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/what-is-the-best-treatment-for-excessive-daytime-sleepiness/"&gt;Chronic fatigue&lt;/a&gt; magnifies the effect. Continually short-changing rest lowers baseline alertness, trimming snapshots day after day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over months, life can feel like it’s slipping through the cracks, not because the clock sped up but because the recorder slowed down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/mind-and-mood/dopamine-the-pathway-to-pleasure" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Dopamine&lt;/a&gt;, a neurotransmitter tied to motivation and time estimation, also dips with sleep debt, further warping the &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/psychology/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2024.1364166/full" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sense of duration&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Endless feeds promise variety, yet most algorithms serve look-alike posts. Swipe through video after video of the same dance trend, and the brain barely registers a change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hours evaporate while the memory log remains nearly blank. Compound that with the blue-light-induced bedtime delay, and you have a double punch: fewer snapshots captured and fewer hours slept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cutting back on passive scrolling or swapping it for an activity with genuine novelty – trying a new recipe, learning a chord on guitar – feeds the brain more distinct moments. Those moments stretch subjective time, turning a blur of an evening into something that feels full.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-with-age-comes-responsibility"&gt;With age comes responsibility&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond slower processing, adults juggle long lists of responsibilities. Focus narrows to tasks at hand – emails, errands, budgets – scanning less of the environment for new input. Novelty drops, and subjective days shorten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tiaa.org/public/institute/publication/2023/young-adults-their-attitudes-and-outlook-toward-retirement-and-the-future" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;A 2023 survey&lt;/a&gt; comparing young adults with retirees found that the older group reported the year as “rushing by” nearly twice as often, linking the feeling to the predictability of daily routines rather than to health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even so, not every senior feels the rush. Researchers tracking so-called “&lt;a href="https://www.nm.org/healthbeat/healthy-tips/4-habits-super-agers" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;super-agers&lt;/a&gt;” note that those who keep learning new skills and staying socially engaged maintain sharper senses of time, along with stronger memory performance. Variety keeps the brain’s camera clicking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-use-your-brain-to-slow-time-perception"&gt;Use your brain to slow time perception&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s the good news – the tools to lengthen your days fit into ordinary life. Go to bed on a schedule that honors the seven-to-nine-hour rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plan at least one activity each week that forces you out of autopilot: a different jogging route, a museum you’ve never visited, a new language app.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While doing it, pay close attention to sights, sounds, and textures. Engagement packs extra snapshots into the mental album.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay curious daily. Swap a lunchtime scroll for a short walk and notice five things you’ve never clocked before – a mural, a bird call, the scent of a bakery vent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those micro-discoveries add pages to the flipbook, expanding the subjective afternoon. Over time, the habit can “thicken” the memory book that tells the story of a year, making December feel like it belongs twelve full months away, right where the calendar says it should be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/european-review/article/why-the-days-seem-shorter-as-we-get-older/2CB8EC9B0B30537230C7442B826E42F1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;European Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 23:45:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxPNTNRaXFET2w2MkRxWHRsLTU1Qjl4QllUeWZvQzE2NVJyOElIUE1jUnI5VmlmSDVRV0t6endfZEtLbExDWHJxYnFsVHNQa2FYT1ZGSktFbC1VSlB0R2N6dVV2cE9NdnFBdmNfR2ZHeDhUUlAyRFV6NDVHakc2eXNCUk5wN05LYmpsNTQ3VFdmNU5OQ3dwVXMyd1N4WTN3Skt0bk1JSjBmdUZZc3NaV3Jv</guid></item><item><title>这棵流行树的叶子可以改善血液循环并防止血栓- Earth.com | Leaves from this popular tree may improve circulation and prevent blood clots - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxONnBNaDY3VV9zOVd4M2tWNUJkLUE0YVFVb1QtZmR6Zjg1T0ZvX2dBbDNudmhxSjJmLWJZWnBtemhyd2wzaDA0WXprOGxRSktmRnZIWjF3NDQ5dlg3aXFRcUI1U2o4VTJVQmRtd0Q4Y0lucU05UHNvT2tLcHBEaFZEWUtvcnFwbXZROTJQYkxtYlpvdFRfMFNhSm5KZWlrMWND?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Varicose veins bulge and twist across the calves of up to 30 percent of adults, a reminder that blood sometimes pools instead of flowing home to the heart. When sluggish blood flow lingers, clots can form and, in rare cases, travel to the lungs or brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Centuries ago physicians in China brewed teas from &lt;a href="https://www.missouribotanicalgarden.org/PlantFinder/PlantFinderDetails.aspx?kempercode=z990" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ginkgo biloba&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; leaves to sharpen memory. Today researchers wonder whether the same ginkgo leaves might support weary leg veins and cut the risk of small, yet dangerous, blood clots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-circulation-can-falter"&gt;Why circulation can falter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood rising from the feet must fight gravity, and faulty valves can leave veins stretched and valves leaky. The lingering pressure distends vein walls, encourages &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/fasting-helps-the-body-fight-inflammation-and-chronic-diseases/"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt;, and slows platelet aggregation, the first step toward clotting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slow venous return creates the setting for deep‑vein thrombosis as well as the aching, throbbing symptoms many patients feel after a day of standing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That overlap has pushed vascular specialists toward plant‑based compounds that might tone the vein wall and limit sticky platelets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After logging stroke cases at Xuanwu Hospital in Beijing, neurologist &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/scientific-contributions/Xiangqian-Huang-2265510495" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Xiangqian Huang&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href="https://ccmu.cucas.cn/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Capital Medical University&lt;/a&gt; began probing ginkgo’s effects on clot behavior in the brain, work that now informs leg‑vein research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ginkgo-leaves-and-blood-flow"&gt;Ginkgo leaves and blood flow&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ginkgo extract made &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/drinking-from-plastic-bottles-linked-to-high-blood-pressure-and-heart-problems/"&gt;blood platelets&lt;/a&gt; less sticky when triggered by one type of chemical but didn’t have much effect when triggered by another. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Xiangqian Huang and the team also noticed that blood took slightly longer to clot after treatment with the extract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The leaf contains natural compounds that seem to interact with enzymes responsible for forming clots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a 2025 animal &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40462336/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;, researchers found that ginkgo reduced damage inside blood vessels in rats with clotting problems and slightly increased the time it took for their blood to clot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-insights-from-a-beijing-stroke-ward"&gt;Insights from a Beijing stroke ward&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huang’s real‑world study followed 99 patients for five days. Among stroke survivors who received ginkgo plus baby &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/daily-aspirin-use-strongly-tied-to-colorectal-cancer-prevention/"&gt;aspirin&lt;/a&gt;, arachidonic‑acid platelet aggregation fell more than in peers on aspirin alone, while major bleeding did not rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minor nose or gum bleeds surfaced in four of thirty‑three combination patients, a signal that enhanced anticoagulation deserves monitoring. No severe hemorrhages occurred, suggesting short‑term safety when doses stay low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The design also enrolled participants with internal jugular venous stenosis, a group whose &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/artificial-sweetener-erythritol-sugar-substitute-linked-to-blood-clots-heart-disease/"&gt;clots&lt;/a&gt; mirror those in leg veins. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In that arm ginkgo alone curbed blood platelet stickiness within 24 hours, and the effect held steady through day five.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-aspirin-ginkgo-and-blood-clots"&gt;Aspirin, ginkgo, and blood clots&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team of &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17982321/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;scientists&lt;/a&gt; led by &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/profiles/christopher-gardner" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Christopher Gardner&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Stanford Department of Medicine&lt;/a&gt; examined the potential adverse effects of concomitant aspirin and Ginkgo biloba on blood platelet function after giving the duo to older adults for four weeks. The worry was that the herbs might blunt or boost common drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gardner and colleagues detected no dangerous bleeding, yet laboratory tests showed additive platelet inhibition, suggesting that low‑dose pairings could protect high‑risk patients who cannot tolerate stronger pharmaceuticals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors, however, should adjust regimens around surgeries or when other blood thinners enter the mix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the leaf targets arachidonic‑acid pathways that aspirin already touches, the partnership makes pharmacologic sense. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, anyone taking nonsteroidal anti‑inflammatory drugs should discuss timing and dosage to avoid stacking identical mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-helping-legs-feel-lighter"&gt;Helping legs feel lighter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deep veins are not the only place where endothelial cells detach under strain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a classic double‑blind trial, scientists found that a capsule combining ginkgo, troxerutin, and heptaminol cut circulating endothelial cell counts by 14.5 percent in patients with chronic varicose veins, placebo achieved only 8.4 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK26848/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Endothelial cells&lt;/a&gt; are early barometers of vein injury, so their decline hints at real structural healing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants also reported reduced ankle swelling and night cramps, benefits echoed by later Russian and Italian studies that tracked leg circumference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modern &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/home/phl" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;phlebology&lt;/a&gt; still relies on compression stockings and laser ablation, yet many sufferers ask for gentler first steps. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A standardized ginkgo formula, already licensed for vascular disorders in parts of Europe, may slot neatly between lifestyle changes and invasive procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-blood-clot-prevention-with-ginkgo"&gt;Blood clot prevention with ginkgo&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yang’s rat data showed lighter &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cause-of-strokes-cervical-artery-dissection-has-increased-400-percent-since-2005/"&gt;clots&lt;/a&gt;, higher nitric‑oxide levels, and longer clotting times after gavage with 60 milligrams per kilogram of extract. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nitric oxide relaxes vessel walls and counters platelet stickiness, aligning with human data from stroke and vein clinics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26030402/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Network‑pharmacology&lt;/a&gt; maps place AKT1, ALB, and TNF at the center of ginkgo’s target web. Those same genes regulate inflammation, suggesting that the tree’s reach extends beyond platelets to the very lining of our veins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because oxidative stress weakens venous valves, the antioxidant side of the extract warrants equal attention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flavonols scavenge free radicals, potentially slowing the progressive dilation that makes early spider veins blossom into rope‑like cords.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-talking-with-your-doctor"&gt;Talking with your doctor&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ginkgo supplements crowd store shelves, yet extracts used in clinical trials are highly standardized. Look for&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/12757407/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; EGb 761&lt;/a&gt; or products specifying at least 24 percent flavonol glycosides and 6 percent terpene lactones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients on warfarin, &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/JAHA.120.017559" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;direct oral anticoagulants&lt;/a&gt;, or upcoming dental work should alert their clinicians before starting any form of ginkgo. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health professionals may stagger doses, check clotting labs, or advise pausing the herb to keep bleeding risk low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those with aching calves and a family history of clots, discussing ginkgo as an adjunct to compression or low‑intensity exercise could make sense. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evidence remains preliminary, yet the plant’s dual action on platelets and vein walls is steadily moving from bench to bedside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future multicenter trials ought to track long‑term safety and measure quality‑of‑life changes such as heaviness, itch, and nightly restlessness. If findings stay positive, an ancient tree might soon earn a modern role in vascular medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11803947/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thrombosis Journal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 21:11:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxONnBNaDY3VV9zOVd4M2tWNUJkLUE0YVFVb1QtZmR6Zjg1T0ZvX2dBbDNudmhxSjJmLWJZWnBtemhyd2wzaDA0WXprOGxRSktmRnZIWjF3NDQ5dlg3aXFRcUI1U2o4VTJVQmRtd0Q4Y0lucU05UHNvT2tLcHBEaFZEWUtvcnFwbXZROTJQYkxtYlpvdFRfMFNhSm5KZWlrMWND</guid></item><item><title>为什么你的大脑比你想象的更擅长八卦-神经科学新闻 | Why Your Brain Is Better at Gossip Than You Realize - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMibkFVX3lxTE1UOVVFVzAwRXZyQ2V5SzE5RmN4T3J1Wlg0TnZwbklHVUQySWpVa25JRE1uckdyUkI1SkJNalNMbFNzei1ENEtsVjAteTU0NmwtOUJEakpEYTZLbExVWThDczZlbVV0SFJHRFFhUDJR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study reveals how humans instinctively calculate who to gossip with by weighing popularity and social distance. This cognitive process allows gossip to spread widely while minimizing the risk of it reaching the wrong person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers found that people unconsciously build mental maps of their social networks to predict how gossip travels. These findings highlight the sophisticated role of gossip in social dynamics and the brain’s hidden computational power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;People gossip most to popular yet distantly connected individuals to minimize risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mental “social maps” help predict how gossip spreads through networks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The brain’s calculations resemble algorithms behind social media virality.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Brown University&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognitive neuroscientists at Brown University investigated one of humanity’s favorite pastimes and discovered how people can spread gossip without the subject of that gossip finding out — at least not right away.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a study supported by a federal grant from the National Science Foundation, the researchers found that gossiping relies on a person’s ability to perform complex computational processes each time they decide to spread information, and that most people do this instinctively. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers defined gossiping as talking about third parties who are not present. They found that people tend to gossip less with those who are friends with the subject of the gossip — especially if the subject is considered popular — and gossip the most with those who are popular yet distantly connected to the subject. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-111388"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a brain." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/07/gossiping-brain-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Drawing on this data, the researchers teamed up with Matt Nassar, an assistant professor of neuroscience affiliated with the Carney Institute, to create a computational model of how a person’s brain simulates and predicts the movement of gossip through their social network. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their findings were published in&lt;em&gt; Nature Human Behaviour.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We draw on two important factors when calculating who to share a morsel of gossip with: how popular the person is and how distantly connected they are to whoever the gossip is about,” said study author Oriel FeldmanHall, an associate professor of cognitive and psychological sciences at Brown University who is affiliated with the Carney Institute for Brain Science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This winning algorithm enables us to share information widely without the subject knowing that we’re talking about them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The power of these computations is evident in recent social phenomena, according to study author Alice Xia, a Ph.D. student in cognitive science at Brown. While humans rely on these calculations to predict where their gossip may end up, Xia said, the technology underpinning social media platforms likely capitalizes on similar computations to maximize user engagement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Social media platforms use functionally similar algorithms to predict sharing behavior based on information like number of likes or follower counts, which signal a user’s influence and potential ability to amplify content across the network,” Xia said. “This is essentially how we get viral content.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Mapping the spread of gossip&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The human ability to make these calculations hinges on a mental process called cognitive mapping. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a paper published in 2024, FeldmanHall and Assistant Professor of Cognitive and Psychological Sciences (Research) Apoorva Bhandari established that humans replay memories of daily social interactions while sleeping to build a mental map of their social network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though people do not consciously recognize the relationship of every person in their social network to every other person, FeldmanHall said the maps they unconsciously create serve as reliable guides for whom to spread gossip to, whom not spread gossip to and how gossip will travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the new study, FeldmanHall and Bhandari taught participants about a fictional nine-person network. Then they gave participants a target of gossip and asked them to determine how likely they were to share that gossip with others in the network. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The initial results showed that participants were using social distance and popularity — measured by the number of direct friends a person had — to predict how information would spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, the researchers tested their theory on approximately 200 first-year Brown University students living in campus residence halls. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers mapped this social network by asking all of the study participants about their friendships. Then they asked a subset of 100 participants to judge the likelihood that someone in their network would hear news shared by someone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even in such an intricate social network comprising tens of thousands of possible connections, the researchers found that people were able to successfully use social distance and popularity to predict where gossip would flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drawing on this data, the researchers teamed up with Matt Nassar, an assistant professor of neuroscience affiliated with the Carney Institute, to create a computational model of how a person’s brain simulates and predicts the movement of gossip through their social network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The brain compresses what a person observed — Mary getting coffee with James, then James hanging out with Adam, for example — into a simplified map of the network, which allows the person to make educated guesses about who will hear what, even when those people are several steps removed from each other,” Xia said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to FeldmanHall, the new study findings throw cold water on common conceptions of gossip as mere idle chatter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The fact that our brains invest this much mental math in keeping our gossip out of the wrong hands is testament to the power of gossip and the sophistication of the human brain,” FeldmanHall said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;This study was funded by the National Science Foundation (2123469).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this social neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#43202c31312a261c332a28362f0321312c342d6d262736" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Corrie Pikul&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://brown.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Brown University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Corrie Pikul – Brown University&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Closed access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41562-025-02241-2" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Knowledge of information cascades through social networks facilitates strategic gossip&lt;/a&gt;” by Oriel FeldmanHall et al. &lt;em&gt;Nature Human Behavior&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge of information cascades through social networks facilitates strategic gossip&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social networks are composed of many ties among many individuals. These ties enable the spread of information through a network, including gossip, which comprises a sizeable share of daily conversation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the number of possible connections between people in even the smallest networks, a formidable challenge is how to strategically gossip—to disseminate information as widely as possible without the target of the gossip finding out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here we find that people achieve this goal by leveraging knowledge about topological properties, specifically, social distance and popularity, using a gossip-sharing task in artificial social networks (experiments 1–3, &lt;em&gt;N&lt;/em&gt; = 568).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We find a similar pattern of behaviour in a real-world social network (experiment 4, &lt;em&gt;N&lt;/em&gt; = 187), revealing the power of these topological properties in predicting information flow, even in much noisier, complex environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Computational modelling suggests that these adaptive social behaviours rely on mental representations of information cascades through the social network.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 19:50:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE1UOVVFVzAwRXZyQ2V5SzE5RmN4T3J1Wlg0TnZwbklHVUQySWpVa25JRE1uckdyUkI1SkJNalNMbFNzei1ENEtsVjAteTU0NmwtOUJEakpEYTZLbExVWThDczZlbVV0SFJHRFFhUDJR</guid></item></channel></rss>