<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>一种鲜为人知的热带病毒正在拉丁美洲悄然爆发—科学家们看到另一场全球大流行的早期迹象-银河日报 | A Little-Know Tropical Virus Is Quietly Exploding Across Latin America — Scientists See Early Signs of Another Global Pandemic - The Daily Galaxy</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi7gFBVV95cUxOaE53WTk3N0l0NzZrM2tVRkhnZlJhVkZ4cl9NdmYwWUpDdjVpNk1HQ252cDJ6TExybEN2LUJjNjVEMVZ5cGxaWDFJbDNtQTdla1FNNjZ2T2h4ZmhOR2VpeE1zTjB1RlBnZE5Vcm1ZdWVBRDdDbGx3N1dHNWI1V2JrUlJSemJwenJDMlA1dWdPa2NlUkV2bHk2Y2R2WUs5Z2NlMWNWYVZ3V19LMVZuRTdhNFE4bVdQRUJPNHQ3emc1YmctVEdVM21kR0RvZ2xmeFZDdjU5aW5mb1o0SzZZTExBR2lOVHhVTURNYlM2YlRR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A virus largely unknown outside scientific circles is spreading rapidly across parts of &lt;strong&gt;Latin America&lt;/strong&gt;, drawing comparisons to &lt;em&gt;Zika&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;dengue&lt;/em&gt; and prompting concern from epidemiologists. Known as the &lt;strong&gt;oropouche virus&lt;/strong&gt;, it has already infected over &lt;strong&gt;20,000 people&lt;/strong&gt; in the region since late 2023, with confirmed cases across &lt;strong&gt;Brazil, Peru, Colombia, Bolivia&lt;/strong&gt;, and the &lt;strong&gt;Caribbean&lt;/strong&gt;. The virus, first documented in &lt;strong&gt;1955&lt;/strong&gt; in &lt;em&gt;Trinidad and Tobago&lt;/em&gt;, is now being watched closely by international health researchers who warn of its “massively under-diagnosed” presence in tropical regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-2"&gt;

    
    &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="1096651400" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
    
    
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Virus Mistaken for Zika or Dengue for Decades&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Oropouche virus symptoms are frequently mistaken for those of &lt;em&gt;dengue&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Zika&lt;/em&gt;, leading to widespread underreporting. Patients often present with &lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/05/this-ancient-killer-is-rapidly-becoming-resistant-to-antibiotics-making-it-deadlier-than-ever-before/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="89396" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;fever, headaches, joint and muscle pain, chills, nausea, vomiting,&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;skin rashes&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. While many recover, some develop more serious conditions such as &lt;strong&gt;viral meningitis&lt;/strong&gt;, a brain infection that can result in severe complications. Because the symptoms are so similar to those of other mosquito-borne diseases, misdiagnosis is common and has masked the virus’s true spread for years.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Recent findings by a team at &lt;strong&gt;Charité – Universitätsmedizin Berlin&lt;/strong&gt;, led by &lt;strong&gt;Professor Jan Felix Drexler&lt;/strong&gt;, have shown that oropouche virus infections are far more widespread than previously believed. In a study published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/laninf/article/PIIS1473-3099(25)00110-0/fulltext" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The Lancet Infectious Diseases&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, Drexler’s team analyzed over &lt;strong&gt;9,400 blood samples&lt;/strong&gt; collected in &lt;strong&gt;Bolivia, Brazil, Colombia, Costa Rica, Ecuador&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Peru&lt;/strong&gt; between 2001 and 2022. The presence of antibodies revealed that, across all regions, around &lt;strong&gt;6%&lt;/strong&gt; of people had been exposed to the virus. In parts of the &lt;strong&gt;Amazon&lt;/strong&gt;, this number climbed to over &lt;strong&gt;10%&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;






&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Climate Change and El Niño Amplify the Spread&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The current spread of oropouche virus appears to be driven largely by &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/01/earths-arctic-region-flips-releasing-more-co%e2%82%82-than-it-absorbs-for-the-first-time/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="77239" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;climatic conditions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, particularly consistent &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://dailygalaxy.com/2025/05/discovery-atlantic-global-consequences/" target="_blank" data-type="post" data-id="88252" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;heat and rainfall&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Researchers believe that weather events like &lt;strong&gt;El Niño&lt;/strong&gt;, which increase humidity and temperatures across the tropics, have played a major role in creating ideal breeding conditions for the virus’s insect vectors. Unlike traditional mosquitoes, oropouche is spread by tiny biting midges known as &lt;strong&gt;Ceratopogonidae&lt;/strong&gt; — insects small enough to pass through conventional mosquito nets.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Machine learning models used by Drexler’s team suggest that these climate conditions are the most significant contributors to the virus’s transmission patterns. The virus remains most prevalent in the &lt;strong&gt;Amazon rainforest&lt;/strong&gt;, but high-risk zones have also been identified across &lt;strong&gt;Central America&lt;/strong&gt;, the &lt;strong&gt;Caribbean&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;southern coastal Brazil&lt;/strong&gt;. People living in higher-altitude regions were found to be less affected, as the cooler temperatures reduce insect activity.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Rising Risks for Pregnant Women&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Public health researchers are now turning their attention to the virus’s potential impact on &lt;strong&gt;pregnant women&lt;/strong&gt;. Recent reports from affected countries include &lt;strong&gt;two deaths&lt;/strong&gt; of young, healthy women and &lt;strong&gt;several cases&lt;/strong&gt; where infection during pregnancy appeared to cause &lt;strong&gt;miscarriages&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;congenital malformations&lt;/strong&gt;. While Drexler notes that oropouche seems to harm unborn babies “less frequently than Zika,” the full extent of its effects remains unclear and needs further investigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;“There is still relatively little known about the virus,” Drexler said, emphasizing the need for urgent research into how the virus affects fetal development. With no vaccine or specific treatment currently available, health experts are urging people in high-risk areas — especially women who are pregnant or planning to become pregnant — to take strong precautions. These include wearing &lt;strong&gt;long-sleeved clothing&lt;/strong&gt;, using &lt;strong&gt;insect repellents&lt;/strong&gt; like &lt;em&gt;DEET&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;icaridin&lt;/em&gt;, and seeking medical advice before traveling to affected regions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Insect Control Remains the Only Defense&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Despite its growing prevalence, the oropouche virus remains without a &lt;strong&gt;licensed vaccine&lt;/strong&gt; or &lt;strong&gt;approved antiviral treatment&lt;/strong&gt;. For now, protection hinges on preventing bites from the midges that carry the disease. Unlike the more widely known &lt;em&gt;Aedes&lt;/em&gt; mosquitoes, the midges that transmit oropouche are extremely small — often no larger than &lt;strong&gt;3 millimeters&lt;/strong&gt; — and are able to pass through many types of &lt;strong&gt;mosquito netting&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Because of this, &lt;strong&gt;fine-mesh nets&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;protective clothing&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;repellents&lt;/strong&gt; are currently the only effective defenses. Drexler warns that as long as high infection rates persist and the virus remains poorly understood, the public — particularly in the &lt;strong&gt;Amazon basin&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;tropical lowlands&lt;/strong&gt; — should remain cautious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="code-block code-block-3"&gt;


&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-6966113680805338" data-ad-slot="4349301016" data-ad-format="auto" data-full-width-responsive="true"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Daily Galaxy</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 11:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7gFBVV95cUxOaE53WTk3N0l0NzZrM2tVRkhnZlJhVkZ4cl9NdmYwWUpDdjVpNk1HQ252cDJ6TExybEN2LUJjNjVEMVZ5cGxaWDFJbDNtQTdla1FNNjZ2T2h4ZmhOR2VpeE1zTjB1RlBnZE5Vcm1ZdWVBRDdDbGx3N1dHNWI1V2JrUlJSemJwenJDMlA1dWdPa2NlUkV2bHk2Y2R2WUs5Z2NlMWNWYVZ3V19LMVZuRTdhNFE4bVdQRUJPNHQ3emc1YmctVEdVM21kR0RvZ2xmeFZDdjU5aW5mb1o0SzZZTExBR2lOVHhVTURNYlM2YlRR</guid></item><item><title>与疫苗和治疗有关的RSV婴儿住院率急剧下降-卫报 | Dramatic dip in baby hospitalizations for RSV linked to vaccine and treatment - The Guardian</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxQdjVTWWQwQVpfNk9jcFJaRjZubWVBWnQxbVRYNzZ3QlVGUFhuejg0OE90bWtmNWZpdmtwbHVaRjlYc3RmY0tNeUJZUVk5c0k1OVQyRmI1WWNjQXpVV1hPcEQ1XzNra2JRV25ydUFMZEZCZDMzdHhIdGphTUdZWVpsX3NDM25qZlhwUGZmYQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;New &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/vaccines" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt; and treatments are linked to a dramatic decline in RSV hospitalizations for babies, according to a new &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7416a1.htm" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;This past winter was the first RSV season with widespread availability of a vaccine given during &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/lifeandstyle/pregnancy" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;pregnancy&lt;/a&gt; and a monoclonal antibody treatment given in the first eight months of life to prevent RSV (respiratory syncytial virus).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"us-news","tags":[{"id":"us-news/healthcare","type":"Keyword","title":"US healthcare"},{"id":"science/infectiousdiseases","type":"Keyword","title":"Infectious diseases"},{"id":"society/children","type":"Keyword","title":"Children"},{"id":"us-news/us-news","type":"Keyword","title":"US news"},{"id":"science/medical-research","type":"Keyword","title":"Medical research"},{"id":"society/health","type":"Keyword","title":"Health"},{"id":"society/society","type":"Keyword","title":"Society"},{"id":"society/vaccines","type":"Keyword","title":"Vaccines and immunisation"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"profile/melody-schreiber","type":"Contributor","title":"Melody Schreiber"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/us-news","type":"Tracking","title":"US News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"us-news/2025/may/18/rsv-cases-decline-vaccines-treatment","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;RSV is the leading cause of hospitalization for infants in the US, and newborns under two months are most at risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Compared with the RSV seasons from 2018 to 2020, before the Covid pandemic took off, this year’s RSV hospitalizations in babies under the age of seven months dropped by as much as 56%, depending on the data used. In newborns, hospitalizations decreased by as much as 71%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Heather Auerbach, an emergency physician, noticed that trend, saying: “There was definitely less RSV this year compared to the last two to three years.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The young children who did get sick enough to go to the emergency room often needed lower levels of care, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“I think I saw fewer critically ill kids from it this year than I have the last couple of years,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Even if the kids get sick and even if they wind up in the hospital, there’s a difference between just needing some suction and oxygen versus needing to be on high flow [oxygen] or BiPap or in the PICU or things like that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Auerbach wishes her own family could have benefited from the RSV shots, sharing that her son was hospitalized with RSV in January 2020 when he was only three weeks old. He was born full-term with no complications, and then he got sick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“All of a sudden, his breathing had just gotten much worse,” Auerbach said. He was less alert and started using his stomach muscles to help him breathe – classic signs of respiratory complications with RSV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Even when infants don’t show these signs, they are still at risk from RSV infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Little babies with RSV can have periods of apnea where they stop breathing, and it can happen suddenly, even if they don’t have other symptoms,” Auerbach said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Her son was admitted to the hospital, and when he returned home, she and her husband, who is also a physician, needed to suction away mucus regularly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“I wish the shot had been around then, but we were a few years too early,” Auerbach said. “I genuinely think that could have saved him a hospitalization.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;For parents, a child’s RSV hospitalization can be a wrenching time, full of uncertainty and fear. Hospital stays of any length are disruptive and expensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Kids get very, very sick from this” without vaccines and preventative treatments, and preventing any of that is a major breakthrough, Auerbach said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;She also wonders whether the shots could have prevented, even for a time, additional complications down the road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Her son started wheezing a few months after his illness. He received an asthma diagnosis, which was “very early and unusual”. Auerbach, her husband and their son’s pulmonologist believe it was related to the RSV infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“There’s no guarantee that he may not have ended up with [asthma] regardless. But do I think he would have had it at six months? No,” Auerbach said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;According to one tool for tracking RSV hospitalizations, the CDC’s &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/php/surveillance/rsv-net.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;RSV-Net&lt;/a&gt;, the peak in hospitalizations for children under the age of one this year was roughly half of that at the height of the 2023-24 season, and one-third the peak of the 2022-23 season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Such a dramatic decline only holds for these very young children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Children aged 1-4 and 5-17 had higher rates of hospitalization from RSV this winter compared with last winter, according to RSV-Net.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Higher RSV hospitalization rates in older children – who are not eligible for RSV prevention products – suggest this season may have been more severe than previous seasons,” Jasmine Reed, a CDC spokesperson, said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Notably, hospitalization rates in babies under three months old were half of previous seasons.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Typically, more young infants are hospitalized during worse RSV seasons. That hospitalization rates still “dropped markedly” among babies likely means the shots are working well, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;It could mean the shots are working even better than the numbers indicate, because the drop in hospitalizations is occurring even amid a more severe season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;These trends track with the new CDC study. Babies under eight months old had a decrease in RSV hospitalizations of 43%, according to RSV-Net, or 28%, according to the New Vaccine Surveillance Network (NVSN).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;When the researchers excluded Houston from NVSN data – the city saw an early RSV season before preventatives were widely available – that drop went from 28% to 56%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The biggest change happened among newborns under the age of two months – the most vulnerable group to RSV infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;In these very young babies, RSV hospitalization dropped by 52%, according to RSV-Net. The rate dropped by 45%, according to NVSN – but when Houston was excluded, the decrease was 71%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Older children did not see the same benefit, indicating that the shots are behind the decrease, rather than a change in behavior, testing or transmission rates, the researchers said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="b838a10c-fa52-4502-a284-5027dd9914d6" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-1your1i"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":31,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Trump health cuts create ‘real danger’ around disease outbreaks, workers warn","elementId":"b838a10c-fa52-4502-a284-5027dd9914d6","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/may/11/health-cuts-trump-disease-outbreaks"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Children older than eight months, who were largely not eligible for the preventatives, were hospitalized at higher rates this winter compared with the same times in 2018–20.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;That means the significant drop in young infants’ hospitalizations now could be an underestimate, researchers concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The monoclonal antibody treatment, nirsevimab, may be given to babies under eight months old either at birth, if they are born during RSV season, or as they enter winter. It is given to babies aged eight to 19 months old if they’re at high risk because of medical conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;A vaccine for pregnant people, Pfizer’s Abrysvo, is offered in the third trimester during RSV season, which is usually between September and January. Those antibodies offer protection to newborns for several months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The study shows how high uptake of the vaccines and preventative treatments “can lead to remarkable public health impact in protecting young babies from severe illness”, Reed said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Increased use of RSV prevention products during future seasons might lead to even larger reductions in RSV hospitalizations among infants.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 11:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQdjVTWWQwQVpfNk9jcFJaRjZubWVBWnQxbVRYNzZ3QlVGUFhuejg0OE90bWtmNWZpdmtwbHVaRjlYc3RmY0tNeUJZUVk5c0k1OVQyRmI1WWNjQXpVV1hPcEQ1XzNra2JRV25ydUFMZEZCZDMzdHhIdGphTUdZWVpsX3NDM25qZlhwUGZmYQ</guid></item><item><title>童年时期的健康饮食与第一次月经后期有关-《华盛顿邮报》 | Healthy diet in childhood linked to later first menstrual period - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxQUkY3c3d0RkN4Z1NyLWtOcjRoeWxCNGt3UFJPU1RvanlmOWpuNC1PMmZfREt5OFMyRGw5cjZHTzNLX1JkamRqQTNpdTd0OGpyeE9TNXhfdHpwNWZubnR6LTl2SldEa1J3Z1o0Tmxfc2F4R1JpNXE1OERpUWpVai1hOWNleE9UUHdXMnI3TkZDUVJ2dw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BHF5Z6NKTRH6DLA3EKIYGEYWX4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Eating an unhealthy diet is tied to an earlier first period, a new analysis suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NXLZLIPWHVHNVGOWOP7GMJ2BY4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/humrep/advance-article/doi/10.1093/humrep/deaf072/8125832?login=false" target="_blank"&gt;study linked&lt;/a&gt; a girl’s first menstrual period — a milestone known as menarche — to what she ate, showing ties between potentially inflammatory diets rich in processed and refined foods, red meat and beverages such as soda and an earlier onset of menstruation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IKHLDPCTNRGY3PIVFG6V6MLLQI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Published in Human Reproduction, the study looked at 7,530 participants in the Growing Up Today Study, an ongoing study that evaluates factors thought to influence health across a lifetime. Participants enrolled in 1996 and 2004 and answered questionnaires about diet and activity, general health, family history, demographic factors and when they got their first period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Y5HZMNIXFFET5O5OA4YFMAKRIY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Researchers assessed participants’ diets using two rubrics: the Alternative Healthy Eating Index, a score based on participants’ adherence to a healthy diet, and the Empirical Dietary Inflammatory Pattern, which identifies diets linked to inflammation. These potentially inflammatory diets are higher in processed foods, beverages like soda and juice, and red meat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HXEPQEJIUVE6VC26USTSUZAAPM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Ninety-three percent of participants started their period during the study, at a median age of 13.1 years. But the age of menarche varied among participants with different diets. Overall, having a healthier diet predicted later menarche, and those who ate the healthiest diet were 8 percent less likely to get their first period in the next month. The association remained after researchers adjusted for body mass index, height and neighborhood socioeconomic status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="H2SYSSHYGZEPXDSJGZA6TPUFJA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The association could be affected by diet’s effects on sex hormones, the researchers write — influences that may be “at least partially independent” of body size or height.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SDXSF6G4UVCY5NYGIEPRJZAD7Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Importantly, these results were independent of BMI and height, demonstrating the importance of a healthy diet regardless of body size,” Holly Harris, an associate professor at the Fred Hutchinson Cancer Center who led the study, said in a news &lt;a href="https://www.eshre.eu/Press-Room/Press-releases-2025/dietary-patterns-menarch" target="_blank"&gt;release&lt;/a&gt;. “As earlier age at menarche is associated with multiple later life outcomes, including higher risk of diabetes, obesity, cardiovascular disease and breast cancer, this may be an important period for trying to reduce the risk of these chronic diseases.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WROXWMWSZZHRTBEJ6IGHRXDVWI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;According to a 2020 &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data/nhsr/nhsr146-508.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, the average age at first menstrual period in the United States fell from 12.1 in 1995 to 11.9 in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p id="M2XSMXC77JFKJCW3X3XCZRESSA" class="wpds-c-esEUdQ wpds-c-esEUdQ-hqvHjm-isBold-false wpds-c-esEUdQ-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="M2XSMXC77JFKJCW3X3XCZRESSA" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Dietary patterns and age at menarche in a prospective study of girls in the USA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:32:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxQUkY3c3d0RkN4Z1NyLWtOcjRoeWxCNGt3UFJPU1RvanlmOWpuNC1PMmZfREt5OFMyRGw5cjZHTzNLX1JkamRqQTNpdTd0OGpyeE9TNXhfdHpwNWZubnR6LTl2SldEa1J3Z1o0Tmxfc2F4R1JpNXE1OERpUWpVai1hOWNleE9UUHdXMnI3TkZDUVJ2dw</guid></item><item><title>外科医生首次进行人膀胱移植-《纽约时报》 | Surgeons Perform First Human Bladder Transplant - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMie0FVX3lxTE5KSHpCNTFTMUM4RmRRWkdyVjk5OGdRR3BmcU5CUUpQdGYzOU1VOVI3UjNocFlHTHZzM1FCYkppWUJJTF9XUm1EUUtvcUpOeDVZcGxUZ2xwU0dpZnVRazFkZGItRk1WeGc1M3l2bWdtdlo5ZFZEQ3k5UFZCaw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;Surgeons in Southern California have performed the first human bladder transplant, introducing a new, potentially life-changing procedure for people with debilitating bladder conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The operation was performed earlier this month by a pair of surgeons from the University of California, Los Angeles, and the University of Southern California on a 41-year-old man who had lost much of his bladder capacity from treatments for a rare form of bladder cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“I was a ticking time bomb,” the patient, Oscar Larrainzar, said on Thursday during a follow-up appointment with his doctors. “But now I have hope.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;The doctors plan to perform bladder transplants in four more patients as part of a &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://www.uclahealth.org/clinical-trials/deceased-donor-bladder-or-combined-kidney-bladder" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt; to get a sense of outcomes like bladder capacity and graft complications before pursuing a larger trial to expand its use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-s99gbd StoryBodyCompanionColumn" data-testid="companionColumn-1"&gt;&lt;div class="css-53u6y8"&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;&lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://keck.usc.edu/faculty-search/inderbir-singh-gill/" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Inderbir Gill&lt;/a&gt;, who performed the surgery along with &lt;a class="css-yywogo" href="https://profiles.ucla.edu/nima.nassiri" title="" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Nima Nassiri&lt;/a&gt;, called it “the realization of a dream” for treating thousands of patients with crippling pelvic pain, inflammation and recurrent infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-at9mc1 evys1bk0"&gt;“There is no question: A potential door has been opened for these people that did not exist earlier,” said Dr. Gill, the chairman of the urology department at U.S.C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-kbghgg"&gt;&lt;div class="css-121kum4"&gt;&lt;p class="css-171quhb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="css-asuuk5"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-7axq9l" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-1b5b8u1"&gt;&lt;path fill="currentColor" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M2.5 12a9.5 9.5 0 1 1 19 0 9.5 9.5 0 0 1-19 0Zm8.5 1.75v-7.5h2v7.5h-2Zm0 2v2h2v-2h-2Z" clip-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-noscript-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;We are having trouble retrieving the article content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Please enable JavaScript in your browser settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dv1kvn" id="optimistic-truncator-a11y" tabindex="-1"&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access. If you are in Reader mode please exit and &lt;a href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F05%2F18%2Fhealth%2Fbladder-transplant-human.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;log into&lt;/a&gt; your Times account, or &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F05%2F18%2Fhealth%2Fbladder-transplant-human.html"&gt;subscribe&lt;/a&gt; for all of The Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="css-1g71tqy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 24 24" aria-hidden="true" class="css-63woee" data-testid="optimistic-truncator-spinner"&gt;&lt;g fill="currentColor"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.28 22.8a.72.72 0 1 0 1.44 0v-6.72a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72Z" opacity=".37"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M17.766 21.16a.72.72 0 1 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.436a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.437Z" opacity=".26"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.506 14.653a.72.72 0 0 0 .445 1.37l6.391-2.078a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.369l-6.39 2.077Z" opacity=".61"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M5.07 20.314a.72.72 0 0 0 1.164.847l3.95-5.437a.72.72 0 1 0-1.165-.846l-3.95 5.436Z" opacity=".48"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.049 16.022a.72.72 0 0 0 .445-1.37l-6.391-2.076a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.39 2.076Z" opacity=".17"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M22.494 9.347a.72.72 0 1 0-.445-1.37l-6.391 2.078a.72.72 0 1 0 .445 1.369l6.39-2.077Z" opacity=".09"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M6.234 2.84a.72.72 0 0 0-1.165.846l3.95 5.436a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165-.846l-3.95-5.437Z" opacity=".87"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M1.951 7.978a.72.72 0 1 0-.445 1.37l6.391 2.076a.72.72 0 1 0 .445-1.37l-6.39-2.076Z" opacity=".74"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M18.93 3.686a.72.72 0 0 0-1.164-.847l-3.95 5.437a.72.72 0 0 0 1.165.846l3.95-5.436Z" opacity=".02"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M12.72 1.2a.72.72 0 1 0-1.44 0v6.72a.72.72 0 0 0 1.44 0V1.2Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;div data-testid="optimistic-truncator-message" class="css-6yo1no"&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Thank you for your patience while we verify access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Already a subscriber? &lt;a data-testid="log-in-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://myaccount.nytimes.com/auth/login?response_type=cookie&amp;amp;client_id=vi&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F05%2F18%2Fhealth%2Fbladder-transplant-human.html&amp;amp;asset=opttrunc"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="css-3kpklk"&gt;Want all of The Times? &lt;a data-testid="subscribe-link" class="css-z5ryv4" href="https://www.nytimes.com/subscription?campaignId=89WYR&amp;amp;redirect_uri=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nytimes.com%2F2025%2F05%2F18%2Fhealth%2Fbladder-transplant-human.html"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 10:00:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE5KSHpCNTFTMUM4RmRRWkdyVjk5OGdRR3BmcU5CUUpQdGYzOU1VOVI3UjNocFlHTHZzM1FCYkppWUJJTF9XUm1EUUtvcUpOeDVZcGxUZ2xwU0dpZnVRazFkZGItRk1WeGc1M3l2bWdtdlo5ZFZEQ3k5UFZCaw</guid></item><item><title>您的身体是否需要寄生虫清除？可能不会- Salon.com | Does your body need a parasite purge? Probably not - Salon.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQT2FxYWJzc191b2lvMlZ0dS1MU3ZqNHdoNGZNMzFKeFpzSVE0aWRYZXpMcUJXeWNtcldzeGl0UDlZSzlEeHJvQk9ucmRKaTljbTBvSnhUR3pHbzMxQmEtMkhweWlRSVJsa0RCaHoyVUUyRC1zNGdCdVBZTS1GNGF6R1Jwd3hhdzFTbXNj?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="article-content"&gt;
								&lt;input type="hidden" id="article_url" value="2025/05/18/does-your-body-need-a-parasite-purge-probably-not/"&gt;
																	
																
								&lt;p&gt;In 2008, Kurt started to experience things that hadn't bothered him before: dry skin, fatigue, irregular bowel movements and a white coating that formed over his tongue. For years, he saw both traditional doctors and &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2015/09/05/the_dark_side_of_alternative_medicine_and_holistic_healing_partner/" target="_blank"&gt;holistic medicine&lt;/a&gt; providers, who recommended or prescribed certain treatments to help him feel better. But he didn’t see much progress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To try and find a solution, he started researching his symptoms online, where he came across a forum of people reporting their experiences with parasite cleanses. Soon after, he bought a 30-day protocol, marketed to rid the body of &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/parasites" target="_blank"&gt;parasites&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Nothing was working,” Kurt, who is using his first name only for privacy reasons, told Salon in a phone interview. “I was kind of just willing to try anything.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parasite cleanses have been around for decades, but they have recently &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/search?q=parasite%20cleanse&amp;amp;t=1747162348188"&gt;surged in popularity on social media&lt;/a&gt;, with influencers and companies endorsing products or homemade solutions that promise to rid the body of harmful intestinal worms. Many doctors say the likelihood of having an intestinal parasite in the U.S. is relatively low and recommend people see a health care provider to get tested for a parasite if they think they have one rather than turning to online therapies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While many people report positive impacts when taking herbal supplements, these substances can come with side effects and contraindications just like pharmaceutical medications. Some of the ingredients included in these cleanses can be harmful when taken too frequently or at too large of a dose, and these formulations could also impact the natural balance of bacteria in the gut keeping us healthy. In any case, self-medicating with supplements online inherently carries its own risks, said Dr. Thomas Moore, an infectious disease doctor at the University of Kansas School of Medicine at Wichita.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“If someone does have a parasite, there is actual medicine to address those parasites,” Moore told Salon in a phone interview. “There is no need to go on the internet for it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The prevalence of intestinal parasites in the U.S.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hundreds of parasites have the ability to infect humans, including lice, mites and ticks. However, parasite cleanses typically promise to purge the body of intestinal parasites such as tapeworms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="right_quote"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"If someone does have a parasite, there is actual medicine to address those parasites. There is no need to go on the internet for it."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The majority of intestinal parasites that have historically infected humans have been declining in prevalence and are currently rare in the United States, according to a 2023 review in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0893395223001229"&gt;Modern Pathology&lt;/a&gt;. Hookworms, for example, used to devastate communities in the South, but they were &lt;a href="https://www.pbs.org/wgbh/nova/article/how-a-worm-gave-the-south-a-bad-name/"&gt;by and large eradicated with the introduction of indoor plumbing and urbanization&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, intestinal parasite infections do still occur in the U.S., and many &lt;a href="http://www.ajtmh.org/view/journals/tpmd/90/5/article-p783.xml" target="_blank"&gt;disproportionately affect people with reduced access to health care&lt;/a&gt; like &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7847297/" target="_blank"&gt;those living in poverty&lt;/a&gt; or immigrant communities. Some of these parasites like the microscopic &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/cryptosporidium/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;cryptosporidium&lt;/a&gt; — usually transmitted through water or food that has been contaminated with feces, including &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2024/12/23/why-conservatives-are-now-obsessed-with-raw-milk/" target="_blank"&gt;raw milk&lt;/a&gt; — have become more common over the past decade, according to the review.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may have heard of some of the more common intestinal parasite infections. &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pinworm/about/index.html"&gt;Pinworms&lt;/a&gt;, for example, cause itchiness in the anus and primarily spread between young children and their families, affecting &lt;a href="https://cchp.ucsf.edu/resources/illness-sheets/pinworms#:~:text=It%20is%20estimated%20that%20five,re%2Dinfect%20a%20treated%20child."&gt;up to 15% of the population&lt;/a&gt; at any given time. &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/giardia/about/index.html"&gt;Giardia&lt;/a&gt;, which causes diarrhea and can be acquired from drinking water from streams that has been contaminated, is estimated to affect &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/healthy-water-data/documentation/giardiasis-nndss-summary-report-for-2019.html#:~:text=Figure%201.,%E2%80%932019%20(N%20=%20158%2C344)&amp;amp;text=Since%202011%2C%20the%20incidence%20of,confirmed%20and%203.4%25%20nonconfirmed)."&gt;3.7% of the U.S. population&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other intestinal parasites can have more severe side effects. &lt;em&gt;Ascaris lumbricoides, &lt;/em&gt;a type of roundworm from pigs that has been reported in a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25626125/" target="_blank"&gt;few cases&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38526329/" target="_blank"&gt;humans&lt;/a&gt;, can cause issues with the lungs or growth problems in children in severe cases. However, there are medicines available to eradicate it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Want more health and science stories in your inbox? Subscribe to Salon's weekly newsletter &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/newsletter"&gt;Lab Notes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In general, intestinal parasite infections are far more common in developing countries, where deworming practices are sometimes performed on populations that are exposed to high levels of contamination that put them at risk. But that is not the case in the states, where exposure to raw sewage or other things that can transmit intestinal parasites are comparably low, said Dr. Carlos Chaccour, a tropical disease researcher at the Barcelona Institute for Global Health in Spain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“In the U.S., which is highly urbanized and there are laws for sanitation, waste management, etc., the prevalence is substantially low,” Chaccour told Salon in a phone interview. “It’s definitely not a public health problem.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Finding out if you actually have a parasite&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the case that someone is infected with a parasite, it’s important to get tested to identify which one it is, as each one has its own treatment protocol. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people online say the tests used to diagnose parasites are inaccurate and prone to false negatives. While it is true that some infections could be missed in a single sample, the CDC recommends testing stool three times. In one &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC85240/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; of refugees in the U.S., for example, the first stool sample detected 80% of cases, the second increased the sensitivity to 92% and the third detected the remaining cases. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, other techniques are available to detect parasitic infections like blood tests, which vary based on the test but are generally even more accurate. One 2014 &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/24427320/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found many different versions of these tests accurately detected the parasites causing pinworm close to 100% of the time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="left_quote"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"These cleansers often just encourage that. They irritate the stomach lining and encourage mucosal shedding, and to the untrained eye, it looks like a parasite."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Self-diagnosing parasites in your own stool can be tricky. For one, there are many different kinds that all look different, and evidence of parasitic infection can be excreted as parasitic larvae, which are microscopic. Some of the body’s natural processes can also mimic something that looks like an intestinal worm. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, some of these supplements can change stool in a way that makes it look like a parasite is being shed when it isn't, said Chris Brianik, a biologist who moderates a Reddit group about parasites where people commonly discuss cleanses. The intestines shed their lining periodically, which produces a mucus that can be visible in stool and &lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/rope-worm#intestinal-mucus-theory"&gt;may be misidentified as a parasite,&lt;/a&gt; he explained.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In two published &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6791610/#s3"&gt;case reports,&lt;/a&gt; two patients took the herbal supplement &lt;em&gt;Mimosa pudica&lt;/em&gt;, which they had read online could “cleanse” gut parasites. However, the report concluded that “this substance clumps together in stool, causing long, stringy structures to form,” which made the patients think they were passing worms when they were not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“These cleansers often just encourage that,” Brianik said. “They irritate the stomach lining and encourage mucosal shedding, and to the untrained eye, it looks like a parasite.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Savina Bertollini, an herbalist in Marche, Italy, said she has worked with health care providers to treat people who were infected with a parasite while traveling. While some herbs have been effective in her experience, these supplements can cause side effects when taken long-term and are not “miracle pills,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bertollini said she is skeptical of cleanses marketed for large numbers of people that are used in a “preventative” way without confirming that they have a parasite in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Someone might indeed need a parasite treatment,” Bertollini told Salon in an email. But for someone who does not know whether they have parasites and has not consulted with a health care professional, using a cleanse they bought because of an ad on social media or something similar "could create negative health consequences,” she added.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supplements are not without risks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of the ingredients in things marketed as a parasite cleanse online may contain things like dietary fiber, which are unlikely to do harm, said Sebastian Lourido, a biology professor at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But if you are suffering from a real parasite infection, that is not going to help, and delaying treatment is probably going to be detrimental,” he told Salon in a phone interview.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parasite cleanses contain a wide range of ingredients depending on the product, and much of the information about how these supplements impact the body is anecdotal. One small study found &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17472487/"&gt;dried papaya seeds were associated with reduced intestinal parasites&lt;/a&gt; in Nigerian children. But the majority of studies looking at the effects of herbal supplements like these on parasites have been &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37230485/"&gt;conducted in test tubes&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10392325/#s0002"&gt;culture dishes&lt;/a&gt; — not in humans. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to herbal supplements, however, some cleanses include &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/topic/ivermectin" target="_blank"&gt;ivermectin&lt;/a&gt;, an antiparasitic drug used to treat river blindness and elephantitis, which leads to the painful enlargement of body parts. While ivermectin has saved millions of lives around the world from conditions like these, taking these drugs without having parasites or without a doctor to help guide dosing can be dangerous, Chaccour said. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In recent years, ivermectin has been caught up in misinformation circulating online: During the height of the COVID-19 pandemic, inaccurate claims that it cured the virus spread on social media, and many began using animal formulations in an attempt to treat &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/consumers/consumer-updates/ivermectin-and-covid-19#:~:text=Here's%20What%20You%20Need%20to,against%20COVID%2019%20in%20humans." target="_blank"&gt;COVID&lt;/a&gt; and even &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/the-monitor/covid-vaccine-concerns-and-claims-about-ivermectin-as-cancer-treatment-the-monitor/"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;. Despite &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/31/well/ivermectin-cancer-covid.html"&gt;concerns of misuse&lt;/a&gt;, legislation allowing ivermectin to be sold over-the-counter instead of requiring a prescription has recently &lt;a href="https://edition.cnn.com/2025/04/24/health/ivermectin-infection-treatment-prevention-wellness"&gt;passed in Idaho, Tennessee and Arkansas&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moore said ivermectin was not the panacea some are making it out to be and that it is not a benign drug in large quantities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All drugs have risks and benefits,” he said. “If you're taking any drug, regardless of what it is to treat something that you don't actually have, then you're taking all of the risk and you get none of the benefit.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some substances in parasite cleanses may disrupt the microbiome: the balance of natural bacteria in the gut that &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s41231-021-00091-4" target="_blank"&gt;helps digest food and keep the body healthy&lt;/a&gt;, Lourido said. Although scientists are still uncovering how the balance of bacteria in the microbiome impacts the body, upsetting this balance in the gut has been associated with changes to the &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5695238/"&gt;immune and metabolic systems &lt;/a&gt;— and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10384867/"&gt;even mental health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many cleanses also recommend eating certain foods or restricting one’s diet, which could also disrupt this system. Alternatively, those dietary changes could also be behind some of the positive changes reported after a cleanse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“When you cause significant changes in the intestine, you are at times obliterating many of the beneficial organisms that are helping us digest food, but in some cases, producing vitamins that are actually occupying that niche and preventing bad organisms from taking over,” Lourido said. “All of those different functions … cease to occur correctly when we have diarrhea and we all of sudden make a dramatic change to eating only one kind of food.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kurt’s cleanse contained black walnut, cloves and wormwood, along with a handful of other herbs. Most of the cleanse went by without him noticing any changes, but he started to have what he described as “a lot coming out of him in the bathroom” in the last week of it. Then, things took a dark turn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Extreme anxiety woke him up sweating in the middle of the night. His mental health changed for the worse, and he started to feel numb and anhedonic — things that used to make him happy no longer did. This went on for years. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“At least a year or two after, I was in really bad shape,” Kurt said. “I was wondering if I was ever going to be the same person that I was prior to doing this cleanse.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kurt is not entirely sure whether he had a parasite or not, or how the supplements interacted with his system. But he does think they caused a major shift. He was excreting things he had never seen in his stool before and feeling things he had never felt before. Looking back, he thinks he overdid it and that his body was not ready for the supplements he was taking. To him, it seemed like his reaction was not typical compared to what he had seen others report online.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“At the end of the day, there are a lot of herbs out there and they are very powerful," he said. “I suppose that I will never really get answers as to what really happened because unfortunately, I never really knew what I was dealing with prior to this.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Supplements are regulated for safety but not efficacy by the 1994 Dietary Supplement Health and Education Act, which is enforced by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration. This agency, along with the Federal Trade Commission, is in charge of monitoring companies to make sure what they're selling on the shelves matches what is being advertised.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Years after Kurt did his cleanse, the FDA sent a warning letter to the company that he bought it from, alleging the company mislabeled its supplements as medical treatments and did not contain enough information about the ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The problem with these parasitic cleansers is you don’t really know what is actually going on,” said Dr. Michael Schmidt, a microbiologist and immunologist at the MUSC Medical University of South Carolina. “In general, they come with ‘buyer beware’ attached.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The rise of the parasite cleanse&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bertollini, the herbalist, said she has seen a “dramatic upswing” in the popularity of these sorts of products in recent years, but that much of it seems to be based on people’s “fear of having parasites.” This fear makes evolutionary sense: Parasites aren't technically predators, but they can cause serious harm as they leech off of their hosts. (On the other hand, some parasites &lt;a href="https://www.salon.com/2023/10/31/parasites-are-the-bedrock-of-life-and-the-unifiy-its-time-to-give-them-the-respect-they-deserve/" target="_blank"&gt;can actually be beneficial&lt;/a&gt; — it depends on the species and the relationship with its host.) In one &lt;a href="https://source.washu.edu/2012/02/study-extends-the-ecology-of-fear-to-fear-of-parasites/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;, raccoons and squirrels would sacrifice food to avoid tick-infested areas, suggesting that they valued the threat of parasites more than the promise of food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This ancient, justified fear could be the root of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK541021/#:~:text=Epidemiology,Go%20to:"&gt;delusional parasitosis&lt;/a&gt;, a mental health condition in which people have psychological delusions that they have a parasite when they don't really. These folks may be particularly at risk of overconsuming cleansing products, Moore said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, many people are turning to online treatments for various conditions because of a growing mistrust in the medical system and a lack of access to health care. Although it has a far lower rate of parasitic disease than other countries, the &lt;a href="https://www.factmr.com/report/4496/detox-products-market#:~:text=What%20is%20Propelling%20the%20Demand%20for%20Detox%20Products%20in%20the%20United%20States?&amp;amp;text=The%20market%20in%20the%20United,detox%20products%20in%20the%20U.S."&gt;U.S. is the biggest buyer of detox products,&lt;/a&gt; including parasite cleanses. At the same time, one Gallup poll estimated that &lt;a href="https://news.gallup.com/poll/658148/inability-pay-care-medicine-hits-new-high.aspx"&gt;11% of the population cannot afford or access health care&lt;/a&gt; as more people turn to online supplements in an attempt to treat their health problems. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take people with conditions that notoriously lack treatments like Crohn’s disease or other inflammatory bowel disorders, which share some common symptoms with intestinal parasite infections. Of the estimated &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/digestive-diseases/crohns-disease/definition-facts" target="_blank"&gt;1 million people&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. with Crohn’s, &lt;a href="https://www.crohnscolitisfoundation.org/patientsandcaregivers/What-is-crohns-disease/treatment#:~:text=Surgery,frequently%20recurs%20later%20in%20life."&gt;two-thirds will end up needing surgery&lt;/a&gt; because available medications are not enough to keep the progression of the disease at bay. Many may be trying these cleanses in an attempt to feel relief, Moore explained. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“They’ll try a parasite cleanse not because they are convinced they have a parasite, but because they are reaching for something out of desperation,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, more people might be thinking they are infected with parasites as mistrust also grows surrounding the environmental systems designed to protect our food and ecosystems from dangerous waste. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some individuals have gone so far as to stop using &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2017/12/29/dining/raw-water-unfiltered.html"&gt;the water grid&lt;/a&gt; altogether, instead &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2024/12/31/us/raw-water-natural-springs.html"&gt;collecting water from natural streams&lt;/a&gt;. However, that might ironically &lt;em&gt;increase&lt;/em&gt; the risk of drinking water that is contaminated with parasites, if those streams are downriver from waste exposures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There is a bit of truth in the sense that the U.S. has been somehow lax in terms of how much processing you allow for food and how much additional ingredients you have,” Chaccour said. “But that is not the same as going out to nature to collect your own water.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over time, the symptoms Kurt was experiencing after the cleanse faded away. In 2016, he started going to the gym, and his energy levels returned. His gut stopped bothering him, and he had what he describes as some of the best years of his life. Despite the reaction he had to the cleanse, he does feel that it helped him get there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It's hard to say if it was the cleanse that helped me or was it ultimately going to the gym and being a lot more active, or a combination of both.” Kurt said. “Looking back, I could probably say that it was a positive decision.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, Kurt has recently entered into another challenging part of his life. He is experiencing a range of new symptoms he thinks stem from an exposure to toxic mold. He has considered doing a parasite cleanse again, even though he doesn't think he has a parasite. On one hand, he feels it helped him 10 years ago and could have a similar effect again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“But I feel like, if that's not the case, I'm not really in a position to be able to deal with negative effects that might come from it,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is burnt out from visiting doctors. In his search for more information on what could be causing his malaise, he finds it difficult to sort through what information online is real and what is bogus, he said. But the anecdotal experiences can only go so far, and what works for one person may not work for another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“There's a lot of misinformation, but I do think there is a lot of good information out there, and it's just that it comes to a point when it's very difficult to separate which is which,” he said. “It’s certainly a gamble and I think it has its place. You just have to tread with caution.”&lt;/p&gt;

							&lt;/article&gt;

							

														
							

							
															&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Salon.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 09:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQT2FxYWJzc191b2lvMlZ0dS1MU3ZqNHdoNGZNMzFKeFpzSVE0aWRYZXpMcUJXeWNtcldzeGl0UDlZSzlEeHJvQk9ucmRKaTljbTBvSnhUR3pHbzMxQmEtMkhweWlRSVJsa0RCaHoyVUUyRC1zNGdCdVBZTS1GNGF6R1Jwd3hhdzFTbXNj</guid></item><item><title>一位经过认证的瑜伽和普拉提老师- Fit&amp;Well说，您只需要这五项练习即可建立全身力量和稳定性 | All you need are these five exercises to build full-body strength and stability, says a certified yoga and Pilates teacher - Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi9AFBVV95cUxQUi1EVy1iYmNaYVRMazhKb1pDa2d6OF9HeEptQzdBUDRYeGt2SXZ4Zng1aXNUZW4yQlB4dC1OQUZHSUhwb2wySlZYLXprd1NNMVkxZzBvQkVUVDkwdlBPQXFSc0VNay1jYkZTdzhYTmItZVBlaUQ0Q3d0VzFDNWhUZDF0Sy0yaFk3M2tLZzk1UWJaV0pjb3A4TDdhT2hIWnhMY1ZzRUpDV2YxdUFraGowMWgzMmhsR3h2WEYtbFp5clBYRGptUFFiLU5ibVU5bUhoUXB1a1N4MGY5dF9OMGw2LUVVMXh0OHc3eG9YT0VtVWViTExk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spend any time in a yoga or Pilates class and your body will thank you. Both are mindful movement practices that connect breath with body, but each offers something unique.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yoga draws on thousands of years of wisdom to improve body and mind, while Pilates is a more modern system targeting deep stabilizing muscles, often overlooked in traditional strength training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what if you could unite the best of both worlds? Former professional dancer Tina Traina has done exactly that. She created &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://blog.davidlloyd.co.uk/exercise-classes/introducing-spirit/" target="_blank" data-url="https://blog.davidlloyd.co.uk/exercise-classes/introducing-spirit/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;SPIRIT&lt;/a&gt;, a yoga-Pilates fusion class at &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.davidlloyd.co.uk/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.davidlloyd.co.uk/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;David Lloyd Clubs&lt;/a&gt;, to build strength, alignment, mobility and flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traina says everyone's training should strike a balance between building strength and flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If I constantly train my chest and never stretch, it will start to get tight and lead to poor posture,” says Traina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But you can’t ignore strength work either. “There needs to be enough strength in the body to support good posture,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might think you don’t have time to train both, but Traina specializes in maximizing your returns on the time you have to exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-pgEFQUTQJyNVtZc2DCt4e6" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-pgEFQUTQJyNVtZc2DCt4e6 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;These five bang-for-your-buck moves from her SPIRIT class strengthen your core and legs, support your training if you’re a runner, help improve full-body mobility, and help offset the strains and aches caused by a sedentary lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-five-yoga-and-pilates-exercises-for-strength-and-stability"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Five yoga and Pilates exercises for strength and stability &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-bridge"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Bridge &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 10-12&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lie on your back with knees bent and feet flat on the floor hip-width apart and arms by your sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Press your lower back into the floor to activate your deep core.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lift your hips until your body is in a straight line from shoulders to knees.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tense your glutes, then slowly lower your hips to the floor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traina says:&lt;/strong&gt; “The bridge position focuses on articulating your spine. It stretches the front of your body, especially the hip flexors and thighs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It also strengthens the back of the body, especially the glutes, hamstrings and lower back to help support good posture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You’ll find this exercise in both yoga and Pilates."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-cat-cow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Cat-cow&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Prostock-Studio / iStock / Getty Images Plus)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 30-40sec&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Start on your hands and knees with your wrists under your shoulders and your knees under your hips, with a neutral spine.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inhale as you slowly arch your back, letting your belly drop toward the floor, and lifting your chest and chin.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exhale as you round your spine, pushing your palms into the floor, drawing your belly button in, and tucking your tailbone and your chin toward your chest.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continue moving slowly in time with your breath.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traina says:&lt;/strong&gt; “This simple and often overlooked exercise trains you to articulate all the vertebrae in your spine, and as with yoga and Pilates, it teaches you that every move is controlled by your breath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Think: inhale as you arch and extend and exhale as you round and flex. This drill is great for promoting good breath control which is very important for runners.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-side-lying-leg-lift"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Side-lying leg lift&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: svetikd / Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reps: &lt;/strong&gt;15-20&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lie on your side, supporting your head with one hand and the other hand on the floor in front of you to help with balance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Make sure your ankles, knees and hips are stacked one on top of the other.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lift your top leg slowly, then lower it with control.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;To make this exercise harder, lift your top leg, then lift the bottom leg to meet it, then slowly lower both to the start position. Because it’s a harder progression, reduce the number of reps to 5-10.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traina says:&lt;/strong&gt; “If you struggle with weak or unstable knees, this move will help strengthen the thigh and glute muscles while still promoting good posture and a strong core.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s quite an unstable position, so use your other hand for support and focus on super slow movements. It really helps strengthen the muscles.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-4-pigeon"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Pigeon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Xavier Lorenzo / Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 30-40sec each side&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;On your hands and knees, bring your right knee to your right wrist, and your right foot toward your left wrist, as close as is comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extend your left leg back, lowering your hips toward the floor as far as is comfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your upper body upright or for a deeper stretch, fold forward over your shin.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inhale and exhale slowly, allowing tension to release with each breath.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold for time, then repeat on the other side.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traina says:&lt;/strong&gt; “This classic yoga pose is essential for tight hips and backs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To advance it further, you can keep your body upright and bring your back heel off the floor to stretch the front of your thigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“An easier alternative is child's pose, where you kneel and sit back onto your heels with arms stretched in front of you can ease any tightness in your lower back.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-5-tree"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5. Tree&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 10-20sec each side&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet together and engage your leg muscles.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lift one foot off the floor and place it on the inner thigh, calf or ankle of your standing leg.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bring your hands together in front of your chest, and if you’re able to keep your balance, extend your hands overhead.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fitandwell.com/how-to/how-to-engage-your-core" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/how-to/how-to-engage-your-core"&gt;Engage your core&lt;/a&gt;, upper back and breath to hold this position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold for time, then switch sides.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Traina says:&lt;/strong&gt; “Balancing on one leg strengthens your leg muscles for activities like running, while also training core stability for improved posture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Done right, it also encourages you to open your chest and squeeze your back muscles so that you're at once strengthening and stretching your body.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 05:02:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9AFBVV95cUxQUi1EVy1iYmNaYVRMazhKb1pDa2d6OF9HeEptQzdBUDRYeGt2SXZ4Zng1aXNUZW4yQlB4dC1OQUZHSUhwb2wySlZYLXprd1NNMVkxZzBvQkVUVDkwdlBPQXFSc0VNay1jYkZTdzhYTmItZVBlaUQ0Q3d0VzFDNWhUZDF0Sy0yaFk3M2tLZzk1UWJaV0pjb3A4TDdhT2hIWnhMY1ZzRUpDV2YxdUFraGowMWgzMmhsR3h2WEYtbFp5clBYRGptUFFiLU5ibVU5bUhoUXB1a1N4MGY5dF9OMGw2LUVVMXh0OHc3eG9YT0VtVWViTExk</guid></item><item><title>80张有趣的图片滚动浏览，因为您正在经历当天的第三次心理崩溃（新图片） -无聊的熊猫 | 80 Funny Pics To Scroll Through As You’re Having The Third Mental Breakdown Of The Day (New Pics) - Bored Panda</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMicEFVX3lxTE9wMVROMFM0a1AzdVhSSm5kZG1hRGN3aFI4Y0VyM2tJc0JHZGl3YjE4RThrZ2x0TTlwcDBsN0t5bTNMNjJZRHZVZTk5cFpJLTl3U3NZX2wwLVhiNTBxTy1vb245bU9SYzE4eDl5aUg1MWs?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="open-list-post-description"&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Going for a walk. Getting plenty of sleep. Staying hydrated and eating a balanced diet. Socializing with friends. Any number of these behaviors can be beneficial for your &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/topics/mental-health/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer " class=" staff-link"&gt;mental health&lt;/a&gt;. But as cliché as it sounds, it’s important to remember that laughter truly can be a powerful medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ql-align-justify"&gt;And if you’re not convinced, perhaps our compilation below of posts from the &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/profile.php?id=100044223829888" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;Mental Illness and Memes&lt;/a&gt; Facebook page will change your mind. We’ve gathered some of their silliest posts down below that anyone who’s in therapy might find painfully relatable. So enjoy scrolling through these memes, and keep reading to find conversations with psychotherapists Matt Teal, from &lt;a href="http://www.rochestercounseling.com/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link"&gt;Rochester Counseling Group&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.sonia-jaeger.com/en/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link"&gt;Dr. Sonia Jaeger&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ql-align-justify"&gt;More info: &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/mental_illness_and_memes" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="open-list-items clearfix "&gt;  &lt;p class="desktop-in-content-ad post-ads "&gt; &lt;span class="dfp-ad" data-source="primis"&gt; &lt;span id="desktop-widget-loaded"&gt;    &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;     &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-3"&gt;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about how a sense of humor can be beneficial for our &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/amusing-mental-health-memes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer " class=" staff-link"&gt;mental health&lt;/a&gt;, we got in touch with a couple of experts who were kind enough to share their thoughts on the topic with &lt;strong&gt;Bored Panda&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matt Teal LCSW, CASAC, the practice director at &lt;a href="http://www.rochestercounseling.com/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link"&gt;Rochester Counseling Group&lt;/a&gt; in Upstate, New York, says it’s absolutely healthy to try to find humor in our mental health struggles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Laughter has been shown as a highly effective way to ‘complete the stress cycle’ in the human body,” Matt shared. “It releases tensions and negative thoughts, according to Dr. Emily and Amelia Nagoski.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-4"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Think about the act of laughing, especially when it comes from the gut,” the therapist continued. “You are throwing your head back, exposing your throat, and closing your eyes. When you do this, the body associates the act with being safe.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is also this phrase called the ‘knowing laugh,’” Matt noted. “It's when you share something that you think is quirky or unique to you and all of the sudden the room erupts because everyone else thought it was ‘just them’ who experienced that same thing. Here’s an &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/funny-shy-introverts-memes-69/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer " class=" staff-link"&gt;example&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also got in touch with psychologist, psychotherapist and digital nomad &lt;a href="https://www.sonia-jaeger.com/en/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link"&gt;Dr. Sonia Jaeger&lt;/a&gt; to hear her thoughts on this topic. She agrees that humor can be a powerful coping tool when it comes to &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/freakshow-of-madness-mental-health-memes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer " class=" staff-link"&gt;mental health&lt;/a&gt;. “While it shouldn't replace professional support or minimize real struggles, finding humor in our experiences can offer a sense of relief, validation, and connection,” the therapist shared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-7"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Memes, in particular, have a unique way of capturing complex emotions and experiences in a simple, often humorous format. They can make us feel less alone in our struggles and help us view our challenges from a different, sometimes more compassionate perspective,” Dr. Jaeger explained. “Laughing at a relatable meme can be a small but meaningful way to release tension and feel understood.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-10"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Matt believes memes can certainly be useful in therapy. “I use them to help clients understand their diagnosis, describe a symptom we are treating or even a skill they can use to manage symptoms,” he shared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I've also had times where my clients, in trying to explain to me what they are going through, will say there is a meme they saw that relates to it,” the expert continued. “It sometimes even helped us get ‘unstuck’ with how to better verbalize and understand what the person is going through. And it started with sharing a &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TalkTherapy/comments/gl9076/anyone_else_see_memes_and_think_itd_be_the/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;meme&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-12"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Jaeger also says memes can definitely have a place in therapy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They can act as a bridge for communication—especially for clients who find it difficult to articulate their feelings,” she told Bored Panda. “Instead of saying, ‘I don’t know how I feel,’ a client might share a meme that perfectly captures their emotional state. This can spark productive discussions and offer the therapist valuable insight into the client’s inner world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-13"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to how to incorporate memes into therapy, Dr. Jaeger noted that there are several ways. “The therapist can bring in a selection of memes that touch on common mental health themes, letting clients choose ones that resonate with them,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, the client can source memes as well. “Clients can bring memes they've found online that express how they’re feeling or what they’re going through.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-14"&gt;&lt;p&gt;And sometimes, therapists and their clients can work together to create memes. “This creative process can help externalize emotions and promote self-awareness in a non-threatening, humorous way,” Dr. Jaeger says. “When used thoughtfully, memes can help ease into difficult topics, build rapport, and encourage reflection in a way that feels approachable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-17"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also asked the experts why it’s so important for people to feel comfortable discussing their mental health struggles, even if they need memes to do so. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“‘A unicycle, car or horse… All that matters is getting there.’ Memes have become part of our world's language and how we communicate,” Matt says. “Millennials and Gen Alphas have and will continue to use this artform as a way to relate and connect with one another. Forming connections and normalizing the human experience is essential for someone's mental health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-18"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For example, take someone who is feeling depressed and they see &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/ridhigolechha/p/Cjn6SV0vMZj/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" class=" staff-link"&gt;this meme&lt;/a&gt;,” Matt continued. “It is so funny and relatable that they decide to share it with a friend, loved one, or even their therapist.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Now that feeling of sadness has also become a moment of connection, understanding and even laughter that is shared between people. The meme has become a conduit for that person to engage with their world where the moment before they may not have wanted to even be in it,” the therapist says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-20"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Jaeger noted that it’s essential for people to feel safe and comfortable discussing their mental health because silence often leads to isolation, misunderstanding, and shame. “When someone can’t find the words to explain what they’re experiencing, they might shut down—or worse, believe they’re the only one feeling that way,” she explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-21"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Memes can act as a first step toward opening up. They can normalize difficult feelings and remind people that others go through similar experiences,” she continued. “Sometimes, seeing a meme that ‘gets you’ can be more validating than hearing a clinical explanation. If it takes a meme to get someone talking about their anxiety, burnout, or ADHD symptoms, that’s still progress—and it’s incredibly valuable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-24"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Memes create a sense of Common Humanity,” Matt added. “Common Humanity is a central tenet of Mindful Self Compassion as a therapeutic intervention. And anytime we can feel that, it has been shown to lower cortisol (the stress hormone) levels and increase feelings of self compassion (which is a naturally occurring analgesic to suffering).”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Using humor can help us reach people who might not ever otherwise share their feelings with others,” he shared. “Therapy does not need to be a mystical process. We can take the topic of mental health very seriously while also not taking ourselves so seriously.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-26"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, Dr. Jaeger added, “Memes might seem lighthearted or even silly on the surface, but they can play a surprisingly meaningful role in mental health awareness and therapy. They speak the language of the internet generation—accessible, relatable, and often brutally honest. When used creatively and intentionally, they can help people feel seen, spark helpful conversations, and even encourage self-reflection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;div class="open-list-item open-list-block clearfix text-block "&gt; &lt;span id="list-text-27"&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it’s worth keeping in mind that, while &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/hilarious-mental-health-memes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer " class=" staff-link"&gt;memes&lt;/a&gt; can point to shared experiences or even help someone recognize a pattern in their behavior, they don’t tell the full story. “They’re not diagnostic tools, and sometimes what resonates might just be a piece of a much more complex puzzle,” Dr. Jaeger told Bored Panda. “Used alongside—not in place of—professional support, memes can absolutely enrich the therapeutic process.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/div&gt;                                                                                        &lt;/div&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bored Panda</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 23:02:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9wMVROMFM0a1AzdVhSSm5kZG1hRGN3aFI4Y0VyM2tJc0JHZGl3YjE4RThrZ2x0TTlwcDBsN0t5bTNMNjJZRHZVZTk5cFpJLTl3U3NZX2wwLVhiNTBxTy1vb245bU9SYzE4eDl5aUg1MWs</guid></item><item><title>服用维生素B有助于对抗青光眼，研究发现-每日邮报 | Taking vitamin B could help to fight glaucoma, study finds - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxOb0tYUWJaLURjRFdXZjJtMFNJam5iLU9tRk9CRy1UYkNpeVpTSVU5Ym5ZOE9PUExhUzVqQndZYnQ3ay1HQ1NPQ1BzcVhDcWZtSnpYR1Ytc05QX3VndU1tZWtIVk5RNUViNmNwcnh2TjlXeVEtM1E5Z2NOOFZpemRzWWRpZGdGN2tLNXV6ZjhyTS1EY0pOUVpJOGp0VkZyYm5ieFpQaEZB0gGrAUFVX3lxTFBTYnlsdHI4bk9OZndEQjVaR1hsbjhST2tHaFRvZ0JhdnlKdzBCcTdHRDNYRFI4WWFaREhMX2x6NVZOSXAtY1lRVzRoeW9lSVZtV3lUWU5mMTRDckFRQlQxdkNMQUN2eHJZeDh3d29qcUFVT0VTNUk5SkcwSWlOU3VENW8yM2ZJWmtNZ2F5Qmw5bDg4bXhHOUNzWmxJY3dfYzZvWUFYWFllcWhxNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="js-article-text" class="article-text wide  heading-tag-switch"&gt;
            &lt;h1&gt;Taking vitamin B could help to fight glaucoma, study finds&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p class="author-section byline-plain"&gt;By &lt;a href="/profile-2281/Meike-Leonard.html" class="author"&gt;MEIKE LEONARD&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="byline-section"&gt;&lt;span class="article-timestamp article-timestamp-published"&gt; &lt;span class="article-timestamp-label"&gt;Published:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;time datetime="2025-05-17T22:45:20+0100"&gt; 17:45 EDT, 17 May 2025 &lt;/time&gt; &lt;/span&gt; | &lt;span class="article-timestamp article-timestamp-updated"&gt; &lt;span class="article-timestamp-label"&gt;Updated:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;time datetime="2025-05-17T22:45:20+0100"&gt; 17:45 EDT, 17 May 2025 &lt;/time&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                  
    
                  &lt;noscript&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;     &lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A common vitamin supplement could slow down the progression of the degenerative eye disease glaucoma, a study has found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Vitamin B, found in whole grains, dark leafy greens, such as kale and broccoli, eggs, fish and dairy, appears to diminish the damage caused by the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Glaucoma, which is suffered by nearly 700,000 people in the UK, is caused by an abnormality in the eye’s drainage system causing fluid to build up, increasing pressure on the optic nerve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Primarily affecting older adults and those with a genetic disposition to the condition, it causes blurred vision and even blindness if left untreated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Glaucoma is usually managed by reducing the pressure through eye drops, surgery or laser treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers gave supplements of vitamins B6, B9 and B12 to rats and mice with glaucoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In rats with a more aggressive form of the disease, it slowed damage to the optic nerve. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In mice with slower-developing glaucoma, the damage was halted completely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A common vitamin supplement could slow down the progression of the degenerative eye disease glaucoma, a study has found&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists believe this could be due to the increased pressure in the eye changing the retina’s ability to use vitamins which are crucial to maintaining healthy vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr James Tribble, from the Karolinska Institute in Sweden, which carried out the study, said: ‘The results are so promising that we have started a clinical trial, with patients already being recruited.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It comes after a 2019 study showed that vitamin B3 could be effective in preventing glaucoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists at The Jackson Laboratory in Maine, US, added B3 to water given to mice which were genetically predisposed to the condition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It kept their eyes healthier for longer compared to those given plain water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;div class="column-content cleared"&gt;
                &lt;div class="shareArticles"&gt;
                    &lt;h3 class="social-links-title"&gt;Share or comment on this article: 
                        Taking vitamin B could help to fight glaucoma, study finds&lt;/h3&gt;
                    
                
              &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            
                        
            &lt;ad-slot position="smart_feed"&gt;&lt;/ad-slot&gt;
            &lt;p id="taboola-below-article-thumbnails" class="taboola" data-taboolaposition="thumbnail"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                        
            
            &lt;ad-slot position="after_article"&gt;&lt;/ad-slot&gt;
&lt;p id="taboola-below-main-column" class="taboola" data-taboolaposition="afterArticle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



            
            
             
           &lt;p id="most-watched-videos-lazy-container" data-lazy-content data-lazy-manifest-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/api/most-watched-videos/news/internal/?max_age_days=3&amp;amp;lazyManifest=true&amp;amp;lightbox=true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            
            
            &lt;p class="column-content cleared"&gt;
              
            &lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            
            




            
        &lt;/div&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:45:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxOb0tYUWJaLURjRFdXZjJtMFNJam5iLU9tRk9CRy1UYkNpeVpTSVU5Ym5ZOE9PUExhUzVqQndZYnQ3ay1HQ1NPQ1BzcVhDcWZtSnpYR1Ytc05QX3VndU1tZWtIVk5RNUViNmNwcnh2TjlXeVEtM1E5Z2NOOFZpemRzWWRpZGdGN2tLNXV6ZjhyTS1EY0pOUVpJOGp0VkZyYm5ieFpQaEZB0gGrAUFVX3lxTFBTYnlsdHI4bk9OZndEQjVaR1hsbjhST2tHaFRvZ0JhdnlKdzBCcTdHRDNYRFI4WWFaREhMX2x6NVZOSXAtY1lRVzRoeW9lSVZtV3lUWU5mMTRDckFRQlQxdkNMQUN2eHJZeDh3d29qcUFVT0VTNUk5SkcwSWlOU3VENW8yM2ZJWmtNZ2F5Qmw5bDg4bXhHOUNzWmxJY3dfYzZvWUFYWFllcWhxNA</guid></item><item><title>美国研究人员推出AI驱动的疾病预测工具，具有“前所未有的准确性” - KSL.com | U. researchers unveil AI-powered tool for disease prediction with 'unprecedented accuracy' - KSL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiwgFBVV95cUxQdTlEWHBzVFJITmh2ZzNsUEVpU2hVRnIxX0xxOWtkNUdVYUk5aG1OUWJ1UF96N1lRQ1dxRVBIbWgzVzhaeHJOc2NEcDU1alN2T25oMjdJUW5JRnc3aUxHRmh4MjdqMlhvZFBhVWljQjVtdjIwWkJHdlpraDh3RDFlOW45V0hlMWhQRUVodC1hUFpiUmpFdEJDZEdySjFwWURneWtGZ3pvSTlCNEd3a1F6Y2ZqT19falFYTzhhelo5NmVrUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;
                                        Estimated read time: 4-5
                                        minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SALT LAKE CITY — It's long been a goal in medicine to better understand the long trajectories of diseases in hopes of engaging in better prevention and early intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Collectively, they're (chronic and progressive diseases) responsible for about 90% of the health care costs in this country and the vast majority of morbidity and mortality," said Nina de Lacy, a professor of psychiatry and member of the One-U Responsible AI Initiative's executive committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, University of Utah researchers have taken a crucial step in doing so, unveiling a new, open-source software tool kit that uses artificial intelligence to predict whether individuals will develop progressive and chronic diseases years before symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enter RiskPath, a new technology that analyzes patterns in health data collected over multiple years to identify at-risk individuals with "unprecedented accuracy" of 85% to 99%, according to National Institute of Mental Health-sponsored research published last week by the U.'s Department of Psychiatry and Huntsman Mental Health Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The program harnesses explainable AI, which is designed to explain complex decisions in ways humans can understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Explainability means, can I explain enough about how AI accomplished this prediction such that it becomes understandable to humans?" de Lacy said. "That would be things like what RiskPath does."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;De Lacy explained something that has always been a challenge in biomedicine is building models and analyzing longitudinal data, meaning it's collected over many time periods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One of the major use cases in using longitudinal data is course development, understanding how people grow up and develop over time," de Lacy said. "And one of the other ones is what RiskPath is aimed at, which is understanding progressive or chronic disease. There are many progressive and chronic diseases out there, and some of the big ones are things that are the major diseases that affect humans."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research shows current medical prediction systems for longitudinal data often miss the mark, correctly identifying at-risk patients only about half to three-quarters of the time. Unlike existing prediction systems for longitudinal data, RiskPath uses advanced time-series AI algorithms that deliver crucial insights into how risk factors interact and change in importance throughout the disease process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"By identifying high-risk individuals before symptoms appear or early in the disease course and pinpointing which risk factors matter most at different life stages, we can develop more targeted and effective preventive strategies. Preventative health care is perhaps the most important aspect of health care right now, rather than only treating issues after they materialize," de Lacy said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;De Lacy and the rest of the research team validated RiskPath across three major long-term patient cohorts involving thousands of participants to successfully predict eight different conditions, including depression, anxiety, ADHD, hypertension and metabolic syndrome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The technology offers several key advantages:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enhanced understanding of disease progression:&lt;/strong&gt; RiskPath can map how different risk factors change in importance over time, revealing critical windows for intervention. For example, the study showed how screen time and executive function become increasingly important risk contributors for ADHD as children approach adolescence.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Streamlined risk assessment:&lt;/strong&gt; Though RiskPath can analyze hundreds of health variables, researchers found that most conditions can be predicted with similar accuracy using just 10 key factors, making implementation more feasible in clinical settings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Practical risk visualization:&lt;/strong&gt; The system provides intuitive visualizations showing which time periods in a person's life contribute most to disease risk, helping researchers identify optimal times for preventive interventions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;While RiskPath is primarily a research tool to help researchers build better risk stratification models, de Lacy hopes it will eventually be used in a health care setting to improve disease management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Some may be using that to build models that can be implemented in health care, and we kind of hope that they do that. But ... a big part of what my lab is interested in doing is building tools that do a better job of risk stratification. We're very interested in prevention," de Lacy said. "The ultimate aim of RiskPath and tools like RiskPath is to help people build better risk stratification tools and decision support tools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"And what those do is help clinicians, and maybe one day patients, be able to understand their risk for a chronic or progressive disease better and earlier," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 21:04:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxQdTlEWHBzVFJITmh2ZzNsUEVpU2hVRnIxX0xxOWtkNUdVYUk5aG1OUWJ1UF96N1lRQ1dxRVBIbWgzVzhaeHJOc2NEcDU1alN2T25oMjdJUW5JRnc3aUxHRmh4MjdqMlhvZFBhVWljQjVtdjIwWkJHdlpraDh3RDFlOW45V0hlMWhQRUVodC1hUFpiUmpFdEJDZEdySjFwWURneWtGZ3pvSTlCNEd3a1F6Y2ZqT19falFYTzhhelo5NmVrUQ</guid></item><item><title>这种常用处方药可使阿尔茨海默氏症的风险增加46% -印度时报 | This commonly prescribed drug can increase the risk of Alzheimer’s by 46% - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigAJBVV95cUxQejRUWENIWEdyLVRhVmFxenY2bXd4XzdrSjNuM1BJa3M0WDVhcDZUVVdSRV9UX3lTaFNIVkRyOTl4ZXk5TGtZSy02MXlSdXBrNWFtNFVpS2JqVWZEOHAtQlZWS3Y0SWJ3WG41aWt2SzM4aEFYZl9ON3RyVldIemdBb3NwcHZhNVRNOUlFUzBNZF9EZnFZSklTajZ5XzZPRG5UUmxxbUh1VGMtV1NkV0RZYnNMSlZwV1VZOUVWUU91SjZkd1dnc0IybzB6RFdpZjdseHJyakZCaVNHay1wNDlHaHZQM3VmVUNmaFgxc3gxNkxlQ0xOcUI5aWxadHZjaDBf?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;An estimated 57 million people were living with &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/dementia" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; globally in 2021, with Alzheimer’s disease accounting for 60–70% of all cases. Now, a new study warns that adults who take certain prescription drugs may face a significantly higher risk of developing dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a meta-analysis published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33098213/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Neurology and Urodynamics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; journal, people who take certain prescription drugs for more than three months have an increased risk of developing Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s disease is the most common form of dementia, a brain disorder that slowly destroys a person’s memory and thinking skills. This disease leads to a loss of cognitive functioning, such as thinking, remembering, and reasoning, along with behavioural abilities to such an extent that it interferes with a person’s daily life and activities. Over time, Alzheimer’s patients lose their ability to perform simple daily tasks, such as eating or walking. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How does the prescription drug increase the risk of Alzheimer’s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the meta-analysis, the long-term use of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/anticholinergic-drugs" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;anticholinergic drugs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, commonly prescribed for conditions like overactive bladder, allergies, and depression, can raise the risk of dementia by 46%. The study, which analyzed 21 studies and included a meta-analysis of six, looked at the impact of anticholinergic drugs taken for at least three months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These medications block acetylcholine, a neurotransmitter that is critical for memory and cognitive function. Acetylcholine transmits messages in the nervous system.In the brain, acetylcholine is linked to learning and memory. In the rest of the body, it stimulates muscle contractions. Anticholinergic drugs also include antihistamines, tricyclic antidepressants, medications to control an overactive bladder, and drugs to relieve the symptoms of Parkinson's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings revealed a clear association between prolonged anticholinergic use and dementia risk. The study found a people who took these anticholinergic drugs had a 46% increased risk of dementia compared to those who didn’t take them. The risk grew with longer exposure, with some studies noting a dose-dependent effect. “Anticholinergic use for ≥3 months increased the risk of dementia on average by an estimated 46% versus nonuse.This relationship was consistent in studies assessing overactive bladder medications. The risk of developing dementia should be carefully considered in the context of potential benefit before prescribing anticholinergics,” the authors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another study by researchers at the University of Nottingham found that there was nearly a 50% increased risk of dementia among patients aged 55 and over who had used strong anticholinergic medication daily for three years or more. "This study found that there was nearly a 50% increased risk of dementia among patients aged 55 and over who had used strong anticholinergic medication daily for three years or more," Professor Tom Dening, Head of the Centre for Dementia at the University, and a member of the research team said.The study followed 58,769 patients with a diagnosis of dementia and 225,574 patients without a diagnosis of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Study Biotech &amp;amp; Health Tech Abroad: Top Courses at Harvard, Stanford&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 20:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAJBVV95cUxQejRUWENIWEdyLVRhVmFxenY2bXd4XzdrSjNuM1BJa3M0WDVhcDZUVVdSRV9UX3lTaFNIVkRyOTl4ZXk5TGtZSy02MXlSdXBrNWFtNFVpS2JqVWZEOHAtQlZWS3Y0SWJ3WG41aWt2SzM4aEFYZl9ON3RyVldIemdBb3NwcHZhNVRNOUlFUzBNZF9EZnFZSklTajZ5XzZPRG5UUmxxbUh1VGMtV1NkV0RZYnNMSlZwV1VZOUVWUU91SjZkd1dnc0IybzB6RFdpZjdseHJyakZCaVNHay1wNDlHaHZQM3VmVUNmaFgxc3gxNkxlQ0xOcUI5aWxadHZjaDBf</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，与ADHD成人认知表现缺陷相关的淋巴功能障碍- PsyPost | Glymphatic dysfunction linked to cognitive performance deficits in adults with ADHD, study finds - PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivAFBVV95cUxQbUw0VjczWnAxNEdIeFUweWJoVTd5emQ4WXZkNl9HejNYOW1zV0R5em1vRUgtMGxldlhkY3NNQU04YjhtcjlpTldna1k0T29BN0pFTHpUZm8ybFV5MmdJcHlsNVpTZVRJWml2Wk41YXpaSnowMDFoQVQyWXJzUGY3aV9odzEzRDF1cUlsaFE3TGtCemhiUVE3TXM2SElhVVJjWkhYMDRNRVFQU1ZkME5Sa3VET2lfOXFkcU9wbQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0165032725003970" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Journal of Affective Disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; has found that adults with attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) show signs of glymphatic system dysfunction, which may be related to their cognitive difficulties. The findings suggest that disruptions in the brain’s waste clearance system could help explain some of the persistent memory and attention problems seen in adults with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ADHD is a common neurodevelopmental disorder marked by symptoms of inattention, impulsivity, and hyperactivity. While it is often diagnosed in childhood, many people continue to experience symptoms well into adulthood. In adults, ADHD can interfere with work, relationships, and daily functioning, and is often accompanied by cognitive issues such as forgetfulness and difficulty sustaining focus. Although behavioral symptoms are widely studied, the biological mechanisms that underlie adult ADHD are less understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One area of growing interest among scientists is the glymphatic system—a network that helps clear waste products from the brain. This system operates mainly during deep sleep and uses cerebrospinal fluid to flush out harmful substances. Problems with glymphatic function have been linked to other brain disorders, such as Alzheimer’s disease. However, little is known about its role in ADHD, especially in adults. The researchers behind this study wanted to explore whether changes in glymphatic function could help explain the cognitive impairments associated with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To do this, the team analyzed brain imaging and cognitive data from 41 adults diagnosed with ADHD and compared them to 108 healthy adults. The data came from the University of California, Los Angeles Consortium for Neuropsychiatric Phenomic LA5c Study and included both structural and functional magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) scans, along with results from several cognitive tests. The researchers used advanced neuroimaging techniques to assess three indicators of glymphatic function: the volume of the choroid plexus (a part of the brain that produces cerebrospinal fluid), a measure known as the ALPS index (which reflects how well fluid moves along blood vessels in the brain), and the strength of the connection between brain activity and cerebrospinal fluid flow (called gBOLD-CSF coupling).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The participants also completed a range of assessments, including the Adult ADHD Self-Report Scale to measure ADHD symptoms, and standardized tests to evaluate memory, attention, and verbal learning. These included the California Verbal Learning Test and the Wechsler Memory Scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results showed that adults with ADHD had lower ALPS index scores than healthy individuals, suggesting reduced glymphatic activity. This difference was observed across both hemispheres of the brain. The decrease in ALPS scores was linked to reduced fluid movement along specific fiber pathways in the brain, particularly those involved in communication between regions. These findings point to a possible impairment in how effectively the brain is able to clear waste.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the volume of the choroid plexus tended to be higher in the ADHD group, this difference did not reach statistical significance. This may suggest a potential compensatory response or a marker of altered cerebrospinal fluid dynamics, but more research is needed to draw firm conclusions. Likewise, there were no significant differences between the ADHD and control groups in terms of gBOLD-CSF coupling, which reflects functional synchronization between brain activity and fluid flow. This suggests that while structural glymphatic changes may be present, the overall coordination between brain and fluid activity remains intact in adults with ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, the researchers found that lower ALPS index scores were associated with poorer performance on memory tasks, including visual reproduction and delayed recognition. These correlations were stronger in the right hemisphere. The ALPS index also showed links with higher scores on obsessive-compulsive symptoms in participants with ADHD, suggesting a broader relationship between glymphatic function and psychiatric features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In healthy participants, higher ALPS scores were also associated with better memory performance, suggesting that glymphatic activity may play a broader role in supporting cognitive health across individuals, not just those with ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings open up the possibility that glymphatic dysfunction contributes to the cognitive symptoms experienced by adults with ADHD. The researchers propose that impaired waste clearance could lead to the buildup of metabolic byproducts that interfere with brain signaling, particularly in pathways involving dopamine and norepinephrine. These neurotransmitters are already known to play a role in attention, motivation, and reward processing—all areas often affected in ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another possible explanation is that impaired glymphatic function may contribute to low-grade inflammation in the brain, which has been increasingly recognized in ADHD research. Inflammation can disrupt brain development and affect how neurons communicate. The researchers also point out that sleep problems, which are common in ADHD, may worsen glymphatic dysfunction, since this system operates most effectively during deep sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a cellular level, the authors suggest that astrocytes—supportive brain cells that help regulate the glymphatic system—may play an important role. Astrocytes help manage fluid flow through channels called aquaporins and also influence how brain circuits develop. Dysfunction in these cells could create a cascade of problems affecting both waste clearance and neural communication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this study is one of the first to examine glymphatic function in adult ADHD, it has several limitations. Because the data are cross-sectional, the researchers cannot determine whether glymphatic dysfunction causes cognitive problems or results from them. Longitudinal studies are needed to better understand the direction of this relationship. The relatively small sample size also limits the generalizability of the findings, and future research should aim to replicate these results in larger and more diverse groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these limitations, the study adds an important piece to the puzzle of ADHD. It suggests that biological systems beyond neurotransmitter signaling—such as waste clearance—may play a meaningful role in the disorder’s development and persistence. These insights could eventually lead to new therapeutic strategies. For example, improving sleep quality, promoting regular physical activity, or reducing brain inflammation could support glymphatic function and potentially ease cognitive symptoms in adults with ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jad.2025.03.059" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Glymphatic system dysfunction in adult ADHD: Relationship to cognitive performance&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Yan Fang, Juan Peng, Tiantian Chu, Feng Gao, Fei Xiong, and Ye Tu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 20:09:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxQbUw0VjczWnAxNEdIeFUweWJoVTd5emQ4WXZkNl9HejNYOW1zV0R5em1vRUgtMGxldlhkY3NNQU04YjhtcjlpTldna1k0T29BN0pFTHpUZm8ybFV5MmdJcHlsNVpTZVRJWml2Wk41YXpaSnowMDFoQVQyWXJzUGY3aV9odzEzRDF1cUlsaFE3TGtCemhiUVE3TXM2SElhVVJjWkhYMDRNRVFQU1ZkME5Sa3VET2lfOXFkcU9wbQ</guid></item><item><title>您每天步行以降低癌症风险真正需要的步数—忘记旧的“10K”规则-纽约邮报 | The number of steps you really need to walk a day to lower cancer risk — forget that old ‘10K’ rule - New York Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxQWWpxdjFsaHBqS2Z4aTJzWGpiUzdPY3RfSmc3N0pKUFlUallPR1hna3ZxMzRhNWx6ZnN0U1VTRVNsMGJ1RHdZY2U4alp1d3pHVmoyV2p1SExCd003NHRudUpDT2QyNmlMNG5BLXVYUU0zWS1TS2w2dUtOaVB0UU41cTZyaHkzRkxvMFBJekI5dG5SR2h2?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom "&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;Every step counts when it comes to your health — but a &lt;a href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/early/2025/03/14/bjsports-2024-109360" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; suggests hitting a specific number every day could lower your risk of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And no, it’s not 10,000. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Turns out, that magic number we’ve all been chasing wasn’t discovered in a lab. It was actually dreamed up in the 1960s as a &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2022/09/15/do-we-need-10k-steps-a-day-shocking-truth-of-daily-goal/"&gt;clever marketing tactic&lt;/a&gt; to sell pedometers in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Walking lowers cancer risk, but the benefits appear to plateau after a certain number of steps.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Dragana Gordic – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The good news is that the latest recommendations are backed by solid science from the UK.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The large study followed over 85,000 participants who wore activity trackers measuring both the amount and intensity of their daily movement for an average of six years.&lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;Researchers focused on 13 types of cancer and identified a clear trend: the more you move, the lower your risk. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Over the six-year follow-up period, 3% of participants developed cancer. The most common were &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/02/25/health/scientists-find-key-that-could-be-driving-rising-colon-cancer-rates/"&gt;colon&lt;/a&gt;, rectal and lung in men, along with &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/02/20/health/alarming-rise-in-breast-cancer-under-40-across-the-us/"&gt;breast&lt;/a&gt;, colon, endometrial and lung in women.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;The study suggests it’s not the pace that matters — it’s how much you walk. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;nuttawutnuy – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;





&lt;p&gt;The study found that people who walked 7,000 steps a day had an 11% lower cancer risk compared to those logging just 5,000.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At 9,000 steps, the risk dropped further to 16% — but beyond that, the benefits leveled off.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The results held steady even after researchers accounted for demographic, health and lifestyle factors, indicating that it was the steps themselves that made the difference. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Getting more steps into your routine, especially during middle age, could be one of the simplest ways to lower your risk of developing certain cancers,” &lt;a href="https://www.lboro.ac.uk/schools/sport-exercise-health-sciences/people/mhairi-morris/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Dr. Mhairi Morris&lt;/a&gt;, a senior lecturer in biochemistry at Loughborough University who wasn’t involved in the study, wrote in &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/how-7-000-steps-a-day-could-help-reduce-your-risk-of-cancer-255564" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Research consistently points to an increase in sedentary lifestyles among Americans. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;stokkete – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Not a fan of power walking? No problem. If you prefer a leisurely stroll, you’re still doing your body a favor. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While researchers found a faster pace was linked to a lower cancer risk, once overall activity levels were factored in, speed didn’t really matter.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Participants who traded sitting time for physical activity also saw a drop in cancer risk. However, increasing the intensity from light to moderate didn’t provide much additional benefit. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Our research highlights the importance of all forms of movement,” &lt;a href="https://www.ndph.ox.ac.uk/team/aiden-doherty"&gt;Dr. Aiden Doherty&lt;/a&gt;, professor of biomedical informatics at &lt;a href="https://www.ndph.ox.ac.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Oxford Population Health&lt;/a&gt; and senior author of the study, said in &lt;a href="https://www.ndph.ox.ac.uk/news/daily-physical-activity-even-at-light-intensities-linked-to-lower-cancer-risk" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a statement&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Whether it’s increasing daily steps, engaging in light activity, or incorporating moderate-to-vigorous exercise, any level of physical activity appears to contribute to lower cancer risk,” he continued. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Over 2 million new cancer cases are expected in the US this year. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Halfpoint – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;





&lt;p&gt;This study comes at a time when many common cancers, like breast, kidney, colorectal and uterine cancers, are on the rise in the US. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While the increase is multifactorial, experts point to rising &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/03/03/health/more-than-half-of-adults-are-expected-to-be-overweight-or-obese-by-2050/"&gt;obesity rates&lt;/a&gt; and an increasingly &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/02/11/health/this-lifestyle-habit-is-as-risky-to-your-health-as-smoking/"&gt;sedentary lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; as major drivers of the growing cancer risk — particularly among &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/04/18/health/what-to-know-about-rising-cancer-rates-in-young-people/"&gt;young people&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Across the country, more than &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/obesity/adult-obesity-facts/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;2 in 5 adults&lt;/a&gt; have obesity, along with &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/obesity/childhood-obesity-facts/childhood-obesity-facts.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;1 in 5 children and adolescents&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://odphp.health.gov/our-work/nutrition-physical-activity/physical-activity-guidelines/current-guidelines" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Department of Health and Human Services recommends&lt;/a&gt; adults get at least &lt;a href="https://health.gov/sites/default/files/2019-09/Physical_Activity_Guidelines_2nd_edition.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;150 minutes&lt;/a&gt; of moderate aerobic exercise each week, plus muscle-strengthening activities like weightlifting at least twice a week.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Yet, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/72/wr/mm7204a1.htm?s_cid=mm7204a1_w" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;CDC data&lt;/a&gt;, more than two-thirds of Americans aren’t hitting those benchmarks. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Our findings support and enhance current national and international physical activity guidelines, showing that people who often engage in simple low-intensity activities such as walking have a lower risk of developing cancer,” Doherty said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/content/dam/cancer-org/research/cancer-facts-and-statistics/annual-cancer-facts-and-figures/2025/2025-cancer-facts-and-figures-acs.pdf"&gt; American Cancer Society estimates&lt;/a&gt; that more than 2 million new cases will be diagnosed in the US in 2025, and more than 618,000 people will die from the disease. That’s roughly 1,700 cancer deaths every day nationwide. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="wpcom-liveblog-container"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 19:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQWWpxdjFsaHBqS2Z4aTJzWGpiUzdPY3RfSmc3N0pKUFlUallPR1hna3ZxMzRhNWx6ZnN0U1VTRVNsMGJ1RHdZY2U4alp1d3pHVmoyV2p1SExCd003NHRudUpDT2QyNmlMNG5BLXVYUU0zWS1TS2w2dUtOaVB0UU41cTZyaHkzRkxvMFBJekI5dG5SR2h2</guid></item><item><title>中年时期的高品质碳水化合物与更健康的衰老有关- Earth.com | High-quality carbs in midlife linked to healthier aging - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQUWk4NkxyX19iaml5QW5Xb0x2RW8ydV9taE1mNjY5R3dzOXNqeHlHMjY0VEZkanMzVDVra2RyX3pzcWNoVjhzdzNsWnBnTU5kT2RlN2tuOG1hQ2kwVUJJemxpZGsycS1zcmRQd3o4THczZUlBOHVTR3M1Q1FkY0hhOGg3d0JUMjlBUnVZ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aging can mean many things. It can mean slowing down, feeling less sharp, or facing more health issues. But it doesn’t have to. A new study suggests that what women eat in midlife could set the stage for how well they age. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published in JAMA Network Open, the study from &lt;a href="https://www.tufts.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Tufts University&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health&lt;/a&gt; dives into the power of carbohydrates and fiber in shaping &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/organ-aging-can-predict-diseases-decades-in-advance/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; decades later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-carbs-affect-aging"&gt;How carbs affect aging&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all carbs are equal. Some lift you up, while others drag you down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’ve all heard that different carbohydrates can affect &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/how-old-are-you-really-new-tool-measures-aging-from-the-inside-out/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; differently, whether for weight, energy, or blood sugar levels. But rather than just look at the immediate effects of these macronutrients, we wanted to understand what they might mean for good health 30 years later,” said lead author Andres Ardisson Korat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study zeroed in on 47,000 women, ages 70 to 93. The researchers looked at what these women ate over a span of three decades, starting in 1984. They tracked their intake of refined carbs, high-quality carbs, and fiber. They wanted to see who aged well – and who didn’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-healthy-aging-looks-like"&gt;What healthy aging looks like&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Living past 70 doesn’t mean you’re aging well. The researchers defined &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/curiosity-might-help-you-stay-sharp-as-you-age/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;healthy&lt;/a&gt; aging as reaching 70 without major chronic diseases, keeping a sharp mind, staying physically capable, and feeling good mentally. Out of 47,000 women, only 3,706 fit that bill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What did those women have in common? A diet rich in high-quality carbs and fiber. The more they ate from whole grains, fruits, vegetables, and legumes, the better they aged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-high-quality-carbs-boost-aging"&gt;High-quality carbs boost aging&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eating more high-quality carbs wasn’t just good. It was transformative. Women who upped their intake of high-quality carbs by 10% had a 31% better chance of aging well. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same couldn’t be said for refined carbs. Sugary snacks and white bread were linked to a 13% drop in the odds of healthy &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-discover-a-protein-that-reverses-cellular-aging/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;aging&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our results are consistent with other evidence linking consumption of fruits and vegetables, whole grains, and legumes with lower risks of chronic diseases, and now we see the association with physical and cognitive function outcomes,” said study senior author Qi Sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-fiber-s-role-in-protecting-health"&gt;Fiber’s role in protecting health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiber doesn’t just keep things moving. It protects your mind. It shields your body. For every one-standard-deviation bump in fiber intake, the odds of healthy aging shot up by 17 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fruit fiber boosted odds by 14 percent. Vegetable fiber added 11 percent. Even cereal fiber, often overlooked, contributed a 7% increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The benefits of fiber went beyond disease prevention. Women with higher fiber intake had stronger memories, better physical function, and fewer mental health problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-all-carbs-affect-aging-differently"&gt;All carbs affect aging differently&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Glycemic index (GI) and glycemic load (GL) may sound like fancy terms, but they matter. Foods with a high GI hit blood sugar hard and fast. Not great for aging well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High GL foods, on the other hand, had a surprising link to better mental health. But once the researchers factored in fiber intake, that connection weakened. The takeaway? Fiber might buffer some of the negative effects of high-GI foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-replacing-refined-carbs"&gt;Replacing refined carbs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Imagine swapping out refined carbs for high-quality ones. What happens? Women who did had 8% to 16% better odds of aging well. That’s a big jump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Studies are starting to find an association between food choices in midlife and quality of life in later years. The more we can understand about healthy &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/human-bodies-begin-breaking-down-two-very-precise-ages/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;aging&lt;/a&gt;, the more science can help people live healthier for longer,” Korat said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-tracking-women-s-diets"&gt;Tracking women’s diets&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study tracked women’s diets for over 30 years. It connected their midlife eating habits to their health in their 70s and 80s. The findings suggest that small, consistent changes matter more than drastic diets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers saw that women who ate more whole grains, fruits, and veggies over time aged better than those who filled up on white bread and sweets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study mostly included white, educated health professionals. Participants reported their own dietary habits, which might not be completely accurate. And after three decades, memories can get hazy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, the findings were clear. Eating more high-quality carbs and fiber in midlife made a noticeable difference. It wasn’t just beneficial – it was transformative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-this-means-for-women"&gt;What this means for women&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aging well isn’t just about avoiding illness. It’s about staying mentally sharp, physically active, and feeling good. The study suggests that what women eat in their 40s and 50s can impact their health decades later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it’s not just about eating fewer carbs. It’s about eating the right ones. Whole grains, fruits, vegetables, and legumes gave women a better shot at aging well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-carbs-and-fiber-shape-aging"&gt;Carbs and fiber shape aging&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The food choices women make in midlife are more than just meals. They’re investments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High-quality carbs and dietary fiber aren’t just good for digestion. They’re linked to lower risks of chronic diseases, sharper minds, and better physical health in old age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aging doesn’t have to mean decline, and it doesn’t have to mean slowing down. For the women in this study, eating well decades earlier paid off in a big way. The lesson? It’s never too early to think about the future. And it’s never too late to make better choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2834202" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 17:11:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQUWk4NkxyX19iaml5QW5Xb0x2RW8ydV9taE1mNjY5R3dzOXNqeHlHMjY0VEZkanMzVDVra2RyX3pzcWNoVjhzdzNsWnBnTU5kT2RlN2tuOG1hQ2kwVUJJemxpZGsycS1zcmRQd3o4THczZUlBOHVTR3M1Q1FkY0hhOGg3d0JUMjlBUnVZ</guid></item><item><title>谁需要更多的锻炼：女性还是男性？ - Live Science | Who needs more exercise: Women or men? - Live Science</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihwFBVV95cUxOOXBXNHU0a2lzSjJRd2NoOHNyb2Z3R3oydWVvN1E4WDZkSFJmb3VOLXM1d0RWZDlMMXRkaXJEaUhjOEtDR2xacmhyMl9PYnl2QzRmVGFJc0lKa3RHWTNIcFpUWEY5SlphSWQ1cl9ob0dFckh5MkstVFZnVU44NlRqNVl5UzctWjg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exercising regularly is known to lower the risk of death, especially from heart problems. But scientists have discovered that that reduction in risk may differ between the sexes, with some people reaping greater benefits in less workout time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, who has to exercise more to reduce their risk of death: Women or men?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turns out that women may reap these survival benefits more easily than men do. That's according to a large study published in 2024 in the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.jacc.org/doi/10.1016/j.jacc.2023.12.019" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.jacc.org/doi/10.1016/j.jacc.2023.12.019" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Journal of the American College of Cardiology&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which included data from more than 412,000 American adults ages 27 to 61, 55% of whom were female.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The beauty of this study is learning that women can get more out of each minute of moderate to vigorous activity than men do," study co-lead author &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://researchers.cedars-sinai.edu/Martha.Gulati" data-url="https://researchers.cedars-sinai.edu/Martha.Gulati" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Martha Gulati&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, director of preventive cardiology in the Smidt Heart Institute at Cedars-Sinai, said in a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/newsroom/women-get-the-same-exercise-benefits-as-men-but-with-less-effort/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/newsroom/women-get-the-same-exercise-benefits-as-men-but-with-less-effort/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;statement&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. "It's an incentivizing notion that we hope women will take to heart."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers collected participants' physical activity data via the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/nhis/about/index.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/nhis/about/index.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Health Interview Survey&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (NHIS), the largest and longest-running health survey in the U.S. The study looked at data collected between 1997 and 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/11-minutes-of-moderate-exercise-a-day-cuts-early-death-risk-by-20-huge-analysis-suggests" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/11-minutes-of-moderate-exercise-a-day-cuts-early-death-risk-by-20-huge-analysis-suggests"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 minutes of moderate exercise a day cuts early death risk by 20%, huge analysis suggests&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The survey itself included questions about the types of exercises people performed and at what frequencies, durations and intensities. It also included participants' socioeconomic and demographic characteristics and medical conditions. The study excluded people who had certain health conditions at the start of the study time frame, such as &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/heart-circulation/coronary-artery-disease-cad-causes-diagnosis-and-treatment" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/heart-circulation/coronary-artery-disease-cad-causes-diagnosis-and-treatment"&gt;&lt;u&gt;coronary heart disease&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-N4XEYEtRm6XVSbi4VufaKV" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-N4XEYEtRm6XVSbi4VufaKV slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also looked through the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/ndi/index.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/ndi/index.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;National Death Index&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; — a national database of death records — for deaths from any cause, as well as cardiovascular-related deaths. The data from survey participants is &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data-linkage/mortality.htm" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/data-linkage/mortality.htm" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;linked to this death-record data&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, so the researchers could then connect the data from their NHIS participants to the mortality data through the end of 2019. Overall, 39,935 participants died in the study timeframe, including 11,670 cardiovascular-related deaths, such as those from heart disease, heart attacks and strokes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 32% of the women and 43% of the men surveyed said they engaged in regular &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/aerobic-exercise" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/aerobic-exercise"&gt;&lt;u&gt;aerobic exercise&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, exercising for at least 150 minutes per week. Compared to inactive individuals of the same sex, women who exercised regularly had up to a 24% lower risk of death from any cause. For men who exercised regularly, however, the reduction in mortality risk reached only 15%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women also gained these survival benefits much more quickly than men did, the study found. In men, the highest reduction in death risk was seen at about 300 minutes of moderate-to-vigorous physical activity (MVPA) per week. That came with an 18% reduction in all-cause mortality. Women saw an equal benefit in less than half that time, at about 140 minutes of MVPA a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women who trained more than that each week saw a greater benefit until they also peaked at around 300 minutes of weekly MVPA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That trend held true across all durations of exercise, the researchers found, with women consistently seeing "proportionately greater benefits" for any amount of exercise than men did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 20% of women and 28% of men said they engaged in two or more sessions of strength training, such as lifting weights, each week. Overall, though, women reported an average of about 0.85 sessions per week, while men averaged 1.25 sessions per week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On average, the women who strength-trained at least twice a week had a 19% lower mortality risk than women who trained less often or not at all. Men, on average, saw a 11% lower risk compared with inactive men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These benefits were even greater when it came to cardiovascular health specifically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/exercise/why-is-it-harder-for-some-people-to-build-muscle-than-others" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/exercise/why-is-it-harder-for-some-people-to-build-muscle-than-others"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why is it harder for some people to build muscle than others?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared with inactive individuals, women who performed aerobic physical activity had a 36% lower cardiovascular mortality risk, while for active men, this risk reduction was about 14%. Muscle strengthening produced similar outcomes, with a cardiovascular risk reduction of 30% for women and 11% for men, compared to baseline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What surprised us the most was the fact that women who do muscle strengthening had a reduction in their cardiovascular mortality by 30%," &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2024/03/11/1236791784/strength-resistance-weight-training-longevity-aging-heart-disease" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2024/03/11/1236791784/strength-resistance-weight-training-longevity-aging-heart-disease" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Gulati told NPR&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. "We don't have many things that reduce mortality in that way," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study did have some limitations, including that people's exercise data was self-reported, so it relied on the participants accurately reporting their activity levels.The study also tracked only leisure-time exercise, meaning it didn't count exercise completed during household tasks or as part of a job, which may have also contributed to the results. In addition, the study didn't account for potentially unassessed health issues in some participants, or changes in people's exercise trends over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, the results echo similar findings from a 2011 meta-analysis published in the journal &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/full/10.1161/CIRCULATIONAHA.110.010710" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/full/10.1161/CIRCULATIONAHA.110.010710" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Circulation&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;This review of 33 studies concluded that there was a stronger link between exercise and lower death risk in women than men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers behind the 2024 study hope their findings could help motivate more women to exercise, whether through traditional "&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/what-does-cardio-do-to-your-body" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/what-does-cardio-do-to-your-body"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cardio&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;" or muscle strengthening regimes including &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/bodyweight-exercises-without-equipment" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/bodyweight-exercises-without-equipment"&gt;&lt;u&gt;bodyweight exercises&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or lifting weights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am hopeful that this pioneering research will motivate women who are not currently engaged in regular physical activity to understand that they are in a position to gain tremendous benefit for each increment of regular exercise they are able to invest in their longer-term health," &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://researchers.cedars-sinai.edu/Christine.Albert?adobe_mc=MCMID%3D23607495020614261753066950317791887461%7CMCORGID%3DF47CD0AC591352EC0A495E82%2540AdobeOrg%7CTS%3D1747169522&amp;amp;adobe_mc=MCMID%3D23607495020614261753066950317791887461%7CMCORGID%3DF47CD0AC591352EC0A495E82%2540AdobeOrg%7CTS%3D1747169534" target="_blank" data-url="https://researchers.cedars-sinai.edu/Christine.Albert?adobe_mc=MCMID%3D23607495020614261753066950317791887461%7CMCORGID%3DF47CD0AC591352EC0A495E82%2540AdobeOrg%7CTS%3D1747169522&amp;amp;adobe_mc=MCMID%3D23607495020614261753066950317791887461%7CMCORGID%3DF47CD0AC591352EC0A495E82%2540AdobeOrg%7CTS%3D1747169534" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Christine Albert&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, chair of the Department of Cardiology in the Smidt Heart Institute who was not involved in the study, said in the statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-freeText-N4XEYEtRm6XVSbi4VufaKV-7lkHBUcyBLsyA5zGLUPf8tDbQOiX8W3l" class="slice-container freeText-wrapper freeText-N4XEYEtRm6XVSbi4VufaKV-7lkHBUcyBLsyA5zGLUPf8tDbQOiX8W3l slice-container-freeText"&gt;&lt;div class="info-block"&gt;&lt;p class="infoDisclaimer"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and is not meant to offer medical or fitness advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxOOXBXNHU0a2lzSjJRd2NoOHNyb2Z3R3oydWVvN1E4WDZkSFJmb3VOLXM1d0RWZDlMMXRkaXJEaUhjOEtDR2xacmhyMl9PYnl2QzRmVGFJc0lKa3RHWTNIcFpUWEY5SlphSWQ1cl9ob0dFckh5MkstVFZnVU44NlRqNVl5UzctWjg</guid></item><item><title>大平原动物园的蝙蝠狂犬病检测呈阳性- KELOLAND.com | Bat tests positive for rabies at Great Plains Zoo - KELOLAND.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxOY3RqT3E5XzdBTHNYRXNrbnBsUDBVZVlPcHhNOGhVOFhVd3lNc1ZrazRYd0h1TzdEUWl4Q1BfTFVXUGxQYll4RlYtRHZGSVNoTlFiUkxqUE11UDlTZVNSZHR6clZDc1ptOThRNVlXMnRxYkI4MW42TzQ3a081QWhqTUtfeXB6OWRqamFLQm1nTDFlQlpJbFHSAZsBQVVfeXFMTnNCa1VvYXltVkhGMGFoMDZ2ODNsUHEwVlNJa1BocDB3SS0zUE1JS3JRbHdlaTd6Y3RvZW5SY2J6ajVINkRIMEEwOXlrdC1BTVotUlVJelB2NGpLTjZRdGV1VEIydHBxQjlraDExYUpDZkp3Zm1DNjBoMUxTLWl1OU02NjlUWHZuSmRGMlJFMm0wY3JpZERXM3k3V1U?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>KELOLAND.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 16:25:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxOY3RqT3E5XzdBTHNYRXNrbnBsUDBVZVlPcHhNOGhVOFhVd3lNc1ZrazRYd0h1TzdEUWl4Q1BfTFVXUGxQYll4RlYtRHZGSVNoTlFiUkxqUE11UDlTZVNSZHR6clZDc1ptOThRNVlXMnRxYkI4MW42TzQ3a081QWhqTUtfeXB6OWRqamFLQm1nTDFlQlpJbFHSAZsBQVVfeXFMTnNCa1VvYXltVkhGMGFoMDZ2ODNsUHEwVlNJa1BocDB3SS0zUE1JS3JRbHdlaTd6Y3RvZW5SY2J6ajVINkRIMEEwOXlrdC1BTVotUlVJelB2NGpLTjZRdGV1VEIydHBxQjlraDExYUpDZkp3Zm1DNjBoMUxTLWl1OU02NjlUWHZuSmRGMlJFMm0wY3JpZERXM3k3V1U</guid></item><item><title>与精神分裂症动机丧失相关的炎症-神经科学新闻 | Inflammation Tied to Motivation Loss in Schizophrenia - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTE5tYkVNbVdBeDlFV3VjWnNUbjdmYlRLcjB2X2NsX25RLVIyTTNBbXRmM2MtSnFIc3IxSERvTkdrajRLSTk4ODZfeUdkckFpTjlSZ1pRX0ZCQXZLRHd0Y2ZLRi1ENFRaYjZGbVAzdi1JTmFiLVlPU2JQZlVwSTVYUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study has uncovered a biological link between inflammation and motivational deficits in people with schizophrenia, identifying a promising treatment target for symptoms that current medications fail to address. Higher levels of the inflammatory marker C-reactive protein were associated with reduced activity in brain regions involved in reward and motivation, such as the ventral striatum and ventromedial prefrontal cortex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These brain changes were specifically linked to negative symptoms like difficulty initiating work or social relationships, rather than to hallucinations or delusions. The findings lay the groundwork for precision medicine trials targeting inflammation in this subgroup of patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflammation-Motivation Link:&lt;/strong&gt; High C-reactive protein levels correlate with motivational deficits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain Circuit Impacted:&lt;/strong&gt; Inflammation disrupts reward-related activity in the ventral striatum and prefrontal cortex.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Targeted Treatment Trial:&lt;/strong&gt; Infliximab is being tested for patients with both high inflammation and negative symptoms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Emory University&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new study from Emory University has identified a biological connection between inflammation and deficits in motivation in individuals with schizophrenia, offering new hope for treating symptoms that have long been resistant to existing therapies.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Published in Neuropsychopharmacology, the official publication of the American College of Neuropsychopharmacology, the study found that higher levels of C-reactive protein — a blood biomarker of inflammation produced by the liver — were associated with reduced activity in brain circuits tied to reward and motivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-110079"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-770x514.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-293x196.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a man holding his head." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-770x514.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-293x196.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/inflammation-motivation-schizophrenia-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;For example, previous studies of medications targeting inflammation in patients with schizophrenia have largely failed by not identifying which patients would benefit from these approaches. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;These brain changes, in turn, were linked to negative symptoms of schizophrenia specific to motivational deficits, such as difficulties in finding work, relationships or school. The inflammation was not associated with other schizophrenia symptoms such as hallucinations, delusions or depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings are significant because current antipsychotic medications do not address these motivational deficits and, in some cases, may even worsen them. These symptoms are also strongly associated with poor functional outcomes in patients with schizophrenia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers focused on a key brain circuit involving the ventral striatum and the ventromedial prefrontal cortex — areas previously shown to be sensitive to inflammation in studies of depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is the first study in schizophrenia to link inflammation with both brain changes in reward circuits and specific motivational symptoms,” says David Goldsmith, MD, associate professor in the Department of Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences at Emory University School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By identifying a biological mechanism underlying these symptoms, we are closer to developing targeted treatments that could offer real relief to patients.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study supports a precision medicine approach by suggesting treatments targeting inflammation may only benefit a specific group of patients — those with elevated inflammatory markers and significant motivational challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, previous studies of medications targeting inflammation in patients with schizophrenia have largely failed by not identifying which patients would benefit from these approaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work helped lay the foundation for a current experimental-medicine trial at Emory testing the anti-inflammatory drug infliximab, commonly used to treat rheumatoid arthritis and inflammatory bowel disease, in patients with schizophrenia who have high inflammation and motivational deficits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the first study of infliximab in this patient population and designed to test whether the impact of inflammation on this circuit and these symptoms may be causal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is an urgent need to develop new strategies to treat the negative symptoms of schizophrenia, which remains one of the greatest unmet needs in the field,” says Goldsmith.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We hope this line of research will change that. If we want to support recovery from schizophrenia, we must be able to treat these symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;The study was funded by the National Institutes of Mental Health through a K23 Career Development Award (K23MH114037) totaling $957,420 over five years, as well as KL2TR002381 and UL1TR002378. Mentors on the project included Andrew Miller, MD (primary mentor), Michael Treadway, PhD and Elaine Walker, PhD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this inflammation and schizophrenia research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#86ecf4ece9eee8bfc6e3ebe9f4ffa8e3e2f3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Jennifer Johnson McEwen&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://emory.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Emory University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Jennifer Johnson McEwen – Emory University&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Closed access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41386-025-02114-2" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Inflammation is associated with avolition and reduced resting state functional connectivity in corticostriatal reward circuitry in patients with schizophrenia&lt;/a&gt;” by David Goldsmith et al.&lt;em&gt; Neuropsychopharmacology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inflammation is associated with avolition and reduced resting state functional connectivity in corticostriatal reward circuitry in patients with schizophrenia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Low-grade inflammation has been associated with negative symptoms in patients with schizophrenia. Of these symptoms, deficits in motivation and pleasure, especially in the domain of avolition, are particularly disabling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Effects of inflammation on motivational deficits in patients with depression are associated with disruptions in corticostriatal reward circuitry involving the inferior ventral striatum (iVS) and ventromedial prefrontal cortex (vmPFC).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Accordingly, we examined the relationships among inflammation, negative symptoms, and corticostriatal reward circuitry in patients with schizophrenia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Negative symptoms and high sensitivity C-reactive protein (hsCRP) were obtained in 57 individuals with schizophrenia. Resting state functional connectivity (rsFC) was obtained from a subset of 43 of these individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Associations were tested between hsCRP and the motivation and pleasure (MAP) and expressivity (EXP) dimensions of the Brief Negative Symptom Scale (BNSS) as well as targeted rsFC between iVS and vmPFC. Covariates in all statistical models included age, sex, race, smoking, body mass index, depression, and chlorpromazine equivalents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;hsCRP was significantly associated with BNSS MAP (β = 0.34, p&lt;sub&gt;corr&lt;/sub&gt; = 0.022, specifically the domains of avolition and asociality (&lt;em&gt;p&lt;/em&gt; &amp;lt; 0.05), but not BNSS EXP (β = −0.17, p&lt;sub&gt;corr&lt;/sub&gt; = 0.57) or the domains of blunted affect or alogia (both &lt;em&gt;p&lt;/em&gt; &amp;gt; 0.05). hsCRP was also significantly associated with decreased rsFC from right iVS to vmPFC (β=−0.37, p&lt;sub&gt;corr&lt;/sub&gt; = 0.029), which in turn, was associated with increased avolition in individuals with higher (hsCRP &amp;gt;2 mg/L) but not lower inflammation (β=−14.01, &lt;em&gt;p&lt;/em&gt; = 0.007 vs. β = 0.07, &lt;em&gt;p&lt;/em&gt; = 0.77, respectively).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;hsCRP was associated with reduced avolition and corticostriatal rsFC in patients with schizophrenia and increased inflammation, underscoring the need for further research to replicate these associations with brain connectivity changes in this subgroup of individuals with schizophrenia.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:59:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5tYkVNbVdBeDlFV3VjWnNUbjdmYlRLcjB2X2NsX25RLVIyTTNBbXRmM2MtSnFIc3IxSERvTkdrajRLSTk4ODZfeUdkckFpTjlSZ1pRX0ZCQXZLRHd0Y2ZLRi1ENFRaYjZGbVAzdi1JTmFiLVlPU2JQZlVwSTVYUQ</guid></item><item><title>FDA批准首次验血以诊断阿尔茨海默氏症- Axios | FDA clears first blood test to diagnose Alzheimer's - Axios</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMic0FVX3lxTE1ScHhDSVQtX0NXdjZKaFJtQlhZNTlSTGZwbVRWWU1ZRno5cmlETE1kb2VnMHRqS1FEUlFmVGo5UkVuSjlpUE9rb3BQRWl2MUlkTkZueEFDVmppUnBGOGhuaTJUX3lOREhvaGZSYThKbDRLTEE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:48:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE1ScHhDSVQtX0NXdjZKaFJtQlhZNTlSTGZwbVRWWU1ZRno5cmlETE1kb2VnMHRqS1FEUlFmVGo5UkVuSjlpUE9rb3BQRWl2MUlkTkZueEFDVmppUnBGOGhuaTJUX3lOREhvaGZSYThKbDRLTEE</guid></item><item><title>你的大脑喜欢深呼吸，科学解释了原因-神经科学新闻 | Your Brain Loves Deep Breathing, Science Explains Why - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMickFVX3lxTE1LQzJmeVhrN2NiNVhlaHo1Q1pkQlBaUWw1TXhIN2x4U1JINkh2SkJsSk9lOFFTYUhmTjZEWjZDdE9JMnlTSTlqMC1OR0xYYWxId0lpNDJIR2ZJNEV5ZU9lZ0FidGl4di1RTFVJN3BCQTB4QQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Breathwork, or the practice of intentionally controlling one’s breathing, has been shown to calm brain activity, reduce anxiety, and even ease symptoms of depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deep, slow breathing engages neural circuits that regulate emotional states, producing a measurable calming effect. This process is rooted in biology, not belief—animal studies show that consistent slow breathing reduces fear responses, confirming the effect isn’t just placebo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Simple techniques like box breathing and 4-7-8 breathing can offer benefits in as little as five minutes. While intense breathwork methods can cause altered states, most people benefit from basic breathing exercises. Breathwork offers a powerful, accessible tool for managing stress and enhancing mental well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neurobiological Basis:&lt;/strong&gt; Breathwork activates calming signals across brain circuits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Proven in Animals:&lt;/strong&gt; Mice trained to breathe slowly showed reduced fear responses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Simple Is Effective:&lt;/strong&gt; Techniques like box breathing can lower stress in just minutes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;UCLA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Breathwork – intentionally changing breathing patterns to improve physical, mental or emotional well-being – may seem woo-woo, but the science behind the practice is sound, says Jack Feldman, PhD, a professor of neurobiology at the David Geffen School of Medicine at UCLA.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Feldman discussed how breathing affects the brain in a conversation with Tyrone Lindqvist, lead singer of the Australian electronic dance trio Rufus Du Sol, on a recent episode of the “Sing for Science” podcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-110075"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce.jpg" alt="This shows a person in the lotus position. The brain and lungs are highlighted." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/deep-beating-calmness-neurosicnce-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;In other words, do deep breaths calm us down because we expect them to? Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The band has incorporated breathwork into its pre-performance ritual, Lindqvist said, and its new album, “Inhale/Exhale,” was partly inspired by the practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Breathwork has felt like a big part of our last three years,” Lindqvist said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Feldman has been studying breathing and the brain for more than 40 years. In 1986, he discovered and named the area in the brain responsible for generating and controlling breathing, known as the preBötzinger Complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More recently, he and colleagues have investigated the effects of breathing rhythms and patterns on emotions, finding that slower breathing leads to a calmer mental state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We think that the survival of early mammals was improved by their ability to breathe slowly,” Dr. Feldman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“All mammals sigh, and we think under proper conditions they use their own form of breathwork in response to stressful situations. … It’s something we think that evolved early that we ultimately hijacked in terms of breathwork.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What makes breathwork work?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Feldman started his research in this area probing what he thought was a simple question: What mechanisms in the brain allow it to create a reliable breathing pattern that persists throughout the lifespan and adapts to movement, speech and other activities instantly and without thought?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This line of inquiry has led him to publish more than 150 scientific papers to date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The short answer to why breathwork can have such profound effects on the body and mind is that there are signals related to breathing throughout the brain, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An intentionally deep breath affects those signals, resulting in a calming response. Breathing is also involved in the signaling pathway for depression, he said, adding that studies show that consistent breathwork practice can be effective in treating conditions such as anxiety and depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But one doesn’t need to understand how breath affects the brain to benefit from breathwork, Dr. Feldman said, “much like you can drive a car without understanding how an engine works.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Practicing common breathing techniques, such as box breathing or 4-7-8 breathing, for a few minutes a day is a great way to start, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Box breathing involves inhaling for four counts, holding for four, exhaling for four, and holding for four; 4-7-8 breathing refers to inhaling for four counts, holding for seven, and exhaling for eight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Feldman said Navy SEALS are known to use box breathing and other breathwork techniques to calm themselves in highly stressful situations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of Dr. Feldman’s recent work has investigated whether the placebo effect contributes to the efficacy of breathwork. In other words, do deep breaths calm us down because we expect them to?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You have a stressful situation, just sit down and take a few deep breaths, five minutes, and people will discover it’s restorative,” says Dr. Jack Feldman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To that end, he and his colleagues modified breathing rates in mice, causing them to breathe more slowly for 30 minutes a day over a period of four weeks. Tests afterward showed the mice were much less fearful than a control group whose breathing wasn’t slowed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s pretty amazing how much less fearful they were,” Dr. Feldman said. “The fact that we can see the effect of breathwork in mice really indicates that it’s … not all placebo components.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He hopes the study, which is awaiting publication, “will have a positive impact on individuals who think breathwork is one of these woo-woo things, that you have to believe in something in particular to make it work,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Breathing methods&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lindqvist was introduced to breathwork by his father-in-law, who was interested in Wim Hof, a Dutch athlete who advocates an intense breathing technique of quick, deep breaths followed by holding the breath for as long as a minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The practice can lead to lightheadedness and tingling sensations in the hands and feet. Hof claims it supports stress reduction and improves sleep. His website also indicates the technique can lead to loss of consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Lindqvist, the practice created a feeling of being “extremely present” that lasted for several hours, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People new to breathwork should start with something less intense, Dr. Feldman suggested: “Don’t go out and run a marathon when you’ve been sitting on the couch.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Wim Hof Method and a similar technique, Holotropic Breathwork, can lead to altered states of consciousness, which both Lindqvist and Dr. Feldman described as “psychedelic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This – and the tingling physical sensations – likely results from changes in carbon dioxide levels caused by hyperventilation, Dr. Feldman explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carbon dioxide levels determine the pH, or acid base balance, of the blood, which has “a profound effect on the neurons in your brain as well as the rest of your body,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Techniques such as the Wim Hof Method or Holotropic Breathwork can be invigorating, he said. But basic, slow breathing is all that’s needed for most people to experience the stress-reducing benefits of breathwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You have a stressful situation, just sit down and take a few deep breaths, five minutes, and people will discover it’s restorative,” Dr. Feldman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Maybe not everyone, but a lot of people will find that to be beneficial, and to me, that’s amazing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this breathwork and neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#0e5946617b7d7a61604e636b6a606b7a207b6d626f206b6a7b" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Will Houston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://ucla.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UCLA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Will Houston – UCLA&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:45:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE1LQzJmeVhrN2NiNVhlaHo1Q1pkQlBaUWw1TXhIN2x4U1JINkh2SkJsSk9lOFFTYUhmTjZEWjZDdE9JMnlTSTlqMC1OR0xYYWxId0lpNDJIR2ZJNEV5ZU9lZ0FidGl4di1RTFVJN3BCQTB4QQ</guid></item><item><title>与阿尔茨海默氏症风险相关的中年皮质醇水平-神经科学新闻 | Midlife Cortisol Levels Linked to Alzheimer’s Risk - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMibkFVX3lxTE5UQ2tfY3FGMVZSeGx6MS1RMTQ0RmRGb1lyN0I0NDJOdmlmeWhab0YtSWNmTEhVUkxQT1Q1WFg4OEhIR2pPNmhBcTNtZGtBTmQtR2gxS1NmZjNFSFlZVk01Ykthc2RKa2hrY1ZQOFhR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study finds that elevated cortisol levels in midlife are linked to increased brain amyloid deposition—a key marker of Alzheimer’s disease—specifically in post-menopausal women. Researchers tracked 305 cognitively healthy individuals over 15 years and discovered that high cortisol predicted amyloid buildup later in life, but only among women who had gone through menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest that hormonal changes may amplify cortisol’s harmful effects on brain health. No similar relationship was found in men or with tau protein, another Alzheimer’s marker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sex-Specific Risk:&lt;/strong&gt; High midlife cortisol predicted Alzheimer’s risk only in post-menopausal women.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amyloid Link:&lt;/strong&gt; Cortisol levels were associated with increased amyloid buildup, not tau.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prevention Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; Findings suggest early stress reduction and hormone-based strategies could lower Alzheimer’s risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;UT San Antonio&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can stress lead to Alzheimer’s disease? It can in women who are post-menopausal, a study led by The University of Texas Health Science Center at San Antoino (UT Health San Antonio) shows.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Analyzing data from 305 cognitively unimpaired participants in the Framingham Heart Study, a long-term and ongoing community-based cohort study of residents in Framingham, Massachusetts, the scientists discovered that high levels of the stress hormone cortisol in midlife are linked to increased amyloid deposition in post-menopausal persons later.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Amyloids are proteins that have folded incorrectly, preventing biologic function, forming deposits in tissues and organs, and implicated in Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-110071"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a woman and a brain." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/cortisol-Alzheimers-aging-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;No significant associations were observed in males or with tau burden, referring to the tau protein that contributes to neuronal dysfunction and death. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;By comparing midlife cortisol levels at the beginning of a 15-year period with disease indicators at the end, the researchers were able to determine that those levels could serve as an Alzheimer’s disease biomarker, with particular attention to gender differences and menopausal status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No significant associations were observed in males or with tau burden, referring to the tau protein that contributes to neuronal dysfunction and death.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“The results highlight the importance of identifying early risk factors when biomarkers are detectable but cognitive impairment is absent,” said Arash Salardini, MD, associate professor of cognitive and behavioral neurology with the Glenn Biggs Institute for Alzheimer’s and Neurodegenerative Diseases at UT Health San Antonio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Salardini is first author of the study titled, “Elevated serum cortisol associated with early-detected increase of brain amyloid deposition in Alzheimer’s disease imaging biomarkers among menopausal women: The Framingham Heart Study,” published April 24 in &lt;em&gt;Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia: The Journal of the Alzheimer’s Association.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Other authors also are with UT Health San Antonio, as well as the University of Texas School of Public Health San Antonio; Framingham Heart Study of the National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute of the National Institutes of Health; Boston University; Gonzaba Medical Group, San Antonio; University of Galway, Ireland; Cedars-Sinai Medical Center; Massachusetts General Hospital/Harvard Medical School; New York University Grossman School of Medicine; Brigham and Women’s Hospital; Yale University; and the University of California at Davis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our work shows that considering sex and hormonal status in understanding Alzheimer’s disease pathogenesis is important, and suggests that stress reduction and hormonal interventions may hold promise for Alzheimer’s prevention, especially in at-risk women,” said Sudha Seshadri, founding director of the Biggs Institute and senior author of the study.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Targeting risk factors early&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The study notes that “sporadic” Alzheimer’s disease is the leading cause of cognitive decline in older adults. That features a prolonged asymptomatic phase of amyloid beta accumulation, the main component of amyloid plaques, eventually triggering progressive cognitive decline.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Recognizing that these biological changes are already well established by the time symptoms emerge, effective early interventions must target Alzheimer’s disease risk factors during the preclinical stages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, despite significant advancements in understanding how the disease affects the body’s normal biological processes, more than half of the overall risk has remained unexplained, underscoring the critical need to identify additional risk factors that can be targeted during the preclinical stage.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;One promising line of investigation centers on cortisol, a steroid hormone essential for cellular homeostasis, or balance, and the stress response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genetic studies had identified mutations in glucocorticoid, or steroid hormones that have anti-inflammatory and immunosuppressive effects, signaling pathways that increase susceptibility to Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Also, several cross-sectional and longitudinal studies had reported that higher blood cortisol levels are linked to an increased likelihood of developing the disease.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To address gaps and inconsistencies across those studies, the researchers led by UT Health San Antonio conducted a longitudinal analysis using data from the third-generation cohort of the Framingham Heart Study, which dates to 1948 and now is directed by the National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute of the National Institutes of Health.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They assessed the relationship between serum cortisol levels in the 305 cognitively unimpaired, middle-aged individuals – 48.5% female, with a mean age of 39.6 years –and amyloid/tau burdens approximately 15 years later using positron emission tomography (PET) imaging. And they performed multivariable regression analyses adjusted for confounders.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;All this allowed them to investigate cortisol’s impact at an earlier stage of Alzheimer’s disease pathogenesis, where interventions might be most effective.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Given the neuroprotective effects of estrogen and testosterone, which mitigate cortisol’s deleterious impact on neural tissues, they also explored sex-specific differences, focusing particularly on post-menopausal risk.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;They hypothesized that cortisol’s impact on Alzheimer’s pathology would be more pronounced in women, especially after menopause, consistent with some previous findings.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Indeed, they found that post-menopausal women with high midlife cortisol are at increased risk of Alzheimer’s disease, and that post-menopausal hormone changes may amplify cortisol’s effects on amyloid.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;“Longitudinal follow-up of our cohort will be crucial to determine whether these early amyloid changes translate into clinical symptoms and to clarify the causal role of cortisol in Alzheimer’s disease development,” Salardini said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this Alzheimer’s disease research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1d7178786e2f2f5d6869756e7e6e7c33787968" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Steven Lee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://uthscsa.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UT San Antonio&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Steven Lee – UT San Antonio&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1002/alz.70179" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Elevated serum cortisol associated with early-detected increase of brain amyloid deposition in Alzheimer’s disease imaging biomarkers among menopausal women: The Framingham Heart Study&lt;/a&gt;” by Arash Salardini et al. &lt;em&gt;Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elevated serum cortisol associated with early-detected increase of brain amyloid deposition in Alzheimer’s disease imaging biomarkers among menopausal women: The Framingham Heart Study&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="alz70179-sec-0010-title"&gt;INTRODUCTION&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study investigates whether midlife cortisol levels predict Alzheimer’s disease (AD) biomarker burden 15 years later, with particular attention to sex differences and menopausal status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="alz70179-sec-0020-title"&gt;METHODS&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We analyzed data from 305 cognitively unimpaired Framingham Heart Study participants (48.5% female; mean age: 39.6 ± 8.1 years). Serum cortisol was categorized into tertiles, with amyloid ([&lt;sup&gt;11&lt;/sup&gt;C]PiB) and tau ([&lt;sup&gt;18&lt;/sup&gt;F]Flortaucipir) positron emission tomography (PET) imaging conducted 15 years later. We performed multivariable regression analyses adjusted for confounders including, apolipoprotein E4 (APOE4) status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="alz70179-sec-0030-title"&gt;RESULTS&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elevated midlife cortisol correlated with increased amyloid deposition, specifically in post-menopausal women, predominantly in posterior cingulate, precuneus, and frontal-lateral regions (&lt;em&gt;p&lt;/em&gt; &amp;lt; 0.05). No significant associations were observed with tau burden or in males.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading" id="alz70179-sec-0040-title"&gt;DISCUSSION&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings reveal post-menopausal women with high midlife cortisol are at increased risk of AD. Results highlight the importance of identifying early risk factors when biomarkers are detectable but cognitive impairment is absent.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 15:21:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE5UQ2tfY3FGMVZSeGx6MS1RMTQ0RmRGb1lyN0I0NDJOdmlmeWhab0YtSWNmTEhVUkxQT1Q1WFg4OEhIR2pPNmhBcTNtZGtBTmQtR2gxS1NmZjNFSFlZVk01Ykthc2RKa2hrY1ZQOFhR</guid></item><item><title>婴儿与其他人对抗新冠肺炎的方式不同-神经科学新闻 | Babies Fight COVID Differently Than Anyone Else - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMib0FVX3lxTFBsVmlNUUd4TVhRTWkxQ1FTQkNOcG9pc3JZem1MOGlyeVpUcm4tZFFpSlJQdmhuS0QtRDJsUmJWUVFZV1pmcWdZeXR3Qzhxejk5SVZiMmpxeUc4cVBZLW0yeC02VXdJbE9MNEFWZGNkRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Infants hospitalized with severe COVID-19 mount an immune response that looks entirely different from that of adults or older children. Researchers found both interferon responses and inflammation were elevated simultaneously—something never before observed in other viral infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;T and B cells in these infants were still naïve yet highly activated, and some even produced their own strong antibody responses, surprising scientists given their age. These findings suggest that infants’ immune systems operate on distinct principles and may require age-specific strategies for treatment and prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dual Activation:&lt;/strong&gt; Infants showed simultaneous high interferon and inflammation—unusual in viral infections.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Naïve but Active:&lt;/strong&gt; Despite never encountering infection, infants’ T and B cells were strongly activated.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Independent Antibodies:&lt;/strong&gt; Some infants produced robust SARS-CoV-2 antibodies, despite relying on maternal immunity.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Infants hospitalized with severe COVID-19 have significantly different immune responses than adults or older children. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The finding comes from scientists at St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital, The Jackson Laboratory for Genomic Medicine, Weill Cornell Medicine, Nationwide Children’s Hospital, Icahn School of Medicine at Mt. Sinai and Yale University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers established the unique features of hospitalized infants’ immune cells during mild, moderate and severe COVID-19. The study may help identify better ways to protect infants from the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was published today in &lt;em&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is one of the first studies to characterize the immune response in young infants hospitalized with severe COVID-19 with high-resolution,” said co-corresponding author Octavio Ramilo, MD, St. Jude Department of Infectious Diseases chair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We found that the infant immune system’s response to SARS-CoV-2 looks nothing like the immune response at any other age, highlighting the need to study infants, specifically, if we want to prevent severe infections and understand the unique features of the infant immune system.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The collaborators studied immune cells from infants ranging from a few weeks to 16 months old who were hospitalized with mild, moderate or severe disease. They compared those cells to immune cells from healthy infants and a published cohort of adults hospitalized with COVID-19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monocytes (a type of white blood cell) from hospitalized infants appeared to have some similar features to those in adults infected with SARS-CoV-2. However, two other major white blood cell types, T and B cells, looked very different than in any other group. Hospitalized infants had more CD4 T cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, both T and B cells were still activated despite being largely naïve, having never encountered an infection. These infants’ T and B cells also expressed the antiviral interferon response, which led to high expression of interferon-stimulated genes at a much higher level than in older children or adults. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Conflicting signals from the infant immune system &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost all infant immune cells expressed high levels of interferon-stimulated genes. At the same time, when the collaborators tested blood from these infants, they found high levels of inflammation-causing molecules (inflammatory cytokines), which differs from previous observations in infants with mild infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings challenge previous beliefs about infant immune responses to SARS-CoV-2. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Normally, we think about the interferon and inflammation systems being in balance with each other,” said co-first author M. Asunción Mejías, MD, PhD, St. Jude Department of Infectious Diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If one is upregulated, the other is downregulated. But what we found was different. In infants, both systems were upregulated in the same cells, monocytes, which we’ve never seen before in other respiratory viral infections.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists identified the differences in these infants’ immune responses through single-cell RNA sequencing of white blood cells. RNA is a copy of instructions from DNA that lets cells express genes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By looking at the RNA from individual cells, the researchers found the features unique to infants and compared them by disease severity. They found more severe disease associated with higher interferon and interferon-stimulated gene expression. High levels of inflammatory cytokines also correlated with more severe disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s unclear whether these high levels of interferon, interferon-stimulated genes and inflammatory cytokines are protecting those with severe disease or contributing to it,” Ramilo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But they are clearly playing a critical role, which will require further studies.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding infant antibody response is a field in its infancy &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;B cells produce specialized molecules called antibodies that target particular parts of viruses, bind to them and stop infections. An infant typically relies on their mother’s antibodies until they are about 6 months old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the pandemic, the researchers examined whether a mother’s immunity to non-SARS coronaviruses, which cause the common cold, would help protect infants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We found that these infants made a strong and robust new antibody response to SARS-CoV-2,” said Mejías.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Their pre-existing maternal antibodies against the endemic coronaviruses did not block infection at all.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The finding was surprising; some infants were as young as just a few weeks old and still created an antibody response to the virus. Infants are typically much older before they begin building such responses for other respiratory viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The children in the study also lacked anti-interferon antibodies, which have been associated with severe COVID-19 in adults, emphasizing that lessons from adult immunity may not translate to infant immune responses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We showed that these hospitalized infants responded to SARS-CoV-2, but differently than anyone else,” Ramilo said. “As COVID-19 is now an endemic disease, we need to understand the unique features of the infant immune system better so we can find ways to help these babies through such infections during their first months of life.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Authors and funding &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s other first author is Djamel Nehar-Belaid of The Jackson Laboratory for Genomic Medicine. The study’s other co-corresponding authors are Jacques Banchereau, The Jackson Laboratory for Genomic Medicine, and Virginia Pascual, Weill Cornell Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s other authors are Zhaohui Xu, St. Jude; Radu Marches, Rushil Yerrabelli, Guo Chen and Duygu Ucar, The Jackson Laboratory for Genomic Medicine; Pablo Sánchez, Sara Mertz and Fang Ye, Nationwide Children’s Hospital; John Tsang, Yale University and Chan Zuckerberg Biohub and Teresa Aydillo, Lisa Miorin, Anastasija Cupic and Adolfo García-Sastre, Icahn School of Medicine at Mount Sinai. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;The study was supported by grants from the National Institutes of Health (JAX Cancer Center P30CA034196, U01AI131386, U19AI135972, U19AI142733 and U19AI168631), start-up funds from the Jackson Laboratory, CRIPT (Center for Research on Influenza Pathogenesis and Transmission), National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases (Center of Excellence for Influenza Research and Response contract #75N93021C00014) and ALSAC, the fundraising and awareness organization of St. Jude. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this COVID-19 and neurodevelopment research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#a2cfcbc1cac3c7ce8cd1cac7c4c4cbc7cec6e2d1d6c8d7c6c78ccdd0c5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Michael Sheffield&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://stjude.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Michael Sheffield – St. Jude Children’s Research Hospital&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-025-59411-z" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Immune perturbations induced by SARS-CoV2 in infants vary with disease severity and differ from adults’ responses&lt;/a&gt;” by Octavio Ramilo et al. &lt;em&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Immune perturbations induced by SARS-CoV2 in infants vary with disease severity and differ from adults’ responses&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Differences in immune profiles of children and adults with COVID-19 have been previously described. However, no systematic studies have been reported from infants hospitalized with severe disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We applied a multidimensional approach to decipher the immune responses of SARS-CoV-2 infected infants (&lt;em&gt;n&lt;/em&gt; = 26; 10 subacute, 11 moderate and 5 severe disease; median age = 1.6 months) and matched controls (&lt;em&gt;n&lt;/em&gt; = 14; median age = 2 months).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Single cell (scRNA-seq) profiling of PBMCs revealed substantial alterations in cell composition in SARS-CoV-2 infected infants; with most cell-types switching to an interferon-stimulated gene (ISG&lt;sup&gt;hi&lt;/sup&gt;) state including: (i) CD14&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; monocytes co-expressing ISGs and inflammasome-related molecules, (ii) ISG&lt;sup&gt;hi&lt;/sup&gt; naive CD4&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; T cells, (iii) ISG&lt;sup&gt;hi&lt;/sup&gt; proliferating cytotoxic CD8&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; T cells, and (iv) ISG&lt;sup&gt;hi&lt;/sup&gt; naive and transitional B cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We observe increased serum concentrations of both interferons and inflammatory cytokines in infected infants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antibody responses to SARS-CoV-2 are also consistently detected in the absence of anti-IFN autoantibodies. Compared with infected adults, infants display a similar ISG signature in monocytes but a markedly enhanced ISG signature in T and B cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings provide insights into the distinct immune responses to SARS-CoV-2 in the first year of life and underscore the importance of further defining the unique features of early life immunity.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:59:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBsVmlNUUd4TVhRTWkxQ1FTQkNOcG9pc3JZem1MOGlyeVpUcm4tZFFpSlJQdmhuS0QtRDJsUmJWUVFZV1pmcWdZeXR3Qzhxejk5SVZiMmpxeUc4cVBZLW0yeC02VXdJbE9MNEFWZGNkRQ</guid></item><item><title>食品包装正在将有害化学物质泄漏到餐点中- Earth.com | Food packaging is leaking harmful chemicals into meals - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiigFBVV95cUxOT2lKTHJpUHFRVS1xYV8zRXpBeHlSNVhnQ0RRaDNqb0hHbFEzUm9BZ0lTQzBuUGEyOTB5aDVjWklYREJ6S2dFN2hsYnh2X3o3Q0RWUHJlbkNoMkNXcmpFUmNFSFhKeXFhOUVBcDZQUnU0cjhZTl9CcVhlS0tNN1RzTXVfc1lRWjBuZWc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;You grab a snack, tear open the package, and munch away. But have you ever wondered what might be slipping into your food? Synthetic chemicals sneak in through packaging, processing, and storage. You can’t see these chemicals, but they are there, and they’re raising serious health concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Nature Medicine&lt;/em&gt; dives into the hidden world of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/many-people-are-willing-to-switch-to-plant-based-food-to-save-the-climate/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;food&lt;/a&gt; contaminants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was not just focused on preservatives and additives. The team studied chemicals that come from food packaging and contact materials – the plastics, metals, and papers that wrap, store, and process what we eat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-synthetic-chemicals-in-food"&gt;Synthetic chemicals in food&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Synthetic chemicals are gatecrashers in our food &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/coal-emissions-threaten-indias-food-security/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;system&lt;/a&gt;. They don’t come from ingredients. They come from the packaging, the containers, and the processing equipment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bisphenols, phthalates, PFAS – these chemicals don’t just sit there. They migrate, moving from plastic wrap into your sandwich, from the can lining into your soup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turns out, the more ultra-processed &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/earth-day-2025-what-were-really-fighting-for/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;foods&lt;/a&gt; you eat, the higher your exposure. These foods aren’t just packed with artificial flavors and preservatives. Ultra-processed foods are also packed in materials that leach synthetic chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-chemicals-hidden-in-food-packaging"&gt;Chemicals hidden in food packaging &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your meal passes through four critical stages before landing on your plate. The first stage is transportation, where food sits in containers lined with synthetic materials, allowing chemicals to leach into it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next comes processing. Here, machines made from plastic and metal come into direct contact with the food, increasing the risk of contamination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The third stage is packaging. Plastic wraps and aluminum cans may seem harmless, but they can act as chemical conduits, allowing synthetic substances to migrate into the food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, there is preparation. Heating a plastic-wrapped &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/vicious-cycle-food-systems-both-suffer-from-and-cause-emissions/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;meal&lt;/a&gt; in the microwave can exacerbate chemical leaching, effectively delivering those contaminants straight to your table.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-synthetic-chemical-delivery-system"&gt;Synthetic chemical delivery system&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultra-processed &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/food-waste-has-a-surprising-impact-on-climate-change/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;foods&lt;/a&gt; are engineered for taste and convenience, but they’re also perfect carriers for synthetic chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foods that come in contact with synthetic materials during every stage of production are more likely to end up with higher chemical loads. And that’s not all. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study connects these contaminants to serious health issues – cancers, heart disease, metabolic disorders, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-public-health-blind-spot"&gt;Public health blind spot&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jane Muncke, the study’s lead author from &lt;a href="https://foodpackagingforum.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Food Packaging Forum&lt;/a&gt; Foundation, said that the evidence is becoming more clear that today’s packaged ultra-processed foods contain many synthetic chemicals and microplastics from various sources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presence of these chemicals is well-documented, and their harmful effects are clear. Yet, regulatory frameworks remain inadequate, barely addressing the full scope of the problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-outdated-testing-methods"&gt;Outdated testing methods &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Testing for these chemicals isn’t as straightforward as it sounds. Most testing methods are outdated, designed for known contaminants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what about the ones we haven’t identified yet? The study pushes for more advanced testing methods that can catch emerging chemicals and microplastics before they slip through regulatory cracks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Packaging is supposed to protect food. But what if it’s doing the opposite? Plastic containers, metal cans, and even paper wrappers can all leach chemicals into food. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Redesigning these materials for safety isn’t just a nice idea – it’s a necessity. The study urges policymakers to push for safer, more sustainable packaging alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rethinking-food-safety"&gt;Rethinking food safety&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Muncke explained that there’s a broader issue – one that extends beyond just individual chemicals. She noted that the health impacts of this type of food contamination are currently under-appreciated and under-studied. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The scientific evidence shows a need for adopting a holistic approach to policymaking, that integrates considerations of planetary and human health, including hazardous FCCs and their impacts on health,&lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt; said Muncke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“&lt;/em&gt;All food packaging, processing equipment, and other food contact materials need to be adequately tested for their safety with regard to migrating food contact chemicals and microplastics using modern testing methods.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-where-do-we-go-from-here"&gt;Where do we go from here?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we keep eating ultra-processed foods, we keep ingesting synthetic chemicals. The study lays it out clearly – we need safer packaging, stricter testing, and stronger regulations. But we also need to rethink what we eat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultra-processed foods might be convenient, but they come with invisible risks. Maybe it’s time to take a closer look at that snack in your hand and consider what may be hiding inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-025-03697-5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Nature Medicine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:28:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOT2lKTHJpUHFRVS1xYV8zRXpBeHlSNVhnQ0RRaDNqb0hHbFEzUm9BZ0lTQzBuUGEyOTB5aDVjWklYREJ6S2dFN2hsYnh2X3o3Q0RWUHJlbkNoMkNXcmpFUmNFSFhKeXFhOUVBcDZQUnU0cjhZTl9CcVhlS0tNN1RzTXVfc1lRWjBuZWc</guid></item><item><title>根据心脏病专家的说法，吃水果是改善心脏健康的首选- EatingWell | The #1 Fruit to Eat for Better Heart Health, According to a Cardiologist - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMicEFVX3lxTE1adHpENzQxZXpENWNOU1prdGNBem5mUVNxclZGMG9fMjEzUkdMZ1NsV1luam5WMDlhODdCSDJFSjcydG9MYUlDR1BhQ1RBa01wd1R4Nk1ORGxSM2tJUHU4M1ZVN0V2S2E5b2ZzX3BxSGY?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;According to a cardiologist, avocados are the best fruits for heart health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avocados are rich in heart-healthy fats, fiber, vitamins, minerals and antioxidants.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Research has found they may help lower cholesterol and blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Heart disease is the No. 1 cause of death in the United States.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; And millions of Americans take cholesterol- and blood pressure-lowering medication to reduce their risk. But what if we told you there were certain &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7872995/complete-list-of-heart-healthy-foods/#citation-1" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;foods that were proven to protect &lt;/a&gt;against heart disease? Like fruit! Of course, there are loads of choices. So, we asked cardiologist &lt;a href="https://www.northshore.org/apps/findadoctor/physicians/sarah-alexander" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Sarah Alexander, M.D., FACC&lt;/a&gt;, to share her favorite fruit for heart health. Her answer? &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8026117/avocados-benefits/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Avocados&lt;/a&gt; (yes, they’re actually fruits!). 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here’s why she’s such a big fan, plus tasty ways to add more of these heart-healthy fruits to meals, snacks and even desserts. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-avocados-may-improve-heart-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Avocados May Improve Heart Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; They’re Rich in Heart-Healthy Nutrients &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Avocados contain vitamins, minerals and antioxidants that support heart health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; One standout, says Alexander, is potassium. “Potassium helps lower blood pressure by decreasing the effects of sodium,” she says. Think of potassium and sodium like a seesaw, where potassium works to counterbalance the blood pressure-raising effects of sodium.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; With nearly 500 milligrams of potassium per half-avocado, they boast even more &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290053/8-foods-with-more-potassium-than-a-banana/" class="pseudoStyle" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;potassium &lt;/a&gt;than bananas.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That’s not all. Avocados are also packed with antioxidants like carotenoids and vitamin E, which help protect blood vessels, lower harmful LDL cholesterol and promote overall vascular health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; They’re Loaded with Beneficial Fats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Avocados are rich in heart-friendly &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7595261/whats-the-difference-between-saturated-fat-and-unsaturated-fat/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;polyunsaturated and monounsaturated fats&lt;/a&gt;. Research has shown that these fats can help lower LDL cholesterol levels.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;These fats are so beneficial that the Dietary Guidelines for Americans specifically recommends prioritizing them over saturated fats as much as possible.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Several studies confirm a link between avocados and lower LDL and better heart health. For instance, a meta-analysis of seven studies found that avocado eaters had lower total and LDL cholesterol than non-avocado eaters.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Additional research links avocado consumption to less heart disease overall. For instance, one study found that people who ate at least two servings of avocado per week were 16% less likely to develop cardiovascular disease and 21% less likely to have coronary heart disease than those who didn’t eat avocados. The study also found that replacing just half a serving of butter or margarine with avocado was associated with a 16% to 22% lower risk of cardiovascular disease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; They’re a Surprising Source of Fiber &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Avocados are packed with fiber, a nutrient that most of us don’t consume enough of. In fact, half an avocado provides nearly 7 grams of fiber. That’s one-quarter of the 28-gram Daily Value! About half of that is &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-nutrient-to-help-lower-cholesterol-8399539" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;cholesterol-lowering soluble fiber&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This helpful fiber binds to cholesterol building blocks in the gut and sweeps them out of your body like a broom, naturally lowering cholesterol. If that weren’t enough, research has found that fiber also plays a role in reducing blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Contain Cholesterol-Lowering Plant Sterols &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Have you ever noticed how margarine tubs are often plastered with heart-healthy logos or claims? The reason is that many of these products contain cholesterol-lowering compounds called plant sterols. Well, so do avocados! In fact, avocados boast more plant sterols than most other fruits. “Plant sterols can lower cholesterol by preventing absorption of cholesterol, and lower cholesterol can reduce your risk of developing cardiovascular disease,” says Alexander. They work by acting like shields, helping block cholesterol absorption in the gut. They’re so effective that they’ve been shown to lower LDL cholesterol by roughly 10%.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-tips-to-enjoy-avocados"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Tips to Enjoy Avocados &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here are some fresh ideas to enjoy avocados in meals, snacks, drinks or even sweet treats: 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try a New Twist on Avocado Toast:&lt;/strong&gt; Who doesn’t love avocado toast? For a new spin on this heart-healthy favorite, try our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/261611/white-bean-avocado-toast/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;White Bean &amp;amp; Avocado Toast&lt;/a&gt;. Or, for a protein-packed alternative, top it with &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/avocado-toast-with-jammy-eggs-8648174" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Jammy Eggs&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transform Them into Dips: &lt;/strong&gt;Guacamole is one of Alexander’s favorites. Plus, it’s one of the easiest dips to prepare. Chipotle fans will love our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/261795/almost-chipotles-guacamole/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Almost Chipotle's Guacamole&lt;/a&gt;. Craving something different? Whip up our ultra-creamy &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/250924/avocado-yogurt-dip/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;Avocado-Yogurt Dip&lt;/a&gt; and enjoy it with sliced fresh veggies for dunking.  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Swap Them in for Mayo:&lt;/strong&gt; Give your chicken or tuna salad a creamy, heart-healthy makeover by swapping in avocado for all or part of your recipe’s mayo. It’s deliciously creamy in this &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7964485/avocado-chicken-salad/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;Avocado Chicken Salad&lt;/a&gt;. Or, mash it to use in place of mayo or cheese in sandwiches. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blend Them into Smoothies or Soups:&lt;/strong&gt; Add fresh or frozen avocado chunks to smoothies or soups for a rich, creamy texture. Need ideas? Try our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/270514/really-green-smoothie/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="6"&gt;Really Green Smoothie&lt;/a&gt; or this avocado-infused &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/252056/creamy-cucumber-soup/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="7"&gt;Creamy Cucumber Soup&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Try Them in Desserts: &lt;/strong&gt;Really! Avocados can be whipped into mousses, shakes, puddings or even frosting. Chocolate lovers, don’t miss our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/251076/chocomole-pudding/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="8"&gt;“Chocomole” Pudding&lt;/a&gt;, or slurp a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/250693/chocolate-avocado-shake/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="9"&gt;Chocolate Avocado Shake&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-spotlight--1-2-post mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight--1-2-post mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight mntl-block theme-1-2-post"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight__heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight__heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Heart-Healthy Recipes to Try&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Avocados are the No. 1 fruit for heart health, according to a cardiologist. These nutritious fruits are jam-packed with a wealth of heart-healthy nutrients. They’re loaded with unsaturated fats, fiber, vitamins, minerals, antioxidants and plant sterols that support heart health. Thanks to their mild flavor and rich and creamy texture, avocados are delicious in dips, sandwiches, smoothies, soups, shakes and even desserts. So, give your heart the love it deserves and dig into one today!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE1adHpENzQxZXpENWNOU1prdGNBem5mUVNxclZGMG9fMjEzUkdMZ1NsV1luam5WMDlhODdCSDJFSjcydG9MYUlDR1BhQ1RBa01wd1R4Nk1ORGxSM2tJUHU4M1ZVN0V2S2E5b2ZzX3BxSGY</guid></item><item><title>一劳永逸的治愈方法：全新凝胶可在24小时内消除耳部感染- SciTechDaily | One-and-Done Cure: New Gel Wipes Out Ear Infections in 24 Hours - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxOanQxTG1vdm5jWUY2RTRvblFqejFtVlhuTElnQWJhajJYUkNSWGdkelJOcGlyMkNVbWhmbHhWaXNuWXNmN2hiX0FhZmc2NGxfUFNVNEFEMGdtek5qZXNONzFEZ09tdXhpcnBnUzZQbDFmN3QxbkdYdFlDeU9pM0ZyRU94LXBMb1NISHotOVhuM2ZnZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 14:11:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxOanQxTG1vdm5jWUY2RTRvblFqejFtVlhuTElnQWJhajJYUkNSWGdkelJOcGlyMkNVbWhmbHhWaXNuWXNmN2hiX0FhZmc2NGxfUFNVNEFEMGdtek5qZXNONzFEZ09tdXhpcnBnUzZQbDFmN3QxbkdYdFlDeU9pM0ZyRU94LXBMb1NISHotOVhuM2ZnZw</guid></item><item><title>每个人都痴迷于蛋白质，但我们实际上缺少的是纤维-《独立报》 | Everyone’s obsessed with protein but what we’re actually lacking is fiber - The Independent</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxPSHhId0NJLUdwU0lMT3lYNTZ3UjBrVkdyWE9lWU1UUDYwMzhYQk53SmRHbmhlNFBfM0V0a0FaaUlDRUJ3cTZIRzBOME9CWDZPZFliZ2dwV28wQktTLWQ5c3lyUjFFYW4zSVNOd3JxWjlUUXNoTEczV05UaTFIck1WSFJXeHFiRWpNejNITF9FWXJ0QnE5QVRqOHpqeG91bGlweEpnMw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 eWQiqu sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 cGmNxG"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iqSitv"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 dlmCG"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 igdyzJ"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cPkZJS"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 fGzMFb sc-hez36s-16 fJelbS"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 fiXggt"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 eSVQSf"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 cDGSNR"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 kxbAkl"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 kGYWZt"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 kGYWZt"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 kGYWZt"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 eXohla"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 hHATii sc-aja53j-7 jikgMc"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 gFogGN"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 frlkrE"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 gggykT sc-culv3z-0 jLhHRc sc-a5wy94-0 lbKISR"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;s &lt;a href="/topic/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/topic/wellness"&gt;wellness&lt;/a&gt; influencers and recipes gain traction online, one macronutrient outshines the rest: &lt;a href="/topic/protein"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protein-rich foods are celebrated as the golden answer — the key to keeping you feel full with less calories, helping both weight loss and muscle gain. However, the protein craze could mean we’re eating too much for our own good. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There’s always been trends around foods that are extreme,” physiologist George Wells, Ph.D., told &lt;em&gt;The Independent&lt;/em&gt;. “We had low fat, then low sugar, and now we happen to have high protein. The extremes tend to catch people’s attention. But they’re not good for us and they never last.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the protein craze, we’re pushing an important nutrient to the side: fiber. Accredited Practicing Dietitian Kim Lindsay says fiber is ignored because carbohydrates have been demonized and feared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When there's a trend towards a low-carb, higher protein, if we're reducing the amount of carbohydrates that we're eating, we're going to naturally reduce the amount of fiber that we're taking in, right?” Lindsay explained. “We have to have a balanced &lt;a href="/topic/diet"&gt;diet&lt;/a&gt; where we include plant foods, protein-containing foods, and fats in our diet.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 hzcAyL"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, balance is being pushed aside for protein-rich eggs, meat and seafood. Snacks previously called “junk food” are getting a wellness makeover, with added protein now found in many bars, chips and gummies. Even the Kardashians are on board, with Khloe Kardashian recently &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DJEfXdrpOO_/"&gt;launching her protein popcorn&lt;/a&gt;, “Kloud,” which offers seven grams of protein per one cup of popcorn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://foodinsight.org/wp-content/uploads/2024/06/2024-IFIC-Food-Health-Survey.pdf"&gt;The International Food Information Council’s annual survey&lt;/a&gt; found that 71 percent of consumers were trying to increase their protein intake this year, a 6 percent rise from 2023. The survey also found that exposure to food and nutrition content online, much of which is protein focused, is up by 54 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be clear, protein is an essential macronutrient to help bodily functions, like fighting infection, providing energy, and building and maintaining muscle mass. Intake depends on body weight, with general guidance being that a just over a third of the calories we consume each day should come from protein. So, with the average American woman weighing around 171 pounds, she should consume about 62 grams of protein a day. The average American man, at around 200 pounds, should eat about 72 grams of protein daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-482ou5-2 hCNBSR sc-482ou5-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 hXrpsW"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-482ou5-0 dcuwoN"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/05/07/21/23/iStock-1644746219.jpeg" srcset="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/05/07/21/23/iStock-1644746219.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.the-independent.com/2025/05/07/21/23/iStock-1644746219.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 QHifS inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-482ou5-1 eZtLil" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 fsbheq inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-55508"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 jEeRhv"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 kBlcBC kIlksO"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 hAhJPR"&gt;(Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Wells believes that due to social media, we’re only focused on having as much protein as possible. “I think the craze around protein right now probably is linked to bodybuilding and the obsession with body composition — looking like you have the six-pack abs,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that ignores the flip side. “If you have too much protein, it's really hard for the body to deal with all of the amino acids that are floating around,” Wells added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s where fiber comes in handy. Typically found in whole grains, fruits, and vegetables, fiber is particularly beneficial to your digestive system and keeping you regular. While men should have about 38 grams a day and women should have 25 grams, as noted by dietitian Kristin Kirkpatrick, you shouldn’t just jump into doing that if you’ve been eating way less. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Fiber intake should be tailored to the individual and the microbiome. However, if you are well under this amount, you should go slow to allow the body adequate time to adjust,” Kirkpatrick, the owner of &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.kristinkirkpatrick.com/"&gt;KAK nutrition consulting,&lt;/a&gt; explained. She added that fiber can also prevent certain cancers and type 2 diabetes and improve heart health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-482ou5-2 hCNBSR sc-482ou5-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 hXrpsW"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-482ou5-0 gTGbNB"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/05/07/21/59/iStock-95229504.jpeg" srcset="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/05/07/21/59/iStock-95229504.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.the-independent.com/2025/05/07/21/59/iStock-95229504.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 QHifS inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-482ou5-1 eZtLil" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 fsbheq inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-55509"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 jEeRhv"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 kBlcBC kIlksO"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 hAhJPR"&gt;(Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Observational studies have found a fiber deficiency among Americans. According to a study published in &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6124841/#bibr10-1559827615588079"&gt;the American Journal of Lifestyle Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, only five percent of the population has the recommended amount of fiber a day. Inadequate intake can result in health issues like chronic constipation and gastrointestinal problems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 hzcAyL"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similar to avoiding high-processed foods just because they’ve got extra protein added to them, we should focus on eating real foods that are naturally high in fiber rather than ultra-processed foods with bits of fiber in them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We gravitate towards highly processed foods because they're engineered to taste fantastic,” Wells said. ”They're high in sugar and salts, and we crave them as a result. There’s no real incentive for the processed foods to be satiating. They're great for business, but they're really not very good for our health.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 13:58:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxPSHhId0NJLUdwU0lMT3lYNTZ3UjBrVkdyWE9lWU1UUDYwMzhYQk53SmRHbmhlNFBfM0V0a0FaaUlDRUJ3cTZIRzBOME9CWDZPZFliZ2dwV28wQktTLWQ5c3lyUjFFYW4zSVNOd3JxWjlUUXNoTEczV05UaTFIck1WSFJXeHFiRWpNejNITF9FWXJ0QnE5QVRqOHpqeG91bGlweEpnMw</guid></item><item><title>心平气和：根据焦虑类型选择正念-神经科学新闻 | Calm Your Mind: Choose Mindfulness by Anxiety Type - Neuroscience News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidEFVX3lxTFBKMmg0TmllWFlMZlhVVHRwUjNRRFRmQWl5RWNJZnlOa1NrbjJHUnlVQkdydmZIT3hXb09zM3owc0ZlYlRDUjJHdm1LX3BTT1R3cDZTejM1akduandzaTZNem1iNmIwRk9GYThIb3ZOeWI3YzFf?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Mindfulness is well known for its calming effects, but researchers now propose that different types of mindfulness practices may be more effective for specific types of anxiety. A new framework suggests that focused attention meditation may benefit those who worry chronically, while open monitoring may help individuals with hypervigilance and physical symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key mechanism behind this benefit is improved cognitive control—the ability to manage thoughts and behaviors in alignment with goals. Anxiety disrupts this control, but mindfulness strengthens it, helping to break the cycle of worry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tailored Practices:&lt;/strong&gt; Focused attention helps worriers; open monitoring helps the hypervigilant.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognitive Control:&lt;/strong&gt; Mindfulness improves goal-oriented thinking disrupted by anxiety.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scientific Support:&lt;/strong&gt; Brain imaging confirms mindfulness alters areas linked to emotional regulation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;WUSTL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re anxious about work, finances, the state of the world, or anything else, you might try a moment of mindfulness. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paying close attention to the present moment without judgment — the basic idea behind all mindfulness techniques — can help calm anxiety and improve focus, said Resh Gupta, a postdoctoral research associate with the Mindfulness Science and Practice research cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; “A lot of research has shown that mindfulness can reduce anxiety symptoms,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-110055"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a woman and bight colors." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/05/mindfulness-anxiety-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Depending on the type of anxiety people are experiencing, some approaches might work better than others. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The calming power of mindfulness is well-known to people who have made the practice a part of their daily lives. Still, experts continue to investigate how it works and which types of mindfulness might be most useful for different types of anxiety, ranging from fleeting bouts of worry to more chronic, clinical anxiety disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We all experience anxiety, but it can manifest in many different ways,” Gupta said. “It’s a tough problem to pin down.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a paper published in&lt;em&gt; Neuroscience and Biobehavioral Reviews&lt;/em&gt;, Gupta and co-authors laid out a new approach to understanding the relationship between mindfulness and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of taking a one-size-fits-all approach, they propose that different kinds of mindfulness practices might be helpful for different varieties of anxiety. The proposed framework should ultimately help us understand how to match anxiety sufferers with more precise treatments, Gupta said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Todd Braver, the William R. Stuckenberg Professor in Human Values and Moral Development and a professor of psychological and brain sciences, is a co-author of the paper. The other co-author is Wendy Heller, a professor of psychology at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work was supported in part by the Mindfulness Science and Practice cluster and the Arts &amp;amp; Sciences’ Incubator for Transdisciplinary Futures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Braver said that the new paper is emblematic of the kinds of work being done by the cluster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is a growing recognition that these practices can be incredibly useful in enhancing psychological well-being,” Braver said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But we still do not fully understand the mechanisms of action by which mindfulness can produce beneficial effects. That’s where the scientific research can be so valuable, by helping us more precisely identify why and how certain practices are effective.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gupta, Braver, and Heller suggest that mindfulness combats anxiety by improving a mental process called cognitive control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Cognitive control is the ability to regulate your thoughts and your actions in a way that helps you achieve your goals,” Gupta said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For example, if you know you have to go to the grocery store right after work, you can keep that goal in mind during the workday and turn down an offer to do something else after work.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Gupta explained, mindfulness and anxiety have opposite impacts on cognitive control. People who are more mindful generally perform better on tasks requiring cognitive control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That observation is supported by neuroimaging studies, which have shown that mindfulness meditation can effectively modulate activity in brain regions that support cognitive control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, anxiety can worsen cognitive control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Worry occupies a lot of space in the brain’s working memory system,” Gupta said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is where your goals are stored.” This impairment in cognitive control can intensify worry symptoms, but using mindfulness to improve cognitive control can help interrupt the harmful cycle of worry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depending on the type of anxiety people are experiencing, some approaches might work better than others, Gupta said. People who spend a lot of time worrying may especially benefit from a type of mindfulness meditation called focused attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Focused attention teaches you to choose an anchor, such as your breath or a sound,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You keep bringing your attention back to that anchor every time your mind wanders. Instead of focusing on the worry, you’re focusing on the present moment experience.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who are hypervigilant and experiencing a lot of physical symptoms of anxiety — rapid heartbeat, sweaty palms, tightness in the chest — may do better with a different approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For this type of anxiety, a form of mindfulness meditation called open monitoring may be beneficial,” Gupta said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Instead of focusing on one thing, such as the breath, you can observe all internal and external experiences from moment to moment in a non-reactive, non-judgmental way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WashU’s Mindfulness Science &amp;amp; Practice cluster offers many resources for university and community members who want to add mindfulness to their lives. The cluster sponsors regular talks as well as other events, including those in which participants can learn mindfulness practices from trained practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’re dedicated to helping the WashU and greater St. Louis community get access to tools to learn about mindfulness science and practice,” Gupta said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Braver is enthusiastic that recent research from the cluster and other institutions will help people gain a greater appreciation of the wide variety of practices that fall under the mindfulness umbrella.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People have different options they can choose from, so it becomes easier to find one that best fits your particular temperament, concerns, or current situation,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s quite empowering to learn these types of practices, and to feel like we can be in charge of how we use them to improve our quality of life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this mindfulness and anxiety research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6b0718030a0d0d0e192b1c1e181f07450e0f1e" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Chris Woolston&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://wustl.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;WUSTL&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact:&lt;/strong&gt; Chris Woolston – WUSTL&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neubiorev.2025.106146" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Reconceptualizing the relationship between anxiety, mindfulness, and cognitive control&lt;/a&gt;” by Resh Gupta et al. &lt;em&gt;Neuroscience and Behavioral Reviews&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reconceptualizing the relationship between anxiety, mindfulness, and cognitive control&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior research has provided initial support for the claim that cognitive control mediates the relationship between anxiety and mindfulness; however, findings are often inconsistent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this review, we argue that the inconsistency may be due to a lack of both conceptual and methodological precision in terms of how anxiety, cognitive control, and mindfulness are operationalized and assessed, and that this imprecision may be a critical source of study confounds and ambiguous outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We unpack this argument by first decomposing anxiety, cognitive control, mindfulness, and relevant experimental paradigms into key dimensions in order to develop a non-unitary, multi-dimensional taxonomy of these constructs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subsequently, we review and reinterpret the prior experimental literature, focusing on studies that examine the relationship between anxiety and cognitive control, mindfulness and cognitive control, and the three-way relationship between anxiety, mindfulness, and cognitive control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across the reviewed studies, there was great variation in the dimensions being examined and the behavioral and/or neural measures employed; therefore, results were often mixed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on this review of literature, we propose a conceptually and methodologically precise framework from which to study the effects of mindfulness on cognitive control in anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The framework theoretically aligns anxiety dimensions with specific mindfulness states and interventions, further suggesting how these will impact specific cognitive control dimensions (proactive, reactive).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These can be assessed with experimental paradigms and associated behavioral and neural metrics to index the relevant dimensions with high precision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Novel experimental studies and tractable research designs are also proposed to rigorously test this theoretical framework.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 13:52:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTFBKMmg0TmllWFlMZlhVVHRwUjNRRFRmQWl5RWNJZnlOa1NrbjJHUnlVQkdydmZIT3hXb09zM3owc0ZlYlRDUjJHdm1LX3BTT1R3cDZTejM1akduandzaTZNem1iNmIwRk9GYThIb3ZOeWI3YzFf</guid></item></channel></rss>