<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>皱纹是“荣誉徽章” ：如何拥抱衰老的面孔- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251121-how-to-embrace-an-ageing-face</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;b id="much-like-our-other-organs,-our-skin-begins-to-age-from-the-moment-we-are-born.-in-a-world-obsessed-with-youthfulness,-here's-how-you-can-look-after-your-skin-while-embracing-an-ageing-face." class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;Much like our other organs, our skin begins to age from the moment we are born. In a world obsessed with youthfulness, here's how you can look after your skin while embracing an ageing face.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;On Mount Olympus, sometime around 800-900 BC, the gods and goddesses of Ancient Greece were served sweet nectar and ambrosia by &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-031-58691-0_6" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Hebe&lt;/a&gt;, the goddess of immortal youth. A beautiful young woman, Hebe was symbolic of being in the "prime of life". Her counterpart, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-031-58691-0_6" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Geras&lt;/a&gt;, the god or spirit of old age (hence the English words "geriatric" and "gerontology"), was depicted as a haggard, wrinkled man, often leaning on a walking stick. Instead of beauty, he represented biological decline, and the fear of death. Together, Hebe and Geras are just one of the many representations of ageing in our culture and history that serve the reminder: no one can escape the passing of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Humanity's obsession with youthfulness has only intensified since Ancient Greece. Our skin, a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2352552524000756" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;living ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;, is at the centre of this – not only is it the largest organ in the body, but it's also visible – or as one group of researchers in France put it, "&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2352552524000756" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;social&lt;/a&gt;". In fact, in their study of 1,300 people across 54 countries and five sociological age groups (Gen Z, millennials, baby boomers, Gen X and the silent generation), 85% of participants felt that &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2352552524000756" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;their skin reflected their personality&lt;/a&gt;, suggesting it is tied in with their sense of self.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Much like our other organs, skin ages from the moment we are born – so the fight to keep it looking soft like a baby's is an expensive one. As of 2024, the global anti-ageing products market size was valued at approximately &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.grandviewresearch.com/industry-analysis/anti-aging-products-market#:~:text=The%20global%20anti%2Daging%20products,7.7%25%20from%202025%20to%202030." class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;$52bn (£40bn)&lt;/a&gt; in 2024 and is expected to reach $80bn (£63bn) by 2030. But why do we try to resist an ageing face and how can we embrace it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;&lt;span id="how-our-skin-changes-as-we-age" class="sc-d16436d-0 gCPVhV"&gt;&lt;b id="how-our-skin-changes-as-we-age" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;How our skin changes as we age&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Our skin is incredible, really. While only a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279255/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;few millimetres thick&lt;/a&gt;, it makes up one-seventh of our body weight – for the average adult, around &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0899900723003787" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;2.7kg to 3.6kg&lt;/a&gt; (6lbs to 8lbs).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBrYk10dW1PdVZfcVhaZmJZbkhoSmtkeHUtbkJnX19EV2RoNVRsUnZCdmFnQ1RxVmRHSHQ5bUZOMUphZVhvT0wwa0V4TE1SNTd5T2VuSlVmNmxPczlQdTd3V3d3bWkwWVZpcUZGQTNtMTByenh3Q05vangzRnpzQQ</guid></item><item><title>糖尿病专家分享了7个自然控制血糖峰值的秘诀：在饮食中添加胡芦巴籽，补充水分等|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/diabetologist-shares-7-hacks-to-manage-blood-sugar-spikes-naturally-add-fenugreek-seeds-to-diet-hydrate-well-and-more-101763874560017.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/diabetologist-shares-7-hacks-to-manage-blood-sugar-spikes-naturally-add-fenugreek-seeds-to-diet-hydrate-well-and-more-101763874560017.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dietary adjustment is a non-negotiable essential to manage blood sugar spikes. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;If &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fortis-gastroenterologist-calls-sabudana-a-scam-warns-it-can-cause-weight-gain-and-spike-blood-sugar-101763727899466.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="blood sugar"&gt;blood sugar&lt;/a&gt; continues to spike rapidly because of concerning food choices, then there are prominent risks of developing &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gynaecologist-warns-pcos-linked-insulin-resistance-may-raise-type-2-diabetes-risk-shares-lifestyle-tips-to-manage-it-101757316779742.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="insulin resistance"&gt;insulin resistance&lt;/a&gt; and subsequently developing diabetes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/23/550x309/fenugreek_seeds_1756538938194_1763875863264.jpg" alt="Fenugreek seed is recommended by the expert to control blood sugar spikes!(Picture credit: Shutterstock)" title="Fenugreek seed is recommended by the expert to control blood sugar spikes!(Picture credit: Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/23/550x309/fenugreek_seeds_1756538938194_1763875863264.jpg" alt="Fenugreek seed is recommended by the expert to control blood sugar spikes!(Picture credit: Shutterstock)" title="Fenugreek seed is recommended by the expert to control blood sugar spikes!(Picture credit: Shutterstock)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Fenugreek seed is recommended by the expert to control blood sugar spikes!(Picture credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/langlo/article/PIIS2214-109X(23)00502-8/fulltext" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="study"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in The Lancet Global Health in September 2025 shared that 1 in 5 adults, above 45 years, has diabetes. Moreover, urban areas had double the diabetes rates as compared to rural areas, suggesting the role of contemporary lifestyle in diabetes prevalence. It also highlighted that India contributes a large share of the global diabetes burden. India is called the diabetes capital of the world.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mumbai-diabetologist-warns-late-night-eating-may-raise-diabetes-risk-shares-5-dinner-options-for-stable-blood-sugar-101763031477601.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Mumbai diabetologist warns late-night eating may raise diabetes risk; shares 5 dinner options for stable blood sugar"&gt;Mumbai diabetologist warns late-night eating may raise diabetes risk; shares 5 dinner options for stable blood sugar&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But diabetes is not just a problem for older adults. Young Indians are also getting diagnosed with it. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.ijddc.org/doc/UZxkQtNh-10-13410_2024_1357_PrintPDF.pdf" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="study"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in May 2024 found that diabetes is very common in young Indians, with people under 35 years old, already 17 percent having diabetes, and 40 percent if someone already has a family history of diabetes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Given how common diabetes is in older adults, younger adults are at a higher risk. Add to this the hectic lifestyle factors, like increased stress at work, ordering processed and takeaway foods, and low physical activity.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;While early screening is one of the primary tools to detect diabetes, embracing healthy lifestyle habits, such as proper nutrition, regular exercise, and stress management, helps to prevent the disease. The first approach is how to manage a blood sugar spike naturally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;To understand how to manage blood sugar spikes, HT Lifestyle reached out to Dr Aasim Maldar, consultant endocrinologist and diabetologist, PD Hinduja Hospital &amp;amp; Medical Research Centre, Mahim.&lt;/span&gt; He said, "Optimal lifestyle forms the foundation of diabetes therapy and many other chronic illnesses." This means, lifestyle is the basis on which all other treatments rest, as the doctor called it ‘foundation.’&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Many trendy diets or quick fixes are circulating on social media, but Dr Maldar warned against them. “Going ahead with fad diets lacking a scientific basis and nurturing unrealistic expectations can hardly be useful.” These trending diets promise unrealistic and dramatic results, which are unrealistic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Maldar shared 7 ways you can manage your blood sugar spikes naturally, revealing why they work. But he did remind that these are not a ‘cure-all.' They are complementary in nature and support blood sugar management. But they do not replace prescribed medications, especially for those who have been diagnosed with diabetes or are at high risk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Here are the foods and habits the diabetologist recommended:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;1. Add cinnamon to diet:&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/01/10/550x309/cinnamon_1736518194898_1736518195163.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Cinnamon's antioxidants help in blood sugar management. (Please credit: Pexels)" title="Cinnamon's antioxidants help in blood sugar management. (Please credit: Pexels)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Cinnamon's antioxidants help in blood sugar management. (Please credit: Pexels)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cinnamon is rich in antioxidants and has properties that mimic insulin, promoting the transport of glucose into cells. Cinnamon can reduce fasting blood glucose levels in individuals with type 2 diabetes.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Add to foods like oatmeal or smoothies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Stay hydrated:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hydration aids in managing blood sugar levels by preventing dehydration-induced glucose spikes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Aim for consistent water intake to support overall hydration and metabolic processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;But, anything in excess can be harmful, including water intake, especially in people with kidney diseases, electrolyte disturbances, and heart ailments, so drink water in moderation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Fenugreek seeds:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fenugreek seeds contain soluble fibre, which slows down digestion and carbohydrate absorption. They improve blood sugar control and reduce fasting glucose levels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Soaking the seeds makes them easier to digest and enhances their benefits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. Yoga and mindful breathing:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/07/23/550x309/yoga_1_1753277993402_1753277993554.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Calm yourself down with the help of yoga so you can sleep better. (Picture credit: Shutterstock)" title="Calm yourself down with the help of yoga so you can sleep better. (Picture credit: Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Calm yourself down with the help of yoga so you can sleep better. (Picture credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Regular practice of yoga and deep breathing can reduce cortisol levels, a stress hormone that affects blood sugar. These practices promote relaxation and improve glycemic control.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Incorporating them into routine can mitigate stress-related sugar spikes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Vinegar before meals:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Vinegar, particularly apple cider vinegar, boosts insulin sensitivity by slowing the rate of stomach emptying. This can help in lowering postprandial glucose levels, making it a simple addition before meals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Consuming vinegar can help moderate post-meal blood sugar rises, providing temporary improvements in glucose control when used regularly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;6. Add resistant starch:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/07/03/original/brown_rice12_1751528322960.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Brown rice is a healthier alternative to white rice. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Brown rice is a healthier alternative to white rice. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Brown rice is a healthier alternative to white rice. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Resistant starch acts similarly to soluble fibre, providing numerous health benefits, including improved insulin sensitivity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It helps improve insulin sensitivity, which can contribute to better glycemic control over time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Resistant starch is found in foods like green bananas, legumes, and cooked-then-cooled brown rice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7. &lt;span&gt;Magnesium-rich foods:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Magnesium plays a critical role in glucose metabolism and insulin action.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Foods that are high in magnesium, like leafy greens and nuts, can help improve insulin sensitivity, reducing the risk of developing type 2 diabetes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 06:38:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxOTjMxUmh6S0tzTXpOeXJVR3NFRWlubGYwd081REFONHlSMVF0VEZhWV9SNnR5djBZYUFGWk5vaTBpMjl6MUdnb1VEMG5ZQXhZNVJVa2xBamI3THVTczVIOU5IMTJpdHJUeEJ1R281RTF4a2NMdF9aOUtLdlBmdjBaNS1uUWNoZ0JEbG5xUHQ2SS04amVocmpuMERoT00tbUJocUVyQ3dvbjVKaTlpR05HZFF4dmgxWG9MOEdNbHJ3N0UxT3RwZDJWd1huWGxOaThlbDdmQWlqcjFQcWRRTHJOTF9tMkpKZjFaenF1T09KRnJDSHhkcXpiVDY4Y1d5blA5dXBoV3h4WWpzbkRLaFNqT3JTXzXSAZoCQVVfeXFMTnFuX1F2NkFBS3Vwd2pJcm5zV1lOaUVmbFNPQ2tUQm9GM2lyeG9wa1V2VTRvWmZyb3NRQmFyWGRkSER0cndfQjJUemVwS3JVVU9RNG1LRU9NVllJY29vc0k1UGNFNDE1RjIzeVRRZnRTazd0X1hROUFrSmtIc01Yb1ZOTHUybGVYd2JDLXdpTlFOaDJ5Wk1FVDVwTU12OHdySEk2bk9zWDRENGNzbDlyWms3ZGRtUmJIbk1HSTdJQ2xxZkkySGY5UmhOWU5FeU13YU9TSUhfUWpBSWZhOFp4RGlxdy1kbXdpLVZVa04wNlFaZ3ZBRTVmelhkQ3EwdnBnRXZfUDAzU2owdkJYNWdkRVdOV2FPYWJUS0Nn</guid></item><item><title>科学支持的两分钟每日锻炼，以改善心脏健康-《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/exercise-snacking-workouts-heart-health-b2859776.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 bxpovR sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;f you don’t have an hour to exercise each day, can you spare a minute or two? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the logic behind “exercise snacking”, a more accessible approach to keeping fit which can have an impressive positive impact on your &lt;a href="/news/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt;, according to new research. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exercise snacks are bite-sized servings of &lt;a href="/topic/exercise"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt; you can weave seamlessly into opportune moments throughout your day – think squats while the kettle boils or a few stretches at your desk. Each one usually takes between one and five minutes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doing this consistently has the power to improve cardiometabolic health, particularly in physically inactive people, according to a 2025 systematic review and meta-analysis published in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12354995/"&gt;Scandinavian Journal of Medicine and Science in Sports&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular exercise snacking can improve your heart health, reducing your risk of cardiovascular disease, high blood pressure and high blood sugar levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of exercise snacking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study found that exercise snacking is particularly beneficial to physically inactive adults as it can be easily integrated into daily routines, offering a practical solution for those with limited time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study honed in on cardiometabolic health, but if you opt for resistance training exercises like squats and press-ups, you are likely to see an increase in strength and muscle. A short yoga flow or Pilates move may deliver stability and mobility perks, while aerobic activities like stair-climbing can set your cardiorespiratory fitness on an upward trajectory. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At 59, Olympic gold medal-winning hurdler &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/sallygunnell/?hl=en"&gt;Sally Gunnell&lt;/a&gt; uses exercise snacks both personally and with her fitness coaching clients as a way to “&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/sally-gunnell-mobility-daily-trick-b2827375.html"&gt;stay active when life is full-on&lt;/a&gt;”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Being consistent, even in small ways, is often more effective than sporadic intense sessions,” she says. “These small daily movements help keep muscles strong and joints moving freely. They improve posture and balance, boost circulation, improve your mood and build the confidence to move more.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another devotee of exercise snacking is &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/fat-loss-advice-ben-carpenter-personal-trainer-b2751663.html"&gt;Ben Carpenter&lt;/a&gt;, personal trainer and author of the best-selling book &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="http://buy.geni.us/Proxy.ashx?tsid=3658&amp;amp;platform=independentcouk_web&amp;amp;GR_URL=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.amazon.co.uk%2FEverything-Fat-Loss-Definitive-Bullsh%2Fdp%2FB0BT733QD8%3Fascsubtag%3DIN%7C2859776%7CB0BT733QD8%7Cindependentcouk_web"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Everything Fat Loss&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You can improve your health with very small bursts of exercise,” he says. “Exercise snacking is also very good for behaviour change – building a habit. You enjoy exercise more because you do it in small enough doses that you can complete it, rather than doing an hour-long workout and thinking, ‘That was hard, I won’t be doing that again’.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/pilates-roll-down-for-posture-b2848707.html"&gt;The two-minute daily Pilates exercise that’s ‘great for posture, alignment and mobility’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 iDKkCP"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2018/05/15/11/desk-yoga.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2018/05/15/11/desk-yoga.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2018/05/15/11/desk-yoga.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Even small bouts of movement, slipped into your daily routine, can be beneficial for your health" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-328920"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Even small bouts of movement, slipped into your daily routine, can be beneficial for your health&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to create a successful exercise snack&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with any form of exercise, to be successful, exercise snacking workouts must be performed consistently. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One effective approach is to turn your chosen exercise snacks into a habit by stacking them on top of existing daily behaviours so you do them almost automatically. By removing the need to choose a time, place and type of exercise, and instead cueing it with another regular behaviour, you sidestep a phenomenon commonly referred to as “decision fatigue” and reduce the chances that you’ll skip the activity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his best-selling book &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://jamesclear.com/atomic-habits"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Atomic Habits&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the author and habit specialist James Clear says there are four pillars to successfully creating a habit; make it obvious, make it attractive, make it easy, make it satisfying. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are working from home, this could mean unrolling a yoga mat next to your desk at the start of the work day, then developing a consistent trigger for performing an equipment-free exercise. For example, you might do 10 press-ups every time you open your laptop or switch on your computer – the cue is obvious, and the exercise is easy to get into. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alternative examples could be doing squats in the kitchen while the kettle boils, or doing high knees on the spot for 60 seconds after you brush your teeth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Placing a calendar next to your chosen exercise spot and ticking off each completed workout could add a sense of satisfaction, and rewarding yourself at the end of a successful week with something you enjoy, such as a trip to the cinema, makes the act more attractive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To encourage adherence, Clear also recommends keeping new habits to no more than two minutes at first. These can be built up over time, but it is important to start small and lay firm fitness foundations before graduating to longer bouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/strength-training-plan-beginners-calisthenics-b2801421.html"&gt;Everyone is talking about calisthenics – here’s a four-week strength training plan (no fourgym membership required)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 jrNHph"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/07/23/7/07/Calisthenics-is-a-training-method-that-uses-bodyweight-exercises-to-build-strength-boost-fitness-and.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/07/23/7/07/Calisthenics-is-a-training-method-that-uses-bodyweight-exercises-to-build-strength-boost-fitness-and.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/07/23/7/07/Calisthenics-is-a-training-method-that-uses-bodyweight-exercises-to-build-strength-boost-fitness-and.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="If you work from home, unrolling a yoga mat next to your desk at the start of each day can make it easier to stick to exercise snacking habits" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-328921"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;If you work from home, unrolling a yoga mat next to your desk at the start of each day can make it easier to stick to exercise snacking habits&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Two-minute workouts to boost heart health, strength and mobility&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each of these exercise snacking workouts has been linked to a “trigger” of a daily action you are guaranteed to do. When you do the trigger action, assign an exercise snack to immediately follow it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also change the triggers or workouts.. The key to the success of this operation is finding a few short activities you can commit to doing multiple times each day, then making them second nature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise snack one&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger: &lt;/strong&gt;Getting out of bed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workout: &lt;/strong&gt;Three Pilates roll downs (demonstrated in the video below)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits: &lt;/strong&gt;For most people, sleeping involves six-plus hours of minimal movement, so some extra motion can be helpful for getting the body going in the morning. The Pilates roll down is a “great reset for the spine”, says &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.eastofeden.uk/"&gt;East of Eden&lt;/a&gt; fitness studio founder Abby McLachlan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It uses the abdominals to control the movement and it can help with back and neck tension,” she continues. “It’s a great exercise for posture and alignment too, which is why it’s often used in classes to start or finish the exercises.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1wypyku-0 sc-wn0aau-0 lnUWhb kfwxdp"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise snack two&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger: &lt;/strong&gt;Switching the kettle on&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workout: &lt;/strong&gt;Squats (or sit-to-stands to a chair) until it boils&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits: &lt;/strong&gt;This is one of Gunnell’s favourite cues. Squats, or sit-to-stands, recruit leg muscles including major players in your thighs such as the quadriceps. The squat is also a fundamental human movement pattern, so practising it regularly can help develop the strength and mobility needed to perform the movement with ease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise snack three&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger: &lt;/strong&gt;When you open your laptop or turn on your computer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workout: &lt;/strong&gt;Two-minute AMRAP (as many rounds as possible) of the circuit below:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-kk992l-0 sc-1k7glnk-1 dDVXDN irZnNR"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Press-up (you can place your hands against a desk or wall to make it easier) x3 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dead bug x6 (three repetitions each side)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Glute bridge x9 &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits: &lt;/strong&gt;This quick circuit recruits muscles in your core, chest, shoulders, arms and posterior chain – the muscles running along the back of your body. As well as strengthening these areas, the faster pace of the circuit format can also raise your heart rate, leading to bonus cardio perks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1wypyku-0 sc-wn0aau-0 lnUWhb kfwxdp"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise snack four&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger: &lt;/strong&gt;When you close your laptop or turn off your computer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workout: &lt;/strong&gt;Go on a fast-paced five-minute walk outside &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits: &lt;/strong&gt;A brisk pace ensures this walk falls under the “moderate-intensity activity” banner. “All of the research in this area suggests that most of the benefits [of walking] accumulate at a moderate or higher intensity,” says Dr Elroy Aguiar, an associate professor at the University of Alabama who specialises in walking and its impacts on health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benefits may include improvements to cardiovascular risk factors such as high blood sugar, high blood pressure and waist circumference. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise snack five&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger: &lt;/strong&gt;Picking up the TV remote &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workout: &lt;/strong&gt;Complete superman pull-ups for 30 seconds. Do this twice, with 60 seconds of rest between sets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits: &lt;/strong&gt;The muscles of the back can be strengthened with exercises like pull-ups and rows. However, they are much harder to hit without any equipment. The Superman pull-up is one of the few no-kit exercises to manage this, albeit to a lesser extent. It will also engage the glutes and the spine-stabilising erector spinae muscles in the core. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-31azim-0 eBMXOi nextSwipeIgnore sentry-block"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU sc-wlmftc-0 ccDPKb"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-hKDTPf hmBpZX"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/SypQbLAZeYA"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise snack six&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger: &lt;/strong&gt;When an advert comes on while watching TV&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workout: &lt;/strong&gt;Pick two of &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/best-stretches-flexibility-daily-routine-b2737236.html"&gt;flexibility expert Tom Merrick’s five favourite daily stretches&lt;/a&gt; – the 90/90, couch stretch, squat, hang and elephant walk – and hold each one for 30-60 seconds. You can find each move demonstrated in the video below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits: &lt;/strong&gt;Most of us spend a lot of our time sitting down. Staying in one position for prolonged periods can lead to stiffness and soreness. Regularly accessing a range of positions can improve flexibility and mobility while countering the tightness experienced as a by-product of excessive sitting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For most people, the biggest benefit they’re going to get from [stretching to develop] flexibility is that feeling of losing restriction and gaining freedom to be able to move, even if that’s just bending over to pick something up or play with their kids,” Merrick says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise snack seven&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Trigger: &lt;/strong&gt;After brushing your teeth&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workout: &lt;/strong&gt;Walk or run up and down the stairs for one to two minutes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-us-premium-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits: &lt;/strong&gt;One of the best ways to improve heart health and lung function is aerobic exercise – cyclical activities that raise the heart rate. That’s exactly what’s happening here, with the addition of an incline (the stairs) to increase the intensity of the activity. It might only be for a short spell, but, particularly for people who currently move very little, this small burst is likely to be enough to trigger positive fitness adaptations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/best-healthy-habits-every-day-b2837119.html"&gt;Do these five things daily for 90 days to see a ‘profound difference’ in your health, fitness and energy levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxPeWZfMy1lQkVEaWx6aWNtcjF6ZW1pNVpMRk40Qi1kckZycFB6d1FGMWtEc0NWakpyVlZ2LVRmTDY0VzdBME5aVzZIeHVXRW9WNmYyNk1tZEJCTll6Z3Vxd2FNZzFOa290cWJCWV9tMi1QcGE5SlU1MG1xcnNkaXdDNmdUdEo4R3BkQUJCNjBSOW9fdkgxY1VFSDFHVVd1QkNCR3k3NA</guid></item><item><title>五例麻疹病例可追溯到犹他州的一所高中--《盐湖论坛报》</title><link>https://www.sltrib.com/news/2025/11/22/5-measles-cases-traced-wasatch/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-head"&gt;&lt;h1 class="headline"&gt;Five measles cases traced to one Utah high school&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-subheadline"&gt;Wasatch County sees its first measles cases, and health boss says more may pop up.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="image-rootLeft"&gt;&lt;p class="css-1ez1ofp"&gt;&lt;span class=" lazy-load-image-background "&gt;&lt;span class="image-img"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="caption-credit"&gt;(Grace Doerfler | KPCW) Five measles cases have been traced to Wasatch High School students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="f0fvPICkDdVr4HR" data-fusion-collection="features" data-fusion-type="article-byline/default" data-fusion-name="Article Byline v2 New" data-fusion-message="Could not render component [features:article-byline/default]"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="f0fSQqI7MjYN5RL" data-fusion-collection="features" data-fusion-type="article-group-buttons/default" data-fusion-name="Article Group Icons" data-fusion-message="Could not render component [features:article-group-buttons/default]"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-container" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Heber City&lt;/b&gt; • Officials confirmed five measles cases in Wasatch County from Wasatch High School students Saturday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Two more cases are still being evaluated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;Officials also confirmed that one or more of these students attended school or school activities while infectious during school hours on Nov. 14, 17 and 18 and a school play Nov. 15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;“We did have a wastewater test indicate the presence of measles in the community on Nov. 6, and with cases existing in other parts of the state, we weren’t surprised to see cases here,” said health department director &lt;a href="https://www.wasatchcountyhd.org/About-Us" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Jonelle Fitzgerald&lt;/a&gt;. “The cases we have confirmed at the high school are not connected to each other, and because of that, we suspect that other cases may start to pop up in the community.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;These are the first confirmed cases of measles in Wasatch County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-raw"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Note to readers&lt;/b&gt; • &lt;i&gt;Read the full story at&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fox13now.com/news/local-news/southern-utah/passersby-find-man-dead-on-boat-at-lake-powell" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fox13now.com/news/local-news/northern-utah/officials-confirm-5-cases-of-measles-all-wasatch-high-school-students" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;FOX 13&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;. The Salt Lake Tribune and FOX 13 are content-sharing partners.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Salt Lake Tribune</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 02:28:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE56dzVMbmNtMjdtcWpFRWppajZaYlB0TndES1JlcDNaQl9uaU1qdFhqcXQtU05mcVFLVjJ5anlwUGdPVEtwbFFEYmlnMzNhSmpRYldaUXJ3YU1iRGlaZ2dwN2c2U2Fxdzl6cXBzazJxZjdPMGpqNkwwczVn</guid></item><item><title>威斯康星大学的研究：研究人员强调了与慢性大麻使用相关的新诊断- KIRO 7 News西雅图</title><link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/uw-study-researchers-highlight-new-diagnosis-tied-chronic-cannabis-use/LUPADHUMVVHYHIIC4GBTERQ7SI/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;SEATTLE  — &lt;a href="https://newsroom.uw.edu/blog/disabling-cannabis-condition-gets-formal-clinical-identity" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://newsroom.uw.edu/blog/disabling-cannabis-condition-gets-formal-clinical-identity"&gt;The University of Washington says&lt;/a&gt; that a condition that has been connected to chronic cannabis use has been recognized as a formal diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;Cannabis hyperemesis syndrome is a condition tied to long-term cannabis use that can cause severe stomach pain, vomiting, and nausea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;On October 1, the World Health Organization added an official diagnosis code for the syndrome to its medical manual. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;That update now gives doctors a clear way to diagnose the condition — something especially helpful for addiction researchers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;It also lets providers spot the condition more easily by reviewing a patient’s medical history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;“It helps us count and monitor these cases,” said Beatriz Carlini, a research associate professor at the University of Washington School of Medicine who studies the health effects of cannabis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;Because the syndrome is still relatively new, many doctors aren’t familiar with it, and they’re not entirely sure why it affects some cannabis users and not others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;For treatment, doctors have found that home remedies like hot showers help with symptoms when other treatments don’t work. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;Medications like Haldol, and even over-the-counter options such as capsaicin cream, can help ease symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KIRO 7 News Seattle</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 01:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiywFBVV95cUxNR3U1RjZCeFREaWVrTGVuLUpBd2JkMFBpSGUydW5HY0Y3THhtZFNnbHdkY0xZUWY0WjBNalN4dzNWa3lYdnZvanNMX1NVaXFVcW1jVFlQQmdvX0xrZjcyZzBveEsySHpQT1pRdGVQN21weE5pVVRkUjE1V3BnN21BbU5mUVN5N3RNN05YNldKclpIVkNOQVlfcXVoeXNqNWQzR2dJblRiV0NfVUdtMnJFWEpDQVp4ekhsMmItWVQwMnZoN1lOX01JY1Iwb9IB3wFBVV95cUxQWE1weTlxNTVHZjlORXNaTWZfcW92bDR1ZVVRWmtKQVNvbzJZNS1sYVJYeXdmZ3E4ZnprdGpncHVNelFyakgzTXEtcXFBVUFFUFRkRHY3QXQxMU9nN2lFdHROZ0pOUkdQSHFBLV94QXBrOVRwZkZNMDdWNDk3N3NEclFNc3ZTemlHUFRMQW11NVR2ODRLLWNhQzBPbDA0ZVhBWG1wLWIwU2JyS3E4ZXJVSGZfVm5NOTIzcVRDbVdxSVZpZGtJQUlSQ3Vjb3pKTWwzVXVmQzFrNVpBZlRLNkNN</guid></item><item><title>官员确认5例麻疹病例，所有Wasatch高中学生- FOX 13 News Utah</title><link>https://www.fox13now.com/news/local-news/northern-utah/officials-confirm-5-cases-of-measles-all-wasatch-high-school-students</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;HEBER, Utah — Officials have confirmed 5 cases of Measles in Wasatch County from Wasatch High School students Saturday. Two more cases are still being evaluated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials have also confirmed that one or more of these students did attend school or school activities while infectious during school hours on November 14, 17 and 18 and a school play on Saturday on November 15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We did have a wastewater test indicate the presence of measles in the community on November 6, and with cases existing in other parts of the state, we weren’t surprised to see cases here," said health department director Jonelle Fitzgerald. “The cases we have confirmed at the high school are not connected to each other, and because of that, we suspect that other cases may start to pop up in the community."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the first confirmed cases of Measles in Wasatch County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials also state that immediate action is being taken to investigate the circumstances and to limit further spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles vaccine recommendations:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="rte2-style-ul"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Children&lt;/b&gt; should receive two doses of measles vaccine: one dose at 12 to 15 months of age and another at 4 to 6 years. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adults born before 1957&lt;/b&gt; generally do not need to be vaccinated because they are likely already immune to measles due to widespread infection and illness before the measles vaccine became available in 1963. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adults who were vaccinated before 1968&lt;/b&gt; should have a second dose because the vaccine used from 1963–1967 was less effective than the current vaccine, which became available in 1968. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Adults who were vaccinated in 1968 or later&lt;/b&gt; are considered fully protected whether they have one or two doses, though certain higher risk groups (college students, healthcare workers, international travelers) should have two doses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>FOX 13 News Utah</author><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 00:16:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPNm5kYWV5WVBfb1FUNVpZUUhQWnotVzFkVkhETzlZWG1yeDltSGhXMGR0d09IcVMyTVRzRjRFdnZqczJBekRwRHpuVjZ5N3hPcVZFZ1VWa2VNQlNSRVhFQWdxSmJBOUd5bExGWWh1end0SkZid0NHMW9nUjFNdER0X19GcDVlT1dZRElEdjdsdWNyVkxkZk4zaVVBWlJ6YUJlMWloMXozNzRaTEFYel92aGpkUnN6YUJxSlh5emhhbjRCUQ</guid></item><item><title>你六岁的孩子像青少年一样争吵吗？欢迎来到摆动牙齿的青春期-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/parenting/is-your-six-year-old-arguing-like-a-teen-welcome-to-wobbly-tooth-puberty/articleshow/125508937.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;At three, Jas Suri was a timid boy who used to get teary-eyed when he had to let go of his mom Mishika’s hand at the school gate. Even at the age of five, he just needed one instruction and he would clean his room, arrange his toys and get ready for classes. Mishika used to secretly thank God for giving her such an obedient son. These days, she prays for a little cooperation. “Something flipped when he turned six. He just stopped listening to me. Now if I ask him to study or eat or pick up his clothes, he says ‘later’ or flatly refuses,” says the Juhu mom. “I don’t know how to react. It’s like he is seven going on 17.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mishika isn’t the only mom who is struggling with her child’s sass. While parents are mentally prepared for sleepless nights with babies, toddler tantrums and teenage drama, most are caught unawares by the mini rebellions of middle childhood (six to 10 years). Scientists are now calling this phase ‘wobbly-tooth puberty’ (a literal translation of the German word Wackelzahnpubertät) as it is akin to the real pubertal phase. German magazine Wunderkind says this stage is marked by “aggressive behaviour, rebellious activism, and deep sadness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rahela Tayebbi, a parent coach and mom-to-two (boys aged six and 10), admits this phase is way tougher than the toddler years. “When the boys were little, I could lay certain boundaries. Now, they push back so much. It has become a battle to impose even basic rules,” she says. The Indore resident reveals that these days when she announces that TV time is up and hides the remote above the cupboard, the boys climb a stool and retrieve it. “My younger one also rejects food made at home and insists I order pizza. When I tell him we order only on weekends, he argues that his friends get pizza whenever they want. There is drama almost daily now,” she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The forgotten years&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While infancy and adolescence are now well-understood, middle childhood has been long neglected and psychologists call it the ‘forgotten years’. But new research is taking place and experts have found that while adolescent rebellion is driven by hormonal changes, ‘wobbly-tooth puberty’ is caused by drastic changes in the brain as it lays the foundation for more mature thoughts and feelings. During this phase, their identity is forming (“Who am I compared to others?”) and their logical reasoning and cause-and-effect thinking develop. That’s why this stage is referred to as l’âge de raison (the age of reason) in France, notes David Robinson in an article for the BBC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For parents, this means dealing with more attitude, mood swings and sudden outbursts. Mumbai mom Parul Gupta is finding the rudeness too much to handle. Her six-year-old daughter Niya snaps at her often and says, “Aap jao, mujhe aapse baat nahi karni (Go away…I don’t want to talk to you).” The homemaker adds, “I can understand my 12-year-old son saying such lines because he is going through puberty and his hormones are all over the place, but it breaks my heart when my baby talks like that.” Gupta says Niya has started comparing herself to her elder brother a lot. So, if he is watching TV and she asks Niya to brush, change and sleep, she puts up a big fight (“Why should I go to bed now?”)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Little people, big feelings&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers have found that from the age of four, children gradually develop a ‘theory of mind’ which basically means they are able to understand that other people have feelings and perspectives that may be different from their own. This is also linked to development of a conscience as it allows them to reason about moral dilemmas and experience guilt. Neena Bhatt (name changed) realised this recently when her seven-year-old spilled a secret that had been troubling her. Renee admitted that when the teacher asked what they had done over the weekend, she spoke about a thrilling family treasure hunt. Turns out, Riya had heard about this treasure hunt in an audio story and decided to tell her teacher that she and her sister had played this with their parents instead of saying they just spent the weekend watching TV and reading books. “Riya also admitted that one day when a child told the teacher about a death in the family, she too said that her grandfather had passed away recently to gain their sympathy. Her grandpa had actually passed away years before her birth so, she has never really felt bad about the loss,” says Bhatt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The graphic designer realised her daughter was simply adding masala to her stories or telling white lies to gain attention. “While exaggerating is not exactly a wrong thing or hurting anyone, I was confused about how to react. If I dismiss it as ‘no big deal’, she may lie about bigger things tomorrow,” says Bhatt, adding that she told Renee to stick to the facts then. “I realised that she had developed a conscience and that it was now pricking her about lying which is a good thing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Connect, correct and control&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parenting experts believe that one of the reasons kids struggle in middle childhood is because parents start thinking they are all grown up and don’t need as much attention as they did when they were babies. “Parents tend to give up a little when the kid crosses six years. The child starts looking bigger and we think that they have grown up, now I can do whatever I want to do. It's a very normal feeling,” says parenting researcher Harpreet Grover. He points out that parents need to remember that while kids aged six and above are big enough to understand the world around them, they are not big enough to make their own choices. “It is like the milk teeth have fallen, but the new teeth will take a lot of time to come, so the kids need us as much as before,” says Grover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He adds that the “agenda of the world” calls out to the child a lot as they transition from babies to pre-teens and they are lured by everything around them, so the parents need to be super vigilant. “This is the age when kids want to use the mobile phone and play video games. It is the parent’s role to not allow mobile as a companion and stop the kids from playing video games like Roblox which have so much sexual violence,” says Grover, who goes by the name ‘The Curious Parent’ online. He says the onus is on parents to keep the child healthy physically by letting them play and ensuring right nutrition, and mentally by ensuring they're involved with life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tayebbi advises parents to not take the child’s attitude personally. “I remember when we attended the school book fair and my son wanted to buy a book, I said ‘no’ because the book was available for a lesser price on Amazon. He got very angry and said: ‘Aapko to har cheez mein problem hai (You have a problem with everything)’,” she recalls. “Over time, I realised that I should not feel bad because he is just growing up and becoming more expressive. We just need to be prepared to give more logic to convince our kids now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6wFBVV95cUxOOUFtM255VC1iR2JOeG9IWE1UaHFfVjRueDNqY2VKODF3RFZUMEtZMDJqYjFjVzAwVG9TNFB6OXVrQkRXZjdLTGxDYWdyXzFLbUhnaG5ZTEphU3c5WVVIZmRUNnZPWWp1Wl9NU1JEcThCWEp1N2tTSmRNRDdWRk8wVE9lcHBHZHBDbnQtMGZ6aS1BVU44V25TaFFHMG0yWURKUDUwWmZ2ai1YWlFTZE9WSmp3UXA5amRfUXFyY0dtR2h3aXFMNWJ5ODBrVGNQMTJmTE9CbXl6TTVrcUlUWVg2NGJFX2hZZjJMYlNj0gHwAUFVX3lxTFA3dlJVZXBRLS13amFWdElIVWJjUTRnbHlvWnZMT2lsaHJkUm92NU1uSEJLek1uMldEemFpcUpFRDkxN1BWQVY0Q0ctaFlIMlNwaEtHRmwyWi1KRDZ1Y21ReFY4UUZILXNsNGxlNV9IclIxYkJaRjRLVUJVWGI5OUtOTGt1M0FFd2VDOVZYRGh1ZVpndFlRcTV6S2U3SjNibk1JMVpsdnFlQ3F3cTZGQTItMFVybFViVUJPMXpYVjliN3BPNFBpdEw1ZTNwdEpXcW1ad0J0cDlKWFZKeHRVbkkybU1QRDRfZl9oM2tnNFFDSQ</guid></item><item><title>“我从未感到这种不尊重” ：女人花2天时间烹饪感恩节大餐，却被姻亲毁了- boredpanda.com</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;  &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;One of the wildest parts of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/men-share-marriage-regrets/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;marriage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is stepping into a whole new family: learning their quirks, swapping stories, and trying to fit right in. You share your favorite things, try to understand theirs, and hope it all blends together like a good recipe. But sometimes, instead of warm hugs, you get &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/woman-overhears-husbands-family-ends-marriage/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener "&gt;&lt;span&gt;cold criticism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That’s exactly what &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/relationship_advice/comments/9zqnd4/i_27f_hosted_thanksgiving_yesterday_and_my_inlaws/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;happened&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to one woman who poured her heart into hosting Thanksgiving for her in-laws. She spent two full days cooking a feast with her own modern twist… only for them to tear it apart and call her a “bad wife.” Keep reading to see how a holiday meant for gratitude turned into a recipe for family drama.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Many families love sticking to traditional meals during the holidays, it’s comforting, and familiar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Family sharing Thanksgiving dinner with roast turkey and side dishes, highlighting in-laws making fun of woman during holiday meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="1-80" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?image_id=1-80.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“I\'ve Never Felt This Disrespected”: Woman Spends 2 Days Cooking Thanksgiving Meal, Gets Destroyed By In-Laws" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?media_id=1-80" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/1-80.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9674298" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/1-80.jpg" alt="Family sharing Thanksgiving dinner with roast turkey and side dishes, highlighting in-laws making fun of woman during holiday meal." title="Family sharing Thanksgiving dinner with roast turkey and side dishes, highlighting in-laws making fun of woman during holiday meal." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/a-table-full-of-food-and-people-holding-utensils-UBA0j5K0QnM" class=" staff-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;Andy Quezada / unsplash (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One woman revealed how her nontraditional take on Thanksgiving dinner was harshly criticized by her in-laws&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woman hosting Thanksgiving dinner faces criticism from in-laws who say she ruined the holiday and made fun of her efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_9ece5f51774a27ec78c4fa5306dbbe64" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?image_id=author_9ece5f51774a27ec78c4fa5306dbbe64.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_9ece5f51774a27ec78c4fa5306dbbe64.jpg" alt="Woman hosting Thanksgiving dinner faces criticism from in-laws who say she ruined the holiday and made fun of her efforts." title="Woman hosting Thanksgiving dinner faces criticism from in-laws who say she ruined the holiday and made fun of her efforts." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alt text: Woman’s Thanksgiving dinner with experimental dishes criticized by in-laws for changing traditional holiday meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_50510fa9c5d7bd849bf6b33fefad5709" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?image_id=author_50510fa9c5d7bd849bf6b33fefad5709.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_50510fa9c5d7bd849bf6b33fefad5709.jpg" alt="Alt text: Woman’s Thanksgiving dinner with experimental dishes criticized by in-laws for changing traditional holiday meal." title="Alt text: Woman’s Thanksgiving dinner with experimental dishes criticized by in-laws for changing traditional holiday meal." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt about Thanksgiving dinner food choices, highlighting in-laws making fun of a woman's meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_1c1a60975d57ec76ba0385022ac935b4" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?image_id=author_1c1a60975d57ec76ba0385022ac935b4.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_1c1a60975d57ec76ba0385022ac935b4.jpg" alt="Text excerpt about Thanksgiving dinner food choices, highlighting in-laws making fun of a woman's meal." title="Text excerpt about Thanksgiving dinner food choices, highlighting in-laws making fun of a woman's meal." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woman upset as in-laws make fun of her effort at Thanksgiving dinner, accusing her of ruining the holiday celebration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_0de27bbd366373ae49fbe9b460b61431" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?image_id=author_0de27bbd366373ae49fbe9b460b61431.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_0de27bbd366373ae49fbe9b460b61431.jpg" alt="Woman upset as in-laws make fun of her effort at Thanksgiving dinner, accusing her of ruining the holiday celebration." title="Woman upset as in-laws make fun of her effort at Thanksgiving dinner, accusing her of ruining the holiday celebration." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alt text: Woman facing criticism from in-laws about Thanksgiving dinner, feeling disrespected and hurt during the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_d3766eeffca7afd997797f2d87ca3ecf" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?image_id=author_d3766eeffca7afd997797f2d87ca3ecf.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_d3766eeffca7afd997797f2d87ca3ecf.jpg" alt="Alt text: Woman facing criticism from in-laws about Thanksgiving dinner, feeling disrespected and hurt during the holiday." title="Alt text: Woman facing criticism from in-laws about Thanksgiving dinner, feeling disrespected and hurt during the holiday." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older woman sitting alone at Thanksgiving dinner table looking sad while in-laws make fun of her holiday meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="3-26" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?image_id=3-26.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="“I\'ve Never Felt This Disrespected”: Woman Spends 2 Days Cooking Thanksgiving Meal, Gets Destroyed By In-Laws" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?media_id=3-26" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/3-26.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9674336" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/3-26.jpg" alt="Older woman sitting alone at Thanksgiving dinner table looking sad while in-laws make fun of her holiday meal." title="Older woman sitting alone at Thanksgiving dinner table looking sad while in-laws make fun of her holiday meal." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://elements.envato.com/senior-woman-feeling-sad-while-sitting-alone-at-di-LP2NKTL" class=" staff-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;croquem__bouche / envato (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text showing a woman’s in-laws making fun of her for not making traditional dishes, saying she ruined Thanksgiving dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_2357e43fe53d3dc11e8c7794c257eecb" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?image_id=author_2357e43fe53d3dc11e8c7794c257eecb.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_2357e43fe53d3dc11e8c7794c257eecb.jpg" alt="Text showing a woman’s in-laws making fun of her for not making traditional dishes, saying she ruined Thanksgiving dinner." title="Text showing a woman’s in-laws making fun of her for not making traditional dishes, saying she ruined Thanksgiving dinner." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woman upset after in-laws make fun of her Thanksgiving dinner, feeling hurt and unsure how to fix family tensions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_01df459e6186a4a23c7bd729670bf5c8" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/in-laws-berate-host-nontraditional-thanksgiving/?image_id=author_01df459e6186a4a23c7bd729670bf5c8.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_01df459e6186a4a23c7bd729670bf5c8.jpg" alt="Woman upset after in-laws make fun of her Thanksgiving dinner, feeling hurt and unsure how to fix family tensions." title="Woman upset after in-laws make fun of her Thanksgiving dinner, feeling hurt and unsure how to fix family tensions." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/relationship_advice/comments/9zqnd4/i_27f_hosted_thanksgiving_yesterday_and_my_inlaws/" class=" staff-link" rel="nofollow"&gt;croquem__bouche&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;She explained that she isn’t a particularly religious person and shared even more details about how the entire dinner unfolded&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alt text: Online comments about in-laws making fun of woman for Thanksgiving dinner and family conflict over holiday issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit comments discussing in-laws making fun of woman for Thanksgiving dinner and holiday conflict resolution advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In-laws make fun of woman for Thanksgiving dinner, causing family tension and stress during the holiday celebration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit comments discussing in-laws making fun of a woman for her Thanksgiving dinner and holiday tensions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of an online discussion about in-laws making fun of a woman for Thanksgiving dinner and holiday conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit comments discussing in-laws making fun of woman and ruining Thanksgiving dinner, impacting family relationships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversation text about in-laws making fun of woman over Thanksgiving dinner and holiday tensions with family members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a heated online discussion where in-laws criticize a woman’s Thanksgiving dinner, sparking debate about the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advice on handling in-laws making fun of woman for Thanksgiving dinner and ruining the holiday atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit comments discussing in-laws making fun of a woman for Thanksgiving dinner traditions and holiday hosting conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of online comments discussing in-laws making fun of a woman during Thanksgiving dinner and family conflicts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comments on a post about in-laws making fun of a woman’s Thanksgiving dinner, discussing effort and family traditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenters discuss in-laws making fun of woman for Thanksgiving dinner and setting boundaries to handle holiday criticism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;User comments discussing in-laws making fun of woman for Thanksgiving dinner and the food she prepared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alt text: Online discussion about in-laws making fun of woman at Thanksgiving dinner, causing family tension and holiday conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alt text: In-laws make fun of woman hosting Thanksgiving dinner and say she ruined the holiday amid family tensions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 data-start="51" data-end="151"&gt;The Indian dessert market is enormous, with people deeply attached to their traditional favorites&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When someone says Turkey, most people picture Thanksgiving feasts and tables overflowing with comfort food, the same way hearing Christmas instantly brings to mind gingerbread, plum cakes, and hot chocolate. Food has this magical ability to anchor us to traditions almost instantly. Across cultures, festive dishes become part of the celebration itself, so much so that the holiday feels incomplete without them. Every country has dishes that show up only once a year, making them even more special. It’s amazing how the world celebrates its festivals with a plate in hand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Desserts follow the same universal rule: no celebration feels whole without something sweet. In many regions, every festival is practically defined by its signature &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbctv18.com/market/commodities/india-mithai-sweets-industry-evolving-expanding-experts-19477014.htm" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;dessert&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. India is a perfect example, where each celebration has its own sweet tradition. During Holi, families prepare colorful treats that match the vibrancy of the festival. Diwali turns the entire country into a glowing marketplace of mithai boxes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Statista, the Confectionery &amp;amp; Snacks industry is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statista.com/outlook/cmo/food/confectionery-snacks/india?srsltid=AfmBOooXZG2kRwZBMDF78noxEBvMJqsZEsgpRysOMqzWAVHLBI_-12fE" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;enormous&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and still growing. Revenue in 2025 alone is projected to reach US$23.67 billion. The market is expected to grow annually by 6.31% between 2025 and 2030. By 2030, the total volume is predicted to reach 5.85 billion kilograms. Even 2026 is projected to show a volume growth of 3.8%. All these numbers show just how big and competitive this market really is. People love their snacks and sweets, and demand isn’t slowing down. The industry is evolving quickly, fueled by both tradition and innovation. With stats like these, it’s clear this is a massive space to enter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In such a huge and traditional market, introducing nontraditional desserts like cakes and brownies isn’t a simple task. People already have strong attachments to the sweets they grew up with. Winning their trust requires patience, creativity, and a lot of tasting. Today, we spoke with Akshita Agarwal from &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/caramella_by_akshita/?hl=en" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;span&gt;caramella_by_akshita&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a brand that has carved a space for itself in Kolkata. She specializes in premium artisanal tiramisus and modern desserts. Her journey shows how passion can blend beautifully with innovation. Competing in a mithai-driven landscape is bold, but she has managed to make her mark. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“People absolutely love gulab jamun and ladoos, those are always the first choices for gifting,” Akshita shared. “These classics have been around for so many years that they feel familiar and safe.” She explained how deeply emotional and nostalgic people are about these sweets. They remind them of festivals spent with family, childhood celebrations, and happy moments. For many, these flavors are part of their identity. Getting customers to explore something new was definitely a challenge. Traditional mithai has a charm that’s hard to shake. But rather than fighting this, she chose to understand it. Respecting those preferences became step one.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;It’s always exciting when the older generation is willing to try something new&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“In the beginning, convincing people to try different desserts was tricky,” she laughed. “So we started really small, offering free samples just to break the ice.” Gen Z instantly connected with the brand, but older generations needed more time. They already knew their favorite sweets and rarely stepped outside them. To bridge that gap, she started experimenting with fusion-style creations. Ras Malai Cake, Gulab Jamun Cake Jars and similar flavors soon appeared on the menu. These blends quickly caught people’s attention and became instant favorites. Customers found comfort in the familiar flavors and excitement in the new form. It was the perfect meeting point between tradition and novelty.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“We realized that dessert isn’t just about taste, it’s tied to emotions,” Akshita said. “People want to hold on to their traditions because they carry memories.” Instead of trying to replace classic mithai, her team decided to blend traditional flavors with modern textures. This approach gave customers something new without losing what they love. It honored their nostalgia while still feeling fresh. By respecting emotional connections, they created desserts that appeal across generations. Slowly, this fusion style started winning hearts everywhere. It proved that tradition and creativity can coexist beautifully.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“I believe it’s always best to conclude on a simple thought,” Akshita said with a smile. “Tradition doesn’t have to be replaced to make space for something new.” She emphasized that food evolves the same way people do: slowly, naturally, and with an open mind. Her brand’s journey taught her that blending old and new can create something truly memorable. It’s not about proving one dessert better than another; it’s about expanding the table. She feels that every sweet, whether classic or modern, has its own charm. What matters most is the joy it brings to the person eating it. And if a dessert can spark conversation or curiosity, that’s already a win. For her, that’s the perfect note to wrap things up on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In this particular scenario, it did feel like the woman’s nontraditional dishes were judged a bit too quickly. It’s understandable that people cling to familiar flavors, but such harsh criticism seems unfair. A little openness never hurts, especially when someone puts effort into cooking. Food has a funny way of changing minds when given a chance. Everyone has different tastes, but kindness should stay constant. And honestly, trying a new dish costs nothing, who knows, it might even become the next family favorite.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Readers were quick to call out her in-laws’ behavior, saying it was rude and uncalled for&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment criticizing in-laws who make fun of woman for Thanksgiving dinner and say she ruined the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment expressing support for a woman whose in-laws make fun of her Thanksgiving dinner and say she ruined the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a Reddit comment discussing in-laws making fun of a woman for Thanksgiving dinner, blaming her for ruining the holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment emphasizing self-respect and boundaries when dealing with difficult in-laws during Thanksgiving dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;User comment in black text on white background expressing difficulty understanding cruelty in in-laws making fun of woman during Thanksgiving dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of an online comment with strong language about in-laws making fun of a woman for Thanksgiving dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of an online comment praising a woman’s husband and her amazing food amid in-laws Thanksgiving conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a comment defending a woman against in-laws making fun of her Thanksgiving dinner, calling them closed off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenter supports husband addressing in-laws who made fun of woman and ruined Thanksgiving dinner holiday experience.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div id="postPoll-9674236" class="post-poll poll-wrapper single-post" data-poll-viewed="false" data-post-id="9674236" data-main-post-id="" data-poll-id="19308"&gt; &lt;input class="post-9674236-poll-value" type="hidden" value="eyJwb2xsSWQiOjE5MzA4LCJwb3N0SWQiOjk2NzQyMzYsImhpZGVDb21tZW50cyI6ZmFsc2UsInF1ZXN0aW9ucyI6W3siaWQiOjE5MzA4LCJwb2xsSWQiOjE5MzA4LCJ0ZXh0IjoiSG93IGRvIHlvdSBmZWVsIGFib3V0IHRoZSB3aWZlJ3MgZGVjaXNpb24gdG8gYWRkIGEgbW9kZXJuIHR3aXN0IHRvIHRoZSB0cmFkaXRpb25hbCBUaGFua3NnaXZpbmcgbWVudT8iLCJvcmRlciI6bnVsbCwiYW5zd2VycyI6W3siaWQiOjcyOTk3LCJxdWVzdGlvbklkIjoxOTMwOCwidGV4dCI6Ikl0IHdhcyBhIGdyZWF0IHdheSB0byBzaGFyZSBoZXIgc3R5bGUiLCJ2b3RlcyI6NjZ9LHsiaWQiOjcyOTk4LCJxdWVzdGlvbklkIjoxOTMwOCwidGV4dCI6IlNoZSBzaG91bGQgaGF2ZSBzdHVjayB0byB0cmFkaXRpb24iLCJ2b3RlcyI6Nn0seyJpZCI6NzI5OTksInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE5MzA4LCJ0ZXh0IjoiVHJ5aW5nIGJvdGggdHJhZGl0aW9uYWwgYW5kIG1vZGVybiB3YXMgc21hcnQiLCJ2b3RlcyI6NjR9LHsiaWQiOjczMDAwLCJxdWVzdGlvbklkIjoxOTMwOCwidGV4dCI6IlNoZSBzaG91bGQgaGF2ZSBhc2tlZCB0aGUgaW4tbGF3cyBmaXJzdCIsInZvdGVzIjozfV19XSwicG9zdFRpdGxlIjpudWxsLCJwb3N0VXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6XC9cL3d3dy5ib3JlZHBhbmRhLmNvbVwvaW4tbGF3cy1iZXJhdGUtaG9zdC1ub250cmFkaXRpb25hbC10aGFua3NnaXZpbmdcLyJ9"&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: isInitialised()"&gt;    &lt;div data-bind="if: !isLoading() &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults"&gt; &lt;div class="poll-content"&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-title"&gt;Thanks! Check out the results:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-question" data-bind="text: currentQuestionText()"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;  &lt;p class="total-votes" data-bind="visible: totalVotes() &amp;gt; 10 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults &amp;amp;&amp;amp; totalVotesDisplayMode !== 0"&gt; &lt;span class="text"&gt;Total votes · &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-bind="text: totalVotesFormatted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block-wrapper"&gt; &lt;p class="badge"&gt;Newsletter&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block"&gt; &lt;p class="left"&gt; &lt;h3 class="title"&gt;Subscribe to Access &lt;br&gt; Exclusive Polls&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="disclaimer"&gt; &lt;p&gt;By entering your email and clicking Subscribe, you're agreeing to let us send you customized marketing messages about us and our advertising partners. You are also agreeing to our &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/privacy-policy/"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: newsletterSubscribed" class="thank-you"&gt; &lt;div class="wrapper"&gt;  &lt;p class="right"&gt;Thank you! You've successfully subscribed to newsletters!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>boredpanda.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 23:01:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNMmlEQmd6cUlOdl9RUmNfUnJkbVJndWV5TWRqVWI4cXlLb2MySkd0Q2VVY045VWk5a2wxMktFM2xDSEFSLURRRndZWWxnTWNmY1c4X2lOXzJDdFJQWDdLMk9mdmtHbTRhTzhZNkpFMlpjcGQ0ZDA0bC1PSnNjbVJLVw</guid></item><item><title>“整个事情都搞砸了” ：男人认为他的GF从110磅变成120磅是不可接受的- boredpanda.com</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Time goes on, and people change — both inside and out. Now that doctor and Reddit user &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/_this_isnt_fine_/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;_This_isnt_fine_&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; is approaching her thirties, she’s happy to be done with med school and would be excited about the future if it wasn’t for one thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the woman explained in a post on &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TrueOffMyChest/comments/1nt812q/bf_wants_the_old_me/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;r/TrueOffMyChest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, her long-term boyfriend is unhappy that she no longer looks like she did when they first started dating. Throughout the years, she’s gained a few pounds and that, apparently, is a huge problem for him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;This woman worked long and hard to finish med school&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woman in medical scrubs sitting on floor looking stressed, representing depressing weight and relationship issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-2" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Refuses To Accept GF’s Excuses For Why She Gained Weight, Wants Her To Go Back To 110 Pounds" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?media_id=boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-2" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9674959" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-2.jpg" alt="Woman in medical scrubs sitting on floor looking stressed, representing depressing weight and relationship issues." title="Woman in medical scrubs sitting on floor looking stressed, representing depressing weight and relationship issues." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/premium-photo/tired-feeling-bad-exhausted-female-doctor-white-coat-is-hall_151127186.htm#from_element=cross_selling__photo" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;standret (not the actual image)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-tablet-ad-within-content post-ads"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad" data-source="primis"&gt;&lt;span id="desktop-widget-loaded"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h3&gt;But her boyfriend is not happy that it made her gain weight&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt from a woman explaining her boyfriend wants her to look like she did six years ago at 110 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_ed7f16ea89e7fb6ed4a6ef2f0fb98dcc" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_ed7f16ea89e7fb6ed4a6ef2f0fb98dcc.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_ed7f16ea89e7fb6ed4a6ef2f0fb98dcc.jpg" alt="Text excerpt from a woman explaining her boyfriend wants her to look like she did six years ago at 110 pounds." title="Text excerpt from a woman explaining her boyfriend wants her to look like she did six years ago at 110 pounds." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text showing woman’s weight change from 110 to 120 pounds viewed as unacceptable by her boyfriend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_5d618368cdd4df213a100ffdcf03210c" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_5d618368cdd4df213a100ffdcf03210c.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_5d618368cdd4df213a100ffdcf03210c.jpg" alt="Text showing woman’s weight change from 110 to 120 pounds viewed as unacceptable by her boyfriend." title="Text showing woman’s weight change from 110 to 120 pounds viewed as unacceptable by her boyfriend." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text about size small clothing and pants from early dating era not fitting after long time, relating to weight and relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_6cc55fe5b551d804a2a50fa25d26f9ef" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_6cc55fe5b551d804a2a50fa25d26f9ef.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_6cc55fe5b551d804a2a50fa25d26f9ef.jpg" alt="Text about size small clothing and pants from early dating era not fitting after long time, relating to weight and relationship." title="Text about size small clothing and pants from early dating era not fitting after long time, relating to weight and relationship." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alt text: Woman rejects boyfriend's demand to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago, calling it stupid and depressing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_322999213a9ee2d5e682019076773529" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_322999213a9ee2d5e682019076773529.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_322999213a9ee2d5e682019076773529.jpg" alt="Alt text: Woman rejects boyfriend's demand to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago, calling it stupid and depressing." title="Alt text: Woman rejects boyfriend's demand to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago, calling it stupid and depressing." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt discussing stress and weight gain during a six-year relationship, medical school, and personal challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_51e676e935ae82ddf8990127f36bbbbe" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_51e676e935ae82ddf8990127f36bbbbe.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_51e676e935ae82ddf8990127f36bbbbe.jpg" alt="Text excerpt discussing stress and weight gain during a six-year relationship, medical school, and personal challenges." title="Text excerpt discussing stress and weight gain during a six-year relationship, medical school, and personal challenges." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt discussing a man with a PhD in physics explaining his unique academic and personal experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_d693c2b1d056fb0a536507e92b0fd645" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_d693c2b1d056fb0a536507e92b0fd645.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_d693c2b1d056fb0a536507e92b0fd645.jpg" alt="Text excerpt discussing a man with a PhD in physics explaining his unique academic and personal experiences." title="Text excerpt discussing a man with a PhD in physics explaining his unique academic and personal experiences." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content margin-left post-ads"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-aa-adunit="/46481815/bp.com_desktop_singleimage_bottom_728x90" id="adapex-div-gpt-ad-1491844427478-3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;White analog bathroom scale showing a weight near 110 pounds on a dark wooden floor background.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-3" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Refuses To Accept GF’s Excuses For Why She Gained Weight, Wants Her To Go Back To 110 Pounds" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?media_id=boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-3" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9674965" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-3.jpg" alt="White analog bathroom scale showing a weight near 110 pounds on a dark wooden floor background." title="White analog bathroom scale showing a weight near 110 pounds on a dark wooden floor background." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/a-bathroom-scale-sitting-on-top-of-a-wooden-table-TLEI9o1HdY4" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;Joachim Schnürle (not the actual image)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text about a man requiring his girlfriend to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago, causing emotional distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_4051370996e9b0be6960104ce6e51ae7" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_4051370996e9b0be6960104ce6e51ae7.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_4051370996e9b0be6960104ce6e51ae7.jpg" alt="Text about a man requiring his girlfriend to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago, causing emotional distress." title="Text about a man requiring his girlfriend to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago, causing emotional distress." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt discussing the difficulty of losing 10 pounds and questioning a partner's dissatisfaction with a small weight increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_c1c5c5ab2e1b90b20dcdcd71b57412f8" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_c1c5c5ab2e1b90b20dcdcd71b57412f8.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_c1c5c5ab2e1b90b20dcdcd71b57412f8.jpg" alt="Text excerpt discussing the difficulty of losing 10 pounds and questioning a partner's dissatisfaction with a small weight increase." title="Text excerpt discussing the difficulty of losing 10 pounds and questioning a partner's dissatisfaction with a small weight increase." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Man insists girlfriend return to 110 pounds she weighed 6 years ago, sparking debate on weight and relationships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_0706934dd1496f76b0508e02bf8e437d" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_0706934dd1496f76b0508e02bf8e437d.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_0706934dd1496f76b0508e02bf8e437d.jpg" alt="Man insists girlfriend return to 110 pounds she weighed 6 years ago, sparking debate on weight and relationships." title="Man insists girlfriend return to 110 pounds she weighed 6 years ago, sparking debate on weight and relationships." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Man and woman sitting apart on couch looking upset, reflecting conflict over girlfriend's weight and past pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-4" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-4.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Refuses To Accept GF’s Excuses For Why She Gained Weight, Wants Her To Go Back To 110 Pounds" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?media_id=boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-4" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-4.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9674983" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight-4.jpg" alt="Man and woman sitting apart on couch looking upset, reflecting conflict over girlfriend's weight and past pounds." title="Man and woman sitting apart on couch looking upset, reflecting conflict over girlfriend's weight and past pounds." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/image-quarrelled-lovely-couple-sitting-separately-couch-home_6511976.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;position=21&amp;amp;uuid=b3f017ee-e58c-41ee-9522-60c0337d8760&amp;amp;query=couple+argue" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;drobotdean (not the actual image)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt discussing stress in med and grad school and its relation to weight gain in a personal relationship context.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_c793e3f2d3fd18e6d72bfb4da5788edb" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_c793e3f2d3fd18e6d72bfb4da5788edb.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_c793e3f2d3fd18e6d72bfb4da5788edb.jpg" alt="Text excerpt discussing stress in med and grad school and its relation to weight gain in a personal relationship context." title="Text excerpt discussing stress in med and grad school and its relation to weight gain in a personal relationship context." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text on white background stating a disagreement about comparing med school and PhD academics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_dc5b1a92cf2f736ecad581c23ea76433" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_dc5b1a92cf2f736ecad581c23ea76433.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_dc5b1a92cf2f736ecad581c23ea76433.jpg" alt="Text on white background stating a disagreement about comparing med school and PhD academics." title="Text on white background stating a disagreement about comparing med school and PhD academics." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt about a man requiring girlfriend to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_34f9c84a78e1ee32ed18c818e30602c4" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_34f9c84a78e1ee32ed18c818e30602c4.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_34f9c84a78e1ee32ed18c818e30602c4.jpg" alt="Text excerpt about a man requiring girlfriend to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago." title="Text excerpt about a man requiring girlfriend to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text about a man criticizing his girlfriend’s weight and demanding she return to 110 pounds from six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_780a19cc7f6a1060af0e8f27434eaa27" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_780a19cc7f6a1060af0e8f27434eaa27.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_780a19cc7f6a1060af0e8f27434eaa27.jpg" alt="Text about a man criticizing his girlfriend’s weight and demanding she return to 110 pounds from six years ago." title="Text about a man criticizing his girlfriend’s weight and demanding she return to 110 pounds from six years ago." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text discussing a man described as physically perfect, focusing on character flaws and Reddit feedback.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_5f82b9bab112aa769f7dca10fafa5d43" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_5f82b9bab112aa769f7dca10fafa5d43.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_5f82b9bab112aa769f7dca10fafa5d43.jpg" alt="Text discussing a man described as physically perfect, focusing on character flaws and Reddit feedback." title="Text discussing a man described as physically perfect, focusing on character flaws and Reddit feedback." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt stating no other changes except 10 pounds and some white hairs, referencing weight and aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_cd2f5b62dffe78969044bc092f2b7e74" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/boyfriend-asks-girlfriend-lose-weight/?image_id=author_cd2f5b62dffe78969044bc092f2b7e74.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/author_cd2f5b62dffe78969044bc092f2b7e74.jpg" alt="Text excerpt stating no other changes except 10 pounds and some white hairs, referencing weight and aging." title="Text excerpt stating no other changes except 10 pounds and some white hairs, referencing weight and aging." loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits:&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TrueOffMyChest/comments/1nt812q/bf_wants_the_old_me/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt; _this_isnt_fine_&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Stress can, indeed, lead to weight gain&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we are stressed, our bodies create more of a hormone called cortisol,” &lt;a href="https://www.brownhealth.org/be-well/does-stress-cause-weight-gain" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt; Dr. Kristy Dalrymple, a licensed clinical psychologist, associate director of the outpatient psychiatry practice at Rhode Island Hospital, and director of adult psychology at Rhode Island and The Miriam hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to her, cortisol is partly responsible for how our body responds to danger, acts as an internal alarm clock for waking up and going to sleep, helps control blood pressure and glucose metabolism, and can reduce inflammation. Some medications use cortisol—known as hydrocortisone—to help reduce inflammation, either topically or systemically, such as over-the-counter creams for swelling and itching from bug bites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Too much or too little cortisol can contribute to certain health conditions, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;changes in weight (both gain and loss)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;skin conditions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;muscle weakness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;anxiety or depression&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;heart disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we feel stressed—as many of us have for the last few years—our bodies can tip toward releasing too much cortisol, leading to weight gain, acne, trouble sleeping, headaches, and digestive problems,” Dalrymple says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The production of cortisol can also trigger your body to release extra insulin, and together these two hormones can lead your body to storing extra fat around the abdomen. Additionally, for many people, eating comforting foods is one way we respond to stress. The problem is that those foods tend to be less nutritionally valuable for our bodies and contain more calories than our body can expend.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;However, changing or sticking to one’s lifestyle is their own personal choice&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lifestyle choices require motivation to come from within, and if the Redditor isn’t interested in making the effort, her boyfriend can’t force her to lose weight. If anyone, it’s her doctor, not him, who should discuss this topic with her. But judging from the post, there are no health issues—which makes her boyfriend look even worse. In fact, it’s entirely possible that the true reason for his dissatisfaction comes from a deeper place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s true that people value looks in their long-term partners. One &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2015/09/150916162912.htm" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; suggests that 92 percent of men and 84 percent of women say it’s “desirable/essential” that their potential partner be good-looking, and 80 percent of men as well as 58 percent of women want them to have a slender body. But since this particular couple is six years into a relationship, the situation is a little different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When people are asked to list the most important qualities in a potential partner, kindness, physical attractiveness, an exciting personality, and income/earning potential tend to top the list,” &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/close-encounters/201702/5-essential-qualities-for-a-romantic-partner" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Gwendolyn Seidman, Ph.D., Associate Professor of Psychology at Michigan State University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But once you’re actually involved in a relationship, some of these traits become more important than others.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Research … found that those whose partners meet their ideals in terms of warmth and loyalty are more satisfied with their relationships. Having a partner who meets one’s ideals in terms of physical attractiveness, excitement, status, and wealth, on the other hand, is much less correlated with overall satisfaction,” Seidman explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Research also found that having a partner who fell short on attractiveness, status, and excitement did not affect satisfaction if that partner was also highly warm, kind, and loyal. In other words, those more ‘superficial’ traits were not important at all for those whose partners were kind, understanding, and loyal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;People have had a lot to say about the guy and his mean comments&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a social media comment discussing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to her previous weight of 110 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment discussing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to a weight she had six years ago, seen as disturbing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment criticizing a man for requiring his girlfriend to return to her weight from six years ago seen on a social media post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment text on a social media post discussing weight loss and a man requiring his girlfriend to return to her previous weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of an online comment discussing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to a previous weight from six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commenter expressing strong opposition to a man requiring his girlfriend to return to her former weight six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a comment discussing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to the weight she was 6 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a Reddit comment discussing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to her previous weight of 110 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment criticizing man who requires girlfriend to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago, calling it depressing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment criticizing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to her previous weight, calling the demand stupid and depressing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment criticizing a man for requiring his girlfriend to return to her previous weight six years ago, calling him shallow and disgusting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment on Reddit thread questioning if a man demanding his girlfriend return to a past weight is acceptable or okay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit comment criticizing a man who requires his girlfriend to return to her weight of 110 pounds from six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment about metabolism and weight gain, criticizing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to 110 pounds from six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment discussing the emotional impact of requiring a girlfriend to return to a past weight after gaining 10 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a social media comment about a man requiring his girlfriend to return to her previous weight of 110 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment on a weight loss demand, urging to avoid toxic partners and focus on self-respect and health over past weights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit comment discussing emotional impact of man requiring girlfriend to return to previous weight from six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a comment discussing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to her weight from six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment about wife’s weight gain from 100 to 140 pounds, highlighting health and appreciation themes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment text criticizing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to a weight she had six years ago, discussing body changes and immaturity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment discussing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to her previous weight, focusing on weight and relationship pressures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment discussing unhealthy weight demands from a man requiring girlfriend to return to 110 pounds from six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment expressing frustration over a man requiring his girlfriend to return to her weight from six years ago causing upset and sadness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of an online comment discussing a man requiring his girlfriend to return to the weight she had six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment criticizing a man who requires his girlfriend to return to the weight she had six years ago, calling it stupid and depressing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a social media comment criticizing a man who requires his girlfriend to return to her weight from six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment discussing relationship weight and partner's expectations about returning to a previous weight six years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment about control and insecurity in a discussion on a man requiring girlfriend to return to former weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a Reddit comment discussing stress eating and criticizing a man for requiring his girlfriend to return to a past weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment text expressing anger at a man requiring his girlfriend to return to 110 pounds she weighed six years ago.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div id="postPoll-9674300" class="post-poll poll-wrapper single-post" data-poll-viewed="false" data-post-id="9674300" data-main-post-id="" data-poll-id="19333"&gt; &lt;input class="post-9674300-poll-value" type="hidden" value="eyJwb2xsSWQiOjE5MzMzLCJwb3N0SWQiOjk2NzQzMDAsImhpZGVDb21tZW50cyI6ZmFsc2UsInF1ZXN0aW9ucyI6W3siaWQiOjE5MzMzLCJwb2xsSWQiOjE5MzMzLCJ0ZXh0IjoiSG93IGRvIHlvdSBpbnRlcnByZXQgdGhlIGJveWZyaWVuZCdzIHJlYWN0aW9uIHRvIGEgMTAtcG91bmQgd2VpZ2h0IGdhaW4gYWZ0ZXIgNiB5ZWFycz8iLCJvcmRlciI6bnVsbCwiYW5zd2VycyI6W3siaWQiOjczMDk0LCJxdWVzdGlvbklkIjoxOTMzMywidGV4dCI6IlNob3dzIGltbWF0dXJpdHkgYW5kIHNoYWxsb3cgdGhpbmtpbmciLCJ2b3RlcyI6MTY3fSx7ImlkIjo3MzA5NSwicXVlc3Rpb25JZCI6MTkzMzMsInRleHQiOiJDb3VsZCBiZSBjb25jZXJuIGZvciBoZWFsdGggYnV0IHBvb3JseSBleHByZXNzZWQiLCJ2b3RlcyI6M30seyJpZCI6NzMwOTYsInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE5MzMzLCJ0ZXh0IjoiUG9zc2libHkgaW5zZWN1cml0eSBvciBjb250cm9sIGlzc3VlcyIsInZvdGVzIjo1OH0seyJpZCI6NzMwOTcsInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE5MzMzLCJ0ZXh0IjoiTWlnaHQgYmUgYSBtaXN1bmRlcnN0YW5kaW5nIiwidm90ZXMiOjJ9XX1dLCJwb3N0VGl0bGUiOm51bGwsInBvc3RVcmwiOiJodHRwczpcL1wvd3d3LmJvcmVkcGFuZGEuY29tXC9ib3lmcmllbmQtYXNrcy1naXJsZnJpZW5kLWxvc2Utd2VpZ2h0XC8ifQ=="&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: isInitialised()"&gt;    &lt;div data-bind="if: !isLoading() &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults"&gt; &lt;div class="poll-content"&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-title"&gt;Thanks! Check out the results:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-question" data-bind="text: currentQuestionText()"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;  &lt;p class="total-votes" data-bind="visible: totalVotes() &amp;gt; 10 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults &amp;amp;&amp;amp; totalVotesDisplayMode !== 0"&gt; &lt;span class="text"&gt;Total votes · &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-bind="text: totalVotesFormatted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block-wrapper"&gt; &lt;p class="badge"&gt;Newsletter&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block"&gt; &lt;p class="left"&gt; &lt;h3 class="title"&gt;Subscribe to Access &lt;br&gt; Exclusive Polls&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="disclaimer"&gt; &lt;p&gt;By entering your email and clicking Subscribe, you're agreeing to let us send you customized marketing messages about us and our advertising partners. You are also agreeing to our &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/privacy-policy/"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: newsletterSubscribed" class="thank-you"&gt; &lt;div class="wrapper"&gt;  &lt;p class="right"&gt;Thank you! You've successfully subscribed to newsletters!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>boredpanda.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 23:01:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE9uOHM5VElzMzNGcWdLbHNGeGNWSDVKWXJqQ1NKQXZtTzZZRU5BUDJwUHdIaVB6MkNIS2FEN3ZMWGo4N1NNcUJ5N25wVW5fZ0VHM1hidXQ0V0o1LTdRM2hDblAtTWJvT1lyYnZid24wQ0RVSDQ</guid></item><item><title>我儿子关于无法实现这种常见身体功能的评论似乎是无害的—直到我在谷歌上搜索它的含义- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/son-remark-not-being-able-135349637.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It all started at the dinner table one night when my 17-year-old son Gavin said, “You know what? I never burp.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Never?” I asked. He shook his head. “Nope. Never.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/lonely-not-married-happily-single-peace_n_6919e26de4b0b43a45c0cc95?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:I Was Eating Alone When A Man Came Up And Said 4 Words That Have Haunted Me Throughout My Life;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;I Was Eating Alone When A Man Came Up And Said 4 Words That Have Haunted Me Throughout My Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Of course you do,” I nearly replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Everyone burps... don’t they?&lt;/em&gt; I thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, I asked, “Well, does that bother you?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sort of,” he said, shrugging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Family: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/toddler-tantrums-speech-pathologist-advice_l_68111524e4b0188fc5dab6b0?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:3 Surprisingly Simple Tricks for Deescalating And Preventing Toddler Tantrums;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;3 Surprisingly Simple Tricks for Deescalating And Preventing Toddler Tantrums&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We returned to our dinner, but his comment remained in the back of my mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Is it even possible that a person just &lt;/em&gt;can’t &lt;em&gt;burp?&lt;/em&gt; I wondered. &lt;em&gt;And, if so, does it even matter?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m not usually a worrier, and I have been guilty of trying to wait things out rather than take my kids to the doctor, not always with good results. One child turned out to have terrible strep and another one was experiencing a bad bout of pneumonia. But, in this case, because it was such an unusual comment, my mom instincts instantly kicked in. I wanted to know if this was a serious issue and, if so, what could be done to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I decided to see what Google had to say on the subject, and it turns out that yes, it is possible that people can’t burp, and yes, it most definitely matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;The author with Gavin at his college graduation in 2025. &lt;span class="copyright"&gt;Courtesy of Gretchen Scherer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Columbia University Irving Medical Center, the medical name for the inability to burp is &lt;a href="https://www.columbiadoctors.org/news/what-happens-when-you-cannot-burp" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:retrograde cricopharyngeus dysfunction;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;retrograde cricopharyngeus dysfunction&lt;/a&gt; (R-CPD), which is informally known as no-burp syndrome. The diagnosis did not exist before 2019, and instead sufferers were often incorrectly diagnosed with acid reflux, irritable bowel disease or other digestive problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When most people need to let a buildup of air escape from their stomach, the cricopharyngeus muscle relaxes and allows the air to vacate. For reasons that are still somewhat mysterious, some individuals’ cricopharyngeus muscle stays tensed, so they never burp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/son-picky-eater-arfid-therapy_n_68791c50e4b09816d316744f?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:I Couldn't Get My Son To Eat Anything. I Thought He Was Just Picky — But The Truth Was Much More Serious.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;I Couldn't Get My Son To Eat Anything. I Thought He Was Just Picky — But The Truth Was Much More Serious.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The more I thought about it, the more I realized all of the ways in which Gavin’s inability to burp had impacted him throughout his life. He was a terrible spitter-upper as a baby, and he was always more of a snacker than an eater. When he was older, he rarely drank soda, especially out of a can. He also had a reputation in our family for being able to clear a room with his farts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was the smallest of our three boys, and even at the peak of his growth spurt, while he was logging endless miles as a cross-country runner, he only ever ate a small amount of food at each sitting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was common to hear Gavin say he was full after eating only half his meal. No matter how much he loved cheeseburgers, half of it would sit on his plate uneaten. Then, two hours later, he would ask me for another dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If I’m being honest, I didn’t always hide my frustration with those requests. But, luckily for both of us, I was always willing to at least make him a peanut butter and jelly sandwich (otherwise I would be wracked with guilt right now).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/dating-men-women-bisexual-lesbian_n_68e7c3d9e4b0b4458cb74288?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:When Straight Women Find Out I'm Bisexual, There's 1 Big Misconception I Often Have To Clear Up;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;When Straight Women Find Out I'm Bisexual, There's 1 Big Misconception I Often Have To Clear Up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although no-burp syndrome is considered relatively rare, people who suffer from it often deal with significant symptoms. Severe bloating, throat gurgling, and terrible flatulence are some of the persistent issues, and they often become worse as a person gets older. The side effects of R-CPD can cause social anxiety and significantly impact quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few weeks after Gavin made that offhanded comment at dinner, he had his annual checkup with his pediatrician. I made sure he raised the burping issue, and Gavin described his symptoms. Unfortunately, his doctor said he’d never heard of R-CPD. Since Gavin was leaving for college the next week, we let it go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, when Gavin came home at Christmas several months later, he brought it up again. The coping methods he had used before — frequently eating small portions and avoiding carbonated beverages — weren’t as easy to maintain at college. Along with experiencing severe bloating, he now found himself occasionally throwing up. He wanted the problem solved, and I was becoming increasingly concerned about how R-CPD could impact him as he got older, so I kept researching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you google the condition today, an AI overview will tell you everything you need to know. But even just a few years ago, it was incredibly difficult to find a solution, and some of the articles and videos I did find made me worry that it could be doing severe damage to Gavin’s health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read: &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/megyn-kelly-epstein-pedophile-grooming-assault_n_691b4443e4b0023259f639c4?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:I Was 16 When A Grown Man Groomed And Sexually Assaulted Me. I've Kept This Secret For 30 Years — Until Now.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;I Was 16 When A Grown Man Groomed And Sexually Assaulted Me. I've Kept This Secret For 30 Years — Until Now.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luckily, a friend of Gavin’s told us about a clinic near Chicago that had pioneered an experimental treatment designed to treat R-CPD by injecting Botox into the throat. We learned that the drug releases the cricopharyngeal sphincter and allows the patient to retrain the sphincter as the injectable slowly wears off. The success rate for a single procedure, which involves three shots, is over 80%, with nearly 20% needing a second procedure in order to be cured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Armed with that information, I wasted no time trying to find a doctor in Minneapolis that could perform the procedure. Before Gavin returned to the University of Wisconsin for his second semester, I had found a local physician trained to do the throat injections, and I was able to get him evaluated. The doctor numbed Gavin’s throat and performed an endoscopy. Based on that and an evaluation of Gavin’s symptoms, the doctor determined that Gavin most likely did have R-CPD and would be a great candidate for the Botox procedure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gavin headed back to college, and we began the process of getting the injections approved by the insurance company. Our hope was to have the procedure done in Minneapolis, but our insurance rejected the request because the FDA has not approved Botox for this purpose. I made many calls over the next several months to our insurance company, the Minneapolis clinic, and the clinic in Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I finally found a workaround by paying out-of-pocket for the Botox (around $600), so it wasn’t submitted as part of our insurance claim. The rest of the procedure was approved, and, in our case, was 80% covered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two days after finishing his spring exams, Gavin was on his way to the clinic in Chicago because they could see him almost immediately. Once he was there, Gavin underwent another endoscopy, watched a video that explained the procedure, and consulted with a doctor. The next morning, Gavin was put under with general anesthesia and was given three injections of Botox in his throat. Everything went smoothly, and Gavin and his dad were on their way home by 11:30 a.m. that day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;The author's son, Gavin, chugging orange soda. &lt;span class="copyright"&gt;Courtesy of Gretchen Scherer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The worst side effect from the treatment was some temporary discomfort. For the first couple of months, the esophageal sphincter is completely open, and Gavin initially described the feeling in his throat as “a little weird.” Within 24 hours, he started experiencing “micro burps,” which is the first step in retraining the cricopharyngeal sphincter. Some people also experience occasional regurgitation as they practice burping during that first week.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Patients are encouraged to burp as much as possible, so we gave Gavin full permission to burp anytime, anywhere. For most of that summer, burping was his new party trick for friends and family.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Three years after the procedure, Gavin is still burping strong, although he hasn’t quite mastered the alphabet yet. His sphincter is now completely retrained. Gavin said the procedure has been life-changing. Almost immediately, he was able to wolf down entire cheeseburgers for the first time, and the ability to drink carbonated beverages at college parties is a definite plus. I notice that he is happier in general and more energetic because he is not distracted by the discomfort that often came with eating.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I am relieved that we were able to find a solution. My Google searches had turned up stories of the extreme discomfort that some people have to live with on a daily basis. Fortunately, Gavin’s symptoms fell more on the mild to medium side of the spectrum.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The more I tell people about Gavin’s story, the less “rare” R-CPD seems. In fact, it may be more common than originally thought; at least two of my son’s friends have the same issue and one also had the procedure in Chicago. However, very few doctors are familiar with the condition and may not know enough to ask the questions that could lead to a diagnosis. Parents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; may not even notice that a child who burped fine as a baby stopped burping as they got older.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This journey has reminded me of several important truths about being a parent. &lt;span&gt;First, don’t ignore complaints your kids make about their health — even those that seem small or nonchalant. I could have easily shrugged off Gavin’s initial comment, and I’m so glad I didn’t. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Second, doctors don’t know everything. Gavin’s pediatrician is fantastic, but he was even less familiar with no-burp syndrome than I was. I felt a little sheepish questioning him about it, but I’m really glad I kept looking for information and pushing for an answer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Finally, don’t automatically take no for an answer from your insurance company. It took time and persistence to get an approval for (most of) Gavin’s procedure, but it was absolutely worth it in the end. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are a lot of things I’ve gotten wrong as a parent, but thankfully, this is one of the times I got things absolutely right — and Gavin would love nothing more than to take a big swig of beer and show you himself. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Gretchen Scherer is a mother, English teacher, and sometimes writer living in Minneapolis, Minnesota. Her essays and travel articles have appeared in Salon.com, The St. Paul Pioneer Press, Minnesota Monthly Magazine, and a few anthologies. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Do you have a compelling personal story you’d like to see published on HuffPost? Find out what we’re looking for &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/static/how-to-pitch-huffpost" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:here;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="mailto:pitch@huffpost.com" data-ylk="slk:send us a pitch at pitch@huffpost.com.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;send us a pitch at pitch@huffpost.com.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Related...&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/son-no-burp-syndrome-treatment_n_68e7ce84e4b0b4458cb74b0f?utm_campaign=yahoo-recirc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read the original on HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Read the original on HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 22:52:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE5PRHdBck9GR1VzQWMxTi1sM1psVEdIS1FDSW95RXpUeXNlcmJFeU12bDBfQnIwY2hTZ3dZZ1U1aGN3djBETHVEZEZGdVZ2RjRjWUl3R0NZOWlhc1FIM1VMaEk0SXBmWC0zRmdvdDFPc2JWMnBOX1Mzeg</guid></item><item><title>咳嗽或感冒时应该吃的5种水果-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/5-fruits-you-should-eat-when-you-have-a-cough-or-cold/articleshow/125453571.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re dealing with a cough or cold, the foods you choose can actually make a noticeable difference in how quickly you start feeling better. Of course, rest, staying hydrated, and giving your body time to recover are essential, but what you eat can offer an extra boost. Certain fruits, packed with vitamins, antioxidants, and natural anti-inflammatory compounds, can help support your immune system, soothe an irritated throat, and even ease congestion. Including these fruits in your daily diet isn’t just about nutrition; it’s about giving your body gentle, natural support while it fights off the infection, helping you feel stronger and more comfortable during recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fruits that help ease cough and cold symptoms and boost immunity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;1. Pomegranate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pomegranate is rich in polyphenols, particularly punicalagin, which have demonstrated antiviral properties. According to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/19586764/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;a study published in PubMed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, pomegranate polyphenol extract suppressed the replication of influenza A virus in cultured cells and exhibited virucidal effects. The research further identified punicalagin as a key compound responsible for blocking viral RNA replication. These findings suggest that pomegranate extracts might help reduce the viral load during respiratory viral infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Combat Monsoon Cold &amp;amp; Cough: Here's A Quick Fix With Indian Borage Leaf And Turmeric&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;2. Kiwi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kiwi is exceptionally high in vitamin C, a vitamin closely linked to immune function and the management of respiratory infections. According to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-3921/13/3/272" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;a study published in Antioxidants (MDPI)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, consuming two SunGold kiwifruit per day for six weeks restored adequate plasma vitamin C levels in individuals with a history of severe respiratory infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study highlights that kiwi consumption can directly support the body during respiratory illness by boosting antioxidant defences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;3. Lemon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lemon is well-known for its high vitamin C content and flavonoids, both of which support immune function and help modulate inflammation. While specific clinical trials focusing on lemon juice and coughs are limited, broader epidemiological research links higher plasma vitamin‑C levels to a lower risk of respiratory diseases. For example, studies from large population cohorts report an inverse association between vitamin C status and incidence of non‑cancerous respiratory diseases. Additionally, flavonoids in citrus fruits (like hesperidin and naringenin) have been reported to exert anti-inflammatory effects on the respiratory tract, which may help reduce symptom severity in colds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;4. Pineapple&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pineapple contains bromelain, a mixture of proteolytic enzymes known for anti‑inflammatory and immunomodulatory effects. According to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2576519/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;a study published in PubMed&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, bromelain treatment in a mouse model of allergic airway inflammation significantly reduced leukocyte infiltration, including eosinophils and T lymphocytes, in the lungs. These findings suggest that bromelain, and thereby pineapple, may help reduce airway inflammation and ease respiratory symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;5. Berries (e.g., Strawberries, Blueberries, Raspberries)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Berries are rich in flavonoids and vitamin C, which contribute significantly to antioxidant and anti-inflammatory activity. Although direct clinical trials on berries for cough or cold are limited, reviews in the nutritional science literature emphasise their immunoregulatory and antiviral potential. Flavonoids found in berries, such as quercetin, anthocyanins, and catechins, have been shown to modulate immune responses, reduce oxidative stress, and potentially interfere with viral replication in in vitro settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Practical tips for using these fruits when you’re unwell&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choose room-temperature or mildly warmed fruit preparations to avoid irritating a sore throat.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prefer whole fruit over fruit juice: whole fruit retains fibre and results in a slower, steadier blood sugar response.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Combine these fruits with other soothing remedies like honey (if age‑appropriate), herbal teas, or warm broths.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rotate between different fruits to benefit from a range of phytonutrients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Although these fruits support recovery, they are complementary, not a replacement for medical treatment. If your symptoms persist, worsen, or include high fever or breathing difficulties, consult a healthcare professional.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a healthcare professional before making any changes to your diet, medication, or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 22:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0gFBVV95cUxNRlczc2RaS1JCRWJyaU1LNmJvU2pva0RyU0lVUFAxRFFKTDhPWWdiTmZQRk9uMmVHX2MxQU1KX0JBZVY1MVNEbTd3bWJ5V0FwVEJkZWxsVEVtNnJ1QnpPTURKNmpPdUROMl9PakVhRjFlOV8xMDJrRXBxNmtrck96cWw3T3pEbTBfaV9qcjd6NmJKdlZSd2JIOVNYRVlpNkdJajdrbHNzMnkwbXlYbXJhWDRFZ1o2ZE5kMjhaaXpCZzFiRFIyN2gwZG1mQnNFWG9Ea2c</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，年轻人可能特别容易暴饮暴食超加工食品-福克斯新闻</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/young-adults-may-especially-prone-overeating-ultra-processed-foods-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;&lt;div class="featured featured-video video-ct" data-v-324c3b57&gt; &lt;div class="contain" data-v-324c3b57&gt;   &lt;div class="info" data-v-324c3b57&gt;&lt;div class="caption" data-v-324c3b57&gt; &lt;p data-v-324c3b57&gt;Fox News senior medical analyst Dr. Marc Siegel describes the Trump administration's mission against ultra-processed foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div id="beyondwords-wrapper" class="beyondwords-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="info"&gt;&lt;span class="label-bg"&gt;NEW&lt;/span&gt;You can now listen to Fox News articles!
  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="speakable"&gt;Young people may be uniquely vulnerable to &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/nutrition-and-fitness/diet-trends" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;ultra-processed foods&lt;/a&gt; and more likely to overeat when consuming a diet high in them, according to a new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="speakable"&gt;In a tightly controlled Virginia Tech feeding trial, 18- to 21-year-olds ate more at an all-you-can-eat breakfast and again when offered snacks — even when they were not hungry — after two weeks on a high ultra-processed food (UPF) diet compared to their slightly older Gen Z peers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers enrolled 27 adults ages 18 to 25 in a crossover study comparing two diets — one with 81% of calories from UPFs and one without any. Each diet lasted two weeks, with meals prepared in a lab and matched for calories and nutrients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After each phase, participants ate freely from a large buffet breakfast, which offered about 1,800 calories, and then took part in a snack test to measure whether they would keep eating even when not hungry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/additives-ultra-processed-foods-linked-higher-death-risk-major-study" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ADDITIVES IN ULTRA-PROCESSED FOODS LINKED TO HIGHER DEATH RISK IN MAJOR STUDY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Younger adults aged 18 to 21 consumed nearly 100 extra calories and were more likely to eat when not hungry after the ultra-processed diet, according to the findings, published Nov. 19 in the journal Obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A new study finds young adults may overeat ultra-processed foods, even when they are not hungry.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The young people ate about 90 calories more after the UPF diet, and if that occurred three times daily in the three main meals, that would represent approximately 270 extra calories per day," Brenda Davy, a senior author on the paper and professor in Virginia Tech’s Department of Human Nutrition, Foods and Exercise, told Fox News Digital. "Over the course of a week, that could represent almost 2,000 extra weekly calories."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This type of eating habit, eating when not hungry, is linked to weight gain and increased &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/nutrition-and-fitness/obesity" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;risk of obesity,"&lt;/a&gt; Davy added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/even-low-calorie-processed-food-causes-weight-gain-testosterone-loss-men-study-suggests" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EVEN LOW-CALORIE PROCESSED FOOD CAUSES WEIGHT GAIN, TESTOSTERONE LOSS IN MEN, STUDY SUGGESTS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers said the pattern could play out in real life and have long-term implications. Dining halls, takeout and campus food courts give young people unlimited access to ultra-processed items, often paired with sugary drinks and snacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings were unaffected by participants' sex or body mass index (BMI), a measure of body fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Virginia Tech scientists Brenda Davy, left, and Alex DiFeliceantonio researched the influence of ultra-processed foods on young adults.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(Clayton Metz for Virginia Tech)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I thought BMI would be the factor that mattered, but it was age," said neuroscientist and co-author Alex DiFeliceantonio, an assistant professor with Virginia Tech’s Fralin Biomedical Research Institute. "The younger you were when you entered the study, the more you ate after the UPF diet compared to the non-UPF diet," she told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/first-time-more-children-world-who-obese-than-underweight" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FOR THE FIRST TIME, THERE ARE MORE CHILDREN IN THE WORLD WHO ARE OBESE THAN UNDERWEIGHT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, funded by a grant from the National Institutes of Health, was small and had a short duration, so the results can't show long-term weight changes or real-world eating patterns. The experiment also measured behavior at a single buffet meal and short snack test, which doesn't fully reflect how people eat throughout the day or on a college campus with constant food access. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Future studies are needed to determine if this takes place over the course of a day or week," Davy noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers say larger, longer trials including younger teens and real-life dining settings could help reveal how UPFs influence appetite and the brain's reward systems over time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to understand what it is in the ultra-processed foods that could be having these effects," DiFeliceantonio added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;College-age participants (not pictured) in a Virginia Tech trial ate more calories after two weeks on an ultra-processed diet.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers based their work on the NOVA classification system, which sorts foods by how industrialized or altered from their original form they are. Under this framework, UPFs include soft drinks, packaged snacks, flavored yogurts and frozen meals made with additives and ingredients not usually found in home cooking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="c-link" href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/lifestyle/quizzes" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TEST YOURSELF WITH OUR LATEST LIFESTYLE QUIZ&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some experts, however, push back on the definition of UPFs, saying it is too broad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Health authorities across the globe have rejected using the 'ultra-processed food' concept as a basis for public health policy, citing its lack of scientific consensus, its imprecision and potential to cause confusion and the risk that it could undermine established, evidence-based &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/nutrition-and-fitness/nutrition" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;nutrition strategies,"&lt;/a&gt; the International Food and Beverage Association previously told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="c-link" href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE TO SIGN UP FOR OUR LIFESTYLE NEWSLETTER&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Evan Nadler, who co-directed the Children's National Obesity Programs at Children's National Hospital in Washington, D.C., before founding ProCare Consultants and TeleHealth, said that, while the NOVA needs improvement, it is "the best we have for now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The study raises concerns about how highly processed foods affect appetite and development in young people.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nadler said the Virginia Tech findings fit what is already known about adolescent development. "Adolescents are already prone to making rash decisions, and eating UPFs may just be another of them," he said. "I would guess the younger kids might be even more susceptible to the effects of UPFs."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="c-link" href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS?pid=AppArticleLink&amp;amp;af_dp=foxnewsaf%3A%2F%2F&amp;amp;af_web_dp=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.foxnews.com%2Fapps-products" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE TO GET THE FOX NEWS APP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, Nadler said, "This is great preliminary data for a &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/food-drink/food/studies" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;larger study&lt;/a&gt; that I would hope included kids under the age of 18."&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;div class="article-meta"&gt;&lt;div class="author-bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deirdre Bardolf is a lifestyle writer with Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fox News</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 21:59:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQWXFvQkRLRExOT1ZsdkhlY2gxN2U1QzNZZEpVTTVoLVNJNUowOGhyeml3SzVMQVA1RnVhYm9sWVJzb1hHdG5Edlh5YW9NemxlUGpHNjlmV3BrbTJ6Z3VES0tXV0ZPOHE3dUlaSUFJR0VxWHNCY1RGczVUaC0wSEZSN0x6THU0bFlGdHJVNnRPbGJDcVV3Um1MR1ZrZVFBSU03aHlWd1Z4SVhMUGFUcWhPd0pGZw</guid></item><item><title>WTOP的Neal Augenstein ： 4期肺癌诊断3年后，下一步是什么- WTOP</title><link>https://wtop.com/inside-wtop/2025/11/wtops-neal-augenstein-3-years-after-stage-4-lung-cancer-diagnosis-whats-next/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="schema-summary"&gt;During the first three years of Augenstein's lung cancer journey, he's been happy to be able to share things he has been learning along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;div id="Entry-content" class="entry-content Entry-content "&gt;
                                                
                                
                &lt;div class="paragraph-with-figure"&gt;
&lt;figure class="article_featured_image right" data-fancybox data-src="#modal-post-featured-image"&gt;
                            &lt;span class="zoom_icon"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
                            &lt;img src="https://wtop.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/IMG_1972-480x320.jpg"&gt;
                            &lt;figcaption&gt;WTOP's Neal Augenstein was diagnosed with Stage 4 lung cancer in 2022. (WTOP/Neal Augenstein)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
                        &lt;/figure&gt;
                        &lt;div id="modal-post-featured-image" class="reveal-modal" data-reveal aria-labelledby="modalTitle" aria-hidden="true" role="dialog"&gt;
                            &lt;figure class="article_featured_image modal"&gt;
                                &lt;img src="https://wtop.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/IMG_1972-780x520.jpg"&gt;
                                &lt;figcaption&gt;WTOP's Neal Augenstein was diagnosed with Stage 4 lung cancer in 2022. (WTOP/Neal Augenstein)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
                            &lt;/figure&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my first 25 years at WTOP, my reports about lung cancer were primarily stories about famous people who died from the deadliest and second-most common cancer in the U.S. — until I was diagnosed with Stage 4 lung cancer exactly three years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, most of my lung cancer stories have been about living.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within six months of being diagnosed with Stage 4 non-small cell lung cancer just before Thanksgiving 2022, after great results with one-pill-a-day targeted therapy that shrank cancerous tumors and lymph nodes in both lungs, I became eligible for a robotic-assisted lung lobectomy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, I’ve had no evidence of disease, and have remained cancer-free since May 2023, while continuing to take my daily pill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Giving thanks? Indeed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;During the first three years of my journey, I’ve been happy to be able to share things I’ve been learning along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, is the importance of &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2025/07/why-newly-diagnosed-lung-cancer-patients-should-get-this-test-done-before-starting-treatment/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;newly diagnosed cancer patients getting biomarker testing&lt;/a&gt;, and waiting for the results before beginning treatment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Biomarker testing involves testing biopsied lung tissue — often taken during a bronchoscopy — to try to learn the exact cell mutation that caused a patient’s cancer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“The importance of testing is if they have that mutation, then the treatment is very different, and the patient outcomes are also much better,” thoracic medical oncologist Ram Subramanian with Inova Schar Cancer Institute in Fairfax County, Virginia, told me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my case, I was diagnosed with EGFR-positive lung cancer, which has several targeted treatments available, and generally limits the side effects of treatment compared to chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite having no evidence of cancer now, I (and my doctors) wouldn’t say that I’m “cured,” since I was originally diagnosed after cancer had spread from the original site in my left lung.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2025, life with lung cancer can be similar to life with other chronic diseases, including diabetes or heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The key is aggressive surveillance, which in my case involves low-dose CT scans every four months, as well as brain MRIs and liquid biopsies twice a year. If something suspicious were to show up on one of these scans, it would likely be early-stage, which could be removed with surgery or targeted by radiation.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, while the  American Lung Association’s&lt;a href="https://www.lung.org/research/state-of-lung-cancer" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; 2025 State of Lung Cancer&lt;/a&gt; report shows the five-year survival rate for lung cancer in the U.S. has risen to 29.7%, which represents a 26% improvement over the past five years, research continues to enable earlier detection, including the&lt;a href="https://wtop.com/local/2025/11/how-ai-helps-detect-lung-cancer-sooner-improving-survival-rates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; use of artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lung cancer patients in the D.C. region are lucky — there are a &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/health-fitness/2025/04/what-cancer-patients-families-should-know-about-clinical-trials-in-the-dc-area/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;large number of clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; in Virginia, Maryland and the District, offering new options and hope for patients and their families.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Personally, while I’ve been lucky to not have any recurrences in my first three years living with cancer, I often discuss trials with my thoracic oncologist Amin Benyounes, who is the co-leader at the&lt;a href="https://www.inova.org/our-services/inova-schar-cancer/treatment-options/phase-I-program" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; Inova Schar Cancer Institute’s Phase One Program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Benyounes said many patients considering enrollment in a clinical trial worry about the unknown: “Will this make me feel worse, will it make me feel sick, could it hurt more than it would help? Will my kids or my partner have to bear the burden of me feeling sick?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With clinical trials affording the possibilities for longer survival with fewer side effects, some patients ask, “What if I get my hopes up, and it doesn’t work?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Benyounes: “My answer to that is usually, ‘We have to take things one step at a time.’”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s the same guidance he gave me when I began my cancer journey, three years ago.&lt;/p&gt;


                
                
                &lt;p class="After-content"&gt;
                                    &lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Get breaking news and daily headlines delivered to your email inbox by signing up &lt;a href="https://wtop.com/newsletter-signup/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="single-page__signature bottom"&gt;© 2025 WTOP. All Rights Reserved. This website is not intended for users located within the European Economic Area.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WTOP</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 19:32:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxQVklfOU0yblJYcWVfR1psV2h5ZVF3TlZrbF9haUF4T3RnWlVjM1FqcC1aSXVIUHNsX2dQV09HSFNXYmltb1Q2azVNV1JIUk1YZnNQRmZPNDIxVVVNYWJ6aXdCbWxlQjRZUWc0MjZYWTNQdm5GWS1wQ01pMWhKX3ZPSl9qdkR0ZXhtRHJqc2pMYUJNZXM3eHpHeGR6d3l0dThsQWYtY2NIdndQT2U3LWlDRFdJa2o</guid></item><item><title>助听器可将痴呆风险降低61% ，研究称- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51409291/hearing-aids-may-reduce-dementia-risk-by-61-study-says</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SALT LAKE CITY — Only about one in five adults who could benefit from hearing aids actually uses them. But new research shows that treating hearing loss early may do more than improve hearing — it could also protect your brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 20-year &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamaneurology/fullarticle/2837714?guestAccessKey=a1f9c4ab-a0ae-4ca9-afa5-cb8c5e77afc3&amp;amp;utm_source=For_The_Media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_term=081825#xd_co_f=OWUxNzI0Y2UtNzczMi00Y2JlLTg4YWItNDQyNzVmZmZkYzc2~" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in the Journal of the American Medical Association found that adults who started using hearing aids before age 70 had a 61% lower risk of developing dementia. The study followed thousands of people and found the strongest benefits in those who treated their hearing loss early, before it became severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Hearing loss can be gradual or it can be quickly overnight," said Richard Phillips, a hearing instrument specialist with House of Hearing in Moab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said untreated hearing loss forces the brain to work overtime, which can speed up cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Patterson has lived with hearing loss for 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I was always a little concerned about, well, I don't want people to see that I have hearing aids, I don't want to look older," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He recalled the moment he first received his hearing aids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I still remember getting back in my car and turning on the music and almost coming to tears because I could actually hear the full sound," Patterson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say hearing aids won't prevent every case of dementia, but they may be one of the simplest tools to improve communication, reduce isolation and support long-term brain health. They can even help with balance issues, reducing the risk of falls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What we've noticed is the ones that wear them all the time, you can just tell, their cognitive skills seem to be sharper, more alert," Phillips said. "It improves your life and makes the people around you a lot happier, also."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health providers recommend getting a hearing test starting around age 60 — and many clinics offer free screenings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 18:22:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPam5fb0V2NXZVc1VncWV2YUdTNmR1N2E4dGt3eHduODlyLXRwY0NQUDhFa3Zvalg2d1dXbE04N0NWb1U1SnJYaUV3a3hmeU9HRVZ2aGt1ZVNYbDVFTzlyWmtUMTBRSEdrRnZQQU1CQlE2U2c2ajA1ekVPc0pZeGc1b2VsOXI3N0Rrc3U3NDV6MlRBQ18yVHc</guid></item><item><title>在新泽西州城镇， “异常友好”的臭鼬狂犬病检测呈阳性- NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/mercer/2025/11/unusually-friendly-skunk-tests-positive-for-rabies-in-nj-town.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WHPLVJKOYNCBTJBF2DLP2CWKZE"&gt;A skunk reported in West Windsor Township earlier this month has tested positive for rabies, according to local officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NRS6BTTQRJD5NBLOXRDE7ZK5QI"&gt;A resident alerted police after seeing the skunk exhibit abnormal behavior near Quaker Road and University Way on Nov. 14, West Windsor Township’s Department of Human Services said in a public health advisory. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HIUY4C2QJNEM5C5DCBDMLRA2CY"&gt;The skunk did not appear injured or ill, but was acting “unusually friendly,” officials said. An unusual lack of fear is a symptom of rabies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D2NHJZAQLBGMRDEEQ2GNVTGOVQ"&gt;According to local officials, an animal control officer promptly responded to investigate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TFHUTBOKIVCJDFDGITIZ6BB75Y"&gt;Residents are asked to notify police if they notice wildlife acting strangely, or if nocturnal animals — including opossums, raccoons and skunks — are seen during the day. They can also contact the &lt;a href="https://www.westwindsornj.org/departments/health-division" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.westwindsornj.org/departments/health-division"&gt;West Windsor Township Health Department&lt;/a&gt; for additional information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XGN2PT7WQFDQNAQCONISJ66GSQ"&gt;Officials encourage residents to keep their pet vaccinations up to date and avoid contact with wildlife. Children should be cautioned about avoiding contact with stray animals and wildlife, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OWMNSXXPRBETJLSB4FICGJY6PQ"&gt;Residents are encouraged to also take preventative measures, such as securing trash cans, bat-proofing homes and securing pets after dark, according to officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:JHLWHQOEWFGR5IIHUBUXT2CG4A" data-fusion-component="JHLWHQOEWFGR5IIHUBUXT2CG4A"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:JHLWHQOEWFGR5IIHUBUXT2CG4A" data-fusion-component="JHLWHQOEWFGR5IIHUBUXT2CG4A"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOa2lYV2hSQ1UzX0wtNmFEMElTVk9uRXR3MUQyZ01ORnFiODhCWXpFNTFPamxUdUF4RjBaNm1hMVlxLS1WY05wMnE0azl3Ni03eWY3aVllY3R1OFJwUUozNFdLeFZEbDZnNFNoa3FDR3FaOHVzbGRtRlpSdUk2T2FVZzA5b3hCc3kySHhfeEY4VjBfMW1kaHd3N2x6QlNVRmx3OGfSAbYBQVVfeXFMTkJIZjN6ckhuczVNSllQTFo1RFFxbDlzS041YzNPOXlUNDJYdWxuX2w2VEhIQkxlVzR0aFhSNVRTcGstY3BNNU8tcS0tZ3NnYVQzdzdhMkR2OTFNaERsTWVxMGg2WHBReTdrRFlma3Q4VXRYQTY3S0pGOWdiSi1BTUhXeDhBVFhqeG1YQjF6SWZTRmc4YVJDNEdmaTZCNkhjX040M1lxSEYxRXJTenJQNTlTbzAtSHc</guid></item><item><title>7种科学支持的方式，让您在60天内变得更年轻- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/fashion-and-beauty/r-t-7-science-backed-ways-to-be-younger-looking-in-60-days/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;A couple of years ago, after a long week of travel, I caught my reflection in a hotel elevator mirror and thought, “Wow… when did I start looking this tired?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not older. Just tired.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if you have ever had a similar moment, you know the feeling. Aging is not something we control, but how old we look is a different story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Science says we have more influence over that than most people realize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, I want to break down seven science-backed strategies you can use over the next 60 days to look fresher, healthier, and yes, younger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ready to turn back the clock a little?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Improve your sleep quality&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is the funny thing about sleep: you do not notice how much it affects your face until you are not getting enough of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But dermatologists do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sleep is basically your body’s overnight anti aging treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Growing up in the restaurant world, I used to believe that pushing through exhaustion was just part of the hustle. But when I finally cleaned up my sleep routine, my dark circles faded within weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 60 day upgrade you can try: Set a &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/m-if-you-were-taught-these-5-things-growing-up-your-parents-were-more-intelligent-than-most/"&gt;consistent bedtime&lt;/a&gt;, keep your room cool, and avoid screens at least 45 minutes before bed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are like me and sometimes read nonfiction before sleep, switch to a physical book. Your skin will thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Boost hydration (from the inside and out)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever looked at yourself after a salty meal, long flight, or a few glasses of something fun and noticed your face looked puffier? I have, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hydration is one of those unsexy tips we all know, but it is also one of the fastest ways to &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/nat-if-you-want-to-be-younger-looking-in-60-days-start-practicing-these-8-daily-habits/"&gt;look more youthful&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Higher water intake increases skin hydration and improves overall appearance, especially in people who previously drank less than the recommended daily amount.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Moisturizing topically also makes a noticeable difference within days. When the outer layer of skin is well hydrated, it reflects more light. That means you literally glow more.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A quick 60 day fix: Add one extra liter of water to your day and use a moisturizer with hyaluronic acid. It holds up to 1,000 times its weight in water and naturally plumps the skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Eat more antioxidant rich foods&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is something I learned working in luxury food: you can enjoy incredible meals without sacrificing your health or your skin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And when it comes to looking younger, antioxidants matter. Oxidative stress accelerates skin aging, while antioxidants like vitamins C and E help neutralize that damage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Foods high in antioxidants include berries, &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/food-and-drink/k-if-someone-refuses-to-eat-these-8-foods-as-an-adult-you-know-they-grew-up-spoiled-and-undisciplined/"&gt;leafy greens&lt;/a&gt;, nuts, dark chocolate, tomatoes, olives, and coffee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One of my favorite parts of traveling is sampling different local foods. Whether I was eating street market papaya in Thailand or an incredible tomato salad in Italy, I noticed the same thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People with diets full of colorful produce tend to have that naturally vibrant, youthful look.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try this for 60 days: Add at least two more servings of antioxidant rich fruits or veggies to your daily meals. Your skin tone can noticeably improve in as little as eight weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Use sunscreen daily (yes, even indoors)&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-81052" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/Your-paragraph-text-1973-840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nobody loves hearing this, but UV exposure is responsible for up to 80 percent of visible skin aging according to the World Health Organization.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here is the surprising part. Indoor light sources, including the blue light from your computer or phone, can contribute to pigmentation and collagen breakdown.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/fashion-and-beauty/a-10-subtle-beauty-habits-of-women-who-age-gracefully/"&gt;Daily sunscreen use&lt;/a&gt; not only protects skin but can actually reverse existing signs of aging over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I grew up thinking sunscreen was only for the beach. Now it is the first thing I put on each morning. It is like brushing your teeth. If you skip it, you will eventually see the consequences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A simple 60 day commitment: Wear a broad spectrum SPF 30 or higher every day, even when it is cloudy or you are staying inside. You will start noticing more even skin tone and less dullness faster than you think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Strength train 3 to 4 times a week&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This one might sound like it is about your body rather than your face. But the connection is real.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10290068/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;study found&lt;/a&gt; that resistance training actually changes gene expression in skin cells, making them behave more like younger cells. Participants saw improvements in skin structure and thickness within 16 weeks, with visible changes even earlier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strength training also boosts circulation, helping nutrients reach your skin more efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working out has always been my reset button. But once I learned it helps skin function like it is younger, it became a non negotiable part of my routine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your 60 day plan: Include at least two full body strength sessions per week. Even 20 minute routines count. Think push ups, squats, dumbbell presses. Simple movements with big impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your posture improves, your muscle tone improves, and your overall vitality becomes visible.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Reduce added sugar&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I know. This one stings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love pastries. I love crafted desserts. I love exploring bakeries when I travel. I am not giving any of that up and I am not telling you to either.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But added sugar, especially in excess, ages your skin faster through a process called glycation. Glycation damages collagen and elastin, the proteins that keep your skin firm and youthful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/387242540_The_Impact_of_Excessive_Sugar_Consumption_on_Skin_Health_Analysis_of_Biological_Mechanisms_and_Dermatological_Effects" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;A study in&lt;/a&gt; Clinical Dermatology links high sugar intake to accelerated skin aging and deeper wrinkles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is what I noticed when I cut back, not eliminated but reduced. My skin stopped looking inflamed. The puffiness around my eyes dropped. Even my jawline looked a little sharper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A realistic 60 day challenge: Reduce added sugar Monday through Friday. Enjoy your treats on the weekend. It is flexible, sustainable, and your skin will show the difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Manage stress intentionally&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stress eventually shows up on your face. That is not poetic. It is biological.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cortisol breaks down collagen and increases inflammation. Chronic stress does not just make you feel older.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7400286/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research from&lt;/a&gt; the International Journal of Molecular Sciences confirms that it literally makes you look older faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The real question is how do you lower stress without disappearing to a beach in Bali for two months?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, it comes down to tiny, daily habits. Five minute breathing sessions. Short walks with my phone left behind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Saying no more often. Reading a chapter of something interesting instead of scrolling endless feeds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Little moments that help my nervous system settle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try a 60 day approach: Pick one simple stress relief ritual and practice it daily. Meditation, breathwork, journaling, even cooking something nourishing can work. It does not need to be complicated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will feel better and people will start asking why you look so refreshed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The bottom line&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking younger in 60 days is not a miracle. It is a byproduct of stacking small, evidence based habits that improve your health &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/r-7-rules-to-live-by-if-you-want-to-glow-from-the-inside-out-in-your-70s-and-beyond/"&gt;from the inside out&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Better sleep. Better hydration. Better food. Better protection. Better movement. Better balance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nothing extreme. Nothing trendy. Just science and consistency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you stick to even a few of these habits for the next two months, you will not just look younger. You will feel younger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And that is the real goal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-2917581504"&gt;&lt;p&gt;				 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong data-start="380" data-end="431"&gt;If You Were a Healing Herb, Which Would You Be?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="380" data-end="651"&gt;Each herb holds a unique kind of magic — soothing, awakening, grounding, or clarifying.&lt;br data-start="521" data-end="524"&gt;This 9-question quiz reveals the healing plant that mirrors your energy right now and what it says about your natural rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="653" data-end="734"&gt;✨ Instant results. Deeply insightful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 			&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 17:02:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOYTZlTlRGeWt0Y1Ruc2FqdmpCQ1hiUFRSY1dDUWhVVTJVbEN6TVJBNXJoYUdlWkhzM1pQVWJDN3l0b3Q4c2dpUUY4N0VRb3Zmck82Y3B2ZWlQcDU2Zzl1RDV2X3RoRVpkV21jRmQ5ekhrajVsLUxwc3p1UFlqSHBCUURzN2xDRXhacVNVc3pOQm0tRDRNaEplbFZhSzlXdExIMnc</guid></item><item><title>医生解释慢性饮酒对肝脏的影响： “您的肝脏将酒精代谢成有毒物质……” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/doctor-explains-what-chronic-alcohol-consumption-does-to-your-liver-your-liver-metabolises-alcohol-into-a-toxic-101763825596996.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/doctor-explains-what-chronic-alcohol-consumption-does-to-your-liver-your-liver-metabolises-alcohol-into-a-toxic-101763825596996.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If you drink alcohol regularly and have noticed your belly starting to bulge, it may be more than just &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/udaipur-dietician-shares-5-healthy-breakfast-habits-that-may-actually-be-unhealthy-and-cause-bloating-or-fatigue-101763270272792.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="bloating"&gt;bloating &lt;/a&gt;- it could be a warning sign from your liver. While most people know &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fitness-trainer-warns-against-working-out-after-drinking-alcohol-or-without-rest-shares-7-worst-times-to-work-out-101763796483753.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="alcohol"&gt;alcohol &lt;/a&gt;isn’t great for the body, few realise how quickly regular drinking can trigger cell damage, scarring, and serious liver dysfunction. In some cases, that expanding belly can signal fluid buildup caused by advanced &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/liver-disease" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="liver"&gt;liver &lt;/a&gt;injury, a condition that demands immediate medical attention.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/22/550x309/beer_1763826073421_1763826073638.jpg" alt="Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)" title="Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/22/550x309/beer_1763826073421_1763826073638.jpg" alt="Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)" title="Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Find out the various stages of liver damage caused due to alcohol!(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/hepatologist-says-drink-coffee-first-thing-in-the-morning-even-on-an-empty-stomach-debunks-5-myths-about-coffee-101763807975245.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Hepatologist says ‘Drink coffee first thing in the morning, even on an empty stomach…’; debunks 5 myths about coffee"&gt;Hepatologist says ‘Drink coffee first thing in the morning, even on an empty stomach…’; debunks 5 myths about coffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Kunal Sood, an anaesthesiologist and interventional pain medicine physician, has explained what really happens to your body when you drink alcohol. In an Instagram video posted on November 22, the doctor explains how chronic alcohol consumption affects the liver and highlights the various stages of liver damage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Effects of chronic alcohol consumption&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Dr Sood, when you drink alcohol, your liver breaks it down into a toxic compound that can damage liver cells. Regular alcohol consumption can lead to liver scarring and even cause liver cells to die. The doctor explains, “When you drink, your liver metabolises alcohol into acetaldehyde, a toxic substance that can damage your liver cells. With chronic alcohol consumption, your liver cells will become overwhelmed, leading to scarring and cell death.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;First sign of liver damage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Sood emphasises that chronic alcohol consumption can cause serious liver damage, with the earliest signs often appearing as fat buildup in the liver. He states, “The first sign of this damage is fatty liver or fat building up in the liver. If drinking continues, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/nhs-surgeon-explains-real-reason-you-cant-shake-off-inflammation-simply-the-types-of-foods-that-you-are-101763622363895.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="inflammation"&gt;inflammation &lt;/a&gt;will occur, leading to alcoholic &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/world-news/us-news/trump-trolled-for-misspelling-hepatitis-while-talking-about-womens-health-won-t-be-taking-medical-advice-from-101761547207044.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="hepatitis"&gt;hepatitis&lt;/a&gt;. Over time, scarring develops leading to liver cirrhosis which will severely impact normal liver function.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Advanced liver damage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Sood notes that in the later stages of liver damage, fluid can accumulate in the abdomen, causing a visibly distended or bulging belly - a sign that requires urgent medical attention.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; He explains, “At this advanced stage, complications like ascites, which is fluid buildup in the abdomen, can occur. Ascites happens because &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gastroenterologist-warns-liver-cirrhosis-can-affect-your-brain-leading-to-symptoms-like-personality-changes-tremors-101755491343083.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="cirrhosis"&gt;cirrhosis &lt;/a&gt;reduces blood flow to the liver, which will increase pressure in nearby blood vessels causing fluid to leak into the abdominal cavity. This will usually require immediate medical attention.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 15:44:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAJBVV95cUxOWnFiVTdwaHZaYXZkcm0wd0w4OHg1azY4MGpxc3hndi1YX2hxVG51eDhwRXJQS3NDRjdQRGk5TnI5Y3FuR2Jlenh5R3ZIaWFNVzVuMGpNU0hud2loek05MGh1NzltTVQtbjlIcFlvaXdJS1JwT1B2NXlMME1IMkdHVmlpVHN2dWhYMkNmeGVZWUZsMUptNWxSeTZ6WUtYbmlZZk5EVExJREhqalZDMkR1cFVjVVBfeWdRTl9VcTFUTDhRbmpLNHppRkRla3YxZTdPc2xkT3hLX3ZuS05Dbk1OdEZIVUY2ZjNkVWk3UEMyQ3E0Rmh6OW5Ka0JQYnk3VTVFeV81c1dNV0pyZXlD0gGSAkFVX3lxTE8ycDBvWkVWZTltZFNmZTkyMUNwTTc0TmlnUnJHOEhhQ3B2dXhOVUR6cjdlbnVTdHFzVTFnOWFyNE11NWFoOWRrdHZXNEI2TVlMSWs3NDFIMzFyTzFwWG1qUkktSUpRMU9iYmMxLVN3WW5ROGxWbnNiaXk3cUJpbVM5TU8xcTBkc3BzR284Zy03WVE3bGk5R1NQTnJ0bDJuQUhITXpHSkJsNVJrdXBJVHc3aERNNGNPb3RwVmhmTlhGSDc0djV0d0xtQVFnN3NXbmhkYkYxenlYMWdXTklQbkFwenl3MjdpdkpPQlhjNG9tSFRSQlE5YzcwQUpIeXo5a2ZqWm9waU9MYjBzR1ZIX2xkVHc</guid></item><item><title>排名：美国十大主要死亡原因-视觉资本家</title><link>https://www.visualcapitalist.com/americas-leading-causes-of-death/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Visual Capitalist</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 15:36:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE9KeU1kLUFJMkVrV2lzalVkVEJtbURQeERMVTdCSmVxeFJnV1JFM1ZEYmFFeEtXUnhLWFhNVENRODByR214U192cERBbF94OFY4VDZ5eWRMZFdDd3M4WjF1TENSLWxGVG55cmFRMnd5R0QzZWlz</guid></item><item><title>食用这些受欢迎的水果可能会使体内农药含量飙升- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/eating-these-popular-fruits-could-spike-pesticide-levels-in-your-body/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 15:18:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPUDE1LW9QXzM4MDJkaF9sak15VEJoZlpqR0g3Qzl3V0JpLXZTVUxNX3dGSjVjbDJnVnpnaWF5dklHTGozNG1HNG93N3p4ZmlLTm03TkVaVkpGdHo0U0pXMDVfeGg0andITXZPdXF1WFNiVmpqS1owWHloenFwX0JMWGsydjJkUjUyN051OTZ0T1VPTGdZQnllNzVCdw</guid></item><item><title>西海岸卫生联盟，卫生部敦促对疫苗的信任，反对疾病预防控制中心的声明- KOMO</title><link>https://komonews.com/news/local/vaccines-and-autism-robert-f-kennedy-jr-president-trump-tylenol-washington-state-department-of-health-statement-on-vaccine-safety-and-autism-claims</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;OLYMPIA, Wash.  — &lt;/span&gt;The Washington State Department of Health (DOH), along with the West Coast Health Alliance, continue to strongly recommend vaccines to protect children, despite the Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) statement "Vaccines do not cause autism." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC, scientific studies have not ruled out the possibility that infant &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccine-safety/about/autism.html" target="_blank"&gt;vaccines contribute to the development of autism.&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Washington state health officials note that rigorous research of millions of people in multiple countries over decades provides high-quality evidence that vaccines are not linked to autism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The West Coast Health Alliance said they are "deeply concerned about inaccurate claims to the contrary recently posted on the federal Centers for Disease Control and Prevention website." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;READ MORE | &lt;a href="https://komonews.com/news/nation-world/cdc-updates-page-to-say-vaccines-do-not-cause-autism-isnt-an-evidence-based-claim-health-and-human-services-robert-f-kennedy-jr-donald-trump" target="_blank"&gt;CDC updates page to state 'vaccines do not cause autism' isn't an evidence-based claim&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We join health agencies and associations across the country, including the American Academy of Pediatrics and the Autism Science Foundation, in confirming that there is no credible scientific evidence linking vaccines to autism. Claims suggesting a link between vaccines and autism undermine public confidence, reduce immunization rates, and contribute to outbreaks of vaccine-preventable diseases. " DOH said in a statement Friday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;US Health &amp;amp; Human Services Department Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. announced in April that the agency would be launching an investigation into autism and potential causes of the disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy has been a vaccine skeptic for years and has linked some vaccines to autism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In September, during a press conference, &lt;a href="https://thenationaldesk.com/news/americas-news-now/despite-autism-warnings-from-trump-doctors-say-pregnant-women-can-safely-take-tylenol#" target="_blank"&gt;President Donald Trump advised pregnant women not to take Tylenol &lt;/a&gt;because it could be linked to a spike in autism. Health professionals pushed back on Trump's assertion that pregnant women should avoid taking Tylenol or risk having an autistic baby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Washington state health officials, Autism is a complex condition with multiple contributing genetic and environmental factors. Attributing it to any single cause is inaccurate and misleading, DOH said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Decades of research and large-scale studies consistently show no association between vaccination and an increased risk of autism, according to DOH. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Vaccines are thoroughly tested and remain one of the most important tools we have for preventing infectious diseases. They represent one of the greatest public health achievements in history, having saved millions of lives and prevented illness and lifelong disability," DOH said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KOMO</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 15:01:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwJBVV95cUxNMVA2ZDZKYnVxTko1ZjlHMXF5LVhiMC1RV1NrN1JLdzZfVUswRVBHVzU2WGppNVJpZHJpYUExU0NaV2t2TllKbnNqUU1GZVNWcEIwVGlvTXJJRzBKUUhtR3N0eTQ1SXVoeE1XM1FfQmZtVHM2Qmd1bWZNSm1MSjR5RGVNQ1gza2ZwWVMzNXB6dmFLMTNuZTFVNUljdFZRZUZyaEs4MFMwaGxIVFAtSm5VSE9wTklyUVdaVWlJUlNzWVFzQ0xHUGFraVNWZmZHc1FPYWdQNF9JNnFYUWNsa0JTc1FzeFhEaHhHc1l3UFRCVnhJT1BOblJhRDQ3cmpZbXg0c0Y2d3J3ZU9CV1k</guid></item><item><title>专家警告“严重”的流感季节，担心新的流感病毒-独立报</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/h3n2-virus-flu-season-new-strain-b2870479.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 bxpovR sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iBibVd"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 jVZWGn"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 eZqxmv"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 tawua"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 gZmYS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 cglitp"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 keLMOw sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 gyGWOu"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US flu season has begun slowly, but health experts are concerned following the emergence of a new viral strain, according to U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) data released on Friday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An early analysis suggests current vaccines may still be somewhat effective against this new version, which is driving recent infections. However, many scientists and medical professionals are more worried about disappointing vaccination rates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These low rates were a main reason for the unusually high flu hospitalisations and deaths last winter, making it one of the deadliest seasons this century.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think we’re going to see a really severe season," said Asefeh Faraz Covelli of the &lt;a href="/topic/george-washington-university"&gt;George Washington University&lt;/a&gt; School of Nursing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last winter, the overall flu hospitalization rate was the highest seen since the H1N1 flu pandemic 15 years ago. &lt;a href="/topic/flu"&gt;Flu&lt;/a&gt; was the underlying or a contributing cause of more than 18,000 deaths, and one seven-day stretch early this year saw more than 1,800 deaths — the highest one-week spike in at least a decade. Child flu deaths also were far higher than usual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CDC data posted Friday showed low flu activity so far, with only one state — &lt;a href="/topic/louisiana"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt; — reporting moderate activity. Most of the reported infections have been in children, said the CDC's Alicia Budd, who tracks flu infections for the &lt;a href="/topic/atlanta"&gt;Atlanta&lt;/a&gt;-based agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most also have been a new version of the type A H3N2 virus that historically has caused the most hospitalizations and deaths in older people. That type is responsible for most flu infections so far this year, and more than half have been a new subclade K variant that is different from the strain this year's flu shots were built to fight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 lkuiwY"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/16/25/GettyImages-1237727981.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/16/25/GettyImages-1237727981.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/16/25/GettyImages-1237727981.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="A woman arrives at a CVS pharmacy past a sign about free flu and Covid-19 vaccines on January 14, 2022 in Monterey Park, California." class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-244129"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;A woman arrives at a CVS pharmacy past a sign about free flu and Covid-19 vaccines on January 14, 2022 in Monterey Park, California.&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (AFP/Getty)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A preliminary analysis from the &lt;a href="/topic/united-kingdom"&gt;United Kingdom&lt;/a&gt; suggests the shots do provide at least partial protection, although it will take some time for scientists to know exactly how effective they are. Experts say any protection that softens the blow of a flu infection is important to get.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu seasons tend to get bad between December and February, and illnesses likely will accelerate as people travel and gather for Thanksgiving, Covelli said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I think it’s going to start picking up here,” she said. “This is the ideal time to get vaccinated.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers this year have been facing an unusual struggle to get a handle on how respiratory infection and vaccination rates have been trending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They usually rely on the CDC for data, but a recent government shutdown halted data collection and reporting just as respiratory infections started ramping up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, government efforts to promote disease-preventing shots have been more limited since U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. was put in charge of the CDC and other federal health agencies. Kennedy, a leading anti-vaccine activist, has fostered uncertainty about the safety of vaccines, including flu shots that contained a preservative called thimerosal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 hcSZFO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/15/CDC_Autism_16106.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/15/CDC_Autism_16106.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/11/20/15/CDC_Autism_16106.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="US Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr." class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-244130"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;US Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (AP)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, vaccination rates against COVID-19 clearly continue to plummet, with about 6% of children and 14% of adults up to date on their shots, according to other CDC data posted Friday. Each figure is about 3 percentage points less than it was at this point last fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the flu, vaccination trends are a little muddier. Some sources have suggested flu vaccinations are down. Over two million fewer flu shots were given at U.S. pharmacies through the end of October compared to last year, according to data from IQVIA, a health information and research company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the latest CDC data indicates that for children, the vaccination rate this year is about the same as it was at this point last fall, at 34%. And the vaccination rate for adults is up a few percentage points to about 37%, according to the CDC data, which relies on survey information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is early in the season and too early to know if the increase will be sustained or what is causing it, CDC officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of the beginning of November, the U.S. flu hospitalization rate is about the same as it was at the same point in 2024. Hospitalization rates for COVID-19 and another respiratory virus, RSV, are lower so far this season, according to another set of CDC data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPdXRHcFdibHRLZ192WndlRUROTS1TMzVfM0VqNmtwbDNwSVhGOEZFT0ZBSXRndUJlZ2txcmUxSlQydlRXTWRGM1l4djdWdXZpZ1M2VUtnTGFwTTJfaDdJTFdDS2pnZjFyRWJFZDJqU1YwVER3b0MyUXBMc1RqMkFwejdJOHRCNjNqR25RRjR0Z1ZNUQ</guid></item><item><title>糖尿病前期可以在2年内逆转：当你继续欺骗时，你的身体会产生安静的新陈代谢变化-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/prediabetes-can-be-reversed-within-2-years-the-quiet-metabolic-changes-your-body-makes-when-you-stay-consistent/articleshow/125500852.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prediabetes has become an increasingly important area of focus in public health, largely because it sits at a crossroads between normal metabolic function and type 2 diabetes. It is defined by raised blood glucose levels that fall short of the diagnostic threshold for diabetes, yet indicate a shift in how the body processes sugar. This stage often develops quietly, particularly in urban populations where dietary habits, long work hours and reduced movement are common. Although the condition signals an elevated risk, emerging evidence shows that it remains a phase in which the body can still respond positively to sustained lifestyle improvements. Understanding how reversal occurs and why it often takes around two years helps clarify both the biological process and the practical steps that support long-term change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How metabolic flexibility helps the body reverse prediabetes&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prediabetes develops when the body begins to lose its usual glucose handling efficiency, yet retains enough metabolic flexibility to recover with time and effort. Many people at this stage still show partial insulin sensitivity, particularly in muscle cells, which means that healthier behaviours can help the body use glucose more effectively. By reducing excess calorie intake, improving sleep and incorporating moderate movement across the week, glucose fluctuations become less severe and insulin production faces less pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; These shifts allow the pancreas and liver to adjust gradually rather than react to constant metabolic stress. Recovery is often subtle and may involve extended periods where progress feels slow, although the internal changes accumulate steadily over months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What this means for metabolic recovery:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prediabetes involves impaired but still responsive glucose regulation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Partial insulin sensitivity helps the body react positively to lifestyle adjustments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improvements in diet, sleep and activity reduce the strain on insulin production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recovery unfolds slowly, which explains why noticeable change takes time.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Long term evidence showing &lt;keyword id="28344744" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="prediabetes-reversal" source="Orion"&gt;prediabetes reversal&lt;/keyword&gt; in two years&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A decade-long retrospective cohort study from an urban Indian community &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s40200-025-01790-7" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;published in Journal of Diabetes and Metabolic Disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, examined how prediabetes progressed in real-world conditions. The results demonstrated that many individuals reverted to normal glucose levels within roughly two years when they maintained routine screening and reasonable lifestyle improvements. The study highlighted that dramatic changes were not essential. Instead, the most influential factor was consistency, even when actions were modest. Regular checks kept individuals informed, which helped them stay engaged with their progress, while simple adjustments such as reducing portion sizes or adding short walks had measurable metabolic effects. The study’s timeline of around two years reflects the period needed for pancreatic function, body weight and glucose processing to adapt to healthier patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Key insights from the long-term evidence:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular screening helps people track gradual shifts in blood sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Steady lifestyle adjustments deliver significant metabolic benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Biological changes in glucose control align with a two-year adaptation period.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Community-based data shows that sustained habits outperform short-term interventions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How urban living affects prediabetes reversal&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urban environments create a blend of challenges and opportunities for individuals hoping to reverse prediabetes. Long commutes, high stress and sitting for extended hours often contribute to rising glucose levels. At the same time, cities offer health resources that can support recovery, including nutrition counselling, regular medical facilities, fitness centres and organised screenings. People who manage to integrate small changes into their daily routines, such as replacing processed meals with nutrient-rich alternatives or incorporating regular brisk walking, usually show more stable glucose patterns over time. Even modest shifts create a favourable environment for the body to regulate blood sugar more effectively, especially when combined with periodic check-ups that track progress and encourage accountability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How urban factors influence reversal:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;City living contains risk factors such as inactivity and high stress but also valuable health resources.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Small behavioural shifts, like daily walking, help improve glucose management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to medical guidance and screening increases the likelihood of reversal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Habit formation across two years helps counter the metabolic effects of urban routines.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How the body adapts slowly during prediabetes reversal&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reversing prediabetes takes time because metabolic function adapts gradually, not instantly. When individuals increase physical activity, their muscles become more capable of pulling glucose out of the bloodstream. Meanwhile, long-term improvements in diet reduce stored fat in the liver, lowering insulin resistance and giving the pancreas the support it needs to produce insulin more efficiently. Fat tissue itself undergoes changes, becoming less inflamed and more responsive to hormonal signals that regulate glucose. These internal adjustments require continuous reinforcement, which is why brief bursts of effort followed by lapses tend to halt progress. Consistent behaviour is the most reliable driver of improvement, and the two-year timeframe mirrors the natural pace at which tissues recover healthier function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Important take-homes about long-term adaptation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Muscles, liver and fat tissue depend on repeated signals to improve glucose handling.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Long-term behaviour patterns produce more durable results than short, intense efforts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Insulin sensitivity recovers slowly, which aligns with the two-year reversal trend.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gradual biological readjustment makes consistent lifestyle habits essential.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How shared routines and guidance help sustain improvement&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reversal of prediabetes also depends on the environment surrounding an individual, not just personal habits. Access to supportive community networks, group-based wellness activities and culturally relevant dietary guidance can make lifestyle shifts easier to maintain. Many people benefit from social reinforcement, whether through neighbourhood walking groups, workplace health initiatives or family routines that encourage more balanced meals. These forms of support help individuals stay motivated across the long period required for the body to readjust. Health systems that offer regular follow-up visits, early screening and clear communication further increase the likelihood of improvement, particularly in settings where diabetes risk is widespread and long-term prevention is a public health priority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What strengthens the chance of reversal:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Social support helps people maintain lifestyle changes consistently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Group activities and shared routines create accountability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regular follow-up visits reinforce long-term motivation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Community access to health education strengthens early prevention efforts.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a healthcare professional before making any changes to your diet, medication, or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/diet/could-a-low-glutamate-diet-help-reduce-migraines-for-people-living-with-frequent-headaches/articleshow/125491500.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Could a low-glutamate diet help reduce migraines for people living with frequent headaches&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgJBVV95cUxPNDBoRDFCUVhYeldNZTFWeHVpdGh4akVkNkpreWVLT19uRW9jalRsb2h2NjNMNzU2Q3EyM2hTbXZnQ2I2Skw0ZWhDTGxtQ01xWGpGSDhUMjhrYmVvSzVkSFI0ZkFhYk42V29pZXlSeGg3WG9XeE9kOVF3U1Y0R2hGU0tEcVVZRE1UNFE4cnVlVFBNY2s5LUluNmZDVzB6b3RrWFlXYl9ld05OY3didkZtMHhrdUIwNnhtaU1fUkdBWEF3Q05pSVktTVFUQ2kxcDhTQThaXzI5aXpnT3B5QU1KWGRiS3ZLb19DZ0xxb3VCVkRiaFJFUlZubGFla0JvRVRENkZmc1FYNEo4OVRYa3EtazJXdFNrSHZ5N2dHZ0FJWHZHQ3pXWWxZbDFhN0ktUXVybDVCZEN30gG7AkFVX3lxTE9RS3VnSDE1aEJhLWRaU0c2ZFY4QXpQMHd1eGVLaXdNbTNOdWF6RHc1NWc1UXhqVVNxQ2xKTW51eTlqMkM1Wm5nd0pjUm1uT0ZYUkV1ejVoYmpQejBhZXN2RGxtMW4zd2VIWVJ2LW96em9xVTlucVp4Tmp2NlJBZmhRelktYUFMeW5TbHBFcEtQZlpzSExDVm02UVpEem0zS0RsRTdxb0d1dFQ4X1JiZlpHdERMcTZDb3lDOWVIQ2ZGSl9CdnZvckNaS1JVbzhfRTNxWVRJd0Y4MnI0dmRzaTNpcFpsUDVnam1xUDhwMmc2NEZkUzYtMnE2dm9lNVBDRlRUTDlJd2xjYXpFZUZ4cmtWbm5UOXFyc0VvTUMzV3VFNEtQRjBLWHJMbnZSUW1mVjVMdUotanAxdlRPOA</guid></item><item><title>干细胞疗法帮助AMD患者重拾视力- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251121090736.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;In the United States, age-related macular degeneration is one of the most common causes of permanent vision loss in adults who are 60 and older. It affects the macula, the central region of the retina that contains tightly packed cells used for sharp, detailed color vision.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roughly 20 million adults in the country are living with some form of AMD. People with this condition typically lose the ability to see objects directly in front of them, although their peripheral vision remains intact. Available therapies can slow how the disease progresses, but none of them can restore lost vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exploring a New Cell-Based Approach&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a study published in Cell Stem Cell, scientists tested retinal pigment epithelial stem cells in a phase 1/2a clinical trial. The cells were obtained from adult postmortem eye tissue. These early-stage trials are designed to determine whether a treatment can be safely administered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AMD occurs in two forms: dry and wet. More than 90% of patients have the dry type, which develops when retinal pigment epithelial cells begin to malfunction and eventually die.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the early stages of AMD, these cells no longer work correctly. At more advanced stages, they die and cannot regenerate. As the condition worsens, multiple regions in the central retina lose these essential cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Transplanting Specialized Stem Cells&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the current study, individuals with advanced dry AMD received transplants of specialized stem cells originally sourced from eye-bank tissue. These adult stem cells were limited in function and could only mature into retinal pigment epithelial cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Six participants were given the lowest dose of the treatment (50,000 cells) during an eye surgery. The procedure proved safe, with no serious inflammation or tumor growth reported in any of the patients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Early Signs of Vision Improvement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants also showed vision improvements in the treated eye, while their untreated eye did not show the same changes. This difference suggests that the technique itself may hold therapeutic potential. "Although we were pleased with the safety data, the exciting part was that their vision was also improving," said Rajesh C. Rao, M.D., Leonard G. Miller Professor of Ophthalmology &amp;amp; Visual Sciences, and an associate professor of pathology and human genetics. "We were surprised by the magnitude of vision gain in the most severely affected patients who received the adult stem cell-derived RPE transplants. This level of vision gain has not been seen in this group of patients with advanced dry AMD."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When tested on a standard eye chart, the low-dose group was able to read 21 additional letters one year after treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps in the Clinical Trial&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research team is now monitoring 12 more participants who received higher doses of 150,000 and 250,000 cells. If no safety issues are identified, the investigators plan to move on to later stages of the clinical trial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We are grateful to all our participants who are allowing to better understand whether this intervention is safe enough to be a future therapy," Rao said. "These kinds of NIH-funded studies can help us offer advanced treatments in the field of regenerative medicine, and we are happy we can offer this first-in-human, cutting-edge clinical trial at the University of Michigan."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Age-Related Macular Degeneration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Age-related macular degeneration is a condition that gradually damages the macula, the small but vital area at the back of the eye that supports sharp central vision. The disease typically develops as people get older, and it is more common in individuals over 60.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are two primary forms of AMD. The dry form appears most often and involves the slow breakdown of retinal cells that help the eye process detail and color. The wet form is less common but progresses more quickly and involves abnormal blood vessel growth under the retina.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over time, both types can cause blind spots in central vision, making activities such as reading and identifying faces increasingly difficult. While current treatments can slow the disease, scientists have been searching for ways to restore the lost cells, which is why stem cell research has become a promising direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:31:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9YYV9uZVdfZjFhcDhnOENmT3Y4NlpyMmJrY1Y0aVNZQzB0UFp6Y2xvUTlSUmxyZl9yb2pSN0JaXzNVT21idGtVYnB4UlN6bzBWdmtyUV9SQmJnOG5mMElwclQ4RWU1UGI4QjhWSGxWNA</guid></item><item><title>给予实验性混合治疗的小鼠治愈的1型糖尿病- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/type-1-diabetes-cured-in-mice-given-experimental-hybrid-treatment</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A specially devised hybrid treatment has shown tremendous potential for treating &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/type-1-diabetes-may-be-triggered-by-bacterial-infections-scientists-find"&gt;type 1 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; in mice, scoring full marks at preventing the condition in prediabetic animals and at reversing the condition in animals with fully developed  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="182304" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes the new approach stand out is that it successfully combines immune system cells from both the patient mouse and a donor mouse, encouraging them to live in harmony without a need for &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Immunosuppressive_drug"&gt;immunosuppressive drugs&lt;/a&gt; for at least four months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers behind the work, led by a team from the Stanford School of Medicine, are hopeful the same approach could be successful in humans too. The treatment might also have potential for other procedures where &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/uks-first-liver-transplant-for-advanced-bowel-cancer-removes-all-traces-of-the-disease"&gt;transplants are required&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/breakthrough-diabetes-treatment-may-deliver-insulin-through-a-skin-cream"&gt;Breakthrough Diabetes Treatment May Deliver Insulin Through a Skin Cream&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We believe this approach will be transformative for people with type 1 diabetes or other autoimmune diseases, as well as for those who need solid organ transplants," &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2025/11/type-1-diabetes-cure.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; developmental biologist Seung Kim, from the Stanford School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Type 1 diabetes is caused by the body's own &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/4-out-of-5-autoimmune-patients-are-female-the-x-chromosome-could-explain-why"&gt;immune system malfuncting&lt;/a&gt;, triggering an attack on pancreatic cells called beta islets, which produce insulin. While healthy donor islets can be transplanted into the body, they also risk being attacked, if not completely rejected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_182308" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-182308" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/TransplantAbstract.jpg" alt="Transplant abstract" class="wp-image-182308 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/TransplantAbstract.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/TransplantAbstract-600x520.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-182308" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Animals were given a conditioning treatment to prepare their immune systems for the cell transplant. (Bhagchandani et al., &lt;em&gt;J. Clin. Invest.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this recent experiment, researchers subtly rebooted the mice's immune systems, preparing them before the transplant with an immune system inhibitor, a low dose of radiation, and a few select  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/antibody" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73081" data-postid="182304" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;antibodies&lt;/a&gt;, as well as combining blood  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="182304" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt; and islet cells from another animal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, the transplanted cells weren't attacked as foreign invaders, and the immune system began &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-have-discovered-a-special-type-of-immune-cell-that-slows-aging"&gt;functioning normally&lt;/a&gt; again. While a small subset of islet cells showed some signs of inflammation, this critical tissue also wasn't attacked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We need to not only replace the islets that have been lost but also reset the recipient's immune system to prevent ongoing islet cell destruction," &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2025/11/type-1-diabetes-cure.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Kim. "Creating a hybrid immune system accomplishes both goals."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experiment represents a number of wins. The treated mice had their diabetes prevented or reversed, and none of them developed the &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/10255-graft-vs-host-disease-an-overview-in-bone-marrow-transplant"&gt;graft-versus-host disease&lt;/a&gt; that often occurs in humans when cells are transplanted between people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, mixing donor and recipient immune cells has been shown to work for transplants before, including in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/scitranslmed.aax8863"&gt;previous studies&lt;/a&gt; by some of the same research team, which bodes well for human trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of that said, plenty of challenges remain. For example, islet cells can only be donated after death, and must come from the same person as the blood stem cells. It's also unclear just how many of these cells would be needed for the procedure to be successful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers say they're currently looking at ways of getting more of the donated cells to survive, or figuring out ways of producing them in the lab from &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41392-024-02090-x"&gt;pluripotent human stem cells&lt;/a&gt;. We can't &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-treatment-may-cure-severe-type-1-diabetes-study-finds"&gt;cure type 1 diabetes yet&lt;/a&gt; – but &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/first-of-its-kind-cell-transplant-brings-a-cure-for-diabetes-closer"&gt;we're getting closer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The possibility of translating these findings into humans is very exciting," &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/news/all-news/2025/11/type-1-diabetes-cure.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Kim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The key steps in our study – which result in animals with a hybrid immune system containing cells from both the donor and the recipient – are already being used in the clinic for other conditions."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1172/JCI190034"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Clinical Investigation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:04:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPNll2M09GdzREaDNhMkN3TzdlcHFQSGZBelA5RnVYSWZTb0xXZG82Z1NDLWg2amUtTkFJMUVlRTF6dXZGTkV3WFVudEc5alFuYWk5bTUyazM1bDM1RHQ2UEJhRFRYbzZ2MjNldHRTMmtQNThLakZtRS1Hd0VEVjlCQTlsTThlZzh3bnZTR19TNEI4VEozTmRkUlFn</guid></item><item><title>研究人员发现你的大脑“入睡”的确切时刻–从字面上看–印度防御评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/researchers-exact-moment-brain-falls-sleep/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers from&lt;strong&gt; Imperial College London&lt;/strong&gt; has pinpointed the exact moment when the brain “falls” asleep, marking a sharp drop in brain activity just before sleep sets in. This discovery could improve treatments for sleep disorders and have significant implications for public safety, particularly in high-risk situations like driving.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Until now, sleep was often thought to be a slow transition, much like drifting into a dream. However, according to neuroscientist &lt;strong&gt;Nir Grossman&lt;/strong&gt;, who led the research, the change from wakefulness to sleep happens suddenly, much like falling off a cliff. Using EEG monitoring, the researchers observed a distinct point where brain activity sharply declines, signaling the start of sleep. This shift occurs in the final moments before sleep begins, offering a precise definition of the transition from wakefulness to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Sudden Drop in Brain Activity&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For decades, scientists believed sleep began gradually, with brain activity slowly fading until sleep took over. But Grossman’s team found that the transition is much more dramatic. By monitoring&lt;strong&gt; EEG data&lt;/strong&gt;, they identified a specific moment when brain activity drops sharply, signaling the start of sleep. This sharp decline happens just before sleep sets in and is a clear, measurable point that had previously been hard to define, reports &lt;a href="https://www.popularmechanics.com/science/a69451485/your-brain-literally-falls-asleep/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Popular Mechanics&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This discovery offers a more accurate understanding of how the brain shifts from wakefulness to sleep, providing valuable insight into how we process the transition. Grossman emphasized the importance of this finding, saying, in a study recently published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-02091-1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;The tipping point accurately defines the critical time during the transition from a steady wake state into a steady sleep state.&lt;/em&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Graphical Illustration Of The Computational Framework" class="wp-image-96261" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework.jpg 1980w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg" alt="Graphical Illustration Of The Computational Framework" class="wp-image-96261" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/graphical-illustration-of-the-computational-framework.jpg 1980w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Graphical illustration of the computational framework – © Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Sleep-Onset Disorders and Public Safety&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The new findings have important implications for people suffering from sleep disorders, particularly &lt;strong&gt;those who struggle to fall asleep &lt;/strong&gt;or stay awake during critical activities. &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/how-sleep-deprivation-affects-your-brain/" data-type="post" data-id="76260"&gt;Sleep&lt;/a&gt;-onset disorders, where it takes a long time to fall asleep, can severely impact someone’s health and quality of life. By identifying the exact point when sleep begins, this research could lead to more effective treatments for these disorders, helping individuals to fall asleep faster and enjoy better rest.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Moreover, this discovery has public safety implications. &lt;strong&gt;Sleep deprivation &lt;/strong&gt;can be dangerous, especially in situations where alertness is required, such as driving or operating machinery. Understanding when the brain falls asleep could lead to better ways to monitor and address sleep issues, ultimately reducing the risks associated with sleep-deprived individuals.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt=" Fold Bifurcation Of Eeg Dynamics During Falling Asleep Transition" class="wp-image-96263" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition.jpg 1980w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg" alt=" Fold Bifurcation Of Eeg Dynamics During Falling Asleep Transition" class="wp-image-96263" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/fold-bifurcation-of-eeg-dynamics-during-falling-asleep-transition.jpg 1980w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt; Fold bifurcation of EEG dynamics during falling asleep transition – &lt;em&gt;© Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;The Role of Brain Nuclei in the Sleep Transition&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The process of &lt;strong&gt;falling asleep &lt;/strong&gt;involves more than just a decrease in brain activity; it is also controlled by specific clusters of neurons called nuclei. Some nuclei promote wakefulness, while others are responsible for initiating sleep. As the brain transitions, certain &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4660253/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;nuclei&lt;/a&gt; are turned off, causing a sudden shift in how neurons communicate. This change in neural activity leads to the rapid drop in brain activity observed right before sleep.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One key finding from the study was that the&lt;strong&gt; brain’s occipital cortex&lt;/strong&gt;, which processes visual information, reaches the sleep transition point earlier than the frontal cortex, which is responsible for thinking, memory, and emotional regulation. This explains why some people take longer to fall asleep but experience a quicker shift into sleep once they pass the “&lt;em&gt;falling&lt;/em&gt;” phase. By studying this process, Grossman and his team were able to predict when sleep would occur with remarkable accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQTG11dHhFQUdxbHlTYWVTUGd5WDlnWnYzZnVfMzU3OWdRX2paNGRSVjNOaHRxY2ozRVdhRTNLb3RyMTBQVFJKR0VUZ0RqSFdzZk5TZHpHT3dPQVFqZDFKcjJLeV81MTJkWC1hem5wUjlVRmRiLS1KRnNTNEE1aHBkWg</guid></item><item><title>华盛顿州居民在H5N5感染后死亡- DW</title><link>https://www.dw.com/en/washington-state-resident-dies-after-h5n5-infection/a-74847177</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-tracking-name="rich-text" data-tracking-skip="true" class="c17j8gzx rc0m0op r1ebneao s198y7xq rich-text l1evdo4u blt0baw s16w0xvi rcjjkz7 w128axg5 b1fzgn0z"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person believed to be the first confirmed case of H5N5 avian &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/influenza/t-71362030"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt; in humans has died, health authorities in &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/united-states-of-america/t-19065189"&gt;US&lt;/a&gt; state of Washington said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The deceased was a Grays Harbor County resident, according to the Washington State Department of Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote class="fb-post embed" data-facebook="true" data-href="https://www.facebook.com/photo?fbid=1285430896959179&amp;amp;set=a.221538120015134"&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What have health authorities said?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The department said it would not be releasing specific details relating to the deceased's name, gender or age out of respect for the family's privacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They did confirm that the person was an older adult with pre-existing health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"The risk to the public remains low. No other people involved have tested positive for avian influenza," state health authorities said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Public health officials will continue to monitor anyone who was in close contact with the patient for symptoms to ensure that human-to-human spread has not occurred," the department said and added: "There is no evidence of transmission of this virus between people."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the health department statement, the person had a backyard flock of domestic birds which they said was the likely source of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="vjs-wrapper embed big"&gt;&lt;h2 aria-label="Embedded video — Bird flu wreaks havoc on US poultry farms" class="headline"&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;path d="M14.114 7.599H13.5l.002 4.706h.601l4.582 3.25-.005-11.11zM11.084 4.444l-9.007.002-1.336.797.002 9.514 1.334.793 9.007.006 1.509-.799-.004-9.516z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;Bird flu wreaks havoc on US poultry farms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;video id="video-72067212" controls playsinline="" preload="none" poster="data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAEAAAABCAQAAAC1HAwCAAAAC0lEQVR42mNkYAAAAAYAAjCB0C8AAAAASUVORK5CYII=" data-id="72067212" data-posterurl="https://static.dw.com/image/71985603_605.webp" data-duration="02:36"&gt;&lt;source src="https://hlsvod.dw.com/i/dwtv_video/flv/je/je20250328_Superchickens09E_,AVC_480x270,AVC_512x288,AVC_640x360,AVC_960x540,AVC_1280x720,AVC_1920x1080,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8" type="application/x-mpegURL"&gt;&lt;source src="https://tvdownloaddw-a.akamaihd.net/dwtv_video/flv/je/je20250328_Superchickens09E_AVC_1920x1080.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;p class="vjs-no-js"&gt;To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that &lt;a href="https://videojs.com/html5-video-support/" target="_blank"&gt;supports HTML5 video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What is H5N5 avian flu?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;H5N5 is a sub-type of &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/h5n1-bird-flu-spreading-to-poultry-via-migratory-cranes-germany-denmark-netherlands-usa-europe/a-74527770"&gt;avian flu that is not believed to be a greater threat to human health&lt;/a&gt; than the H5N1 virus that has been behind a wave of 70 reported human infections in the US in 2024 and 2025.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of those have been mild illnesses in workers on dairy and poultry farms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The distinction between H5N5 and H5N1 lies in a protein involved in releasing the virus from an infected cell and promoting spread to surrounding cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the Washington State Department of Health website the first human cases of H5 avian influenza were reported in Washington state in October 2024.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The department says that to date, there is no evidence of person-to-person transmission of avian influenza in Washington state.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Health authorities say birds and other animals infected with avian influenza shed the virus in their saliva, mucous and feces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="vjs-wrapper embed big"&gt;&lt;h2 aria-label="Embedded video — German bird flu outbreak sparks fear among farmers" class="headline"&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;path d="M14.114 7.599H13.5l.002 4.706h.601l4.582 3.25-.005-11.11zM11.084 4.444l-9.007.002-1.336.797.002 9.514 1.334.793 9.007.006 1.509-.799-.004-9.516z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;German bird flu outbreak sparks fear among farmers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;video id="video-74576972" controls playsinline="" preload="none" poster="data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAEAAAABCAQAAAC1HAwCAAAAC0lEQVR42mNkYAAAAAYAAjCB0C8AAAAASUVORK5CYII=" data-id="74576972" data-posterurl="https://static.dw.com/image/74510479_605.webp" data-duration="02:38"&gt;&lt;source src="https://hlsvod.dw.com/i/vps/webvideos/ENG/2025/BUSI/BUSIENG251103_QWIBirdfluCMS_01SMW_,AVC_480x270,AVC_512x288,AVC_640x360,AVC_960x540,AVC_1280x720,AVC_1920x1080,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8" type="application/x-mpegURL"&gt;&lt;source src="https://tvdownloaddw-a.akamaihd.net/vps/webvideos/ENG/2025/BUSI/BUSIENG251103_QWIBirdfluCMS_01SMW_AVC_1920x1080.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;track src="https://www.dw.com/media/subtitles/74598849" srclang="en" label="ENGLISH" default&gt;&lt;p class="vjs-no-js"&gt;To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that &lt;a href="https://videojs.com/html5-video-support/" target="_blank"&gt;supports HTML5 video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/track&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Edited by: Saim Dušan Inayatullah, Karl Sexton&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DW</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 13:10:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQSVZRMjUtTWxyejQ1ZU1oRklvTVZvVDA3QTlYeUhvN0tkcnRGMzA2cUFWNkVsVGlONlY3UU1iREphdU9jejhYWkNCLWZfWXZicFpLcDIzLTBpNnk4dXpFS3dGd09HWTBYVGJIRWZBWXIyVDlncEtHdGJzRlRxa0xnY3FCZ08ybmU0TEtoX9IBjAFBVV95cUxQMWR5c3V4OHhGMmlMc1JhUDQ5WEItRmNYYkF3TExvT0tHaGNoYklFN3JiMm9vV3NXdGhwTFBvYjVjRVVVbmhQUDZmZ2ZzaHRNZkJlQnZ0Um00cDZpTlJ4VEh2ak5uTVRaWmNYUnpqXy03Nll4LXRrU1lsR0d4aEFCamtmSzF6OTFLajJreA</guid></item><item><title>“Fish Pedicures”在TikTok上疯传。皮肤科医生恳求您不要买。-今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2025/11/22/fish-pedicures-viral/87297573007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"Fish are friends, not food," &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=c6mVl6fAxLw" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;animated sharks famously&lt;/a&gt; declare in 2003's &lt;a href="/story/entertainment/movies/2022/07/25/what-kind-of-fish-is-dory-finding-nemo/7829566001/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;"Finding Nemo."&lt;/a&gt; But are they &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/11/11/shay-mitchell-kids-skincare-rini/87200918007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;pedicurists&lt;/a&gt;, too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;On TikTok, &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@sydney.sedrowski/video/7530628992211094814" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;videos have gone viral&lt;/a&gt; of people getting so-called "fish pedicures," often while traveling outside of the U.S. In the videos, people stick their bare feet into tanks of fish, which swarm their toes. The fish then eat away at dead skin cells and calluses, leaving their feet supposedly silky and smooth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7398691/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Originating in Turkey&lt;/a&gt;, the practice has become popular for tourists traveling abroad − and though the videos of their shocked reactions can be entertaining, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/04/14/machine-analyze-skin/83056544007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;dermatologists&lt;/a&gt; encourage travelers not to participate. If not done in a sanitary fashion, these fish pedicures can be seriously dangerous. In the U.S., they've even come under legal scrutiny and are not permitted in multiple states, including &lt;a href="https://simasgovlaw.com/fish-pedicures-are-not-permitted-in-california/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;California&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Plus, there are safer, simpler ways of taking care of your feet that don't involve fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"I don't know why people would do that instead of just exfoliating," says &lt;a href="https://rossiderm.com/pages/dr-rossi" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Anthony Rossi&lt;/a&gt;, a dermatologist and surgeon who hosts the podcast &lt;a href="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=83224X1595658&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fpodcasts.apple.com%2Fus%2Fpodcast%2F1-how-your-lifestyle-shapes-skin-health%2Fid1773787097%3Fi%3D1000673975435&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.usatoday.com%2Fstory%2Flife%2Fhealth-wellness%2F2025%2F11%2F22%2Ffish-pedicures-viral%2F87297573007%2F" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-v-afl data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;"Give Good Face: Clean Clinical Science."&lt;/a&gt; "If you're on vacation and you see something and it looks interesting, it doesn't mean you should do it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Why viral 'fish pedicures' are dangerous&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Removing dead skin cells from feet isn't a bad idea. Doing so allows fresh, newer skin underneath to shine through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;When people get a fish pedicure, the fish essentially nibble away at this dead layer − basically exfoliating like a scrub would.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="gnt_em gnt_em_img"&gt;&lt;img class="gnt_em_img_i" fetchpriority="high" data-g-r="lazy" data-gl-src="/gcdn/authoring/authoring-images/2025/11/16/USAT/87299356007-getty-images-601153410-1.jpg?width=660&amp;amp;height=419&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp" data-gl-srcset="/gcdn/authoring/authoring-images/2025/11/16/USAT/87299356007-getty-images-601153410-1.jpg?width=1320&amp;amp;height=838&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp 2x" decoding="async" alt='"Fish pedicures" are viral online. Dermatologists beg you not to get one.'&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_em_img_ccw gnt_em_img_ccw__cap gnt_em_img_ccw__crd" data-c-caption='"Fish pedicures" are viral online. Dermatologists beg you not to get one.' data-c-credit="Baona, Getty Images"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The problem is that, often, it's hard to tell if the fish tanks are sanitary. You don't know what kind of bacteria the fish could be carrying. This can prove especially dangerous if you get a fish pedicure while unknowingly having a cut or opening in your skin. The water these fish swim in can be contaminated, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"You can get mycobacterium, which is like a nasty infection," Rossi says. "Vibrio is a nasty infection, and there have been cases of these infectious outbreaks linked to these fish spas."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Oftentimes too, the same fish are used over and over again for different people's pedicures. So, you're not just getting germs and bacteria from them, but also from other people's feet the fish have feasted on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"These fish, they can harbor bacteria, and they can't be disinfected," dermatologist &lt;a href="https://www.brookejeffymd.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Brooke Jeffy&lt;/a&gt; says. "So, if it's exposed to some kind of infection or germ in one person, it's feasible that they could spread something. The fish themselves can also harbor certain bacteria, which can be really pathogenic for humans as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Not to mention the possible ethical concerns. Some fish pedicure providers have been accused of intentionally starving fish so they're hungry enough to eat dead foot skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;Don't get a 'fish pedicure.' Do this instead.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;What's important to note, Jeffy says, is the same benefits of a fish pedicure can also be achieved through tried-and-true exfoliation techniques.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"Better choices would of course be using typical chemical exfoliants," she says. Physical exfoliators and just good old fashioned moisturizer, she adds, also do the trick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 13:05:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxON1h0b3FZZmNlR0pqeTdUWFRJRHUteXNlVk5DUlQ5dmJLMWRfdFY3OEFVZzY1amxJMGszWUswa1hwY0hHdkRRZFFLYXdkOGRTQ1BWckhfSTZTdmM4V010eDVEd2Y2b0kycXkwQmloazMxMEZNdnR6RlVYZE5IbTdqYm1pRW0tdlh6SW9GNkdnTXdaa1NYcGFBUzd2eTQ</guid></item></channel></rss>