<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>RFK Jr.周末试图破坏儿童疫苗接种计划- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/rfk-jr-tried-to-wreck-the-childhood-vaccine-schedule-over-the-weekend-2000702477</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;Vaccines are in more danger than ever before. Over the weekend, Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. nearly succeeded at shrinking down the childhood vaccine schedule.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On Saturday, Politico &lt;a href="https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/20/rfk-kennedy-danish-vaccine-schedule-denmark-00701999"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; that Kennedy canceled a press conference set for Friday afternoon where he would have formally advised that parents follow the vaccine schedule implemented in Denmark—a system with several fewer vaccine recommendations. Experts have largely opposed the proposed change, noting that the two countries are vastly different from each other. RFK Jr. reportedly balked at the last second due to concerns the decision would face political and legal challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;A near miss&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;RFK Jr. and his allies have been signaling this potential change for quite some time.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At the last meeting of the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices in early December, Tracy Beth Høeg, acting director of the FDA’s Center for Drug Evaluation and Research (CDER), gave a presentation about Denmark’s vaccine schedule. Høeg and others have argued that the U.S. should consider adopting Denmark’s schedule. Denmark universally recommends childhood vaccines for &lt;a href="https://vaccine-schedule.ecdc.europa.eu/Scheduler/ByCountry?SelectedCountryId=58&amp;amp;IncludeChildAgeGroup=true&amp;amp;IncludeChildAgeGroup=false&amp;amp;IncludeAdultAgeGroup=false"&gt;10 diseases&lt;/a&gt;, whereas the U.S. universally recommends vaccines for &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/hcp/imz-schedules/child-adolescent-age.html"&gt;16 diseases&lt;/a&gt; (that number was 17 until the recent ACIP-led change to &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/we-are-doing-harm-rfk-jr-s-acip-guts-universal-hep-b-vaccination-at-birth-2000695747"&gt;revoke&lt;/a&gt; its recommendation for the hepatitis B vaccine).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Soon after, President Donald Trump stated that he would push to change the U.S. vaccine schedule to match that of other “peer countries” and &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/12/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-begins-process-to-align-u-s-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/"&gt;issued&lt;/a&gt; an executive order on December 5 to that effect. This set the stage for HHS last Thursday to announce a press conference for the next day, where RFK Jr. was expected to officially recommend the Danish vaccine schedule as an alternative for parents in the U.S. to follow.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;But it seems the administration grew cold feet mere hours after it announced the press conference. An anonymous senior HHS official told Politico that the HHS Office of the General Counsel deemed that the abrupt change would likely result in a successful lawsuit against the agency. A second official added that the decision would be “politically risky.”&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;An HHS spokesperson told Gizmodo that any reasons for the press conference’s cancellation not provided by HHS are “pure speculation.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;A lack of reason&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;To be clear, Kennedy and others have never presented a reasonable case for such a sweeping change to the vaccine schedule.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;There is no credible evidence that the amount or timing of vaccines currently recommended in the U.S. poses a health risk to children—a reality &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccine-safety/about/multiples.html#:~:text=Scientific%20data%20show,vaccines%20on%20time."&gt;still acknowledged&lt;/a&gt; by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (for now). Some anti-vaccination proponents have also argued that specific ingredients commonly included in vaccines, such as aluminum, could be dangerous if given repeatedly, but the majority of studies have not found any such risk, including one &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-25-00997"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; just this past summer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Experts have also &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/19/denmark-vaccine-schedule-vs-us/"&gt;pointed out&lt;/a&gt; that while Denmark does recommend fewer vaccines in general than the U.S., there are important reasons why this schedule isn’t easily transferable to the latter. For one, Denmark has a universal health care system that’s much more robust than the U.S.’s fragmented system. This includes improved screening for vaccine-preventable diseases like hepatitis B. Notably, the U.S. once tried to vaccinate only high-risk groups for hepatitis B but eventually switched to a universal system after cases failed to significantly decline; this approach then helped dramatically reduce new infections, particularly among newborns.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leaving that aside, plenty of other high-income countries are much closer to the U.S. in the number of vaccines they recommend to their residents, including &lt;a href="https://substack.com/inbox/post/182063328?r=1qy0gl&amp;amp;utm_campaign=post&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;showWelcomeOnShare=true&amp;amp;triedRedirect=true#:~:text=Canada%2C%20Australia%2C%20Germany%2C%20France%2C%20and%20Japan%20all%20have%20schedules%20covering%2014%2D16%20diseases"&gt;Canada, Germany, and Japan&lt;/a&gt;, to name a few. Some countries are also following the U.S.’s example and adding more vaccines to their schedule, such as the U.K., which will &lt;a href="https://www.gov.wales/routine-varicella-chickenpox-vaccination-young-children-1-january-2026-whc2025046-html#:~:text=The%20NHS%20in%20Wales%20will%20introduce%20a,One%20dose%20of%20MMRV%20at%20this%20appointment"&gt;introduce&lt;/a&gt; the chickenpox vaccine to its routine starting next year.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Even health officials in Denmark are baffled by the attempt to use the country as justification for Kennedy’s trimming of the U.S. schedule.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“It’s not at all fair to say look at Denmark unless you can match the other characteristics of Denmark,” Anders Hviid, the lead researcher on vaccine safety and effectiveness at the Statens Serum Institut (Denmark’s equivalent to the CDC), &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/19/health/kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark.html"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; the New York Times Friday. “It is surreal, and it is difficult, from a Danish perspective, to understand what’s going on.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It’s certainly possible that some vaccines aren’t or will eventually not be worthwhile for children in the U.S. to routinely receive. But any changes should be carefully weighed and discussed by actual health experts and researchers, not abruptly implemented under the radar on a Friday afternoon by politicians who have a clear anti-vaccine bias like RFK Jr.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, while Kennedy may have been stymied this time, it’s almost certain that this won’t be his last such attempt.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:20:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxQSDJ3ajdMcVdsbjZkODVHRnFKWmFJODlPNmpFTFhYMUNtdjA0ZFZTeENYdV9tRklfRkd0U1c2Y29WYkk0RjNmcVU1ZUlsOXRhZ3lPcHUyNTZZcWd0aU14ZkJ3TlctZ0ZpUWRuLTF3RXhSa2dybXEwektLRGlZeUJuTmp3WkJGS1hSQno1ZDBNMXhSdHRPZl9iNXdMZldnbkZ4UlE</guid></item><item><title>医生警告90 ％的心脏病发作始于常见的早晨习惯- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/heart-attack-morning-habit-rushing-doctor-warning-080357-20251222</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Keeping on top of your health can feel overwhelming and complicated, but according to one doctor, there's a very simple change you can make to have a huge impact on your overall health and reduce the risk of a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;While you might not know where to start, it turns out there's one morning habit which is attributed to around 90 percent of heart attacks, and it has absolutely nothing to do with how much cholesterol you're eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Doctor Sana Sadoxai regularly takes to &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/tiktok"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt; to share health advice with her 42,000 followers, and recently she revealed just how much your first moves in the morning matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Explaining how much of an impact your lifestyle can have on your chance of suffering a heart attack, she said, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/im-doctor-90-heart-attacks-36386852"&gt;as per&lt;/a&gt; the Mirror: "The real danger starts the moment you wake up and stay still."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;This one habit could be impacting your health (Getty Stock Image)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; professional went on to say 'most people go from bed to phone, to sitting, to rushing out', which she explains means the body is kept in a 'low movement, high inflammation state'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;While you might not understand exactly what that means, Dr Sadoxai says: "This one habit secretly accelerates insulin resistance, belly fat accumulation, high blood pressure, silent inflammation, and metabolic dysfunction, all of which dramatically increase the risk of early heart attacks, especially if you are overweight or obese."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;According to both the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/nhs"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.bhf.org.uk/informationsupport/risk-factors/obesity#:~:text=with%20your%20weight-,How%20does%20obesity%20increase%20the%20risk%20of%20heart%20and%20circulatory,too%20much%20visceral%20fat%20can:"&gt;British Heart Foundation&lt;/a&gt;, being obese significantly increases your chance of having a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;So, what can you do about it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Well, as Dr Sadoxai explains, moving first thing in the morning is one simple change you can make that will make all the difference to your overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;A small change could dramatically reduce your risk of heart attack (Getty Stock Image)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Just five to seven minutes of morning movement - brisk walking, stretching, breathing exercises - boosts circulation, activates metabolism, stabilises sugar levels, and protects your heart more than people realise," she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Your weight, your metabolism, and your heart are deeply connected, ignoring this morning habit is a silent threat. Changing it is lifesaving."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The doctor concluded the video with a stark warning for anyone who might already be edging close to the danger zone, telling her followers: "If you're struggling with obesity, stubborn belly fat, breathlessness, diabetes, or fatigue, these are early metabolic warning signs you should not ignore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Take control before it becomes a cardiac risk."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Dr Sadoxai's advice clearly had an impact on her followers, with one commenting: "Basically getting up and rushing to work is killing us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:14:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNR2lkZ3hGaGxscXRWZ1cwT20yNkxIZjY3WkpYcVVtWVNoZXlIZENpMnJncTFJb0xZci1rVVc5bWxqX01VYnpvZHM2aDJjbkVyZHZrcU1raGhpSEpYQ2NWcHNlZDlOYk5ScWdOZUdneWF2QkxIX29xWmxsWTc3MVQ1RWRCWjlfdXlpcWNpS1lmUnRMV1poV3F1OWN3LS1BbHZiU2VaMg</guid></item><item><title>流感季节正在加剧，一些专家“非常担心” - CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/flu-season-2025-experts-pretty-worried/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Doctors and scientists say this year's influenza season could be tougher than usual. A new version of the flu virus, called H3N2, is spreading quickly. At the same time, fewer people are getting &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/kids-flu-covid-shots-fall-2025-vaccine-guidance-shifts/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;flu shots&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This flu season is no joke. We are seeing more cases than we would expect for this time of year," Dr. Amanda Kravitz, a pediatrician at Weill Cornell Medicine in New York, said on "CBS Mornings." Specifically, she explained, "we are seeing influenza A, and within influenza A we are seeing a subtype or variant called H3N2."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's pretty likely to be an H3N2-dominated flu season," said Jesse Bloom, a scientist at the Fred Hutchinson Cancer Center who studies viral evolution. "I don't see any reason to think that this is an unprecedentedly bad one, but current indicators are that it may be substantially more severe than the typical winter flu season."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bloom said the H3N2 virus has changed just enough to make it harder for people's immune systems to recognize, but a flu shot could still help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Getting the vaccine is something that people, particularly those who are in high-risk groups, can do," he explained. "It's not going to eliminate their chance of getting infected, but it does mitigate their risk."&lt;/p&gt;

    
    &lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;A changing virus&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other experts share Bloom's concern. "I would say pretty worried," said Dr. Helen Chu, a flu expert at the University of Washington. "Based on the U.K. and Japan data, it's looking like it's causing a lot of cases of flu and hospitalizations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said flu activity "is starting everywhere right now," overlapping with RSV but coming before a likely winter COVID-19 wave. &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/flu-vaccine-providing-important-protection-despite-new-subclade" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Early flu vaccine data from other countries&lt;/a&gt; show good protection at first, around 70% in children, but that may not last. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Total season effectiveness is probably going to actually be much, much lower," Chu warned, because immunity fades over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trevor Bedford, who also studies viral evolution at the Fred Hutchinson Cancer Center, said H3N2 tends to evolve faster than other influenza strains. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I expect more H3 incidence than the typical year and poorer vaccine effectiveness," he said. These large "jumps" in how the virus appears to our immune system usually occur every three to four years, he explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.publichealth.columbia.edu/profile/stephen-s-morse-phd" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Stephen Morse&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease epidemiologist at Columbia University, noted that influenza's behavior still defies confident forecasting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Many excellent scientists have come to grief trying to predict what influenza will do — consider 1976," he said, referring to a year with a &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2686218/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;notorious scare&lt;/a&gt; over a swine flu outbreak that didn't end up spreading widely. He added that the emergence of the H3N2 K subclade was "one of those surprises," and while surveillance detected it quickly, "the bad news is that we weren't really prepared for it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why that matters: H3N2 is known for causing tougher flu seasons, especially for seniors. The new strain has changed in ways that make it harder for the immune system to recognize, so more people may get sick and need hospital care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The flu vaccine still helps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with these changes, doctors say the annual flu shot is still the best protection available. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The match to H1N1 and flu B is expected to be good," said Richard Webby, director of the World Health Organization Collaborating Centre for Studies on the Ecology of Influenza in Animals and Birds. "Even though we are expecting a H3N2 mismatch, vaccine effectiveness doesn't always correlate with vaccine match. … Bottom line, still a good idea to get the vaccine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early-season data from the U.K. suggest the flu vaccine is still helping prevent severe illness, especially in children, even with the H3N2 mismatch. Protection in adults appears more modest and is expected to decline over time. Experts stress that flu vaccines are designed mainly to reduce severe disease, hospitalizations, and deaths — not necessarily to prevent every infection.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Gregory Gray, a professor of infectious disease epidemiology at the University of Texas Medical Branch, added that people who work with animals should also be vaccinated. "Persons working with cattle, poultry, and pigs should receive their annual influenza vaccine," he said. That helps stop human viruses from mixing with animal ones and creating new strains that could be dangerous to both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morse also underscored the value of vaccination despite the virus's unpredictability. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I still advocate the annual influenza vaccine… It's still a good precaution," he said, pointing out that flu shots help protect against multiple circulating viruses, not just H3N2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Flu symptoms to watch for, and what you can do&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC estimates there have been 4.6 million flu cases across the U.S. since this season began, and 1,900 patients have died from it, including at least three children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There are tons of these cases throughout the country, and it's causing a very, very severe flu," Kravitz said. "Symptoms that are very intense, they come on really, really rapidly. It's very contagious, so it is spreading quickly through communities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu is often accompanied by "high, high fevers, like 103, 104 degrees Fahrenheit," as well as body aches and cough, Kravitz said. In addition, she added, "we see vomiting in children this year, specifically with this variant of the flu."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She advised parents to help keep their child hydrated, and "if the symptoms last a long time, more than four or five days, especially that high fever, it's a good idea to call their pediatrician."&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc5" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",5]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experts say there's no need to panic, but it's important to prepare. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Get your vaccine," Chu said. "It's still not too late." The shot helps protect against severe illness and may even give "some cross protection against H5N1 as well," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors also stress the importance of early testing and treatment. Antiviral medications like Tamiflu and Xofluza still work against the flu strains circulating this season, including H3N2, but they work best when started within the first couple of days of symptoms — especially for older adults, young children, pregnant people, and those with chronic health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gray said the country needs better flu testing and more vaccines for humans and livestock. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Webby summed it up simply: "It's more of the same: vaccination, hygiene, and keeping an eye out for anything unusual."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bird flu still rare, but worth watching&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first human case of a bird flu strain, H5N5, was recently reported &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/washington-resident-dies-rare-bird-flu-strain/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;in Washington state&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. It has not spread to others, but scientists are watching closely. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The risk to the general public from the H5N1 virus is still very low," Webby said. "But an H5 pandemic could easily make the COVID-19 pandemic look like a cake walk."&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc6" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",6]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chu said fall bird migrations make this the time of year when cases in birds, and sometimes in people, tend to rise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is the time of year when we see the H5 cases," she said. "But a lot of the surveillance programs have been defunded, so in Washington state, there's not been as much as in years past."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morse warned that gaps in surveillance, especially in agriculture, leave room for dangerous blind spots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Surveillance is still crucial. It needs to be sustained. … Agriculture especially has to do much more," he said, noting that past outbreaks in pigs and cattle were missed until they were well underway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say avian flu remains a low risk for most people right now, but it is a low-probability, high-impact threat that requires close monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;

    

                  
        
    
  
    
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 17:04:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE5pMzRGRl9RV3I1QmVqRzFBbjUwalFBR0R0a2o5UFpiWWZEd1RCZFVqdl96cm9PMWhtRGdvUUxuRGlTVkp3aU1fTTJQZ3ZVVEZTVG1Vbk0tR0JuSF9EVUhIUE9wSC1uNkdrOVBZaDJyVEVCMk11Y0hn0gF8QVVfeXFMTVNPWVF6eno3WVoxOFV6NkdSQmI3QnJoN3I1WEtMN2o5Z0pkSWdLUTR4d2NaMXhKam1GdW5YZ1lfZi1OTG4wVnZZTHItS1BZNVhNZkhvaHVrTUZhX1NmZEUtaHEyUzB0ZWp0Zm1Hc3dxdlktWTBZR1AzRW8xTA</guid></item><item><title>神经科学研究员：我用来开启一天美好心情的增强多巴胺早晨活动- CNBC</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/12/22/neuroscience-researcher-my-top-dopamine-boosting-morning-routine.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-articleBody--AEqcE" id="MakeItRegularArticle-ArticleBody-5" data-module="ArticleBody" data-test="articleBody-1" data-analytics="MakeItRegularArticle-articleBody-5-1"&gt;&lt;span class="HighlightShare-styles-makeit-hidden--MFwCR"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We often underestimate how much our &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/10/21/arthur-brooks-leading-happiness-experts-6-step-morning-routine.html"&gt;morning rituals&lt;/a&gt; can set the tone for the rest of the day. When you prioritize activities that spark a natural dopamine release, you aren't just waking up — you're essentially giving your brain a head start on feeling motivated and balanced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Dopamine is a neurotransmitter, which is a chemical released by brain cells, and it's mostly involved in motivation, learning and reinforcement," says &lt;a href="https://www.miasoviero.com/about" target="_blank"&gt;Mia Soviero&lt;/a&gt;, a neuroscience researcher who conducted research at&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;NYU Langone Health and Columbia University's Zuckerman Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It isn't just about feeling good. It's mostly about learning and motivating you. So, it helps our brain understand what actions are worth repeating and what habits we should have in our lives that we should strengthen," says Soviero, who also founded the nonprofit &lt;a href="https://www.miasoviero.com/entrepreneurship" target="_blank"&gt;Research Girl, Inc&lt;/a&gt; to help aspiring science researchers receive more opportunities in their field of interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A common misconception is that dopamine levels are always supposed to be boosted, Soviero says: Neurotransmitter levels are meant to fluctuate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We don't want to always have really high dopamine levels, but we do want to have a healthy dopamine system," she says. "You just want to build these good patterns in dopamine, where dopamine is able to be released the way it's supposed to."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's how Soviero structures her mornings to keep her dopamine system healthy, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;A neuroscience researcher's dopamine-boosting morning routine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Step 1: Exposure to sunlight&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soviero's ideal morning routine for the best mood starts the night before: &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/09/15/3-habits-to-improve-your-quality-of-sleep.html"&gt;Getting adequate sleep&lt;/a&gt; sets the tone for the next day, she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, "I make sure that when I wake up, I get exposure to some light in the morning," she says. "Opening your curtains in the morning and getting sunlight on your face for a few minutes have actually been scientifically proven to reduce depressive symptoms, &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/newsletter_article/shining-a-light-on-winter-depression" target="_blank"&gt;especially if you have seasonal depression&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sunlight exposure directly affects the area of your brain that controls your body's internal clock, or your circadian rhythm, according to &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/newsletter_article/shining-a-light-on-winter-depression" target="_blank"&gt;Harvard Health Publishing&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not getting enough exposure to sunlight each day "can cause your brain to produce too much of the sleep hormone melatonin and to release less serotonin, the feel-good brain chemical that affects mood. The result of this chemical imbalance? You feel low and lethargic," the health blog states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Step 2: Sudoku&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soviero makes time in her mornings to do "small, meaningful activities" like completing a daily Sudoku puzzle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's a great way to kick off the day with a little dopamine from doing a puzzle. It's that feel-good chemical from achieving [it]," she says. "Novelty and new things that you aren't expecting that are good can increase dopamine levels in the brain and contribute to dopamine health. So that's why puzzles are great."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Solving crossword puzzles and physical puzzles can have the same effects on your brain, Soviero says: &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/22581-dopamine" target="_blank"&gt;The brain has a reward system that boosts dopamine&lt;/a&gt; when "something unexpectedly good happens, and then decreases when something worse than expected happens."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This means that evolutionarily, we would strive for goals in the hopes that we'd get this feel good chemical as a reward," she says. "So when you do something, [like] learning a new skill, and you're surprisingly good at it, you get this influx of dopamine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Step 3: Text a friend&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each morning, Soviero practices a simple and significant form of social connection: texting a friend. "I'll send a text to my friends [like], 'Hey, good morning. How are you doing today?'" she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Humans are biologically wired for connections," Soviero adds. "When you get to make that human connection, it's scientifically proven to boost your mood because that's what we're supposed to be doing." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spending too much time without interacting with close loved ones like friends and family can harm your health, she says. Being socially isolated and feeling lonely can increase a person's risk of developing heart disease, dementia, depression and other chronic conditions, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/social-connectedness/risk-factors/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Connecting with others is "really healthy, not only for your brain but also for your body," Soviero says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to give your kids the ultimate advantage?&lt;/strong&gt; Sign up for CNBC's new online course, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://smarter.cnbcmakeit.com/p/how-to-raise-financially-smart-kids?utm_source=cnbc&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=makeitarticle&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=bottom" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Raise Financially Smart Kids&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Learn how to build healthy financial habits today to set your children up for greater success in the future. Use coupon code EARLYBIRD for 30% off. Offer valid from Dec. 8 to Dec. 22, 2025. Terms apply.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-relatedContent--nvEkA" id="MakeItRegularArticle-RelatedContent-1"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-container--UeiCK"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-nonCollapsibleContent--jmjdo"&gt;&lt;h2 class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-header--DqhoP"&gt;Take control of your money with CNBC Select &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CNBC Select is editorially independent and may earn a commission from affiliate partners on links.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="ArticleBody-MobileAdhesion" class="MobileAdhesion-container" data-module="mps-slot"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNBC</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 16:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNMlJlaEFqY3FWMUZTNUFwNWdobUNuTXNaVU9jd0RqenhOQXljZ1BFb0laZ2w2SzhvTnNJMHF6amJqUU84RGgxWFliLS1leU1JRHFhSXI1cE1YRGNaRWcySnpFVzlCUnVaa21ybUdPUUZLQ1Vid3MwMDZUci03YVk5YVd4WjBiY1Z3ckp1VWtyYm1sMDh1THlILU4xTm14UmpnTFpJ0gGoAUFVX3lxTFB1c25fTnMxMU5fMDRnZG90dVlqc1gwSVVkWW81dlpKM1pSZ0lJODZfV0RsSl9QRVl4MndNM0JLMVc2M2cwM19UdFJyaEZRZjdjak9ZVlJ6bjFtSHZRMWx3dlpIc3N1c2FaeU9OeEx6YUxDa19tUFlfTHRGSVBlOWZtaVM4X1NwRFVlWVRGZVVscWh3dkxKRjl4Qk1aMUlvMkVZVGpPS2s0cw</guid></item><item><title>“每个人都得了流感。“医生说，儿童病例迅速飙升。-《波士顿环球报》</title><link>https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/12/22/metro/super-flu-virus-children-kids/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.massgeneral.org/children" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.massgeneral.org/children"&gt;Mass General Brigham for Children&lt;/a&gt; is seeing a similar pattern. Dr. Ari Cohen, chief of pediatric emergency medicine, said flu has become the dominant virus sending children and teenagers to the emergency department in the past two weeks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Everybody’s got the flu,” Cohen said. “That’s really what it seems like right now.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Flu activity is picking up across the country, with several states, including New York and Rhode Island, experiencing “very high” rates of flu-like illness; Connecticut and Massachusetts are listed as “high,” according to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/usmap.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/usmap.html"&gt;the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;In Massachusetts, the share of all emergency room visits that resulted in a patient being hospitalized with flu stood at 1.9 percent as of Dec. 13, more than double the rate at this time last year. And outpatient visits to healthcare providers for flu-like illness reached 4.9 percent, up from 2.8 percent the previous week, according to &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/influenza-reporting" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/influenza-reporting"&gt;the state’s weekly flu dashboard&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mwra.com/biobot/biobotdata.htm" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mwra.com/biobot/biobotdata.htm"&gt;Levels of COVID-19&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/respiratory-illness-reporting" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mass.gov/info-details/respiratory-illness-reporting"&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt; and across the country remain low. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Dr. Larry Madoff, medical director of the Massachusetts Department of Public Health’s Bureau of Infectious Disease and Laboratory Sciences, said flu activity for the general population is rising as expected for this time of year.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Every flu season is different, but this is typically when we start to see an increase in influenza activity,” Madoff said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The surge in pediatric emergency visits comes as influenza A continues to dominate nationally. Public health officials are closely monitoring a newer flu strain known as &lt;a href="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/11/18/metro/new-flu-strain-massachusetts-subclade-k/#bgmp-comments" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.bostonglobe.com/2025/11/18/metro/new-flu-strain-massachusetts-subclade-k/#bgmp-comments"&gt;subclade K&lt;/a&gt;, a subvariant of the H3N2 subtype of influenza A that has drawn attention for driving an earlier-than-usual spike in flu cases &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/europe/news/item/17-12-2025-more-than-half-of-who-european-region-experiencing-intense--early-influenza-season-driven-by-new-strain" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.who.int/europe/news/item/17-12-2025-more-than-half-of-who-european-region-experiencing-intense--early-influenza-season-driven-by-new-strain"&gt;in the UK and several other countries&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Madoff said it is still too early to confirm how widespread subclade K is in Massachusetts because there is not yet enough sequencing data from state laboratories. However, most flu cases identified in Massachusetts so far this season are H3N2, and nationally, about 70 to 80 percent of sequenced H3N2 samples belong to subclade K.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“We fully expect that those will be part of that subclade,” Madoff said, adding that more detailed state data is expected soon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Clinicians emphasized that specific subclades do not change how patients are treated in emergency settings. Hospitals typically test only for influenza A or B, not for subtypes or subclades.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Clinically, it doesn’t change anything I do,” Cohen said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Doctors say children arriving in emergency departments this season are often experiencing high fevers — frequently 103 degrees or higher — along with headaches, body aches, congestion, coughing, and fatigue. Teenagers and older adolescents often present with intense achiness and exhaustion, while younger children are more likely to struggle with respiratory symptoms, clinicians said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Despite the sudden increase in emergency visits for influenza, clinicians say the surge appears to be driven by the number of children getting sick rather than a clear increase in severity. Dehydration and breathing difficulties remain the most concerning symptoms, particularly for infants and children with underlying health conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Public health officials are also watching flu vaccination rates, which lag behind recent years. About one in three Massachusetts residents has received a flu shot this season, according to Madoff — lower than health officials would like to see.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Doctors say vaccination can make a significant difference even when it does not prevent infection entirely, reducing the likelihood that children will need emergency care or hospitalization.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It’s not too late to get vaccinated,” Madoff said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Madoff and Cohen say mixed messaging around vaccines may be contributing to lower uptake.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“When you have national bodies questioning the utility and efficacy of vaccines, people who are on the borderline are going to choose not to get them,” said Madoff.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Cohen said he is seeing the effects firsthand, with there being fewer vaccinated children in the emergency department.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“I think there’s probably vaccine fatigue,” said Cohen. “There are just so many vaccines out there, and especially with COVID, a lot of people feel like they’re over it. But we know the flu kills every year. We know the best protection out there is the flu vaccine.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;As cases rise, clinicians are urging families to focus on supportive care at home when appropriate — and to know when emergency care is truly needed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;McCoy also cautioned that emergency departments have been busy in recent days, with long wait times reported across the state. She urged families to seek emergency care for serious symptoms such as breathing difficulties or dehydration, but to consider urgent care or their pediatrician for milder illness when possible. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;For children, she recommends frequent, small amounts of fluids to prevent dehydration, including electrolyte drinks, along with saline nasal spray and weight-based acetaminophen or ibuprofen to reduce fever and body aches. Honey can help soothe coughs in children over 1  year old.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;By contrast, over-the-counter decongestants, combination cold formulas, and cough suppressants provide little benefit for young children and can cause side effects such as jitteriness, sleep problems, increased heart rate, or stomach upset, McCoy said. She said antibiotics do not treat viral infections like the flu and should only be used for confirmed bacterial infections.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Prescription antiviral medications such as Tamiflu may be helpful for certain patients — particularly young children and those with underlying health conditions. These medications do not cure the flu but can reduce the risk of complications and be especially beneficial for those with underlying health conditions. They should be taken in addition to the vaccination, according to McCoy and Madoff.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Families should seek emergency care if a child has difficulty breathing, signs of dehydration, confusion or lethargy, bluish lips or face, or persistent vomiting that prevents fluids. Children with milder symptoms who are drinking fluids and breathing comfortably can often be cared for at home or seen by a pediatrician or urgent care provider.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;As flu season continues, doctors say the message is one of awareness rather than alarm: get vaccinated, stay home when sick, and seek care when warning signs appear.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Sadaf Tokhi can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:sadaf.tokhi@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;sadaf.tokhi@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOLVVmN2xPQlpVMkxubkF0aEVfRWNwN2hJSVl0TlJUaW5aVzBsZjR5RVlnbkdibUNiNVVaUG0yNG85ODBHZzJIY3pHaVhmam16VG9NOUlsZ1NqZTdFZVQ0dTY3N1JqUnplcHR1T0o4TXprVTdtNTFZMEY1d3Y1RTNpYw</guid></item><item><title>一种新药可以在记忆丧失开始之前阻止阿尔茨海默氏症- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251222080119.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;An experimental drug developed at Northwestern University has demonstrated further promise as an early intervention for Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a new study, Northwestern scientists identified a previously unknown highly toxic sub-species of amyloid beta oligomers -- toxic clusters of peptides -- that appear to drive several of the brain's earliest changes, including neuronal dysfunction, inflammation and activation of immune cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The experimental drug, a small-molecule compound called NU-9, decreased this toxic amyloid beta oligomersubtype and dramatically reduced the damage it causes in a mouse model of Alzheimer's disease. By addressing these changes at the onset of Alzheimer's disease, the researchers are hopeful NU-9 potentially could prevent, or significantly delay, the cascade of toxic events that ultimately destroy neurons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings point to a potential new strategy for targeting the disease in its earliest stages -- before cognitive decline and other debilitating symptoms take hold.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study will be published on Dec. 18 in Alzheimer's and Dementia: The Journal of the Alzheimer's Association.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Alzheimer's disease begins decades before its symptoms appear, with early events like toxic amyloid beta oligomers accumulating inside neurons and glial cells becoming reactive long before memory loss is apparent," said Northwestern's Daniel Kranz, the study's first author. "By the time symptoms emerge, the underlying pathology is already advanced. This is likely a major reason many clinical trials have failed. They start far too late. In our study, we administered NU-9 before symptom onset, modeling this early, pre-symptomatic window."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kranz is a recent Ph.D. graduate from the Interdisciplinary Biological Sciences (IBiS) program at Northwestern's Weinberg College of Arts and Sciences, where he is advised by corresponding author William Klein. An expert on Alzheimer's disease, Klein is a professor of neurobiology at Weinberg and a cofounder of Acumen Pharmaceuticals, which has developed a therapeutic monoclonal antibody currently in clinical trials that targets the subtype of amyloid beta oligomers identified in the study. Richard Silverman, a key co-author of the study, invented NU-9. Silverman, who previously invented pregabalin (Lyrica) to treat fibromyalgia, nerve pain and epilepsy, is the Patrick G. Ryan/Aon Professor in Weinberg's Department of Chemistry and founder of Akava Therapeutics, a startup company commercializing NU-9 (now called AKV9).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The promise of NU-9&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Conceived about 15 years ago, NU-9 emerged as part of Silverman's multi-year effort to discover a small molecule compound that could prevent toxic protein aggregate buildup in neurodegenerative diseases. By 2021, NU-9 demonstrated efficacy in animal models of amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), clearing toxic SOD1 and TDP-43 proteins and restoring health to upper motor neurons. In 2024, it received clearance from the U.S. Food and Drug Administration to begin human clinical trials for ALS.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, Silverman, Klein and Kranz demonstrated that NU-9 also could effectively treat Alzheimer's disease. In the previous study, NU-9 showed it could clear toxic amyloid beta oligomers in lab-grown brain cells from the hippocampus, a region critical for learning and memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"In both ALS and Alzheimer's disease, cells suffer from toxic protein buildup," Klein said. "Cells have a mechanism to get rid of these proteins, but it gets damaged in degenerative diseases like ALS and Alzheimer's. NU-9 is rescuing the pathway that saves the cell."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Early intervention&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To further investigate the drug's potential in treating Alzheimer's disease, the team wanted to evaluate its effectiveness at halting the earliest damage. In the new study, the researchers administered NU-9 to a pre-symptomatic mouse model of Alzheimer's disease. The mice received a daily oral dose for 60 days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results were striking. NU-9 significantly reduced early reactive astrogliosis, an inflammatory reaction that typically begins long before symptoms appear. The number of toxic amyloid beta oligomers bound to astrocytes (star-shaped brain cells that protect neurons and control inflammation) also plummeted. And an abnormal form of the protein TDP-43 -- a hallmark of neurodegenerative diseases that is linked to cognitive impairments -- sharply decreased.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"These results are stunning," Klein said. "NU-9 had an outstanding effect on reactive astrogliosis, which is the essence of neuroinflammation and linked to the early stage of the disease."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The improvements spanned multiple regions of the brain, indicating that NU-9 has a brain-wide anti-inflammatory effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A hidden culprit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While investigating the effects of NU-9 on the pre-symptomatic mouse model, the research team found an unexpected culprit. For decades, scientists have considered amyloid beta oligomers as more toxic than the larger amyloid beta fibrils that form plaques, which appear later in Alzheimer's disease. But not all amyloid beta oligomers are the same. The Northwestern scientists discovered one uniquely problematic subtype.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We identified a distinct amyloid beta oligomer subtype that appears inside neurons and on nearby reactive astrocytes very early in the disease," Kranz said. "It potentially acts as an instigator of early Alzheimer's pathology."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Called ACU193&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; because it is detected by the antibody ACU193, the subtype shows up early inside of stressed neurons, the scientists found. Then, these oligomers appear to migrate to the surfaces of nearby astrocytes. When ACU193&lt;sup&gt;+&lt;/sup&gt; oligomers latch onto astrocytes, they may spark a cascade of inflammation that spreads throughout the brain, long before memory loss begins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A potential prophylaxis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;NU-9 targeted and dramatically reduced this subtype, suggesting the drug may be especially valuable at Alzheimer's earliest stages, when intervention is most effective. By reducing this subtype, NU-9 potentially could prevent the activation of astrocytes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although they serve as the brain's frontline responders, astrocytes become destructive when pushed into a reactive state. This destructive behavior damages synapses, releases inflammatory molecules and accelerates neurodegeneration. Stopping this process might be one of the most powerful ways to slow the progression of Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kranz and Silverman likened the strategy to early intervention approaches for preventing cancer and heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Most people are used to monitoring their cholesterol levels," Silverman said. "If you have high cholesterol, it doesn't mean that you will have a heart attack soon. But it's time to take drugs to lower your cholesterol levels to prevent that heart attack from happening down the road. NU-9 could play a similar role. If someone has a biomarker signaling Alzheimer's disease, then they could start taking NU-9 before symptoms appear."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"There are a couple early diagnostic blood tests for Alzheimer's disease in development," Klein added. "The promise of better early diagnostics -- combined with a drug that could stop the disease in its tracks -- is the goal."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Currently, the team is testing NU-9 in additional models of Alzheimer's disease, including an animal model of late-onset disease that better reflects typical human aging. The researchers also plan to follow animals for a longer period of time to determine whether symptoms develop in treated animals and plan to examine how early intervention with NU-9 affects memory and neuron health over time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study, "Identification of a glia-associated amyloid beta oligomer subtype and the rescue from reactive astrogliosis by inhibitor NU-9," was supported by the National Institute of Health (grant AG061708).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:12:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBhRHZvZGJxdDAyQlltUUNRYi1seDhXNTJ1cl85aTBtLS1CWGYxM05HN0pCS1A0dlpzRTFwQ3c3XzdqM0lUSW90dEVWUWxqWmtjOE9PV0tfNDNfb2VMemNmZU9QVUZoU3Rxd0RKeXlXaw</guid></item><item><title>宾夕法尼亚州的一个中央家庭如何被一只狂犬病猫袭击，如何从宾夕法尼亚州动物控制系统的漏洞中摔下来- PennLive.com</title><link>https://www.pennlive.com/news/2025/12/how-a-central-pa-family-attacked-by-a-rabid-cat-fell-through-gaps-in-pas-animal-control-system.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2YUVL6JBOBESBO5DXSELPGKHOQ"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;Story by Gabriela Martínez of Spotlight PA&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YIQJNHNQAFFSDPMCZXC4QSQTVI"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was produced by &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.spotlightpa.org/berks/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;the Berks County bureau of Spotlight PA&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;, an independent, nonpartisan newsroom. Sign up for Good Day, Berks, a daily dose of essential local stories at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="http://spotlightpa.org/newsletters/gooddayberks" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;spotlightpa.org/newsletters/gooddayberks&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RR5LAHZKWVAQRMREZG2KAKY67U"&gt;PERRY TOWNSHIP — Pennsylvania’s piecemeal system for animal control left a Berks County family scrambling for answers and assistance when they were attacked by a cat who later tested positive for rabies, a virus that is almost always fatal once symptoms begin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3NMYSGBPSJHOPHGK5BGZNFTWG4"&gt;The state divides responsibility among different agencies. The Pennsylvania Game Commission will assist when wildlife is involved, but not domestic animals or pets. The state Department of Agriculture can offer advice about those animals, but won’t seize, euthanize, or test them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="74KTPDQ7RBASXGE3O7NXF2FJ3U"&gt;Some municipalities offer animal control services that handle rabies cases, but there’s no requirement for them to do so, and many in Berks County don’t. That absence, plus a lack of countywide guidance, leaves some residents to fend for themselves while trying to make urgent, often costly decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3DCJBVPROZCJHEGHXFDUWCPOWY"&gt;In early September, a group of residents in Perry Township learned how difficult it can be to get help after a neighborhood cat — later confirmed to have rabies — bit three people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="article__image"&gt;&lt;div class="article__image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="low" loading="lazy" decoding="async" alt="Charlie Miller of Perry Township in the RV she shares with Kameron Biehl." class="article__image-content" src="https://www.pennlive.com/resizer/v2/UPMGQROZ7NGU7HL65CZFOP6QYY.jpeg?auth=bba0ef4ac198e5ff1ac1c886db1a4242d8d7133b256c2c43db5d1faede8ed22e&amp;amp;width=1280&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90" srcset="https://www.pennlive.com/resizer/v2/UPMGQROZ7NGU7HL65CZFOP6QYY.jpeg?auth=bba0ef4ac198e5ff1ac1c886db1a4242d8d7133b256c2c43db5d1faede8ed22e&amp;amp;width=500&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90 500w, https://www.pennlive.com/resizer/v2/UPMGQROZ7NGU7HL65CZFOP6QYY.jpeg?auth=bba0ef4ac198e5ff1ac1c886db1a4242d8d7133b256c2c43db5d1faede8ed22e&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90 800w, https://www.pennlive.com/resizer/v2/UPMGQROZ7NGU7HL65CZFOP6QYY.jpeg?auth=bba0ef4ac198e5ff1ac1c886db1a4242d8d7133b256c2c43db5d1faede8ed22e&amp;amp;width=1280&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 500px) 100vw, (max-width: 800px) 80vw, 60vw"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="article__image-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="article__mm-image-caption-text"&gt;Charlie Miller of Perry Township looks at medical bills for $21,000 in rabies treatment. She is uninsured. A discount left her with about $5,450 to pay.&lt;span class="article__mm-image-credit"&gt;Hanna Holthaus / Spotlight PA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Seeking help&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EY36FY4URNGFXDCHCUEJKLRKCU"&gt;Charlie Miller and Kameron Biehl moved to Perry Township in July. They live in an RV near Biehl’s parents, Kraig and Janet. The Biehls have always had cats as pets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="B5ORPU66VRDKRA437I6GB6D2WQ"&gt;Miller, who at the time was about to start an internship at Red Creek Wildlife Center and now works for Humane Pennsylvania, was helping Janet find resources to spay two semi-feral cats living near a shed outside of the Biehls’ house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3GZNUHQLZRB7FHTARF6XWGAUXU"&gt;She noticed that one of the cats was behaving strangely: vocal, disoriented, and refusing to eat. Miller didn’t know the behavior was a sign of rabies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TJXRRQJADRF3NNQ5RUB53W36FY"&gt;“She wasn’t foaming at the mouth, like everything I pictured rabies to look like,” Miller said of the cat named Callie. “She was adorable, and she was chatty, and I guess that’s a symptom too, but I didn’t know.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SLF34PGH7NGGDATMJYT4Z6RRJQ"&gt;When Miller tried to move Callie out of the road, the cat lunged and bit her. The cat later bit Kraig Biehl when he approached her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GSQWVAQUV5DPTKORVLF2MZR3Q4"&gt;“She got within about two feet and went ballistic,” he said. “She just went nuts.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FYRRK2NVCFB2FHLWD2WURPLETM"&gt;At urgent care, Biehl was treated with rabies immunoglobulin, which is used with the vaccine to prevent infection (he says he was not given that necessary vaccine shot). Miller was uninsured and wanted to confirm whether the cat was rabid before starting a costly treatment. When the patients asked for advice, they say clinic staff told them they had a couple of days to make a decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QVX6GE2IQZCKFLLMIQZ5GFOS2M"&gt;When Biehl went to warn others about Callie, he found out the cat had already bitten a neighbor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MOBGKSVZQRBIZIMFGAQCFHAQ6E"&gt;Miller wanted to trap and quarantine Callie. Biehl opted to shoot the cat to prevent anyone else from being injured. “My philosophy is three strikes, you’re out,” Biehl said. “I had to kill a cat, all right, and then figure out what we’re going to do.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LR446XWF2BAMFIJRTYVASVAASQ"&gt;They said they spent much of a Saturday trying to find someone who could test the cat. Instead, they kept getting shuffled around between different agencies. Now that Callie was dead, they were worried the body would decompose to a point that wasn’t viable for testing, so they felt they did not have much time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:5BXOG4YUCVCT7JY5QDR4XWF53M" data-fusion-component="5BXOG4YUCVCT7JY5QDR4XWF53M"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:5BXOG4YUCVCT7JY5QDR4XWF53M" data-fusion-component="5BXOG4YUCVCT7JY5QDR4XWF53M"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="23PPN3WKNVHUFNGR3ZPFHLRGHY"&gt;They called the State Police troop that oversees the township and were told to call the Pennsylvania Game Commission, which separately referred them to the state Department of Health. Meanwhile, Janet Biehl called two local veterinarians, both of whom said they couldn’t help, either due to lack of staff or because they weren’t previously clients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RUS75WWOBZGYVJ4JY47LGH3OZE"&gt;“We just felt helpless in the beginning, because we didn’t know what we were doing,” Kraig Biehl said. “We knew the possibility of rabies, but we’re not familiar with rabies at all.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OJYZGXOKARDL7HWT7XCI4OQXK4"&gt;Eventually, the Biehls were able to get in touch with a health worker and a community health nurse at a regional Department of Health office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ULRD6QBLEJGSJIE7Z3TWU7TPKM"&gt;The worker said a Department of Health lab in Exton could test for rabies, but could only accept a head. A spokesperson for the agency told Spotlight PA that staff recommended the Biehls contact a local veterinarian to euthanize the animal, prepare it for testing, and send the specimen to the lab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VQWZ6DJ5ORCBVKUIEKP7LE4JJM"&gt;Kraig decided he would have to do it himself with the help of a friend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SAYZMO647RG7XKLOOSA63VQTDE"&gt;“I’m really not interested in cutting the cat’s head off, right?” Biehl said. “However, at that point, you do what you got to do.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Costly gaps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XHDHB7ZGZVH6FDJSSJYE5ITTLA"&gt;For the Biehl family, one of the biggest challenges was that their municipality — Perry Township — does not contract with a company, or employ staff, specifically for animal control services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CDVAXLXH3JB6TKIX2JGNGPVCV4"&gt;Neither does Berks County, which also does not have “specific rabies response staffing,” according to Kimberly Fies, director of agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-28" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-28"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="R4SM76XHIRAQLI6LC7W4S5U4AY"&gt;“I would believe that, if there is some significant outbreak, we could coordinate with the [county] Department of Emergency Services to get some notification out to the municipality,” Fies told Spotlight PA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-29" data-gaid="inarticle-29"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KHOTWC6RJNCQFDIWQ7ECUVTCFI"&gt;A county spokesperson said its role is limited to making referrals to the Game Commission, the local Animal Rescue League (ARL), or the Humane Society, “barring an emergency situation or an outbreak.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-30" data-gaid="inarticle-30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6ETCEYVHY5DOXOCUB6JFGNLVLA"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; READ MORE:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.spotlightpa.org/berks/2025/12/berks-county-rabies-resources-feral-cats-domestic-animals-health/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;What Berks County residents need to know if they encounter a rabid animal&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-31" data-gaid="inarticle-31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EMBRC6L3A5FD7D53HS3ULU4GWY"&gt;Six Berks County municipalities pay ARL for animal control services and rabies response: Bern Township, Jefferson Township, New Morgan Borough, Reading, Upper Bern Township, and Wyomissing Borough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-32" data-gaid="inarticle-32"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="P4LHC2WG4NDVXFYMFHUWPVTIU4"&gt;Ashley Mikulsky, chief executive officer of ARL, said the nonprofit has also responded to rabies cases outside those areas when alerted by residents. All involved cats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-33" data-gaid="inarticle-33"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K7B3WHQOWRHZZK7CLXQWYGFOZU"&gt;Residents outside the coverage area can call ARL to rent out traps and get guidance on best practices for trapping an animal, but they do not have staff readily available to go out to places that do not have local animal control services. ARL can help with testing, at their discretion and at a cost: $100 for the euthanasia ($150 if the animal weighs over 20 pounds) and $250 for specimen prep and testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-34" data-gaid="inarticle-34"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UFAFRGXYUZEMXAXR63WUKZBQP4"&gt;While ARL fills the gap when it can, Mikulsky said the system ultimately leaves residents — and her staff — carrying costs that should fall on local governments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-35" data-gaid="inarticle-35"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IRMLR65RAFDFBGL3H3NDXY2UWQ"&gt;“You cannot rely on a nonprofit to be the unpaid public health and safety for animal control. That’s crazy,” Mikulsky said. “If you have a contractual relationship with them, sure. But that’s what I think we’ve arrived at in Berks County, is many of these municipalities either don’t want to or cannot pay for full-service animal control.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-36" data-gaid="inarticle-36"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7MRGOL2JDRFLPDDUWYS2UVZOJI"&gt;In many cases, local police departments will dispatch officers to put down potentially rabid animals, but Mikulsky said relying on officers is not a solution for communities that lack local animal control services. Officers often lack the equipment to handle rabid animals and are not aware of the steps that need to happen after an animal is killed, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-37" data-gaid="inarticle-37"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FVDIVGLI4RCZLJCAS2OU2LCZWU" data-fusion-component="FVDIVGLI4RCZLJCAS2OU2LCZWU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FVDIVGLI4RCZLJCAS2OU2LCZWU" data-fusion-component="FVDIVGLI4RCZLJCAS2OU2LCZWU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-38" data-gaid="inarticle-38"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;A lack of resources&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-39" data-gaid="inarticle-39"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VYKUF2I4LBDZ3LB64KT3ERAC4Q"&gt;The problem is not unique to Berks County. Many Pennsylvania municipalities lack the funding necessary to have an animal control officer on staff, according to Aliza Simeone, assistant professor of clinical infectious diseases and biosecurity at the University of Pennsylvania’s PennVet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-40" data-gaid="inarticle-40"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XSD2D6AKQFGEDEWRLKGJWKQS2I"&gt;“In many counties in Pennsylvania, they don’t have the same services down to a local level, so they don’t have somebody you can call to come out and get that animal, whereas they do in some of our more populated areas, like in Philadelphia,” said Simeone, who is also a former veterinary medical field officer for the state Department of Agriculture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-41" data-gaid="inarticle-41"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NILMMUWYKRBHZH7BYXBVY6AESY"&gt;In some cases, municipal employees may not be qualified to provide guidance if a resident calls for help. When Kraig Biehl called Perry Township to report the case, he was told to contact the Game Commission, even though that agency does not handle feral cats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-42" data-gaid="inarticle-42"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FBTROFOJIZAOVHF35DFYUEKB3M"&gt;“They dropped me like a hot rock,” Biehl said. “All I want to do is inform.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-43" data-gaid="inarticle-43"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KGIDGVMOI5EPVGTHRJHC43SUII"&gt;When Spotlight PA visited the Perry Township municipal building, an employee directed the reporter to contact the Game Commission and declined to comment further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-44" data-gaid="inarticle-44"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5P6L4HQWWRENJIHR4IUWQIJR54"&gt;The challenges deepen when the animal in question is not a pet, but a feral cat — a category that sits in a gray area of responsibility. A spokesperson for the Game Commission said “stray and feral cats are not considered wildlife, and do not fall under our general jurisdiction.” If a pet has been exposed to a potentially rabid wild animal, and that animal is still in the vicinity, the agency will send a game warden to locate and put down the suspect animal and have it tested for rabies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-45" data-gaid="inarticle-45"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RJA4VKJ3BZAANJMBVULZSYQH4U"&gt;The Department of Agriculture can issue quarantine orders and give guidance for pets exposed to rabies, but it does not have field staff who can trap and euthanize an animal showing signs of the disease. Spokesperson Shannon Powers said the agency “does not capture feral cats for any purpose.” In instances in which there is no local animal control, the department advises residents to report the suspected rabid animal to local law enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-46" data-gaid="inarticle-46"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="W4DCHALBRRCNNJD5P6HWV6VXY4"&gt;Berks County had 10 confirmed rabies infections in animals in 2023, 11 in 2024, and 17 so far in 2025. Of this year’s total, four were cats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-47" data-gaid="inarticle-47"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K6Z3Q35CSZADZHSLPQPF6IVKME"&gt;In 2023, Pennsylvania &lt;a href="https://avmajournals.avma.org/view/journals/javma/263/10/javma.25.05.0344.xml" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;ranked fourth&lt;/a&gt; among U.S. states for confirmed animal rabies cases. Simeone said Pennsylvania reports high numbers of cases, in part, because the state has more labs that can test for rabies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-48" data-gaid="inarticle-48"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3QNJSSYBONEDDB6VQVBGUB44M4"&gt;“It’s just a fact of life in Pennsylvania, because we have raccoon strain rabies here, and have for several decades now, so that particular virus does a better job of getting into other animals,” Simeone said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-49" data-gaid="inarticle-49"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XYVX5OUQE5FA3NDODMQHHMEFHE"&gt;Neil Ruhland, a Department of Health spokesperson, said rabies cases in animals are “normal yearly occurrences” and that there is “nothing abnormal about current levels.” Powers echoed that, saying “the level of reported cases of animals confirmed to have rabies is not sufficient to warrant alarm or widespread new measures, beyond those already in place.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-50" data-gaid="inarticle-50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HLP7C2K62FBSFMLS6MU7VGEENE"&gt;Miller was treated with the rabies vaccine and immunoglobulin after Callie tested positive. Since Miller does not have health insurance, the initial hospital bill was $21,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-51" data-gaid="inarticle-51"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YXG3XPVFOJB3JCJ2SB5ZCKES6I"&gt;The Penn State hospital forgave about $15,000 of the bill after Miller provided financial information, and she’s in the process of negotiating a lower bill and setting up a payment plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-52" data-gaid="inarticle-52"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="F77GOXRXUJGN3G7VVVCL4FGOYE"&gt;The Department of Health does not have assistance programs to help pay for rabies treatment, Ruhland said. Some rabies vaccine manufacturers offer &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rabies/hcp/clinical-care/biologics.html#:~:text=Manufacturers%27%20patient%20assistance%20programs%20that%20provide%20rabies%20medication%20to%20uninsured%20or%20underinsured%20patients%20may%20be%20available%20for%20quali%EF%AC%81ed%20patients.%20For%20more%20information%20on%20these%20programs%2C%20including%20eligibility%20requirements%2C%20please%20contact%20the%20manufacturers%20directly." target="_blank" rel=""&gt;assistance&lt;/a&gt; for uninsured patients, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-53" data-gaid="inarticle-53"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EWFQL7IZVRFEFJIA5POFXBLTL4"&gt;“I just wish there was one phone call that would have made it a smoother day, to tell us what to do next, or where to take the cat,” Miller said. “It took hours to figure out where to take the cat, and the only option was an hour away and behead it yourself. I didn’t feel like that should be the only way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-54" data-gaid="inarticle-54"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LV5OM6OB2NFJTCSDPUBVPA6K2E"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;BEFORE YOU GO…&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt; If you learned something from this article, pay it forward and contribute to Spotlight PA at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.spotlightpa.org/donate" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;spotlightpa.org/donate&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;. Spotlight PA is funded by &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.spotlightpa.org/support" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;foundations and readers like you&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; who are committed to accountability journalism that gets results.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-55" data-gaid="inarticle-55"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:NMWR7KH66JAF7KPAXU3AKJWWIE" data-fusion-component="NMWR7KH66JAF7KPAXU3AKJWWIE"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:NMWR7KH66JAF7KPAXU3AKJWWIE" data-fusion-component="NMWR7KH66JAF7KPAXU3AKJWWIE"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-56" data-gaid="inarticle-56"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PennLive.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 13:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0wFBVV95cUxNaGVTZ2RoNEtHa0IwREtHZDktWV81SFZpM1JBcHhYcHd2RVJ5akR4MUFEcGRuNU5WRXJnbGdGVDB6WlFxeWZIZ2xMaUw2UUM5TmJlYXFyUVZuZjJsYjFkSEVDOGl3T1JwRV9RZUVyM0NVbm1VLWNFbndPWEZTcko0T1ppRW01S2RJM1pqaEpJc2Y4Q0oyZGVYcmlBZWE4VlQxd2ZtTDJiT0lnU1R0aHowUF84dERCWHM1Y3k5VWlkZEdWZUg0Q0JJYmNEdFZwT3JaZF800gHnAUFVX3lxTFAzdGNxT2UxSFVwNzRJOExqY2M5dFlyVHlyT2tBMjVsZEhqMTVJNlhhYkk3RzZ2ZUl4Zk5rbUdfdFdYQlhFZk9tN2lnVlpPTExhemVaWWxIb0pmcElOY1FBeVdXR2F3UGNFX3dISjh0MFVaeFUtQUg5b215MGRfb28wRzVKQVFlVFRZTUpKWldYY0djV01NS2htRktOc0ZCdi0wcWZDa2Q2Qjg4Y2RNRmtOdzdMN3diU2NpdUd0RXpSdHVOUHRObDhXbkhsNVdFVzkzc3h1MkhGaldZLUJIOXZsN084SV9Mdw</guid></item><item><title>在2个深度睡眠阶段花费更少的时间可能会导致阿尔茨海默氏症- thestreet.com</title><link>https://www.thestreet.com/retirement/spending-less-time-in-2-deep-sleep-stages-may-contribute-to-alzheimers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>thestreet.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxObW9uUFNFTUlYNkNaRjFJSzVVUWNlZG5tcGdSWVlncU5TZUE1NXZXUmx2emdBQVZVaVJuUy1RS0FuOW51YWg2UHpkSWlvdFp0d0REY2c5M2JxZmhYZ3paX1VaOUxJNm00YXpUZy1rd01pUlpOaHBaZEtRai1aNy1mdmdHa0l0U0JtM3g3S19ONTZMSTcyME8wV0J4UFA0Sm1McTNGWTRTdWJWbE0</guid></item><item><title>2025年的五大全球健康胜利将挽救数百万人的生命-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/dec/22/five-big-global-health-wins-in-2025-that-will-save-millions-of-lives</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;ith humanitarian funding slashed by the US and other countries, including the UK, this year’s global health headlines have made grim reading. But good things have still been happening in vaccine research and the development of new and improved treatments for some of the most intractable illnesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="millions-of-girls-protected-against-cervical-cancer" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Millions of girls protected against cervical cancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A target to protect 86 million girls against cervical cancer by the end of 2025 was achieved ahead of schedule, boosting hopes among experts that cervical cancer can be &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/initiatives/cervical-cancer-elimination-initiative" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;eliminated within the next century&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Gavi, the vaccine alliance, launched its human papillomavirus (HPV) vaccination programme in 2014, when vaccine coverage in Africa was just 4%. By the end of 2022, it was only 15% – but scientists had discovered that &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/20-12-2022-WHO-updates-recommendations-on-HPV-vaccination-schedule" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;a single dose could give comparable protection&lt;/a&gt; to the two doses originally used. That would make it simpler to deliver vaccination programmes, and stretch supplies twice as far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="a786ece5-795f-4533-96f9-e8206ed46c8f" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;HPV vaccines are administered in Chikowa village in Malawi. It is hoped that the vaccination of 86 million girls will save 1.4 million lives.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Francisco María Galeazzi/WHO&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In 2023, Gavi announced its ambitious &lt;a href="https://www.gavi.org/news/media-room/cervical-cancer-vaccines-save-over-1-million-lives-lower-income-countries" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;target to protect 86 million girls by 2025&lt;/a&gt; and a concerted push saw coverage in Africa rise. By the end of 2024 it was at 44% – higher than Europe’s 38%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In November, Dr Sania Nishtar, Gavi’s chief executive, credited “countries, partners, civil society and communities” for reaching the 86m target early, and “driving major global progress towards eliminating one of the deadliest diseases affecting women”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Cervical cancer remains widespread and deadly in poorer parts of the world – 85% of new cases &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s12961-023-01094-3" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;are in sub-Saharan Africa&lt;/a&gt; – and a woman dies from the disease every two minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But a jab against the virus can avert 17.4 deaths for every 1,000 children vaccinated, according to Gavi, meaning the 86m vaccinations will prevent an estimated 1.4m cervical cancer deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="first-new-type-of-malaria-treatment-in-decades" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First new type of malaria treatment in decades&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After successful clinical trials, the first new type of malaria treatment in decades is to seek regulatory approval. GanLum, from pharma company Novartis, outperformed the standard treatment by demonstrating a cure rate of 99.2% compared with 96.7%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="e0cdc5ac-3b11-4c1c-aa41-3c07259ff55e" data-spacefinder-role="showcase" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-5h0uf4"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;Nets are a traditional way to keep mosquitoes at bay. A new treatment should be effective against the drug-resistant parasites they can carry.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Riccardo Lennart Niels Mayer/Alamy&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Crucially, it should also be effective against malaria parasites that have developed resistance to artemisinin, a component of the current standard treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2024/nov/14/malaria-study-drug-resistance-children-disease-africa-research-artemisinin" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Drug resistance to artemisinin&lt;/a&gt; is a growing concern. In the 1990s, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK2616/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;resistance to chloroquine&lt;/a&gt;, then the standard malaria treatment, led to millions of deaths, says Dr George Jagoe of the Medicines for Malaria Venture. The prospect of an antimalarial such as GanLum gives a “sense of relief”, he said at the &lt;a href="https://www.astmh.org/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;American Society of Tropical Medicine and Hygiene&lt;/a&gt;’s annual meeting, like “having a fire extinguisher” ready to use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-19m4xhf"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Drug resistance is a growing threat to Africa, so new treatment options can’t come a moment too soon&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Researchers also hope GanLum will be more effective at stopping transmission, because of how it affects parasites at certain stages of their life cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“GanLum could represent the biggest advance in malaria treatment for decades,” says Dr Abdoulaye Djimdé, professor of parasitology and mycology at the University of Science, Techniques and Technologies of Bamako, Mali, who was involved in the drug’s development. “Drug resistance is a growing threat to Africa, so new treatment options can’t come a moment too soon.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="more-countries-eliminating-measles" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More countries eliminating &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;measles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Cape Verde, Mauritius and Seychelles became the &lt;a href="https://www.afro.who.int/countries/cabo-verde/news/cabo-verde-mauritius-seychelles-eliminatemeasles-and-rubella" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;first three sub-Saharan countries&lt;/a&gt; to officially eliminate measles and rubella.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The milestone came despite a surge in measles cases worldwide, with an estimated 11m infections in 2024. In November, the Americas region &lt;a href="https://www.paho.org/en/news/10-11-2025-paho-calls-regional-action-americas-lose-measles-elimination-status#:~:text=As%20of%207%20November%202025,States%2C%20and%202%20in%20Canada." data-link-name="in body link"&gt;lost its measles-free status&lt;/a&gt; because of outbreaks in Canada, while the US is facing its worst outbreak in decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="7d68ea5a-9c47-4396-a931-6d5f9ec68b12" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;A baby has the measles, mumps and rubella vaccination at Beau Vallon health centre in Victoria, Seychelles’ capital.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: WHO&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The three African countries’ success was described as “a major public health achievement”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It shows what’s possible when countries put prevention first and make vaccines a priority,” says Dr Mohamed Janabi, the World &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/health" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; Organization’s director for Africa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We must build on this success so that every child in Africa can grow up healthy and protected.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:24,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:4146,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;global-dispatch&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Get a different world view with a roundup of the best news, features, opinion and photography, curated by our global development team&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Global Dispatch&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Every fortnight&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;We'll send you Global Dispatch every fortnight&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;news&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="884abeec-4f83-478c-af24-ba051e4974e3" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":25,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Waiting for the all-clear: how medics and villagers rallied when Ebola returned to DRC","elementId":"884abeec-4f83-478c-af24-ba051e4974e3","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/nov/10/ebola-disease-outbreak-democratic-republic-congo-drc-kasai"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":10,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Twenty-one Pacific island countries also eliminated measles and rubella this year. The status means they have interrupted endemic transmission for more than three years, and also have surveillance systems to rapidly pick up and contain any cases coming into the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Botswana and Rwanda have achieved 95% coverage with measles and rubella vaccination, the benchmark needed to interrupt transmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Globally, measles deaths dropped &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/28-11-2025-measles-deaths-down-88--since-2000--but-cases-surge" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;88% between 2000 and 2024&lt;/a&gt;, with a WHO report finding nearly 59 million lives had been saved by the measles vaccine since 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="a-new-hiv-prevention-drug" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new HIV-prevention drug &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A drug described as a potential “gamechanger” for the HIV epidemic arrived in sub-Saharan Africa &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/sep/24/hiv-prevention-jab-pre-exposure-prophylaxis-prep-lenacapavir-120-poorer-countries-2027" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;within months of its approval&lt;/a&gt; in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Lenacapavir, given as an injection twice a year, can almost completely prevent HIV infection. It was approved by US regulators in June and recommended by the WHO in July.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="b60bc205-e8d7-415e-b440-7b4842fa0799" data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-a2pvoh"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-9ktzqp"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;The manufacturer of lenacapavir, Gilead, will provide the drug at no profit for up to two million people over the next two years.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Nardus Engelbrecht/AP&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Manufacturer Gilead has signed agreements with six manufacturers of generic drugs, allowing them to produce cheaper versions for use in 120 countries. Those will be provided at about $40 (£30) for each patient for a year under deals struck with Unitaid and the Global Fund.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Until that production comes online, Gilead has committed to providing lenacapavir at no profit for up to two million people over the next two years. In November, &lt;a href="https://www.liverpool.ac.uk/centre-of-excellence-for-long-acting-therapeutics/global-news/stories/title,1536563,en.php#:~:text=mark%20an%20importan-,Arrivals%20of%20the%20twice%2Dyearly%20PrEP%20option%20in%20Eswatini%20and,finally%20ending%20the%20HIV%20epidemic." data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the first shipments arrived in Eswatini and Zambia&lt;/a&gt;. Rollout is expected to begin in early 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Campaigners say access needs to go further – poor communities in countries excluded from Gilead’s generic agreements will still struggle to afford the drug, at a list price of $28,218 to treat one person for a year. The drug will need to be rolled out at vast scale to turn the tide of new infections. And funding for HIV services is fragile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Peter Sands, executive director of the Global Fund, said the introduction in low- and middle-income countries “nearly simultaneously with high-income countries […] alone is a breakthrough, as previous drugs for HIV prevention have taken an average of five years to become available in these settings after evidence of their efficacy is first known”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="advances-in-fight-against-tb" class="dcr-12ibh7f"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Advances in &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;fight against&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; TB&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Since it was named in 1882, tuberculosis has killed &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7985566/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;more than a billion people&lt;/a&gt; and remains the world’s leading killer from infectious disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But treatment options are advancing at pace. Four vaccines are &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/observatories/global-observatory-on-health-research-and-development/analyses-and-syntheses/tuberculosis/analysis-of-tb-r-d-pipeline" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;in their final testing&lt;/a&gt; stages; easier to use tests, including &lt;a href="https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2025.07.03.25330836v1" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;simple tongue swabs&lt;/a&gt;, could improve detection; and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/nov/19/new-drug-could-be-breakthrough-killer-tb-tuberculosis-sorfequiline" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;a new treatment&lt;/a&gt; could boost cure rates and shorten the time needed to treat TB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="842b4626-7f93-47dd-9c6d-a90210db5c99" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1qvd3m6"&gt;A TB trial participant at Setshaba research centre in  Soshanguve, South Africa.&lt;/span&gt; Photograph: Jonathan Torgovnik/TB Alliance&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A new antibiotic, sorfequiline, showed stronger action than existing treatments in trial results presented at the Union World Conference on Lung Health in November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Science continues to surge forward, to the benefit of healthcare systems, people with TB, their families and their communities,” says Dr Mel Spigelman, president of TB Alliance, which developed the drug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="supporting" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-19m4xhf"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Goals that once seemed wholly aspirational, such as the eradication of TB, are made increasingly possible&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The advance builds on a new regimen for people with more complicated forms of TB, introduced in 2019, which itself shortened treatment from more than 18 months to six.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Replacing one drug in that regimen with sorfequiline could shorten treatment further, with more trials planned for 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Goals that once seemed wholly aspirational, such as the eradication of TB, are made increasingly possible because of advancements like sorfequiline,” says Dr Rod Dawson of the University of Cape Town Lung Institute. “But we have a lot of work ahead of us and cannot stop until TB is no longer a threat.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 12:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixgFBVV95cUxNdC0yNFg4TjU4Skg2YVFybG9SVWNLZG54c3lvZVRIMURsUGxvUTFhNFp1OXZzc243anp4VHFUZ2JqWl82MnEtTFptOHdYaXNIT05yXzV0LVVpU1VPWlVaU3NQaTdzZ2k0Nk9JeXJrWFgyMWlYTkhla2pOM01GZ1hLMzRmQ2FBSVNxTTFIMHdFbGo1ZDBKYkMtTjJHakMzT1NqZkExQ2RscVpGWElFMDNWUDNKQW43cUN0YjhFaWwxdnBTX29HdVE</guid></item><item><title>衰老精子的突变速度比科学家预期的要快- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/aging-sperm-are-mutating-faster-than-scientists-expected/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:22:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQaUFHUHRtNmdqX21kX1RwajVra0dPTk81ZUtFMl9NMkd1emhtMnNGRVY1aV96ZGJ4ZTFzX1ZSLWQ3UVk5S1Q4Vmh0T2ZQcFBjeHNtTDd6YWdkN3VRb01QWFJtRk9EVGtjcU1EMEcwSUNNNFVMaWV0TjdFLXpkN3dNR2RhWUlRNnJUT3c</guid></item><item><title>驻军：为什么女性在更年期体重增加—以及可怕的“更年期腹部” — Star Tribune</title><link>https://www.startribune.com/tips-to-fight-weight-gain-in-perimenopause/601549065</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;Vercel Security Checkpoint&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="hide-mobile" data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;|&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;sfo1::1766417663-cJZXlvJpNf4iiWCJ9dNt3tNddmmUbvLO&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Star Tribune</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 11:03:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxPY0pRYmxlV2taZmdaZE9ZQTdFSUYzYkNUNnJ1VnhwX3ZCeVgtX3pBdkl4dGdmdGdLWFlhSXd1Z1dLa1J3UVJKZVB3LU5hYlVFSk56Q1BVb3NKM1FXM3lBYnFpbGlZcGJMSDZVak1NdjBUS2RtUE9iMUl2cVZwalZWOUNmRUZzekU</guid></item><item><title>一种果糖饮料对免疫系统的影响- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/what-one-fructose-drink-does-to-the-immune-system/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:47:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNVEpGUC1zRWhVcmNyQ3ZodEI3a1p0TTdzRXcxRlFvZkROV0dhRnpUejAxRU5Jal9tU0tSYTNrZzhhTmk4WjgtbWlqUU1WTFFxd2ZGWnhxRzdQSTFBN2RjMy1NUEphWG56aDhCclBZUGpPYS1CSk5ZUzAxOXl0QmxETQ</guid></item><item><title>儿童疫苗可能会出现混乱- Axios</title><link>https://www.axios.com/2025/12/22/childhood-vaccines-denmark-cdc-lawsuits</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:30:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE1lUDJGT2pMTWFhZ0diVHMta0QweFJ3SFk5SXBtdUlVbUVIWEktMzVMMEVLUTMyV3hJX0FpTjZRTVpMUXFFSkQxcjdHaTZXMTZVS29WUkszSGZUdFMtYnZ6dlpWNDZ3UGVfbkhaamVfZTZVSmU0ejREWHRlamI</guid></item><item><title>这种大脑发现可能会改变多动症的治疗方式- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/this-brain-discovery-could-change-how-adhd-is-treated/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:12:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxPTEV4M2V6MlYwTEhSVWYycEFidG1VakRYZExBR2NQX3ZhQTg4MXcxR3VPRUxlbGMzcDFGZVZ2cTBNQ1ZtUjZYZVZOcENULV9IWGctWVRhdkRvckJ0Y0lORi1wUDQybVRVZHUwTVBuck1XMEdIMkdHQ3NNbUZ1dHl0Yk1mb2lfUQ</guid></item><item><title>列|我是一名医生。这里有10个基于科学的建议，可以帮助您变得更健康。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/22/health-tips-new-year/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YZHK4XOCFVHSDBCWJMDRRZD2DY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If you want to build healthier habits in 2026, here’s my advice: Give yourself time. New routines don’t stick overnight. A classic study found that it takes &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/ejsp.674" target="_blank"&gt;on average 66 days&lt;/a&gt; of practicing a new dietary or physical behavior each day before it becomes a habit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SM6CNLN4QZG3RPYKYVNAML5SCY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;You need to &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/15702599/" target="_blank"&gt;make it easy&lt;/a&gt; to make it last. So choose one habit and list every barrier that will keep you from hitting the mark. Then pre-solve each one. Is it too cold to go for a jog early in the morning? Find a 30-minute cardio routine on YouTube that you can do in your bedroom. Don’t have time to cook veggies from scratch? Frozen vegetables can save you time and money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:09:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE5EcDJQMHFtUmlwX3NnVXdJYzRnYVltR1I3SUlGWFBKV3l6OWttX1l6QmMwcFFOcFpwQ1RoSHE1akpPbW1MbUxlcVR2S2dKbkwtWXBZRkVwdGlQYlZ1RVpvMk5uTkxqc3hhUWJkWWYzTEkySTBucnM1eEJERFg</guid></item><item><title>一些患者在获得艾滋病毒预防药物方面面临障碍。以下是须知事项-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/22/nx-s1-5645054/hiv-prevention-drug-prep-billing</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-103272" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Oona Zenda/KFF Health News
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When a librarian in Berkeley, Calif., was looking to take PrEP to prevent HIV, the doctor hadn't heard of the medicine, and the bills that came were expensive ... and wrong.  The process was so frustrating that at one point they wondered, "Am I just going to stop this medication to stop having to deal with these coding issues and these scary bills?"&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;— Matthew Hurley, 30, from Berkeley, California&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A couple of years ago, Matthew Hurley got the kind of text people fear. It said: "When was the last time you were STD tested?"&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Someone Hurley had recently had unprotected sex with had just tested positive for HIV.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Hurley, who uses they/them pronouns, went to a clinic and got tested. "Luckily, I had not caught HIV, but it was a wake-up call," they said.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That experience moved Hurley to seek out PrEP, shorthand for preexposure prophylaxis. The antiretroviral medication greatly reduces the chance of getting HIV, the virus that causes AIDS. The therapy is &lt;a href="https://www.hiv.gov/hiv-basics/hiv-prevention/using-hiv-medication-to-reduce-risk/pre-exposure-prophylaxis" target="_blank"&gt;99% effective&lt;/a&gt; at protecting people against sexual transmission when taken as prescribed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hurley started PrEP and all was well for the first nine months — until their health insurance changed and they started seeing a new doctor: "When I brought PrEP up to him, he said, 'What's that?' And I was like, oh boy."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hurley, who is a librarian, went into teaching mode. They explained that the PrEP regimen they'd been on required daily pills and lab work every three months to look out for breakthrough infections or other health issues.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Hurley was surprised they knew more about PrEP than the physician. The FDA approved the first drug, Truvada, &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/drugsatfda_docs/nda/2012/021752_truvada_toc.cfm" target="_blank"&gt;back in 2012&lt;/a&gt;, and Hurley lives in the San Francisco Bay Area, a place with one of the &lt;a href="https://williamsinstitute.law.ucla.edu/publications/lgbt-rankings-metro-areas/" target="_blank"&gt;highest concentrations&lt;/a&gt; of LGBTQ+ people in the nation and a &lt;a href="https://www.sfaf.org/collections/status/from-awareness-to-activism/" target="_blank"&gt;deep history&lt;/a&gt; of HIV and health care activism. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hurley said older friends and acquaintances who survived the AIDS epidemic shared the horror of living through a time when there was no effective treatment or drugs for prevention. Deciding to take PrEP felt like an empowering way to protect their health and their community.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;So Hurley pushed the doctor, and after the physician did his own research, he agreed to prescribe PrEP.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hurley got the care they needed, but they had to be the expert in the exam room.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;blockquote class="edTag"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health Care Helpline helps you navigate the health system hurdles between you and good care. Send us your tricky question and we may assign a reporter to puzzle it out.&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/health-care-helpline-share-your-story/" target="_blank"&gt; Share your story and your question here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"That's a big burden," said Beth Oller, a family medicine physician and board member of GLMA, a national organization of LGBTQ+ and allied health care professionals focused on health equity. "You really want someone you can just go in and talk [to] about your health concerns without feeling like you are having to educate and advocate for yourself at every turn."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Oller said many queer people have had &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/womens-health-policy/lgbt-peoples-health-status-and-access-to-care/" target="_blank"&gt;negative experiences&lt;/a&gt; during health care visits. "I have a lot of patients who had not done preventive care for years because of the medical stigma," she said.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Billing Headaches&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Clearing the access hurdles to HIV prevention medicine was just the beginning. Hurley started receiving a string of bills for PrEP-related care: Blood test: $271.80. Office visit: $263.&lt;br&gt;Again, Hurley was surprised. They knew — even if the billing office didn't — that under the &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/affordable-care-act/sexual-health-preventive-services-covered-by-the-aca/" target="_blank"&gt;Affordable Care Act&lt;/a&gt;, most private insurance plans and Medicaid expansion programs are &lt;a href="https://nastad.org/sites/default/files/2021-12/PDF-PrEP-Coverage-Brief.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;required to cover&lt;/a&gt; PrEP and ancillary services, &lt;a href="https://www.uspreventiveservicestaskforce.org/uspstf/recommendation/prevention-of-human-immunodeficiency-virus-hiv-infection-pre-exposure-prophylaxis#bootstrap-panel--7" target="_blank"&gt;like lab tests&lt;/a&gt;, as preventive with no cost sharing.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The bills for doctor visits and blood draws piled up.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hurley would appeal the bill and get a denial almost every time. Then, they would appeal again.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hurley shared a series of appeal letters for one service, in which the billing office acknowledged that blood work had been initially incorrectly coded as diagnostic. Once that was corrected, Hurley said, the insurer paid for the service.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;That might sound quick or easy to resolve, but Hurley said it took "forever to get through the process." They dealt with at least six incorrect bills over several months. Hurley estimated they spent more than 60 hours contesting the bills.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;During that time, Hurley said, the billing department "is continuing to send me emails and bills that are saying, &lt;em&gt;You're overdue. You're overdue. You're overdue.&lt;/em&gt;"&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Fed up with the hassles, Hurley decided to find a health provider (and billing office) better informed about PrEP. They settled on the AIDS Healthcare Foundation. The care team there was able to discuss the pros and cons of different PrEP regimens and knew how to navigate the formulary for Hurley's insurance.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hurley hasn't gotten an unexpected bill since.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But siloing sexual health care and PrEP off from primary care hasn't been ideal.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I have multiple organizations that I have to deal with to get my holistic health dealt with," Hurley said.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A provider doesn't need to be an HIV specialist, an infectious disease expert, or a physician to prescribe PrEP. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention encourages primary care providers to treat PrEP like &lt;a href="https://stacks.cdc.gov/view/cdc/130758" target="_blank"&gt;other preventive medications&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;To avoid some of the headaches Hurley faced, try these tips:&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;1.  Do your homework to learn if PrEP is right for you&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The CDC estimates &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchhstp/director-letters/New-Injectable-HIV-PrEP%20.html#:~:text=According%20to%20the%20most%20recent,available%20strategies%20for%20preventing%20HIV." target="_blank"&gt;2.2 million&lt;/a&gt; Americans could benefit from HIV prevention drugs, but just over a quarter of that group have been prescribed them.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-103273" class="bucketwrap image small"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Oona Zenda/KFF Health News
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;"Not enough people know about PrEP, and there are a number of people who know about PrEP but do not realize it's for them," said Jeremiah Johnson, executive director of PrEP4All, an organization dedicated to universal access to HIV prevention and medication.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;According to the CDC's clinical guidelines, PrEP can be prescribed as part of a preventive health plan to &lt;a href="https://kff4.sharepoint.com/sites/KHNLibrary/Shared%20Documents/Forms/AllItems.aspx?viewid=83609977%2D1a7a%2D4af3%2D9cfb%2D9decb10cf0f8&amp;amp;ga=1&amp;amp;id=%2Fsites%2FKHNLibrary%2FShared%20Documents%2Fteam%5Faudio%2FHealth%20Care%20Helpline%2FQueer%20Health%20Helpline%2Fcdc%5F130758%5FDS1%2Epdf&amp;amp;parent=%2Fsites%2FKHNLibrary%2FShared%20Documents%2Fteam%5Faudio%2FHealth%20Care%20Helpline%2FQueer%20Health%20Helpline" target="_blank"&gt;anyone who's sexually active&lt;/a&gt;. It's especially recommended for people who don't use condoms consistently, intravenous drug users who share needles, men who have sex with men, and people in relationships with partners living with HIV or whose HIV status is unclear.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The vast majority of PrEP users are men. There are big race, gender, and geographical &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12256081/" target="_blank"&gt;disparities in the distribution&lt;/a&gt; of HIV and the populations taking the prevention medicine. For example, based on the patterns of new infection in the U.S., a group that would benefit from PrEP is &lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/prep-hiv-prevention-drug-cisgender-black-women/" target="_blank"&gt;cisgender Black women&lt;/a&gt;, whose gender identity aligns with their sex assigned at birth.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;2. Don't assume your provider knows about PrEP&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If your doctors aren't well informed, start by &lt;a href="https://www.aidsmap.com/about-hiv/pre-exposure-prophylaxis-prep" target="_blank"&gt;educating yourself&lt;/a&gt;. There are also clinical guidelines and information you can share with your provider. Check your state or local health department for a how-to guide for prescribing PrEP. For example, the New York State Department of Health AIDS Institute has information &lt;a href="https://www.hivguidelines.org/guideline/hiv-prep/" target="_blank"&gt;for providers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hivnexus/hcp/prep/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;CDC also has PrEP guidelines&lt;/a&gt;, but many of the agency's websites dealing with LGBTQ+ health are in flux. Under the Trump administration, some HIV/AIDS resources have been taken down from federal websites. Others now have &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/hiv/prevention/prep.html" target="_blank"&gt;headers saying&lt;/a&gt;: "This page does not reflect biological reality and therefore the Administration and this Department rejects it."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;3. Get lab work in-network&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Johnson said Hurley's experience with billing mistakes is common. "The lab expenses in particular end up being very tricky," Johnson said.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-103274" class="bucketwrap image small"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Oona Zenda/KFF Health News
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;For example, a doctor's office may mistakenly code the lab work required for PrEP as a &lt;a href="https://nastad.org/sites/default/files/2023-10/PDF-HIV-Prevention-BillingAndCoding-101223.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;diagnostic test&lt;/a&gt; instead of preventive care. Patients like Hurley can end up with a bill they shouldn't have to pay. If your doctor's office is making mistakes, share the &lt;a href="https://nastad.org/resources/billing-coding-guide-hiv-prevention" target="_blank"&gt;PrEP billing and coding guide&lt;/a&gt; from NASTAD, an association of public health officials who administer HIV and hepatitis programs.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Try to get your lab work done in-network. If the lab is out-of-network, Johnson said, it can be difficult to appeal.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If the bills keep coming, appeal them. And if you can't resolve the dispute, Johnson said, file a complaint with the agency that regulates your insurance plan.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;4.  Look for ways to save&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There are different kinds of PrEP. There are lower-cost, generic versions of Truvada, for example, sold as emtricitabine/tenofovir disoproxil fumarate, often shortened to FTC/TDF. Newer PrEP drugs &lt;a href="https://viivuspricing.com/apretude.html" target="_blank"&gt;Apretude and Yeztugo&lt;/a&gt; have list prices in the thousands of dollars. Check your insurance formulary and ask your doctor to prescribe medicine your plan will cover.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;With many health care premiums set to dramatically increase and millions at risk of losing Medicaid coverage, many people may go without health insurance in 2026. Drug manufacturers such as &lt;a href="https://advancingaccessconsent.iassist.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Gilead&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.viivconnect.com/hcp/orals/" target="_blank"&gt;Viiv&lt;/a&gt; have assistance programs for qualifying patients. If you have to pay out-of-pocket, prescription price comparison websites, like GoodRx, can help you find the pharmacies with the cheapest price.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;5. Consider telehealth&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Telehealth is an &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2842105" target="_blank"&gt;increasingly popular&lt;/a&gt; option if you don't live near an affirming provider or are looking for a more private way to get PrEP. In 2024, roughly 1 in 5 people on PrEP used telemedicine. Online pharmacies like &lt;a href="https://heymistr.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Mistr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://qcareplus.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Q Care Plus&lt;/a&gt; offer PrEP without an in-person appointment, and lab work can be done at home. Some telehealth options have ways to &lt;a href="https://news.emory.edu/stories/2025/12/hs_telemedicine_hiv_prep_02-12-2025/story.html" target="_blank"&gt;lower the cost&lt;/a&gt; if you're uninsured.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Telehealth can also broaden the number of doctors who are ready to prescribe PrEP. And some patients say speaking with a remote provider feels like a safer setting to talk about sexual health. "They're in the comfort of their own bedroom or living room but can interface virtually with a provider. It can open up a lot of doors for honesty and trust," said Alex Sheldon, executive director of GLMA.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-103275" class="bucketwrap image small"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Oona Zenda/KFF Health News
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;6. Seek Out Affirming Care&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;GLMA created the &lt;a href="https://lgbtqhealthcaredirectory.org/" target="_blank"&gt;LGBTQ+ Healthcare Directory&lt;/a&gt;, a searchable database of health care providers across the nation who identify as queer-friendly. As Hurley discovered, living in a major metro area is no guarantee your doctor is up to date on LGBTQ+ health care.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Ask locals you trust for recommendations. You might be surprised to find good options nearby.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Health Care Helpline helps you navigate the health system hurdles between you and good care. Send us your tricky question and we may assign a reporter to puzzle it out.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/health-care-helpline-share-your-story/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Share your story and your question here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. The crowdsourced project is a joint production of NPR and KFF Health News.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/about-us/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF Health News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is a national newsroom that produces in-depth journalism about health issues and is one of the core operating programs at &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/about-us/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;KFF&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxPbGVzbUtjNzFEek1wblFkSUhvVklrblktS2tnSlAtQUhZOUIzbzIyLU1WVUhDby1Uamh2TG1RSHlWQ0ZpWE93YlRrcFRsOV94aXgxZF9xSDJMT3pDb0pLZ2ppYXdHSXRqZHNMRmxSS1h1RFUxUFVKQ0VmMWVtNTVuMTVEUQ</guid></item><item><title>研究重启了有关癌症患者不受欢迎的饮食的争论- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/22/cancer-neutropenic-diet-lessened-risk-of-infection/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oncologists have been moving away from the notoriously unpopular neutropenic diet. It requires nearly all food to be cooked to high temperatures — or, as some have described it, “boiled to death” — to reduce the risk of food-borne illnesses. But since evidence in recent years suggested the diet didn’t actually help ward off infections, doctors started leaning away from a strict neutropenic diet.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Now, a new study published last week in the&lt;a href="https://ascopubs.org/doi/10.1200/JCO-25-00889#abstract" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; Journal of Clinical Oncology&lt;/a&gt; is giving some physicians pause about fresh fruits and vegetables for patients whose treatment involves heavy suppression of the immune system, particularly neutrophils, white blood cells that are key to preventing infection. Contrary to research in the past, the trial found that certain blood cancer patients who were allowed a less restrictive or liberalized diet had 11% more infections than patients who were prescribed the neutropenic diet.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“There has been a move in the last 10 years in liberalizing diets for patients, for sure,” said Talal Hilal, a hematologist oncologist and bone marrow transplant physician at the Mayo Clinic who did not work on the study. But reading the paper, Hilal said, “it does pose the question of maybe we need to revisit how liberal we want to be with our patients.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Oncologists first began using the neutropenic diet decades ago, particularly for intensively treated cancer patients like those undergoing hematopoietic stem cell or bone marrow transplants. These procedures can give certain blood cancer patients an opportunity for a cure, but sometimes use heavy doses of chemotherapy that’s extremely harsh on the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While the weakened immune system is recovering after the procedure, infections have a higher potential of turning deadly, until the patient’s cell counts recover. Hospitals have been known to go to great lengths to protect these patients including&lt;a href="https://ascopubs.org/doi/10.1200/JCO-24-02046" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; preventing outside food or fresh flowers&lt;/a&gt; from entering their rooms. As cruel as it may have felt, clinicians assured themselves it was better than potentially introducing dangerous bacteria, viruses, or fungal spores to the defenseless.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Over the years, though, evidence suggested that normal diets don’t pose much of an infection risk. Rather, neutropenic diets were&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3228185/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; blamed&lt;/a&gt; for decreasing patient quality of life and increasing malnutrition. So hospitals have gradually shifted toward being more liberal when it comes to neutropenic patients.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In particular, a group at the University of Milan published the first &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2022/12/10/bone-marrow-transplant-patients-neutropenic-diet/"&gt;randomized evidence&lt;/a&gt; that a non-restrictive diet was not inferior to the neutropenic diet for certain stem cell transplant patients in 2023, leading many oncologists to rejoice that the benefits of the neutropenic diet were finally debunked. They also showed a non-restrictive diet improved quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But John Wingard, a hematologist-oncologist and emeritus faculty at the University of Florida, wanted to take another look. In particular, he wanted to know if un-restricting the diet for neutropenic patients would actually improve patients’ nutrition, an ongoing challenge for many cancer patients undergoing intensive therapy. Like the Milan group, Wingard enrolled over 200 blood cancer patients and randomized them to get either a liberalized diet allowing fresh fruits, vegetables, and pasteurized yogurt, or the neutropenic diet. In this study, patients were allowed to eat home-cooked or restaurant food as long as it adhered to diet guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Wingard planned to look at how many clinically confirmed infections were in each group at different time periods. “We had to prematurely stop the trial from data safety monitoring committee because the liberalized diet had 11% more infections,” Wingard said. Only about half of the patients who were allowed the liberalized diet actually consumed fresh fruits or vegetables, Wingard added. “When we did an analysis of just the people who complied with the liberalized diet, the rate of infection was 1.5 times higher.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study also suggested that allowing the liberalized diet didn’t seem to improve patients’ nutrition or quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Taken together, Mayo Clinic’s Hilal said he’s starting to rethink his practice of being more permissive with transplant patients’ diets. “I feel like if you are liberalizing diet and you’re not even seeing improvements in quality of life or nutritional status, then there is no trade-off here. Why would I be very easy with liberalizing my diet, if I don’t benefit in any other domain?” he said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There are some caveats, Hilal said. For one, the patient population in both the 2023 Milan group study and this study are different. The 2023 paper was a multi-center study, which can help remove hospital-specific biases. It was also done in Europe, where certain practices may be different than what’s typical in the U.S., which could plausibly make comparison harder as well. “They are also a higher-risk population that seems to be enrolled in this JCO paper,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, Hilal said he felt the study may reignite a debate on the neutropenic diet, and cancer researchers might argue over the strengths and weaknesses of both trials. “It’ll probably get discussed. People will take sides,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Notably, Hilal and other physicians, including Wingard, said that it’s likely still reasonable to allow a non-restrictive diet with other patients like solid tumor patients who may still be neutropenic, but not as high risk or neutropenic for as long as bone marrow transplant patients. This study also showed that being neutropenic longer was the main variable associated with infection. No patients died during the study intervention either, and oncologists can manage many infections well.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As for why neither diet improved nutrition or quality of life for patients, Wingard thinks that might be because intensive cancer treatment can leave patients nauseous, without an appetite, and generally uncomfortable. No matter what food they get, some patients will just struggle to eat.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I don’t think the neutropenic diet is that bad,” Wingard said. “It’s just that patients who have been treated this way have a symptom called dysgeusia, which means everything tastes bad. And then you have nausea and stuff.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Probably the best way to settle the neutropenic diet debate and help patients’ quality of life and nutrition, Wingard said, is to focus on improving treatment. New effective therapies that are less toxic to the immune system would mean there’s no need for something like the neutropenic diet.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:32:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQRVZ6aU5QbkducXB4M1dOSm5iYTFVVWdiZ2F1aUlCRkEza2tweVRDdHhHNS1GMjE0VFJHek5qdXBmNW85NFBad2dKcUdSR0lsN1lBTlNjd1c5UWJfVHhvRTFqRGNRU0taTmVGYzcyZTMxbUZDZk1yZkhnQjl2dl9TZmtULU5ESFJhZEdMbzVtanA</guid></item><item><title>美国食品安全可能会崩溃- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/22/american-food-safety-funding-cuts-foodnet/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The infant botulism outbreak that sickened dozens of babies who drank &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/11/14/byheart-baby-formula-fda-recall-company-response-criticized/"&gt;ByHeart formula&lt;/a&gt; is a reminder of how vulnerable we all are to the companies that sell us food — and how important it is to have a robust food safety system that responds quickly to problems and prevents illness in the first place. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But federal cuts this year will leave more people exposed to potential foodborne illness in the future, food safety experts predict. The changes they say will degrade U.S. food safety include the &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-quietly-scaled-back-surveillance-program-foodborne-illnesses-rcna227089" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;reduced number of pathogens&lt;/a&gt; now monitored by a key surveillance program, brain drain of the foodborne illness staff at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention and Food and Drug Administration amid low morale and overwork, and cuts to the administrative staff who support FDA inspectors, which agency officials say has already led to a &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/foreign-food-safety-inspections-historic-low-fda" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;historic low in inspections&lt;/a&gt; of foreign facilities that import food to the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It’s not that they [the Trump administration] are necessarily choosing to harm the system,” said Daniel Jernigan, who worked at the CDC for 30 years before &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/08/28/profiles-cdc-officials-who-resigned-in-protest/"&gt;resigning&lt;/a&gt; from his position as head of the agency’s National Center for Emerging and Zoonotic Infectious Diseases in August. “It’s that all of these cuts that are not coherent are all working against each other, and therefore you end up with a system that’s just not functioning well.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As it is, foodborne illness causes around &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/food-safety/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;48 million illnesses and 3,000 deaths&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. each year.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration has taken some measures to try to protect food safety, restoring funding to states to carry out more inspections, said Sarah Sorscher, director of regulatory affairs at the consumer advocacy group Center for Science in the Public Interest. Nonetheless, she said, the cumulative effect of the cuts is to make food safety “collateral damage in this war on government.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;She added, “Consumers are certainly going to feel it when they get sick from outbreaks that could have been prevented.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-cost-of-scaling-back-foodnet"&gt;The cost of scaling back FoodNet&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One significant area of concern is the Trump administration’s decision to scale back the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/foodnet/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Foodborne Diseases Active Surveillance Network&lt;/a&gt;, or FoodNet, program, reducing the number of pathogens in its reporting requirements from eight to two — salmonella and E. coli. Ten state health departments participate in the FoodNet program, which surveys about 16% of the U.S. population with the goal of detecting outbreaks early and tracking down their sources.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The CDC &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-quietly-scaled-back-surveillance-program-foodborne-illnesses-rcna227089" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;cited funding issues&lt;/a&gt; as a reason for the change and said that other CDC systems also conduct national surveillance for the pathogens. “Narrowing FoodNet’s reporting requirements and associated activities will allow FoodNet staff to prioritize core activities,” a CDC spokesperson told STAT.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;But experts said that what makes FoodNet unique is that it conducts active surveillance, reaching out to state laboratories to ask about cases, rather than passively relying on states to notify the CDC about illness. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;FoodNet is “the best measure we have for whether the system is working or failing us,” said Sorscher. “So the fact that they cut that first is just really dark.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The fault doesn’t just lie with the Trump administration, said Sorscher — Congress has also failed to provide sufficient funding to detect and prevent foodborne illness. (The CDC typically requests a budget of $72 million a year for food safety, about half of which goes to states.) &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;With FoodNet cuts, Sorscher said, “what’s being lost is accuracy and the ability to compare [trends] over time.” That means “we will not be able to say with any certainty moving forward what the DOGE [Department of Government Efficiency] cuts did, what the shutdown did. So it really just wipes away any form of accountability for these other changes.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Carlota Medus, supervisor of the foodborne diseases unit at the Minnesota Department of Health, said via email that the immediate impact of cuts to FoodNet in the state could be the speed with which his department is able to identify the source of an outbreak. “Long term, the cuts will affect our ability to use surveillance data to better understand risks in the food supply, and which areas food producers and regulatory agencies should prioritize,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-brain-drain-pipeline-problems-and-low-morale"&gt;Brain drain, pipeline problems, and low morale&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Food inspectors at the FDA weren’t targeted by federal cuts. But &lt;a href="https://projects.propublica.org/federal-health-worker-cuts-rfk-trump-administration/?_gl=1*wz6vu1*_ga*MTA1NzkzMTMyOS4xNzYxNzQzNjY2*_ga_K9RW8M6GL5*czE3NjU4MTkyOTUkbzExJGcxJHQxNzY1ODE5MzI4JGoyNyRsMCRoMA.." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;65% of support staff&lt;/a&gt; charged with tasks like booking and reimbursing travel were eliminated. Jernigan compares the loss of support staff to a person trying to use a banking app on a smartphone that needs a software update. “The app may be perfectly fine,” he said, “but if you don’t have the operating system on the phone, you’re not going to be able to use the app.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There was already a chronic shortage of food inspectors at the FDA and the Department of Agriculture, said Barbara Kowalcyk, director of the Institute for Food Safety and Nutrition Security at George Washington University. Now morale is low, experienced inspectors are retiring or leaving for the private sector, and the people who remain are overextended.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The staffing losses and the brain drain is huge,” said Sorscher. “The inspection is only as good as the person doing it, and we’re losing so many experienced staff.” The FDA food inspection workforce is about 20% understaffed, with 470 out of a ceiling of 589 positions filled, the agency told consumer groups last week. The infant formula team has only 5 inspector positions filled out of 10, though there are 11 traditional inspectors who can also examine facilities. There’s no hiring freeze on inspectors — the problem is recruiting and retaining staff.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;The FDA reassured consumer groups that current staffing was adequate in spite of being below the budgeted ceiling, Sorscher said. “No specifics really, just seemed like they were trying to keep a stiff upper lip for external partners,” she added.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In her own view, “[e]ven if they’re able to bring in new people, it’s going to take years to have the level of competency we had before Trump took office.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;ProPublica reported last month that, in the aftermath of support staff cuts, the FDA will have the &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/foreign-food-safety-inspections-historic-low-fda" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;lowest number of inspections of imported food&lt;/a&gt; since 2011, excluding the pandemic. “That’s particularly concerning,” Kowalcyk said, because a lot of fruits and vegetables are imported into the U.S., and “fresh produce is our riskiest product” when it comes to foodborne illness. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Imported foods “don’t have the same level of regulation when it comes to things like irrigation water and food safety practices,” Kowalcyk said. Back in 2008, for example, a nationwide salmonella outbreak that led to hundreds of hospitalizations and two deaths was eventually traced back to contaminated irrigation water used to &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1005741" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;grow peppers&lt;/a&gt; in Mexico. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Food safety experts also predict pipeline problems for years to come as students who might normally seek out jobs in government look for private sector roles instead. “If a student were to come to me today to say, ‘Hey, I’m considering a career in the federal government in food safety,’ I might say, ‘Maybe not right now,’” said Don Schaffner, a distinguished professor of food science at Rutgers University. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Brain drain among food safety experts at the CDC is underway as well. That’s a problem because state health departments rely on the CDC to identify and manage responses to foodborne illness that affects people across state lines, according to Medus of the Minnesota foodborne diseases unit. “With a decrease in expertise and capacity at the CDC, it will be harder to coordinate the investigation efforts across the U.S.,” and harder to arrive at answers about the root cause of outbreaks, Medus said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Jernigan also noted that DOGE cut a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/orr/topics-programs/orise-fellowship.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;CDC fellowship program&lt;/a&gt; with the Oak Ridge Institute for Science and Education that provided training to young people who often went on to become junior employees at the agency, including in food safety. “It was a significant cut to the incoming pipeline for young scientists, and I think we’ll be feeling that impact for years,” Jernigan said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The entire staff of 40 or so people in the CDC’s Washington office, which coordinated communication between the agency and Congress, also &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/10/11/cdc-firings-government-shutdown-hhs/"&gt;lost their jobs&lt;/a&gt; in October. That means policymakers on appropriation and oversight committees may not be getting the information they need about outbreaks and other issues, Jernigan said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-funding-cuts-are-weakening-food-safety"&gt;How funding cuts are weakening food safety&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;State health departments do most of the initial work on foodborne illness, but they’re heavily dependent on CDC funding. It’s hard to lay out exactly how those cuts have impacted state food safety efforts, said Sorscher, because states’ work is largely funded through federal block grants that can be allocated for a wide range of purposes. “Those grants have decreased dramatically and they’ve probably had to make layoffs, but we can’t really follow the money,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One change that Jernigan said has definitely weakened the food safety system is the &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/03/26/trump-pulls-back-billions-covid-funding-local-health-departments/"&gt;rescission of Covid-related funding&lt;/a&gt; and the fallout effect on &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/advanced-molecular-detection/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Advanced Molecular Detection&lt;/a&gt;, a CDC program that allows state health departments to use newer genomic sequencing techniques rather than older methods of microbiology. &lt;/p&gt;


		&lt;aside class="wp-block-stat-article-newsletter-signup logged-out"&gt;
			
			&lt;div class="newsletter-signup-container"&gt;
				&lt;div class="newsletter-signup-heading"&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;
						Newsletter												&lt;span class="frequency"&gt;Weekdays&lt;/span&gt;
											&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;div class="newsletter-signup-text"&gt;
										&lt;h3&gt;Sign up for Morning Rounds&lt;/h3&gt;
															&lt;p&gt;Understand how science, health policy, and medicine shape the world every day&lt;/p&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
						
					&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/aside&gt;
		


&lt;p&gt;For foodborne illness, that could mean that when a sick person shows up at the hospital and their stool sample tests positive for salmonella, the sample then gets sent to a state public health laboratory to sequence that particular bacteria. Two weeks later, if someone in another state gets sick, the sequencing would be able to identify a match between the two cases and, from there, help investigators more speedily identify the source of contamination. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The taking back of those dollars meant that they no longer had money in state health departments to pay for the people doing the sequencing,” Jernigan said. As a result, he said, “what you will see is later detection of outbreaks, and probably larger numbers of cases.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-we-ll-know-if-the-food-safety-system-is-breaking-down"&gt;How we’ll know if the food safety system is breaking down&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;One challenge with communicating the importance of food safety, said Kowalcyk, is that it’s fundamentally about prevention. “If we’re doing our jobs right, you don’t ever see it.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;It may be hard to see the impact of cuts, too. “If you stop looking for things, then you will not find them,” said Jernigan. “Your overall foodborne illness rate will start going down. Yay! No, that’s bad.” Fewer outbreaks, with larger numbers of cases, could be one sign of worsening food safety. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Beyond foodborne illness, a side effect of the cuts may be to discourage Americans from eating fresh food. “If we have a lot of fresh produce outbreaks, that’s going to reduce consumer confidence,” Kowalcyk said. Ultra-processed foods, by contrast, “tend to be pretty safe because they’ve had preservatives added to them and are shelf-stable.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Overall, experts said, food safety and nutrition go hand in hand. “We’re supposedly trying to make America healthy again,” said Schaffner. “And that’s hard to do without people that understand food safety.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;STAT’s coverage of chronic health issues is supported by a grant from &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.bloomberg.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bloomberg Philanthropies&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Our &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/supporters/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;financial supporters&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; are not involved in any decisions about our journalism.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:32:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOYVRJaUY4MDZwQVF4N1RUeHAybW4zR2JxZ0pGZGR1X2ZwMER3TjJvRkxYdWNZY3lfMjBWdE1JZ3FLaFlkejVxUDctSXYxRGV3ZGpacGNRVXpLQjY3dURmVFVaWEZzYUI1Q1lqVWNNNE1QNGpRT2tBWXZFbkZoZktxODRMZmk</guid></item><item><title>NIH研究是局部类固醇戒断社区的指路明灯。然后，在联邦动荡中，研究停滞不前- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/22/topical-steroid-withdrawal-study-derailed-american-science-shattered/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-constrained wp-block-post-content-is-layout-constrained"&gt;&lt;p class="has-drop-cap"&gt;On May 23, 2023, Kelly Barta arrived at the National Institutes of Health to figure out what was wrong with her. In a sense, she already knew: She had diagnosed herself with topical steroid withdrawal in 2012, and had gone on to become the president and executive director of a TSW advocacy group. But many doctors weren’t convinced the disorder existed, and as far as Barta could tell, most researchers didn’t care enough to dig into it. The fact that the biggest funder of biomedical research in the world was even trying to decipher its biology felt like a breakthrough.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It had started with eczema when she was a child in Grand Rapids, Mich.: itchy patches in the creases behind her knees and elbows, which spread to her hands and face when she became a preteen. Her doctors managed it with moisturizers and topical steroids. That worked, but over the years, the strength of her steroid prescriptions crept upward — and one day, when she was in her late 30s, working as a musician in Atlanta, a pharmacist casually mentioned that she should be careful, these were really potent steroids, how long had she been taking this sort of stuff? Probably around 10 years, Barta replied. “Just for a second, her eyes kind of popped open, and she got this look on her face, and it made me sick to my stomach,” Barta said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When she did stop her steroids, what had been patches of eczema here and there morphed. Now, she burned everywhere, a redness that covered almost her entire body. She was beset by a new itch, different from an eczema itch, a “bone-deep itch” rather than a superficial one. “An itch like a panic attack, an itch so intense you can’t think of anything, you literally want to claw your skin off, you don’t care if it’s bleeding. It’s indescribable,” Barta said. Her clawed-at skin oozed. She would lie naked on towels, peeling her crusted self off to take a bath every two hours. It hurt to wear clothes. It hurt to move. She couldn’t sleep. She tried the breathing exercises she’d used to get through childbirth. This lasted for years. Eventually, her 21-year marriage fell apart.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Early on, in a moment of sleepless Googling, she had stumbled on the term “topical steroid withdrawal,” or TSW. “It was like check, check, check, checking the boxes,” she said. “Even though it was a horrible realization, I just knew that was me. It all clicked into place.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The underlying biology, though, was a mystery. The ailment was defined by symptoms and stories. Some dermatologists were skeptical. They thought it might just be eczema, roaring back with a vengeance when someone stopped treatment. That drove the TSW community up the wall: They had lived with eczema, they knew what it felt like, this felt different. Other physicians worried that these activists were scaring patients away from medications that could be enormously helpful. Activists retorted that they weren’t against steroids, just against their wanton use.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Into this disputed terrain stepped Ian Myles, an allergist-immunologist at the NIH. The vast majority of the agency’s $48 billion annual &lt;a href="https://www.nih.gov/about-nih/organization/budget" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;budget&lt;/a&gt; is sent out to researchers elsewhere, but about 11% stays in house, funding research on the campus itself. Myles ran one of those intramural government labs. He was the person who’d invited Barta to Bethesda, Md., to give little hole-punches of her forearms, swabs of her microbiome, and vials of her blood — to be both a research participant and a co-author. When their study of some three-dozen people &lt;a href="https://www.jidonline.org/article/S0022-202X(25)00014-4/abstract" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;came out in August 2025&lt;/a&gt;, the patient community saw it as a triumph: the first preliminary glimmer of evidence that TSW might be microbiologically distinct — something you could one day test for. Certain other researchers weren’t so sure. Critiques came from both TSW skeptics and TSW allies, a disagreement about how best to probe the unknown when that unknown was tearing apart people’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure class="wp-block-image alignright size-full"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/93EC3D0D-0FC1-43CF-B802-80E810F2B138-rotated.jpeg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/93EC3D0D-0FC1-43CF-B802-80E810F2B138-rotated.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-1416245" srcset="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/93EC3D0D-0FC1-43CF-B802-80E810F2B138-rotated.jpeg 480w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/93EC3D0D-0FC1-43CF-B802-80E810F2B138-328x437.jpeg 328w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/93EC3D0D-0FC1-43CF-B802-80E810F2B138-432x576.jpeg 432w" sizes="(min-width: 625px) and (max-width: 767px) 719px, (min-width: 768px) and (max-width: 899px) 835px, (min-width: 900px) and (max-width: 1023px) 635px, (min-width: 1024px) and (max-width: 1199px) 803px, (min-width: 1200px) and (max-width: 1439px) 994px, (min-width: 1440px) 982px, 576px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Kelly Barta, while she was suffering from TSW.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;wbr&gt;&lt;/wbr&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Courtesy Kelly Barta&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What both sides could agree on was that these questions needed more research. But by the time his initial study came out, Myles had already set aside the follow-up trial he’d planned. Last February, in the name of cost efficiency, the Trump administration had &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/trump-credit-card-freeze-sparks-alarm-health-agencies" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;frozen&lt;/a&gt; the credit cards government scientists use to purchase lab supplies. By spring, there had been several rounds of mass federal layoffs; employees who’d previously helped with fiddly tasks were gone. Administrative requirements began taking longer. Myles wasn’t angry, just matter-of-fact about the fluctuations of his job. He didn’t want to start enrolling patients if he was uncertain about his ability to follow through. He put the study on indefinite pause. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In federal bureaucracy jargon, the term for a layoff is a “reduction in force.” It’s easy to make an acronym of it, a RIF, and pay little attention to the words themselves. But they capture the results of what has happened this year within government agencies: not only the loss of personnel but also the various disruptions to business as usual. Some argue this is a necessary correction to a bloated ecosystem. But it comes at a cost: offices and labs more limited in what they can accomplish, their forces reduced. While the sweeping termination of NIH grants to external scientists has sparked lawsuits to stop them and databases to track them, these diminished internal abilities have drawn less notice. To TSW patients, though, they’re no less maddening.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity is-style-default"&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-rising-eczema-rates-and-a-fight-for-tsw-research-nbsp"&gt;Rising eczema rates and a fight for TSW research &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Myles hadn’t meant to study TSW. The whole saga started in 2019, when he happened to hear Barta speak at a Food and Drug Administration event, designed so that skin researchers could learn from patient perspectives. “I had never heard of it in my entire medical training. Initially, it sounded insane,” he said. But when he looked online, he noticed a discrepancy: posts about #topicalsteroidwithdrawal with hundreds of millions of views, but not much in the way of microbiological research. “Whatever was going on, there wasn’t a mountain of evidence &lt;em&gt;against&lt;/em&gt; these people, right?” he said.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure class="wp-block-image alignright size-large"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Getting-biopsied-at-NIH-May-23-2023.jpeg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Getting-biopsied-at-NIH-May-23-2023-1024x1665.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-1416241" srcset="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Getting-biopsied-at-NIH-May-23-2023-1024x1665.jpeg 1024w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Getting-biopsied-at-NIH-May-23-2023-328x533.jpeg 328w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Getting-biopsied-at-NIH-May-23-2023-768x1249.jpeg 768w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Getting-biopsied-at-NIH-May-23-2023-500x813.jpeg 500w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Getting-biopsied-at-NIH-May-23-2023-640x1041.jpeg 640w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Getting-biopsied-at-NIH-May-23-2023-354x576.jpeg 354w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Getting-biopsied-at-NIH-May-23-2023.jpeg 1284w" sizes="(min-width: 625px) and (max-width: 767px) 719px, (min-width: 768px) and (max-width: 899px) 835px, (min-width: 900px) and (max-width: 1023px) 635px, (min-width: 1024px) and (max-width: 1199px) 803px, (min-width: 1200px) and (max-width: 1439px) 994px, (min-width: 1440px) 982px, 576px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Myles takes a skin biopsy from Barta’s forearm as part of his study at NIH.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;wbr&gt;&lt;/wbr&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Courtesy Kelly Barta&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Still, he wasn’t the researcher they were looking for. He had other projects to tend to. He was interested in rising eczema prevalence. Among American children, it had &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamadermatology/fullarticle/2801443" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;jumped from 7.9% to 12.6% between 1997 and 2018&lt;/a&gt;. That had deep implications. Dermatologic health is a bellwether for our relationship with the outside world. It underpins the comfort that allows us to be functional, but also hints at other bodily goings-on — and childhood eczema is among the biggest predictors of food allergies. Unlocking the driver of these rashes might help explain our age of hypersensitivities. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Myles suspected that the root of the problem lay in pollutants, toxins, and detergents disrupting our microbiomes, and he was busy looking into that hypothesis, swabbing skin to see what bacteria were living on it, spraying on different species to see if that might help. He was speaking at an eczema conference about that work in 2022 when Barta came up to him; he recognized her as “that lady with TSW.” She said she wanted to meet with NIH officials about organizing research into TSW. He put her in touch with government employees involved in underwriting skin studies, who in turn referred her to a network of NIH-funded dermatologic researchers at various universities — a kind of royal court of American eczema scientists. Initially, their response was encouraging. “I gave them a whole presentation, and they’re like, ‘Oh yeah, this is really compelling,’” Barta recalled. “They ended up publishing a paper calling for more research.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But the research itself — the nitty-gritty microbiological study that Barta was waiting for — never came.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It became painfully obvious that every lab that had the resources to do this work did not have the interest to do it,” said Myles. There was a pattern there. The contestedness of a contested illness can feel like a trap, gripping tighter the more you try to extricate yourself. With no official diagnostic criteria, some doctors aren’t sure there’s a diagnosis there at all. But the research that might help establish diagnostic criteria depends on a certain level of recognition: not only an openness to the idea, but a conviction that this is worth spending precious time and funding on. For patients, that creates a catch-22. The less they’re listened to, the more insistent they become, and the more insistent they become, the less doctors are inclined to listen. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-stat-article-recirc-curated"&gt;		&lt;aside class="recirc-curated-content"&gt;
			&lt;span class="recirc-curated-bg-text"&gt;Science&lt;/span&gt;
			&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;More in American Science, Shattered&lt;/h2&gt;
			
		&lt;/aside&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;“Nothing is being done, and then they get angry, and then there are echoes of less scientifically grounded arguments,” Myles said. “When they start saying, ‘the pharmaceutical companies are corrupting medicine,’ or ‘the FDA isn’t really doing anything to try to help us,’ or ‘everybody’s just out for the money and covering their butt,’ you start to hear echoes of chem trails and whatever. But that’s not them, right? They’re making good points.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He didn’t think there was some profit-motivated Big Pharma cover-up. Steroids were old drugs, patents long since expired, now sold as cheap generics. Yes, they were prescribed often, and companies got revenue from them. To him, the denials and dismissals likely had a simpler, less nefarious explanation: experts’ fear of not knowing, of having been wrong, of having potentially caused harm, of going against the professional grain. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;On TSW social media, you could see that some people, frustrated with mainstream medicine, had turned elsewhere, willing to try anything. Had anyone tried CBD? Had anyone tried fasting? What about ivermectin? Red-light therapy? Restricting water intake and moisturizer use? What about one specific clinic in Thailand offering cold atmospheric plasma? A possible association with the fringes didn’t exactly draw researchers in. Barta had heard from one doctor who’d backed off from publishing on TSW because she didn’t want to cloud her kid’s future in dermatology. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Myles was freer from those sorts of pressures than most. As an intramural NIH researcher, his lab had an annual budget. While every project still had to go through multiple approvals, he wasn’t fighting to convince reviewers that an idea was worth funding. Plus, he wasn’t a dermatologist. “I’m not in their pecking order,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nor was he afraid of scientific conflict. In 2023, he’d self-published a book about “how population genetics failed the populace.” In both the academic press and on YouTube, he has called out specific other researchers for what he sees as scientific racism. “Keep in mind, I’m a guy who’s busy spraying people with bacteria to try to treat their skin disease, so everybody knows this guy does things a little differently,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;If the royal court of American eczema research wouldn’t take this on, Myles thought, he might just do a little study himself. When he wrote to Barta about the idea, she began to cry.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/E7E78402-6B29-4E51-A6AD-FA3E25A49226_1_105_c.jpeg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/E7E78402-6B29-4E51-A6AD-FA3E25A49226_1_105_c.jpeg" alt="" class="wp-image-1416249" srcset="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/E7E78402-6B29-4E51-A6AD-FA3E25A49226_1_105_c.jpeg 784w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/E7E78402-6B29-4E51-A6AD-FA3E25A49226_1_105_c-328x428.jpeg 328w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/E7E78402-6B29-4E51-A6AD-FA3E25A49226_1_105_c-768x1003.jpeg 768w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/E7E78402-6B29-4E51-A6AD-FA3E25A49226_1_105_c-500x653.jpeg 500w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/E7E78402-6B29-4E51-A6AD-FA3E25A49226_1_105_c-640x836.jpeg 640w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/E7E78402-6B29-4E51-A6AD-FA3E25A49226_1_105_c-441x576.jpeg 441w" sizes="auto, (min-width: 625px) and (max-width: 767px) 719px, (min-width: 768px) and (max-width: 899px) 835px, (min-width: 900px) and (max-width: 1023px) 635px, (min-width: 1024px) and (max-width: 1199px) 803px, (min-width: 1200px) and (max-width: 1439px) 994px, (min-width: 1440px) 982px, 576px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Barta poses with her two children.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;wbr&gt;&lt;/wbr&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Courtesy Kelly Barta&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-steroids-world-war-ii-and-a-medical-mystery-nbsp"&gt;Steroids, World War II, and a medical mystery &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The race to develop steroids began as a matter of national security. In 1929, rheumatologist Philip Hench &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26611547/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;noticed&lt;/a&gt; that patients’ arthritis improved dramatically when they became sick with jaundice. Something similar happened, he observed, when patients experienced pregnancy or surgery — as if the body, under stress, was producing its own inflammation-fighting elixir. “Substance x,” Hench called it. The hypothesis he and chemist Edward Kendall hit on were hormones produced by the adrenal glands, which perch on the kidneys like little woolen hats.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But it was World War II that transformed this research into an urgent patriotic quest. Rumor had it that the Nazis were importing cow glands by the submarineful from Argentina; there were fears of Luftwaffe pilots, hormone-boosted to withstand higher altitudes. Apocryphal as such stories might’ve been, American science would not be outdone. When the National Research Council set priorities for government-funded wartime research, one was understanding what Hench had called “Substance x.” By 1944, a candidate had been synthesized from ox bile.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The war ended. The portfolio of studies jump-started for military ends was transferred to the burgeoning NIH, part of a plan to make the U.S. into a biomedical mecca — economic and technological dominance driven by nerds. Like many other wartime discoveries, corticosteroids had a peacetime use. When the stuff was injected into rheumatoid arthritis patients, the results seemed nothing short of magical. In 1949, there was a presentation at the Mayo Clinic with motion pictures: “On the screen the gathering saw fourteen men and women, some bedridden, some in wheel chairs, stiff of joint and ridden with pain, get up and walk briskly,” The New York Times &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/1949/04/21/archives/aid-in-rheumatoid-arthritis-is-promised-by-new-hormone-hormone-is.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt;. One man — previously too tender to be touched — had improved “to the point where he could dance a jig.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Patients clamored for cortisone. There were competing patent claims. A black market emerged. But the magic was short-lived: The first patient who’d gotten treated soon found herself in a locked psychiatric ward, at turns depressed, euphoric, and psychotic. It’s a pharmacologic tenet: What separates remedy from poison is simply a matter of use and dose. Corticosteroids are a prime example. They can quell allergic reactions, soothe rashes, curb asthma attacks, quiet the nausea of chemo, forestall organ rejection, pause the autoimmune disintegration of the colon in Crohn’s disease and of the joints in lupus — and plenty more. But with prolonged systemic exposure, the side effects are just as varied, increasing risks musculoskeletal, metabolic, cardiovascular, gastric, psychiatric, and ophthalmological. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;By the 1960s, the public had gotten so spooked about the potential dangers of corticosteroids that a whole group of commonly used drugs — which includes aspirin, naproxen, and ibuprofen — was &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/25064056/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;named&lt;/a&gt; “nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs,” specifically so people wouldn’t fear them. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;TSW slotted uncomfortably into this history. Steroids are a double-edged sword, but topical formulations are more localized and generally considered safer. Though there had been TSW-like case reports for decades, questions about safe dermatologic use burst into the public consciousness care of TikTok and Instagram. Some doctors warned of “steroid phobia,” which the patient community hated, because it suggested wariness about these drugs was unfounded, even pathological. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The answer for those patients is clearly not more steroids. That’s what’s so frustrating to me,” said Peter Lio, a dermatologist at Northwestern University who both incorporates alternative practices like acupuncture into his practice and has &lt;a href="https://openpaymentsdata.cms.gov/physician/21983" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;received&lt;/a&gt; payments from makers of newer, nonsteroidal topical drugs. Even before his name got around as the doctor to see if you have TSW — before people began to fly from New York, California, France, and New Zealand to see him, before he was even sure he believed in the diagnosis — he thought these patients had been through a vicious cycle of overuse: Eczema not responding well to treatment, doctors prescribing more and stronger courses. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Eventually, though he knew some colleagues disagreed, he realized this didn’t really look like eczema to him. These people had “red-sleeve sign,” as if their arms had been uniformly and deeply sunburned right up to a line at their wrist. They had “elephant skin,” parts of them thickened and wrinkled like a pachyderm. They had “headlight sign,” their faces affected but for a patch around their nose and upper lip. Their temperatures were dysregulated, their lymph nodes swollen, their skin flaking like crazy. “Patients refer to it as snow,” Lio said. “They sweep it up and bring me bags of it.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There were overlaps with other dermatologic conditions, but also what seemed to some like weird particularities. The explanation, though, remained unclear. As drugs, corticosteroids were an external reproduction of our bodies’ own fight-or-flight chemicals. They constricted blood vessels — and so stopping them might trigger a violent rebound dilation that didn’t stop when it should. Long-term use might be causing steroid tolerance, or throwing specific receptors out of whack, or impairing the skin’s ability to function as a barrier, which in turn triggered an inflammatory Rube Goldberg machine. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;a href="https://www.annallergy.org/article/S1081-1206(23)01507-7/fulltext" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;perspective paper&lt;/a&gt; from 2024 explained, even the most basic information was still uncertain. There was no diagnostic smoking gun doctors could use to be sure something was TSW. Risk factors included at least six months — but more often, over a year — of “inappropriate” medium- or high-potency steroid use, especially in sensitive areas like the face or genitals, though patients might quibble with some of those details. Prevalence was unknown. Onset was variable, ranging from days to months after stopping steroids. Prognosis, too, was unpredictable, with symptoms lasting months to years. It was unclear why some minority of patients got this and others didn’t, why flare-ups could differ from person to person, or what might actually help.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There was a private Facebook support group with some 27,000 members, though it was possible that some subset of those members in fact had something else. Still, it was clear that these patients were suffering. Some sequestered themselves in other rooms, hoping to spare their spouses the presence of so much agony. More than anything, they wanted these symptoms to end. But they also wanted recognition of what they were going through. On both fronts, some biological signature — a small step toward a test for TSW — could help. That was what Myles was hoping to find. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure class="wp-block-image alignwide size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14784-1024x683.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1416205" srcset="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14784-1024x683.jpg 1024w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14784-328x219.jpg 328w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14784-768x512.jpg 768w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14784-500x333.jpg 500w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14784-2048x1365.jpg 2048w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14784-1600x1067.jpg 1600w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14784-640x427.jpg 640w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14784-864x576.jpg 864w" sizes="auto, (min-width: 625px) and (max-width: 767px) 719px, (min-width: 768px) and (max-width: 899px) 835px, (min-width: 900px) and (max-width: 1023px) 635px, (min-width: 1024px) and (max-width: 1199px) 803px, (min-width: 1200px) and (max-width: 1439px) 994px, (min-width: 1440px) 982px, 576px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;A copy of Myles’ controversial study published in the Journal of Investigative Dermatology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;wbr&gt;&lt;/wbr&gt;&lt;cite&gt;André Chung for STAT&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-searching-for-the-biology-of-tsw-nbsp"&gt;Searching for the biology of TSW &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The idea was to bring three different groups of patients to the NIH — 16 with TSW, 10 with plain old eczema, and 11 healthy volunteers — and then run a battery of tests on their blood and skin to see if there was something that set TSW apart. In some analyses, those with TSW and those with eczema looked similar. Compared with the healthy volunteers, the swabs from both groups showed higher populations of Staphylococcus aureus and lower bacterial diversity, the skin biopsies showed more of the T cells and macrophages one might expect to see in a place with inflammation, and the serum samples showed the interleukins that help coordinate that sort of immune response. These bodies were all riled up, as if under attack.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What differed, though, between the two skin-disease groups appeared when Myles’ team looked at other molecules present in the skin biopsies. The TSW patients had abnormally high levels of vitamin B3, or niacin, and abnormally low levels of tryptophan, their paper reported. One possible explanation lay in the mitochondria, the tiny powerhouses of our cells, performing the daily alchemy of transmuting nutrients and oxygen into energy, which included breaking down tryptophan and producing niacin. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To Myles and Nadia Shobnam, the first author of the paper, it looked like a specific bit of mitochondrial machinery was overactive in TSW. That also jibed with an idea that was already in the scientific literature. When niacin was first used as an oral drug to fight cholesterol in the 1950s, it was limited by an uncomfortable side effect of making patients flush, their skin red, warm, and sometimes itchy — not so different from one common complaint in TSW. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But the study didn’t stop there. A colleague of Myles’ had casually mentioned that metformin, a common diabetes drug, blocked the specific bit of mitochondrial machinery they thought was working overtime, and an herbal supplement called berberine — “nature’s Ozempic,” according to a &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/berberine-social-media-trend/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;social media&lt;/a&gt; fad — had a similar chemical effect. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Myles wasn’t about to turn this pilot study into a randomized controlled trial of these compounds, but he told the participants who had TSW that they could try either of these substances on their own, and that if they did, he wanted to hear how their symptoms changed. Based on lab analyses, he helped counsel patients about which berberine vendors were actually selling what they said they were; otherwise, to him, they might as well be trying sawdust.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Three patients got metformin prescriptions from their doctors, nine ordered berberine online, and within three to five months, they tended to report improvements in the “bone-deep itch” and some clearance of their rashes, though their TSW still sometimes flared up occasionally. These results might be attributable to the placebo effect; after all, these patients’ experiences were being compared to the expected course of TSW — hardly the level of evidence doctors hope for when considering a therapy. Still, it seemed worth a shot; the TSW community was desperate. When the manuscript was ready, it contained, along with graphs and signaling-pathway charts, a few before-and-after photos.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity is-style-default"&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-thank-you-for-giving-us-credibility"&gt;‘Thank you for giving us credibility’&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;When a patient community feels ignored and gaslit by the institutions of medicine, and members of those institutions worry that patient stories aren’t entirely reliable as data, pressure builds. Every study becomes a battleground. In April 2024, Myles’ team &lt;a href="https://www.medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2024.04.17.24305846v1" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;posted&lt;/a&gt; the paper on a preprint server, not yet peer-reviewed. In early May, Myles &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TSFiKlrIDUI" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;broke down&lt;/a&gt; the results for patients on YouTube. In the comments section, the relief was palpable. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“As someone who has been going through TSW, this study has been an incredible gift, and I feel like a weight has been lifted off my shoulders. We have so much more work to do, but you just opened the door to let other reputable people such as yourself take this topic seriously,” one person wrote.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;“Thank you for giving us credibility and proof of our condition,” wrote another. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Other researchers weren’t convinced this paper counted as proof, though, once it &lt;a href="https://www.jidonline.org/article/S0022-202X(25)00014-4/abstract" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;came out&lt;/a&gt; in the Journal of Investigative Dermatology in August 2025. To some, there was a gnarly old problem of diagnostic criteria. Though Myles had established a framework for how many symptoms a patient had to have to qualify for participation, the symptoms remained self-reported. “How do you know you are describing the same condition?” asked Eugene Tan, a dermatologist at the University of New South Wales, in Australia, who &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40696952/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;coauthored&lt;/a&gt; a critique of the paper. He worried that the criteria were based on a survey done by the International Topical Steroid Awareness Network, the patient advocacy group that Barta had led, and that without a less subjective diagnosis, the study results didn’t mean much. “How do you know that these patients are not primed to say stuff you want them to say? In court, you’d say, ‘leading question, your honor.’”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The first thing I would like is for it to be determined whether topical steroid withdrawal exists in the first place,” he added in an email. He didn’t mean to dismiss the experience of TSW sufferers, but to him, compliance was the Achilles’ heel of any topical treatment, making it tough to differentiate between TSW and eczema that was poorly controlled by a drug not being taken as directed; he has eczema himself and knows how difficult such regimens are to keep. Before anything, he wanted to see a study chronicling the natural history of eczema when investigators are monitoring how and when patients apply creams. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Two researchers in the U.K., meanwhile, wrote a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40480485/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;critique&lt;/a&gt; from the opposite perspective. They trusted TSW patient experiences, but they worried that this NIH study oversold its results and that the evidence for mitochondrial involvement remained “speculative.” Myles and Shobnam &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40562352/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;responded&lt;/a&gt; in print, claiming the letter writers had misunderstood the technical details they were picking apart. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Beneath this back-and-forth lay the very murk that scared some researchers away from this topic in the first place. Designing a TSW study could be a high-stakes puzzle; satisfying both those agnostic to whether the condition is real and those who are suffering from it was unlikely if not impossible. The combination of patient desperation and lack of scientific interest meant that there was a risk for any finding to be seen as &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; answer, case closed, rather than one small step in an iterative accumulation of evidence. That was the irony. Though they disagreed about what it might look like, every side in the dispute about Myles’ study wanted the same thing: more research.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14814.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14814-1024x1536.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1416209" srcset="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14814-1024x1536.jpg 1024w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14814-328x492.jpg 328w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14814-768x1152.jpg 768w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14814-500x750.jpg 500w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14814-640x960.jpg 640w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14814-384x576.jpg 384w, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Research-14814.jpg 1600w" sizes="auto, (min-width: 625px) and (max-width: 767px) 719px, (min-width: 768px) and (max-width: 899px) 835px, (min-width: 900px) and (max-width: 1023px) 635px, (min-width: 1024px) and (max-width: 1199px) 803px, (min-width: 1200px) and (max-width: 1439px) 994px, (min-width: 1440px) 982px, 576px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Myles, a commissioned officer in the U.S. Public Health Service, poses in his uniform.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;wbr&gt;&lt;/wbr&gt;&lt;cite&gt;André Chung for STAT&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-frozen-credit-cards-layoffs-shifting-priorities"&gt;Frozen credit cards, layoffs, shifting priorities&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That had been Myles’ plan. In January 2025, even before the paper had officially come out, he was ready to request approval for a bigger berberine trial. It would’ve involved around100 people. But then, under the Trump 2.0 mandate for a slimmer, more “efficient” federal apparatus, the credit cards NIH workers used to buy supplies were temporarily frozen. Getting berberine, biopsy punches, microbiome swabs, and chemicals for molecular tests would have to wait. Plus, some of the employees involved in purchasing had left or been laid off. “When they told us, ‘OK, you can purchase now,’ you’re like, how? And so then we all had to file for what we call purchase cards. And that took several months,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;These slowdowns weren’t the only reason Myles set aside his next TSW study. In October, Shobnam, the initial paper’s first author, left the NIH for personal reasons, not political ones, with the idea of potentially collecting samples from her TSW patients in New Jersey and sending them back to her old place of work for analysis. But that wasn’t certain. “My new job is purely clinical, and I haven’t had any time for research yet,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;TSW was also a side project for Myles. His main research on environmental factors and eczema dovetailed with what he saw as the priorities laid out under health secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. He doesn’t blame the new administration or take it personally. It would not have been impossible for him to pursue more TSW research; it just would’ve been slower. With competing demands on his time, he chose the sort of science he was best at, uncertain that whatever would emerge from the follow-up trial he’d planned would warrant the hurdles involved. “The juice-to-squeeze ratio has shifted,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He’s philosophical about the fact that this is the nature of his job as a government scientist. Priorities change. Cancer moonshots come and go. Agency budgets fluctuate. Staffing numbers rise and fall. “If Secretary Kennedy came down and said, ‘Oh my God, I can’t believe a pharmaceutical is doing all this, we’ve got to research this, give this man $10 million and go do it,’ I’m not going to tell him no,” Myles said. “So I have to deal with the reality of the flip side of that. If they want to make it harder to do research, that’s also part of our existence. The administration’s priorities change, and we adapt. But it is true that part of the adaptation in this particular case is that we just can’t commit to starting an entire trial again.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;To a mind bent on smaller government, such refocusing might be a cause for celebration. It’s not as though all TSW research would stop. The two U.K. researchers who’d critiqued Myles’ study were &lt;a href="https://www.isrctn.com/ISRCTN49789010" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;recruiting&lt;/a&gt; patients to try to look for biological patterns among this patient population. They would be taking saliva samples in addition to skin and blood, to figure out whether long-term topical steroids had suppressed the body’s own production of such chemicals, which might be at the root of some of these symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Barta has, herself, a healthy suspicion of the federal bureaucracy. She’d long thought that agencies needed to be better held accountable to taxpayers. But as someone who’d spent years pushing to understand TSW, this slowdown in Myles’ lab felt like a blow. “I understand the need for a shake-up,” she said, “but it really has set things back and pushed pause and been super frustrating.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The steroids at the center of the whole controversy had emerged from a sense that biomedical science was a patriotic public good — a boon for the war effort and for the U.S. as a whole. That in turn became a midcentury surge in research, symbolized by the behemoth that is the NIH. Knowledge production, the thinking went, could boost economies, create jobs, reduce illness, and lengthen lives. In this grand sweep, a relatively small berberine trial for a potentially rare illness may seem insignificant. The supplement was hardly the surefire cure that the TSW community was hoping for, according to those who’d tried it. Yet these ongoing steroidal questions, some 75 years after these drugs were introduced, are just one example of how science builds upon itself — and of what might be lost in weakening the structure that undergirds it. Even Myles’ critics worry about the loss of momentum that his scrapped protocol represents. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It’s really quite sad, because science is just a tool to find the truth. Someone needed to publish this, and someone needed to critique it,” said Tan, of Myles’ initial study. The issues he’d raised were not an admonishment to stop but a reason to keep going, to look deeper. “Hopefully, he’ll respond by saying, ‘I am going to validate this, I am going to prove you wrong.’ I hope he succeeds.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:32:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQenVLNHpVd1hHMl9INGNxSy14YUdKT1BhSklvbV9WVVhnUWJORkl0T2R2dmlzOHg3UWlfX0t2bXpJbHM2OW41YzZESkJSMEFrR01NemJlRHNqMnBQQTA5UEFQUkt5R19nUmpXSEhibnNJN0RTZW9lenhaS2pocHBNaEg2eFRDTng0eUhOdUk5YWUxbW5MbHVMbzF2UUNSRDI4OHQyMkVsT2c</guid></item><item><title>Ozempic可能会告诉我们关于阿尔茨海默氏症未来的信息- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/22/ozempic-alzheimers-iconic-drugs/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the weeks leading up to Dec. 3, I imagined a fantastic headline: “Ozempic treats Alzheimer’s disease.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;On that day, at the &lt;a href="https://www.ctad-alzheimer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;CtAD 2025&lt;/a&gt; meeting (CtAD stands for Clinical Trials in Alzheimer’s Disease), in the Sapphire Ballroom of the Hilton San Diego Bayfront hotel, Novo Nordisk would present to the assembly of scientists and biopharma executives the results of its &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT04777409" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;EVOKE studies&lt;/a&gt;, two clinical trials testing whether semaglutide can treat people with early-stage symptomatic Alzheimer’s disease. Semaglutide is, of course, the chemical name for the brand Ozempic, &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/drugsatfda_docs/label/2023/209637s020s021lbl.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;FDA labeled&lt;/a&gt; for the treatment of diabetes and to reduce the risk of major cardiovascular events, but widely known as &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2023/03/05/weight-loss-drugs-changing-obesity-narrative/?utm_campaign=morning_rounds&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;_hsenc=p2ANqtz-9KN2JWKLzSKiD7sRYCvdv-qYG-yk9UCPvkV3ORcAgdmFdtdf46SeUuHJcZJaT7a6jmAsAL0zy2b-nIDUdeiHmTt0Zf7FMIVJG0lSw8-VBaDjhZ_IQ&amp;amp;_hsmi=389884444&amp;amp;utm_content=389884444&amp;amp;utm_source=hs_email"&gt;a drug for obesity&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Widely known — that’s an understatement.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker article" aria-labelledby="restricted-story-heading" aria-describedby="restricted-story-description" checked&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-bar"&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-text"&gt;STAT+ Exclusive Story&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-login"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;img class="restricted-content-breaker-bg" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-breaker-bg.png" alt="STAT+"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper"&gt;
				&lt;span class="stat-paywall-archive"&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/"&gt;
						&lt;img class="stat-plus-logo" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-logo-white.svg" alt="STAT+"&gt;
					&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/span&gt;
				&lt;h2 id="restricted-story-heading"&gt;This article is exclusive to STAT+ subscribers&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;h3 id="restricted-story-description"&gt;Unlock this article — plus in-depth analysis, newsletters, premium events, and news alerts.&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper-cta mobile"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta mobile"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-cards"&gt;
					&lt;div class="slider-container" aria-label="Subscription plan toggle"&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="individual" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Individual plans&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;p class="switch" role="switch" tabindex="0" aria-checked="false"&gt;
							&lt;button class="slider"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="group" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Group plans&lt;/button&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
							

		
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button view-all" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker view all plans" aria-label="View All Plans"&gt;View All Plans&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="restricted-message-breaker"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-wrapper"&gt;
								
								&lt;div class="restricted-content-message"&gt;
					&lt;p class="restricted-content-text"&gt;
						To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.					&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button restricted-button" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker subscribe cta 1"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
								
							&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:32:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE95RUVROEZCcklCQzI2eVpEejNBazVpMWpMbVFNSEVxSjhlQnBGLVRmZmhueW9jb0lSbThYWW5iM2EzQWZvM3VJNkYxYW95Wm9zNDA2QU82bkxjbWc0MW5RcTV2aDBiOWloaXFxdld0N1B6RVZEV3pV</guid></item><item><title>暴风雨前的平静：洪堡手表流感激增，因为呼吸道疾病在全州占主导地位-红发黑带</title><link>https://kymkemp.com/2025/12/22/calm-before-the-storm-humboldt-watches-for-flu-surge-as-respiratory-illness-dominates-statewide/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Redheaded Blackbelt</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:03:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixgFBVV95cUxNTFI4Zk11T21McHFiRTRuby1hakQ2VGlsZ2QwTDVKOHl3MnNXaXlmZjZFRjNFblVud0dYZHMwWWtISVFpTTdPR2VaaWlUaXRTY29RZTkzN3JldlJxRHZnUWMwdGFjdGc4dUlzU0ZraUpqTmpobVJKWHl0UXBPYlhXdWN3QXB6M3B5U01veUdhaEFRTXhKcHRnNU15NG1WWDhjU05udkhOMjZzX3BpRHFXYjVTQUhHejFYTTRzYjBtSUlFeUEtRXc</guid></item><item><title>质子泵抑制剂受到严格审查：风险有多大？ - Medscape</title><link>https://www.medscape.com/viewarticle/proton-pump-inhibitors-under-scrutiny-how-real-risk-2025a1000zxh</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since their development and widespread adoption in the late 1980s, proton pump inhibitors (PPI) have transformed the field of gastroenterology. Their high efficacy and favorable safety profiles have made them essential in the management of potentially life-threatening conditions, including &lt;a href="https://emedicine.medscape.com/article/181753-overview" class="cl_ref_article"&gt;peptic ulcer disease&lt;/a&gt; and upper gastrointestinal bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite their established role, PPI have been increasingly &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/ajg/pages/articleviewer.aspx?year=2019&amp;amp;issue=02000&amp;amp;article=00017&amp;amp;type=Abstract" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;portrayed as harmful&lt;/a&gt;. Claims in both the scientific literature and general media have raised concerns about possible long-term adverse effects. This perception has become widespread, leading nearly 40% of individuals to discontinue PPI, most without informing their clinician, primarily because of the fear of side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For clinicians, the growing disconnect between evidence and perceptions has practical consequences. Distinguishing between speculative associations, confirmed adverse effects, and inappropriate prescriptions is essential to ensure rational use and maintain patient confidence in effective therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Associations Without Proven Causality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of the criticism directed at PPI in recent years has been based on retrospective studies, linking their use to outcomes such as dementia, fractures, kidney disease, and &lt;a href="https://emedicine.medscape.com/article/278744-overview" class="cl_ref_article"&gt;gastric cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In most instances, these findings represent &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/apt.13324" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;statistical associations&lt;/a&gt; rather than causal relationships and are strongly influenced by confounding factors, including advanced age, polypharmacy, and underlying comorbidities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their potent acid-suppressive effects are associated with &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/apt.13324" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;structural and functional changes&lt;/a&gt; in the gastric mucosa, including enterochromaffin-like cell hyperplasia and &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/apt.13800" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;fundic gland&lt;/a&gt; polyps. Evidence indicates that these findings are largely benign and do not warrant specific endoscopic surveillance in most cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The association between PPI and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/6605024" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;gastric cancer&lt;/a&gt; was initially suggested in studies published over a decade ago. However, subsequent meta-analyses have questioned these findings, highlighting the potential methodological biases. These include the failure to account for &lt;em&gt;Helicobacter pylori&lt;/em&gt; infection, a &lt;a href="https://www.cghjournal.org/article/S1542-3565(16)30205-1/fulltext" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;well-established&lt;/a&gt; and independent &lt;a href="https://gut.bmj.com/content/55/11/1538" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;gastric carcinogen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Defined Risks, Limited Magnitude&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some adverse effects that are clearly associated with PPI use have been well described. The risk for &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/ajg/abstract/2012/07000/risk_ofclostridium_difficileinfection_with_acid.11.aspx" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Clostridioides difficile&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; infection increased modestly, with an odds ratio of 1.74 (95% CI, 1.47-2.85; &lt;em&gt;P&lt;/em&gt; &amp;lt; .001). This risk is higher in hospitalized individuals and those receiving concurrent antibiotic therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The association between &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0024320518308592?via%3Dihub" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;osteoporosis and fractures&lt;/a&gt; is a frequently cited concern. Meta-analyses confirm a small increase in risk, with a relative risk of 1.3 (95% CI, 1.16-1.45). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, there is no convincing evidence of a clinically relevant long-term effect of PPI on &lt;a href="https://www.gastrojournal.org/article/S0016-5085(09)02030-7/fulltext?referrer=https%3A%2F%2Fpubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov%2F" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;bone metabolism&lt;/a&gt; in humans. These findings suggest that residual confounding factors, such as frailty or advanced age, may account for much of the observed associations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerns regarding the interaction with &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1007964" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;clopidogrel now appear&lt;/a&gt; to be largely resolved. Randomized clinical trials have not shown an increased incidence of cardiovascular events in patients treated with PPI. Pharmacokinetic interactions are primarily limited to &lt;a href="https://reference.medscape.com/drug/prilosec-omeprazole-341997" class="cl_ref_drugs"&gt;omeprazole&lt;/a&gt; and can be avoided by using alternative agents such as &lt;a href="https://reference.medscape.com/drug/prevacid-solu-tab-lansoprazole-341991" class="cl_ref_drugs"&gt;lansoprazole&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://reference.medscape.com/drug/aciphex-rabeprazole-342002" class="cl_ref_drugs"&gt;rabeprazole&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Central Issue: Inappropriate Prescribing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most tangible and clinically relevant risk associated with PPI use is their unnecessary prolonged use. Treatment should be reviewed periodically, particularly after the eradication of &lt;em&gt;H pylori&lt;/em&gt; infection or the discontinuation of nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When no clear ongoing indication exists, gradual dose reduction or withdrawal should be considered to minimize the risk for rebound acid hypersecretion following &lt;a href="https://www.gastrojournal.org/article/S0016-5085(09)00522-8/fulltext?referrer=https%3A%2F%2Fpubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov%2F" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;abrupt discontinuation&lt;/a&gt;. Deprescribing should not be understood as depriving patients of effective therapies. Rather, it should reflect an ongoing individual assessment of benefits and risks over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PPI remains one of the most reliable pillars of digestive therapies. Their introduction has fundamentally altered clinical outcomes, prognosis, and mortality in conditions that, until recently, lacked effective treatment options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portraying these drugs as inherently dangerous risks causes more harm than benefit by fostering fear and undermining trust in life-saving interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The priority should not be restriction driven by media alarm, but to ensure that each prescription is clinically justified with an appropriate duration and responsible follow-up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Conflicts of interest of the authors of the cited studies are available in their original publications.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story was translated from&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.univadis.es/viewarticle/inhibidores-bomba-protones-un-riesgo-real-2025a1000y09" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Univadis Spain&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, part of the Medscape Professional Network.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medscape</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 07:30:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNVWkzZDVzb2tINlowMHZCTkp3QVdvVVl2UWR5UnlzWGV4cndDdGpMc0lveWtfSVl1bElpVlMzMVFPMGRhT3VJb1VoNmh3bk5SVzAwbVBqcHZSVWdXQVVodEZlaWVSQ2ZSaTA4RnNreGpJQkd0aGVsRW1TWkZoNmxWT0hUTzI2UXctTkZqenRxS3V3NzI1VTY3N0FXVmptN3hKQXQw</guid></item><item><title>帕金森的突破改变了我们对多巴胺的了解- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251221043225.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A new study led by researchers at McGill University is calling into question a long-standing idea about how dopamine influences movement. The findings suggest a shift in how scientists understand Parkinson's disease and how its treatments work.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research, published in &lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;, shows that dopamine does not directly control how fast or how forcefully a person moves, as many experts previously believed. Instead, dopamine appears to provide the basic conditions that allow movement to happen in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Our findings suggest we should rethink dopamine's role in movement," said senior author Nicolas Tritsch, Assistant Professor in McGill's Department of Psychiatry and researcher at the Douglas Research Centre. "Restoring dopamine to a normal level may be enough to improve movement. That could simplify how we think about Parkinson's treatment."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Dopamine Does in Parkinson's Disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dopamine plays a key role in motor vigor, which refers to the ability to move with speed and strength. In people with Parkinson's disease, the brain cells that produce dopamine gradually break down. This loss leads to hallmark symptoms such as slow movement, tremors, and problems with balance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Levodopa, the most common treatment for Parkinson's, helps restore movement by increasing dopamine levels in the brain. However, scientists have not fully understood why the drug is so effective. In recent years, improved brain-monitoring tools detected brief spikes of dopamine during movement. These rapid bursts led many researchers to think dopamine directly controlled movement intensity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new findings challenge that assumption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dopamine Acts as Support, Not a Speed Controller&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study suggests dopamine does not act as a moment-by-moment controller of movement. Instead, it serves a more fundamental role.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Rather than acting as a throttle that sets movement speed, dopamine appears to function more like engine oil. It's essential for the system to run, but not the signal that determines how fast each action is executed," said Tritsch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracking Dopamine in Real Time&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To test this idea, the researchers monitored brain activity in mice while the animals pressed a weighted lever. Using a light-based method, they were able to switch dopamine-producing cells "on" or "off" during the task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If rapid dopamine bursts were responsible for movement vigor, changing dopamine levels at that exact moment should have altered how fast or forcefully the mice moved. Instead, adjusting dopamine activity during movement made no difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the researchers tested levodopa, they found that the drug improved movement by raising the brain's overall dopamine level. It did not work by restoring the short-lived dopamine bursts that occur during motion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toward More Targeted Parkinson's Treatments&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than 110,000 Canadians are currently living with Parkinson's disease, and that number is expected to more than double by 2050 as the population ages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the researchers, a better understanding of why levodopa works could guide the development of future treatments that focus on maintaining steady dopamine levels rather than targeting rapid dopamine signals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings also encourage researchers to reexamine older treatment strategies. Dopamine receptor agonists have shown benefits in the past but often caused side effects because they affected large areas of the brain. The new insight may help scientists design safer therapies that act more precisely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Study&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Subsecond dopamine fluctuations do not specify the vigor of ongoing actions" by Haixin Liu and Nicolas Tritsch et al., was published in &lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study was funded by the Canada First Research Excellence Fund, awarded through the Healthy Brains, Healthy Lives initiative at McGill University and the Fonds de Recherche du Québec.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 06:40:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBnMW9NU05ONlNoZlhMb0tqZnRTTDNtQkFsbmhBR1NsbjB1Smc5dU4tdGpFUlhsU0pHMmlOZG9HZ1g4SDM4WHRteGpFZGRjR19lN0NmczJqeGIxUFl0YkJ2TU9EWFBJNEJ1QUVxOUVTVQ</guid></item><item><title>8种缓慢、不性感的习惯，悄悄地融入非凡的稳定生活-硅运河</title><link>https://siliconcanals.com/c-bt-8-slow-unsexy-habits-that-quietly-compound-into-extraordinary-life-of-stability/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Silicon Canals</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 06:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxPR016UmxDbmpLMnhuRl80eG1kRVoxbzg1c0ZaRnV3azBtazdRazQwLVdrTHFJak96NHU3TUZla3JNZlFGcVhmcUlLNVc2UDJBQmp0WWQtMDRiZmhmTFlIVndvT0xwOEkyWlRBM1dIQ3N0SXRpNmtmS2JvS2dRcjVMcTE3QjIwanhvWnVYUnRpYUh4SzRiZHdERFZsWmNQeVlzallSOTMtWGFPS2MweUMxYg</guid></item><item><title>传统的巴西植物显示出对抗关节炎的意想不到的力量- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251221043237.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A research team in Brazil has found strong evidence that the Joseph's Coat plant (Alternanthera littoralis) is both safe and effective at reducing inflammation, easing pain, and protecting against arthritis. The study was carried out by scientists from the Federal University of Grande Dourados (UFGD), the State University of Campinas (UNICAMP), and São Paulo State University (UNESP).&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Joseph's Coat grows naturally along Brazil's coastline and has long been used in traditional medicine to treat inflammation, infections, and parasitic illnesses. Despite its widespread use, there had been little scientific research confirming whether these benefits were real or whether the plant was safe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Identifying Active Compounds and Testing Anti Inflammatory Effects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study, published in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of Ethnopharmacology&lt;/em&gt;, began with a detailed chemical analysis of the plant. Researchers examined the ethanolic extract made from the plant's aerial parts to determine which bioactive compounds it contained. This phase of the work was led by Marcos Salvador, a pharmacist from the Institute of Biology (IB) at UNICAMP.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After identifying the compounds, the research moved to biological testing. A team led by pharmacologist Cândida Kassuya from the Faculty of Health Sciences at UFGD evaluated how well the extract reduced inflammation in experimental models of arthritis. Toxicological testing followed to assess safety. "Finally, we performed the toxicological analyses under my coordination," explains Arielle Cristina Arena, associate professor in the Department of Structural and Functional Biology at the Institute of Biosciences at UNESP's Botucatu Campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Laboratory Results Show Reduced Inflammation and Joint Damage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The experiments revealed that the ethanolic extract of A. littoralis significantly lowered inflammation in laboratory animals. "In the experimental models, we observed reduced edema, improved joint parameters, and modulation of inflammatory mediators, suggesting antioxidant and tissue-protective actions," says Arena.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These findings indicate that the plant does more than reduce swelling. The results also suggest that it may help protect joint tissue and limit damage associated with inflammatory conditions like arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Promising Safety Profile With Limits on Immediate Use&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Arena, the results strengthen the scientific case for the plant's medicinal value and provide a foundation for future preclinical studies. The findings also point to a favorable safety profile at therapeutic doses, which could be encouraging for eventual human use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, the researchers caution that the extract is not ready for clinical application. Additional toxicological testing, human clinical trials, and standardized preparation methods are still required to confirm safety, effectiveness, and quality. Regulatory approval would also be necessary before any therapeutic use.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supporting Biodiversity Through Science&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This research is part of an ongoing line of investigation developed by UFGD, UNESP, and UNICAMP, and our purpose is to value Brazilian biodiversity and traditional knowledge, but with a rigorous scientific basis, promoting the safe and rational use of natural products," says Arena.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research received funding from FAPESP (projects 06/06079-4, 09/05992-6, 15/03726-8, 16/06407-3, 17/19523-4, and 21/09693-5).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 05:47:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBZaDQxdW1KT251cUhXWl9fZVZYamd4ZnNpcjJUOHpkSDJWQldTaUxpN2c5d0d6TjlFZ19FNXRrTmRYVnNDTy1ySm1XcmlUZlA0R3Ayb2dOd2Zqc2U4RnlHaDJLZHNJczVKR0ptNEliRQ</guid></item><item><title>一种蛋白质比胆固醇更能预测心脏病- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/one-protein-is-a-better-predictor-of-heart-disease-than-cholesterol</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Heart disease is the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/products/databriefs/db521.htm"&gt;leading cause of death in the United States&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since researchers first established the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/14364826/"&gt;link between diet, cholesterol and heart disease in the 1950s&lt;/a&gt;, risk for heart disease has been partly assessed based on a patient's cholesterol levels, which can be routinely measured via blood work at the doctor's office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1161/01.CIR.97.20.2007"&gt;accumulating evidence over the past two decades&lt;/a&gt; demonstrates that a biomarker called &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diagnostics/23056-c-reactive-protein-crp-test"&gt;C-reactive protein&lt;/a&gt; – which signals the presence of low-grade inflammation – is a better predictor of risk for heart disease than cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/huge-study-finds-inflammation-could-be-a-core-feature-of-depression"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/poor-oral-hygiene-could-be-taking-a-toll-on-your-heart-expert-says"&gt;Poor Oral Hygiene Could Be Taking a Toll on Your Heart, Expert Says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, in September 2025, the American College of Cardiology published &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jacc.2025.08.047"&gt;new recommendations for universal screening of&lt;/a&gt; C-reactive protein levels in all patients, alongside measuring cholesterol levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_186417" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-186417" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/GlowyGoldLiverInBlueTorsoOutline.jpg" alt="Glowy gold liver in blue outlined torso" class="wp-image-186417 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/GlowyGoldLiverInBlueTorsoOutline.jpg 683w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/GlowyGoldLiverInBlueTorsoOutline-642x481.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/GlowyGoldLiverInBlueTorsoOutline-600x450.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 683px) 100vw, 683px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-186417" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The liver produces C-reactive protein. (Sebastian Kaulitzki/Science Photo Library/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is C-reactive protein?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;C-reactive protein is created by the liver in response to infections, tissue damage, chronic inflammatory states from conditions like autoimmune diseases, and metabolic disturbances like obesity and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="186391" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;. Essentially, it is a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJMra2206346"&gt;marker of inflammation&lt;/a&gt; – meaning &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/what-is-inflammation-two-immunologists-explain-how-the-body-responds-to-everything-from-stings-to-vaccination-and-why-it-sometimes-goes-wrong-193503"&gt;immune system activation&lt;/a&gt; – in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;C-reactive protein can be easily measured with blood work at the doctor's office. A low C-reactive protein level – under 1 milligram per deciliter – signifies minimal inflammation in the body, which is protective against heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An elevated C-reactive protein level of greater than 3 milligrams per deciliter, signifies increased levels of inflammation and thus &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/biomedicines11092444"&gt;increased risk for heart disease&lt;/a&gt;. About 52 percent of Americans have an &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJM200504143521525"&gt;elevated level of C-reactive protein&lt;/a&gt; in their blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research shows that C-reactive protein is a better predictive marker for heart attacks and strokes than &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJMoa2405182"&gt;"bad," or LDL cholesterol, short for low-density lipoprotein&lt;/a&gt;, as well as another commonly measured genetically inherited biomarker called &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/nejmoa2405182"&gt;lipoprotein(a)&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One study found that C-reactive protein &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S0140-6736(09)61717-7"&gt;can predict heart disease just as well as blood pressure can&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does inflammation matter in heart disease?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflammation plays a crucial role at every stage in the development and buildup of fatty plaque in the arteries, which causes a condition called &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/arteriosclerosis-atherosclerosis/symptoms-causes/syc-20350569"&gt;atherosclerosis&lt;/a&gt; that can &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1161/hc0902.104353"&gt;lead to heart attacks and strokes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the moment a blood vessel is damaged, be it &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.5772/intechopen.71433"&gt;from high blood sugar&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1046/j.1365-2613.2000.00162.x"&gt;cigarette smoke&lt;/a&gt;, immune cells immediately infiltrate the area. Those immune cells subsequently engulf cholesterol particles that are typically floating around in the blood stream to form a fatty plaque that resides in the wall of the vessel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related:&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-mouth-and-your-heart-are-connected-gum-disease-linked-to-heart-risks"&gt; 'Your Mouth And Your Heart Are Connected': Gum Disease Linked to Heart Risks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This process continues for decades until eventually, one day, immune mediators rupture the cap that encloses the plaque. This triggers the formation of a blood clot that obstructs blood flow, starves the surrounding tissues of oxygen and ultimately causes a heart attack or stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence, cholesterol is only part of the story; it is, in fact, the immune system that facilitates each step in the processes that drive heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Can diet influence C-reactive protein levels?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lifestyle can significantly influence the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/2047487319885458"&gt;amount of C-reactive protein produced by the liver&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Numerous foods and nutrients have been shown to lower C-reactive protein levels, including &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3109/09637486.2014.959898"&gt;dietary fiber from foods like beans, vegetables, nuts and seeds&lt;/a&gt;, as well as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.fct.2019.110922"&gt;berries&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/10408398.2025.2525446"&gt;olive oil&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ctim.2019.08.019"&gt;green tea&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12986-024-00847-3"&gt;chia seeds&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.prostaglandins.2024.106868"&gt;flaxseeds&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/archinte.167.1.31"&gt;Weight loss&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/bjsports-2016-095999"&gt;and exercise&lt;/a&gt; can also reduce C-reactive protein levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Does cholesterol still matter for heart disease risk?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though cholesterol may not be the most important predictor of risk for heart disease, it does remain highly relevant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it's not just the amount of cholesterol – or more specifically the amount of bad, or LDL, cholesterol – that matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two people with the same cholesterol level don't necessarily have the same risk for heart disease. This is because risk is determined more so by the number of particles that the bad cholesterol is packaged into, as opposed to the total mass of bad cholesterol that's floating around. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1161/CIRCULATIONAHA.124.068885"&gt;More particles means higher risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is why a blood test known as &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diagnostics/24992-apolipoprotein-b-test"&gt;apolipoprotein B&lt;/a&gt;, which measures the number of cholesterol particles, is a better predictor of risk for heart disease than &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamacardio.2021.5083"&gt;measurements of total amounts of bad cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like cholesterol and C-reactive protein, apolipoprotein B is also influenced by lifestyle factors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1055/a-2580-0722"&gt;like exercise&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12944-019-1094-4"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt; and diet. Nutrients like &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1017/S0954422416000147"&gt;fiber, nuts and omega-3 fatty acids&lt;/a&gt; are associated with a decreased number of cholesterol particles, while &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu9030211"&gt;increased sugar intake is associated with a larger number&lt;/a&gt; of cholesterol particles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/cholesterol/genetic-conditions/lipoprotein-a"&gt;lipoprotein(a)&lt;/a&gt;, a protein that lives in the wall surrounding cholesterol particles, is another marker that &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1161/ATV.0000000000000147"&gt;can predict heart disease more accurately than cholesterol levels&lt;/a&gt;. This is because the presence of lipoprotein(a) makes cholesterol particles sticky, so to speak, and thus more likely to get trapped in an atherosclerotic plaque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, unlike other risk factors, lipoprotein(a) levels are purely genetic, thus not influenced by lifestyle, and need only be measured once in a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/huge-study-finds-inflammation-could-be-a-core-feature-of-depression"&gt;Huge Study Finds Inflammation Could Be a Core Feature of Depression&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What's the best way to prevent heart disease?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, heart disease is the product of many risk factors and their interactions over a lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Therefore, preventing heart disease is way more complicated than &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/jn/128.2.449S"&gt;simply eating a cholesterol-free diet, as once thought&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing your LDL cholesterol level alongside your C-reactive protein, apolipoprotein B and lipoprotein (a) levels paints a comprehensive picture of risk that can hopefully help motivate long-term commitment to the &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-lifestyle/how-to-help-prevent-heart-disease-at-any-age"&gt;fundamentals of heart disease prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These include eating well, exercising consistently, getting adequate sleep, managing stress productively, maintaining healthy weight and, if applicable, quitting smoking.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/271143/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/mary-j-scourboutakos-1518645"&gt;Mary J. Scourboutakos&lt;/a&gt;, Adjunct Assistant Professor in Family and Community Medicine, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/macon-and-joan-brock-virginia-health-sciences-at-old-dominion-university-6646"&gt;Macon &amp;amp; Joan Brock Virginia Health Sciences at Old Dominion University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/how-c-reactive-protein-outpaced-bad-cholesterol-as-leading-heart-disease-risk-marker-271143"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 03:02:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNdGxIZ2VRT3lzTVJnRDdRa25OUndaTGt3QkhsOUdSZEVkdVhWUDNHcHhubFllX09TbXJZRGdveEwwdG9IQWl0Rzd5dmFkcGk5VmtyblJXTzR2S2hPSzNTbjVzdG1pVHZkLXhvTW82OHBkU2JQTnpUNzBXSi1veEh4dC1WLXRaV1BjajNrLWVnV2JUYUtjU2JtRmxXT3E</guid></item><item><title>为什么科学家将线粒体与孤独的身体代价联系起来- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/why-scientists-are-linking-mitochondria-to-the-physical-toll-of-loneliness/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic stress and social isolation are frequently cited as precursors to physical illness, yet the biological machinery driving this connection has remained partially obscured. A new scientific review proposes that mitochondria, the energy-generating structures within cells, serve as the primary translator between psychological experience and physical health. By altering their function in response to stress, these cellular components may drive conditions ranging from depression to cardiovascular disease. The paper detailing these connections was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/09637214251380214" target="_blank"&gt;Current Directions in Psychological Science&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, researchers have utilized the biopsychosocial model to understand how social and psychological factors influence the body. This framework links biological processes with social environments, yet it has historically lacked specific details on how feelings physically alter cells. Critics of the model note that it offers limited mechanistic specificity regarding how an experience like loneliness translates into molecular change. Without identifying the precise biological pathways, it is difficult to predict or treat stress-related diseases effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To address this gap, a team of researchers synthesized evidence linking cellular biology with psychology. Christopher P. Fagundes, a professor in the Department of Psychological Sciences at Rice University, led the review. He collaborated with E. Lydia Wu-Chung from the University of Pittsburgh and Cobi J. Heijnen from Rice University. They sought to identify a cellular system sensitive enough to respond to mood but powerful enough to regulate whole-body health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers conducted their review by examining existing literature from the fields of psychoneuroimmunology and mitochondrial biology. They analyzed data from preclinical animal models and human studies to construct a clearer picture of cellular adaptation. Their analysis focused on how mitochondria function as a hub for stress physiology, immune regulation, and energy balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mitochondria are often called the powerhouses of the cell because they generate adenosine triphosphate, or ATP. This molecule fuels nearly all biological activity, including brain function and muscle movement. The review highlights that these structures do much more than produce fuel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They serve as sophisticated sensors that detect hormonal signals and environmental shifts. Mitochondria possess the ability to adjust their activity based on the body’s immediate needs. This adaptability is known as metabolic flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During moments of acute stress, the body releases hormones like cortisol and catecholamines. These hormones prompt mitochondria to increase energy production to handle the immediate challenge. This rapid adjustment supports resilience by providing the resources needed for a “fight or flight” response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the authors note that chronic stress creates a vastly different outcome. Prolonged exposure to stress hormones causes mitochondrial efficiency to plummet. Instead of adapting, the machinery begins to malfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When these structures become overworked, they produce excess reactive oxygen species. These are volatile by-products that function like cellular exhaust fumes. While small amounts are necessary for signaling, an accumulation leads to oxidative stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This damage disrupts the balance of energy and leads to cellular dysfunction. The researchers point to this breakdown as a potential root cause of fatigue and cognitive decline. The brain is particularly susceptible to these energy deficits because of its immense fuel requirements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even slight mitochondrial impairments can limit the energy available for neurotransmission. This can undermine the neural processes that support mood regulation and memory. Consequently, mitochondrial dysfunction is increasingly linked to psychiatric conditions such as anxiety and depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review also details how mitochondria communicate with the immune system. When mitochondria sustain damage, they can release fragments of their own DNA into the bloodstream. They may also release other internal molecules that are usually contained within the cell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immune system perceives these fragments as danger signals. This triggers an inflammatory response similar to how the body reacts to a virus. Chronic inflammation is a well-established risk factor for heart disease, diabetes, and neurodegenerative disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This pathway suggests that psychological stress creates physical inflammation through mitochondrial damage. Fagundes and his colleagues cite studies involving human subjects to illustrate this connection. One highlighted area of research involves caregivers for family members with dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caregiving is often used as a model for chronic psychological stress. Research indicates that caregivers often display lower mitochondrial health indices compared to non-caregivers. Those with lower mitochondrial efficiency reported worse physical functioning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, caregivers with higher mitochondrial capacity appeared more resilient. They were better buffered against the negative emotional effects of their heavy burden. This suggests that cellular health may dictate how well a person withstands psychological pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social isolation also appears to leave a biological mark on these cellular structures. The review mentions that individuals reporting high levels of loneliness possess lower levels of specific mitochondrial proteins in the brain. This creates a feedback loop where social disconnection degrades physical health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fagundes notes the importance of this cellular perspective in understanding disease. He states, “The actual cellular machinery that links these experiences to disease really starts at the level of the mitochondria.” This insight moves the field beyond vague associations to concrete mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors argue that this helps explain the overlap between mental health disorders and physical ailments. Conditions like anxiety and diabetes may share this common cellular origin. It provides a unified theory for why emotional distress so often accompanies physical illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team also reviewed interventions that might restore mitochondrial health. Exercise provided the most consistent results in the analyzed literature. Endurance training boosts the number of mitochondria and improves their efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical activity stimulates a process called mitochondrial biogenesis. This creates new power plants within the cell to replace old or damaged ones. The authors suggest this is a primary reason why exercise supports both physical and psychological resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mindfulness and psychotherapy showed potential but lacked robust evidence in the current literature. Some studies indicated biological changes following these interventions. For example, a mindfulness program was associated with altered oxidative metabolism markers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, these biological shifts did not always align with reported symptom improvement. In some cases, the studies lacked necessary control groups to confirm causality. The researchers characterize these findings as promising proof of concept rather than definitive proof.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social support is another theorized intervention. It is believed to protect mitochondrial health by reducing cortisol and dampening inflammatory activity. However, the authors note that very few studies have measured mitochondrial outcomes directly in relation to social support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors acknowledge that much of the current evidence relies on correlations. It remains unclear if mitochondrial dysfunction causes psychological distress or if distress drives the dysfunction. There is likely a bidirectional relationship that exacerbates over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most human studies reviewed were cross-sectional, meaning they looked at a single point in time. This limits the ability to determine the direction of the effect. The researchers emphasize the need for longitudinal designs to clarify these pathways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future work must integrate mitochondrial measures with broader systems. These include the immune system, the autonomic nervous system, and the brain. Studying these systems in isolation often misses the complexity of the human stress response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors also call for standardized ways to measure mitochondrial health in psychological studies. Current methods vary widely in cost and accessibility. Developing consistent biomarkers will allow for larger studies that reflect diverse populations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fagundes emphasizes the potential of this approach for future medicine. He says, “If we focus more at the cellular level, we’ll have a much deeper understanding of underlying processes.” This could lead to new treatments that target the cell to heal the mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By establishing mitochondria as a key player, this review refines the biopsychosocial model. It offers a testable biological mechanism for decades of psychological theory. Ultimately, it suggests that resilience is not just a state of mind but a state of cellular energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/09637214251380214" target="_blank"&gt;Psychological Science at the Cellular Level: Mitochondria’s Role in Health and Behavior&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Christopher P. Fagundes, E. Lydia Wu-Chung, and Cobi J. Heijnen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 01:07:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxPN2ZtN3BTWnQ5QnB2WFNlbF9KLTJ4Mmx0Z1ExZFBWODhzTmZDYS1JeU16MnVDNkl4QkhQR3F4TjlmZXo5bEVGTWV6SlNaQmt6VEFBY3BzVWhzaEhITWlEQ1hDbGFPQlNnQjBYX1czUTBZMVowa3gtLVhCR2lXVlJOMFZwdmR1Q2NvSUZLRk85RVBfdGlJWXRlNUlfSnhmNVgx</guid></item><item><title>美国老年人用药过度-《华尔街日报》</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/health/healthcare/americas-seniors-are-overmedicated-f397bb1d</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQYmZxa3NtR2xsT0Z5SmlQYzRKUmFOM21IUVhTaEliSTNMeWxzZzgtYUh5WnZLSWxQUmdfQWVCaHlwdlhhYzJaUkpEZnpxd3lVQUQtRVlQQzZVdS1kRFN1UzF1ZURWMTJiY2xQVjdfeldobTd6djFxNk9hSjFUa3VwUVRoUGJoRUdr</guid></item><item><title>研究人员在多年的研究中使用流行的膳食补充剂后对结果感到震惊： “导致显著增加” -冷静下来</title><link>https://www.thecooldown.com/sustainable-food/omega-3-fatty-acids-vegan-study-health-benefits/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content"&gt;
					
&lt;p&gt;Researchers were surprised after a lengthy study of an essential fatty acid, &lt;a href="https://www.news-medical.net/news/20251217/Plant-based-omega-3s-work-better-than-expected-in-a-year-long-diet-study.aspx" target="_blank"&gt;News-Medical&lt;/a&gt; reported, with findings particularly relevant to several popular dietary lifestyles.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The study, published in &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/nutrition/articles/10.3389/fnut.2025.1727308/full" target="_blank"&gt;Frontiers in Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;, focused on long-chain polyunsaturated fatty acids, which the authors stipulated were of concern for those on vegetarian and vegan diets.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Omega-3 fatty acids play a vital role in several critical health metrics, supporting cardiovascular and immune function, cognition, and fighting inflammation. The study noted that these essential nutrients were often found in meat, fish, and dairy, posing a challenge to plant-based diners.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Flaxseed oil is a known plant-based source of alpha-linolenic acid, an essential omega-3 fatty acid, and News-Medical mentioned a standing "widespread assumption that the human body only poorly converts plant-derived ALA" versus omega-3s found in meat and fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="theco-dd5d8154a7dddd210267264b57e0df70 theco-biolite-woah-widget" id="theco-dd5d8154a7dddd210267264b57e0df70"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="theco-f08166b4b2896cebc6f94db7ace149c9 theco-recurrent-woah-widget" id="theco-f08166b4b2896cebc6f94db7ace149c9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="theco-8e6f799210d60a2599df4aaceb8eeee3 theco-trashie-widget-woah" id="theco-8e6f799210d60a2599df4aaceb8eeee3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="theco-1a6dbef5b9f0666b82004d36cebd1efe theco-rewiring-america-widget-woah" id="theco-1a6dbef5b9f0666b82004d36cebd1efe"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="theco-bcb081c0ea85a715aab660e91d307c2d theco-greenportfolio-woah" id="theco-bcb081c0ea85a715aab660e91d307c2d"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers identified 168 individuals aged 18 to 70, all of whom had followed an omnivorous, flexitarian, vegetarian, or vegan diet for one year prior to the start of the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="theco-5c7e6d6b6248df2d647cbc52e0b9570e theco-nolan-interior-permalink" id="theco-5c7e6d6b6248df2d647cbc52e0b9570e"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As the authors indicated, vegetarian and vegan lifestyles are becoming increasingly popular worldwide for myriad reasons, particularly among &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11241807/" target="_blank"&gt;Generation Z&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="theco-inline-advertorial theco-target" id="theco-33088864" data-theco-trackid="641395" data-theco-trackbid="1"&gt;&lt;div&gt;

		
             &lt;td class="container-cell" align="center"&gt;

	                         &lt;table class="section"&gt;
                  &lt;tr&gt;
                    &lt;td class="section-inner"&gt;
						
                      &lt;p class="standard-title"&gt;
                        &lt;h1&gt;FROM OUR PARTNER&lt;/h1&gt;
                        
                      &lt;/p&gt;
                      &lt;h1&gt;Stay hydrated and refreshed this holiday season — without any sugar or harmful additives&lt;/h1&gt;
                      &lt;a href="https://go.linkby.com/DSPOIMIE"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
                   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://go.linkby.com/DSPOIMIE"&gt;Nuun’s&lt;/a&gt; zero-sugar hydration tablets are a perfect, guilt-free way to enhance your water throughout the day. You’ll get &lt;b&gt;five essential electrolytes&lt;/b&gt; for everyday hydration — with &lt;b&gt;zero grams of sugar&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Plus, Nuun tablets are &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://go.linkby.com/DSPOIMIE"&gt;certified vegan and gluten-free&lt;/a&gt;, and they’re the perfect size to keep in your car, purse, or anywhere you'll want a healthy, restorative drink.&lt;/p&gt;
                      
                    
					  &lt;/td&gt;
                  &lt;/tr&gt;
                &lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/td&gt;			
		
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p class="theco-0cef1f4246938b8dc9e44fb7fa2f94f7 theco-embedded-video" id="theco-0cef1f4246938b8dc9e44fb7fa2f94f7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They cited a range of ethical, &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/sustainable-food/vegetarian-diet-cancer-study-reduced-risk/" target="_blank"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt;, and environmental benefits as a factor in the growing popularity of &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/explore-plant-based-food-options/" target="_blank"&gt;plant-based diets&lt;/a&gt;. Rising &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/sustainable-food/rising-grocery-costs-us-states-strain/" target="_blank"&gt;food costs&lt;/a&gt; are likely fueling some dietary changes, since &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/sustainable-food/study-groceries-cost-less-eating-meatless/" target="_blank"&gt;meatless alternatives&lt;/a&gt; tend to be &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/journeys/eat-cleaner-cheaper-food/" target="_blank"&gt;more affordable&lt;/a&gt; and less perishable.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;High-profile campaigns like &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/sustainable-food/veganuary-participation-vegan-diet-plant-based/" target="_blank"&gt;Veganuary&lt;/a&gt; are another factor, as is a broader tendency toward hybrid dietary approaches and &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/grow-your-own-food/" target="_blank"&gt;growing food&lt;/a&gt; at home. Opting for &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/sustainable-food/plant-based-meats-sustainable-food/" target="_blank"&gt;plant-forward meals&lt;/a&gt; rather than a 100% vegan lifestyle, sometimes called "&lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/sustainable-food/gen-z-flexitarian-diets-vegetarian/" target="_blank"&gt;flexitarianism&lt;/a&gt;," is also becoming &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/sustainable-food/reducetarian-foundation-colorado-denver-meat/" target="_blank"&gt;more common&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="theco-697c3c9fc457884bb6d53dcdb4e3b8e5 theco-recurrent-2-woah-widget" id="theco-697c3c9fc457884bb6d53dcdb4e3b8e5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Participants followed "nutrient-optimized menu plans" for one year, supplementing their diets with flaxseed oil for nine months after the first three months of the study. The authors collected blood samples at three-month intervals, examining the study subjects at 12 and 24 months.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At the end of the study, researchers determined that "systematic long-term dietary intake of ALA … leads to a significant increase in EPA, DPA and DHA concentrations" irrespective of participants' dietary patterns.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p aria-hidden="true" class="wp-block-spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Strikingly, researchers also found that while vegans and vegetarians demonstrated lower blood "concentrations than omnivores" at the study's conclusion, they "on average surpass omnivorous levels at the beginning of the intervention."&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As such, the authors advised vegans and vegetarians to "regularly consume" plant-based foods or supplements rich in essential fatty acids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="theco-4cbc6ba96c4c8c9121dd35d5ca0ab725 theco-ad-after-12th-p" id="theco-4cbc6ba96c4c8c9121dd35d5ca0ab725"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="has-text-align-center has-medium-font-size"&gt;Get TCD's &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/newsletter/?utm_source=recid8OZXyINddekh" target="_blank"&gt;free newsletters&lt;/a&gt; for easy tips to save more, waste less, and make smarter choices — and earn up to $5,000 toward clean upgrades in TCD's exclusive &lt;a href="https://links.thecooldown.com/rewards-club" target="_blank"&gt;Rewards Club&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class="theco-23504d63098636c41382d2b14db62ab6 theco-article-bottom" id="theco-23504d63098636c41382d2b14db62ab6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;					
								
				
					&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Cool Down</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPSlNBZllyVWgzaU1jUlJNV1hrbXZiM3JvQWdONGpNQUlFMEJiSlN6bkswelE0UEI1cmlxVDdjdFVCZlZEWTlYTU9ETGVLWU1ZbmJVV3JCM0diaGwyY0NaM1NOMDVEZ0s2S3RzcG1ocmVIaXJNWm5Tb1Y1RjRENk5tNnVWdkJpX3pReDA4OTBxa0RqWlNVdkZwdg</guid></item><item><title>专家说，未来几周流感季节可能会变得更糟-西雅图时报</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/flu-season-could-get-a-lot-worse-in-the-coming-weeks-experts-say/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPMUFwQ3A4dUo5dXhGVGtURnNGUVphODRsMERMZkRvRmV2VWp0RXd0dDAyZDkzV1ZCYXhjandKZXQyRTR6bVZBVXFyOE9kSEdRcGREbmxzdm90b1NfYWZlak4tb3hjSTlNUkhLN3BMb2ZlTFFTbE4wZnBJWkhsQ0FxZUo3VUxGYmZrUUw2ckIxRUx3czAzNDVxTVYwT012Z1dHZkxiejFRVFkwVm8?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Flu season could get a lot worse in the coming weeks, experts say&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipgFBVV95cUxNY1VyWFVZcm9iM2NITzBaMGtRd2diVzljdVNQQ3VyOHhYOS1MRnpUMjJzYnBOdXRCVzRwOE5XQjgyQmlyTGlDUWNZRG9SMmk2aXNLQkswRU5YUGJJUmdyQUVxaExNQWZNM1hfUjJpN0h4LU1ZVmw3VW02MHFta1puLV8ydUcxV3dmaG5FbnUyNUdlNGNGUVBnQWU4MG5ScHJ1TThmUS1R0gGrAUFVX3lxTE9seEU3MkZ5YlhmNFN4WXNudVFHV3VqeTRzM2dVRVpxeXpqNW5sQW1wNGd1NWVkZV9PaDQ4dk04V0dXOUhpOG16SVVoTGc4OS00MzEyUG9oQVVCdFlWQUdpWGZpZXNwMzE0WVd6dTAtQVdSS2ktdEE4VVhGMlFJZ1BvLWd3bGM1QW1pbmY2YVMzX0FocHktUHU1MUFtQzdDNko5bGhVcEdISGZabw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Nearly 5 million flu illnesses reported so far nationally, latest CDC data shows&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;ABC News&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizAFBVV95cUxNZ2pxbHpJWEZMeEtqb2IzVmE3V0VmRVBveG1NSkEzTnM4UF9vODdEcC1NNWY2QmdtTDVpd3g0bnJ3Z0dXMjJpLURlUy0zLUxDRTBseHlQUkJCSkdQNllnSk5hTy1wN3V6dVF2encwdkxPbkZMOEdDV2poUVgtX2thbHFqTEE1ZkFwcTFVMXAxZnh4bkFWbXR1NmQ4QUJhUHMzVG1vZlhaRjBDUGV5UEJOM3I1ODBCaXdBelVWMHJUZU5pX3V4Z2ZiWVZUUkzSAdIBQVVfeXFMTkNrbzlGU1A5QUNPMFJFUVBuNkpvOS1sNng0UlZJR1pOUzBQZ2c0ZE84OEg5THBGUVludkhBNXNPN2ZjZHZ2Uk5TY3hWeUE0X09GSGlfSmsyNFMweVZ2c3ZHZ3JzUjJuUmlPVEx1RGx3bVI1QmtuQVN0cDZ4MzFuMDR1YnFzbDRhOTdGSy1KLW5xeEZocFl3cWdEZWJNMmpPeVJIbmxGVmFuOUs0UFFPZDJJZ2VMTDV6dkZUMWRZaUFBQzE5SFJpUWs0RVMwYVNKbnRB?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;MAP: Influenza hitting these states hardest as ‘super flu’ continues to spread&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;thehill.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiugFBVV95cUxQWXFLWm13bm00eDFOVnp1RUZGZ2JheF9QMi1VZFlMaWM0YnRNV0hpOXFFT0IzUDl5NWlZbUg1Y1Z5c2JNSm5iMXNJSm5PbnJvMmJ3MFJaU2hjOUZ3QUl2Uk1nc1FDRUxUSU5MangxcXU2VTA3S2FscmpmUXJ5cklWUU5vcUxmbHkzYk1oNG9Ub2JndFZ0ZXkyY21yV09lWHZNSGFDaUgtX1MxSWFlTDRIR1NhSXN2ZEY1cWc?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Contagious flu strain spreading. Here’s what you need to know about the mutation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Fort Worth Report&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPQ2F5XzZlQXJsSTh1Qy1PWEx3Ym9Rd3U3cENsQ1R2VVBlOThheUFueDl4ZkVlU3R0d2E0MjhyZ2dER2pYLU5VX0p6NExFeDNUeDRSWEdGV1pPdXBoOVMtMEcyaTRwMDZoWndUU1VHb3VxQkZoMzdZMGlKZWdLN3dFUWZjUmFTY3BLVk51Rk1icWhld3pnVFR6ZUhOWmpjcjhNVzRSajY0S01OZnPSAb8BQVVfeXFMUHUyc29iWnZZcjRWMTJqMDQ4Z2JvSnU0VmZkYUJRTlViXzV6TlBXQXRwTXRRd3cwbkVGVk9aYW1RckFvZzdYbUdqU1NsSUswSVNMaGZ0YzBkX0picG1yM0RtYWx6SnM2WnJWTjdNd1JQMTg2WVJScEpvNVBhbXhZaVZ1T0VSQlJWOEwzcVp4NU1vMFhpcG81cmhWanZGRTJKY1RNRjA1NzJSZlBDOUZDb1JSRTRYc0J4blJWa1NTTnc?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;‘Super flu’ hitting these states the hardest: What are the symptoms?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;MassLive.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 00:00:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPMUFwQ3A4dUo5dXhGVGtURnNGUVphODRsMERMZkRvRmV2VWp0RXd0dDAyZDkzV1ZCYXhjandKZXQyRTR6bVZBVXFyOE9kSEdRcGREbmxzdm90b1NfYWZlak4tb3hjSTlNUkhLN3BMb2ZlTFFTbE4wZnBJWkhsQ0FxZUo3VUxGYmZrUUw2ckIxRUx3czAzNDVxTVYwT012Z1dHZkxiejFRVFkwVm8</guid></item><item><title>不应与酒精混合的六种常见药物-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15343427/Medications-never-drink-alcohol.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As the holiday season gets underway, Americans are beginning to note recipes for festive cocktails and choose the best wines for the dinner table.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But experts are raising the alarm about potentially deadly interactions between &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/alcohol/index.html" id="mol-0b9d5570-cf02-11f0-8b88-6fc0aba21bba"&gt;alcohol&lt;/a&gt; and certain medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol is a depressant, meaning it slows down the functioning of the central nervous system, impacting brain activity, reaction time, speech and a person's mental well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Adding certain medications on top of consuming alcohol - &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15187669/medications-cancer-colorectal-gut-microbiome-antidepressants-xanax-antibiotics.html"&gt;such as anti-anxiety drugs&lt;/a&gt;, drugs for insomnia, blood thinners and antidepressants - compounds these effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The deadly combination can destabilize the heart's rhythm and blood pressure. And, because both the medications and the alcohol independently suppresses brainstem activity, which controls automatic functions, the combination reduces the brain's drive to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But more innocuous medications do not play well with alcohol, either. That group includes &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15152543/over-counter-painkillers-alcohol-risk.html"&gt;over-the-counter pain relievers&lt;/a&gt; like ibuprofen, which can contribute to liver and gastrointestinal damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Combining ibuprofen and alcohol raises the risk of bleeding in the stomach and small intestine, which can result in vomiting blood. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Barbara Sparacino, an adult and geriatric psychiatrist, told the Daily Mail that a practical rule of thumb is to avoid mixing alcohol with any medication that helps you sleep, relax or relieve pain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group artSplitter"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The holiday season often means festive drinks and special wines, but experts warn that mixing alcohol with common medications can pose serious risks that are easily avoided (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group artSplitter"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs (NSAIDs) like ibuprofen, naproxen and aspirin already increase the risk of gastrointestinal bleeding. Adding just one alcoholic drink can raise that risk by approximately 37 percent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For stronger sedatives, such as opioids and benzodiazepines, complete abstinence from alcohol is safest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And if you do decide to drink, you should avoid drinking heavily and never drive after. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By one estimate, roughly 40 percent of Americans take a medication that interacts dangerously with alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In addition to dangerous side effects, the medicine might lose its efficacy when it comes in contact with alcohol and speed its clearance from the body without working as intended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A medication can also influence the absorption of alcohol, potentially resulting in higher blood alcohol concentrations (BACs) and other adverse effects like shallow breathing and overdose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol can also heighten the effects of a medication and increase the amount of it in a person's body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After speaking with several doctors, the Daily Mail can reveal which over-the-counter and prescription medications&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt; &lt;/span&gt;you should not mix with alcohol - along with the experts' reasons why.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Over-the-counter pain relievers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Non-steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs such as ibuprofen (sold under the brand names Advil and Motrin), naproxen (sold as Aleve and Naprosyn) and aspirin are associated with a higher risk of GI bleeds on their own. But, when combined with just one drink, that risk climbs by about 37 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's likely fine to take an occasional dose of ibuprofen if you've consumed a small quantity of alcohol, roughly one or two drinks. The combination becomes more dangerous if you take ibuprofen regularly and tend to drink heavily. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Acetaminophen (sold as Tylenol) is the most popular pain reliever in the US, but it interacts in a unique - and potentially deadly - way with alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taking too much acetaminophen accounts for almost half of all cases of acute liver failure in North America and approximately 20 percent of liver transplant cases in the US. Mixing acetaminophen with alcohol compounds the risk of deadly liver damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The liver of a person who drinks heavily and often produces more of a specific enzyme called CYP2E1 to break down the alcohol. This same enzyme also processes acetaminophen. The problem is that this process creates a toxic byproduct called NAPQI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taking acetaminophen preemptively or after heavy drinking causes the overactive enzyme system to produce dangerously high levels of NAPQI, which can overwhelm and destroy the liver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because of this, the FDA has mandated that every bottle of acetaminophen products have a label stating that 'severe liver damage may occur if an adult has three or more alcoholic drinks every day while using this product.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group artSplitter"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The main ingredient in common cold and flu medicines is a central nervous system depressant, like alcohol. Combined, they make a person feel dizzier and more impaired than they would by taking either one alone&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Over-the-counter cold and flu medicines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cold and flu remedies should never mix with alcohol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A bad flu is dehydrating, and adding alcohol dehydrates the body further as alcohol triggers a diuretic effect. All of the efforts to hydrate, from bottles of water to a bowl of soup, are then eliminated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dehydration can exacerbate flu symptoms like headache, fatigue, dizziness and muscle weakness, and ultimately prolong recovery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol also exacerbates the side effects of popular cough medicines like Theraflu cough syrups, Dayquil, Nyquil and Tylenol Severe Cold and Flu. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like alcohol, their main ingredient, dextromethorphan (DXM), is a central nervous system depressant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Combining the two increases side effects such as dizziness, drowsiness, impaired coordination and difficulty concentrating. People who combine the two are at higher risk of light stumbles turning to dangerous falls and other injuries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taking DXM with alcohol can also cause breathing to slow or stop entirely, feelings of dissociation, brain lesions, epilepsy or permanent psychosis. It is best to avoid alcohol until the drug has left your body, about 24 to 48 hours after your last dose. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group artSplitter"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Alcohol exacerbates the effects of allergy medications, such as drowsiness and loss of coordination, putting someone at risk of injury&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Allergy medicines&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol heightens the side effects of popular allergy medicines, including Mucinex, Allegra, Claritin and Zyrtec, leaving you feeling more drowsy, dizzy or impaired than you would from the medication alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many antihistamines - the main ingredients in allergy medicines - are central nervous system depressants just like alcohol. Combining them can have an additive effect, slowing down brain activity more than either substance would by itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Benadryl, the oldest generation of current allergy medications, has a stronger sedative effect than others, and that effect is amplified further when combined with a drink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sudafed, a common nasal decongestant, is a stimulant that can mask the sedating effects of alcohol and make someone feel less intoxicated than they actually are. This can cause a person to drink more than they intended, raising the risk of alcohol poisoning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both Sudafed and alcohol can raise heart rate and blood pressure individually. Combining them can heighten this effect, which is especially dangerous for individuals with preexisting heart conditions or hypertension. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For safety, it is generally recommended to avoid alcohol when taking these medications, especially if you need to drive or operate machinery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group artSplitter"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Both alcohol and many antibiotics such as azithromycin are metabolized by the liver. Drinking while on medication forces the liver to work harder, placing significant strain on the organ&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Antibiotics&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Combining alcohol with antibiotics can interfere with your body's healing process in several key ways. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;First, alcohol can impair the immune system's efficiency, making it harder for the body to fight the very infection the antibiotic is meant to treat. This can potentially prolong illness and delay recovery. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;More directly, both alcohol and many antibiotics are metabolized by the liver. Consuming them together places a significant strain on this vital organ, as it must work overtime to process both substances. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This can exacerbate common antibiotic side effects like nausea, dizziness and drowsiness, making a person feel significantly worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the case of certain antibiotics, like metronidazole, the interaction is severe and deliberate, causing a chemical reaction that leads to intensely unpleasant symptoms such as severe vomiting, rapid heart rate and headache. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Beyond the immediate discomfort, mixing alcohol and antibiotics can compromise the medication's effectiveness. Alcohol can disrupt the absorption and metabolism of the drug, potentially lowering its concentration in the bloodstream to a level that is insufficient to eradicate bacteria. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This not only risks treatment failure, but contributes to a larger public health crisis: antibiotic resistance. When antibiotics are not allowed to work at full strength, it creates an environment where stronger, more resistant bacteria can survive and multiply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Therefore, abstaining from all alcohol for the full duration of the prescription is critical. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group artSplitter"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Dr Barbara Sparacino, a psychiatrist, advises never mixing alcohol with sleep, relaxation, or pain medications. With strong sedatives like opioids or benzodiazepines, total avoidance of alcohol is essential, especially for older adults or those on multiple sedating drugs &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Antidepressants&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Combining antidepressant medications with alcohol has a similar effect on the respiratory system as benzodiazepines. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While drinking may provide temporary relief from depression symptoms and aid in dealing with social anxiety, alcohol blocks the ability of antidepressants to do their job. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;SSRIs like Zoloft and Prozac, and SNRIs like Effexor work over time to regulate and stabilize key neurotransmitter systems (serotonin and norepinephrine) to improve mood, sleep and anxiety in a sustained way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol is a chemical disruptor. It initially causes a brief, artificial release of serotonin and dopamine, creating a mood boost, but a rapid depletion of those neurotransmitters follows. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the short term, this leads to mood swings. With regular use, it can create or worsen a chemical imbalance that promotes depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The combination impairs reaction time, judgement, and decision-making more than either substance on its own, and, due to the depletion of mood-boosting neurotransmitters, has a higher likelihood of causing suicidal ideations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Drinking while taking antidepressants also reduces the odds that the medicine will work as intended. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There's no universally safe limit for drinking alcohol while taking antidepressants, because even a small amount can interact poorly with the medications and make depression or anxiety worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many doctors advise avoiding alcohol altogether or sticking to one to two moderate drinks - a 12-ounce beer, a five-ounce glass of wine or a one-ounce shot of liquor, regardless of gender.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group artSplitter"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Alcohol plays a role in about 20 percent of all benzodiazepine overdoses, making it one of the most lethal drug interactions. Both substances severely depress the central nervous system, specifically slowing the body's ability to breathe, which can lead to fatal respiratory failure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Benzodiazepines &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol is implicated in approximately 20 percent of all benzodiazepine overdoses, constituting one of the most dangerous drug interactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People taking benzodiazepines should avoid alcohol entirely.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The danger primarily stems from how both substances profoundly suppress the central nervous system, specifically targeting the body's capacity to breathe. When combined, they dramatically increase the risk of severe and potentially fatal respiratory depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This life-threatening consequence occurs because both alcohol and benzodiazepines, along with many antidepressants, amplify the effects of the neurotransmitter GABA (gamma-aminobutyric acid).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;GABA is responsible for calming neural activity, and its excessive enhancement leads to extreme sedation of the body's vital functions, resulting not only in respiratory failure but also in cardiovascular collapse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Beyond the acute physical dangers, the mixture of benzodiazepines and alcohol can induce severe psychological and behavioral problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Users may experience complete anterograde amnesia, in which they cannot form new memories properly, losing all memory for hours while conscious and active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This blackout state is associated with high-risk behaviors, including unsafe sexual practices, impulsive aggression or severe self harm. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Individuals may experience intense suicidal thoughts and act on them, with no subsequent recollection of their actions, creating a uniquely hazardous situation for both the individual and those around them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This combination is a major contributor to ER visits and accidental overdoses, even at doses people think are "normal,"' Sparacino said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The risk of severe interactions are even higher among older people.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So a drink that felt "mild" at 40 can feel like three drinks at 75, especially when layered on top of sedating meds,' she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'That's part of why we see more falls, confusion and ER visits in older adults mixing alcohol with prescriptions.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group artSplitter"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Alcohol and blood thinners each independently slow the blood's clotting ability. When used together, their effects are dangerously amplified, making it significantly harder to stop bleeding&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Blood thinners&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Just as risky are prescription blood thinners, common among older people with blood clotting disorders that increase the risks of heart attack and stroke. The danger comes as alcohol can significantly raise someone's risk for dangerous bleeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Both alcohol and blood thinners independently inhibit the blood's ability to clot. Together, their effects can be more than additive, creating a powerful synergy that makes bleeding much harder to stop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For example, a simple scrape or nick that would normally stop bleeding within minutes could bleed for much longer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol also irritates the stomach lining, and any kind of perforation due to an ulcer can cause internal bleeding in the GI tract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other popular blood thinners significantly alter alcohol metabolism. This means that a person who drinks a modest amount but is on a blood thinner might actually have a much higher BAC than a person who drinks the same amount of alcohol but is not taking the medication. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol can also cause dangerously low blood pressure, causing dizziness and fainting.&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To prevent the negative effects, doctors recommend that patients limit their alcohol intake to one to two standard drinks at a time, alternating with water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sometimes taken in addition to blood thinners are cholesterol medications known as statins. These come with their own risks when paired with alcohol, Dr Raul Santos, a board-certified cardiovascular specialist, told the Daily Mail. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Excessive alcohol consumption or binge drinking in individuals using statins may increase the risk of muscle problems, muscle aches and, very rarely, muscle inflammation or even destruction of muscle cells [Rhabdomyolysis],' Santos said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Muscle aches in randomized controlled trials occur in one to three percent of the population, while in real life, numerous confounding factors affect ten to 20 percent of people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Rhabdomyolysis is extremely rare, occurring in 0.01 percent of patients taking statins. Excess alcohol can harm the muscles, and statins may exacerbate this effect.'  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:05:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxNZV9MMGdnbjl2TTVUNkpBYUN1RVhGZm5mdFBGRnpueE9BdjluUVRZdXp3Q18tLVBCTzNUWmxqN3hKUXRkYmpNTHloRzBJU0puSFphTUFuOTJyOFo4a2h4Tk1OWGhsaF81bWhjQmFTNnBwUzg0RmRiSUM4YTBEZktzRmpTUlpydkVqYmFLWFpVRnh1UQ</guid></item><item><title>那一年，我给了女儿一个新的肝脏--泰晤士报</title><link>https://www.thetimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/article/elle-daniel-daughter-living-donor-transplant-surgery-mw08ghz9p</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;That day, Wednesday, June 11, was the culmination of months of worry, research and preparation as we undertook the life-changing journey of living donor&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt; transplant surgery in an attempt to improve my adored, medically complex little girl’s quality of life. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;When Ruby was born in October 2023 we had no knowledge of what was to come regarding her health. She was discharged as normal the day after her birth and followed up by community midwives, who were happy with her initial progress. The first alarm bells began to sound at around three to four weeks, when weight gain and feeding were proving to be a significant challenge. At the time, her only diagnosis was that of an “un-greedy baby”. That changed dramatically at around two months, when ultrasounds showed that she had huge volumes of fluid in her abdomen and around her heart, and she was rushed to Great Ormond Street Hospital (GOSH) for immediate life-saving treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Our first Christmas morning as a family was in intensive care. At just under three months she was diagnosed with the rare metabolic condition known as PMM2-CDG, a diagnosis she shares with an estimated 1,000-2,400 others worldwide, and one that threw up so many complications that it has seen her spend most of her young life at GOSH, where my husband, Steve, or I would take turns staying in a single bed in her room. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="2.2"&gt;&lt;div id="2cee193d-b3b1-451d-b966-5c27afbb4354"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;Ruby was diagnosed with the rare metabolic condition known as PMM2-CDG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Ruby’s condition is multi-systemic, and had a particularly detrimental effect on her liver from a very early stage. This turned out to be the cause of the dangerous episodes of fluid retention, inability to gain weight or grow muscle, and also two catastrophic seizures, which saw her requiring full resuscitation and admission to the paediatric intensive care unit (PICU), because her liver could not adequately filter her blood, resulting in a toxic level of ammonia in her system. These were the most terrifying times of my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;At first, a transplant was discussed only as a last resort (“We do not expect that to be the case,” the consultant said), but as time passed it became clear that it had the potential to be, not an all-out cure, but transformative within the context of her condition. Sure enough, after an in-patient assessment in King’s College Hospital’s Rays of Sunshine Ward, including extensive scans and blood tests, as well as careful discussions about the efficacy and safety of this major procedure, it was confirmed that Ruby was indeed a candidate for a liver transplant. She would be the first PMM2-CDG patient in Europe to receive one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/life-style/parenting/article/born-an-addict-my-adopted-daughters-heartbreaking-struggle-w2dtkrrc9" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Born an addict, my adopted daughter’s heartbreaking struggle&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;I knew immediately that I wanted to be her donor. As well as being in good health, and a close genetic match, I felt that any other option such as waiting for a deceased donor would simply delay things for too long. I also instinctively felt that, as her mother, it had to come from me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;My work-up began the following week, starting with a day of imaging and tests. The living donation process is complex and considered high risk, not just for the recipient, but the donor as well. Of course, the benefit of helping my child to become well was worth any risk, but I found that my deeply emotional connection to the whole process was often tempered by the surgeons’ meticulous precision and logic. I was assigned a living donor transplant co-ordinator, the wonderful Matilda, who helped to humanise the process by translating clinical scenarios into words I could actually understand and thus helping me prepare mentally, allowing space for me to deal with the myriad and often conflicting emotions of excitement, fear, impatience and relief, alongside the many practicalities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The first date we were offered was in April, which, when given in January, felt like a very long time to wait. Little did I know at the time, but we would end up waiting longer. Liver transplants in vulnerable babies are complex enough already, and the element of a live donor adds an extra layer, meaning that various things have to be in place, such as two surgical teams being available at the same time, plus two theatres in close proximity, two intensive care unit (ICU) beds for the aftermath, and so on. Only about 15 of these surgeries take place a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="2.11"&gt;&lt;div id="9c7f6fe5-955e-4051-a00a-19c995f7a571"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;Being in good health and a close genetic match, Elle signed up to be her daughter’s liver donor&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Although we were all ready to go in April, another child awaiting transplant had become more critical, and so urgently needed to take that slot. Our new surgery date was pushed back until May, which didn’t feel too long to wait by then, but the anxiety of trying to keep our daughter well, especially when we were spending so much time in hospital, was extreme. Even in protective isolation, she could easily destabilise in ways that would see the surgery cancelled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;On the eve of the May surgery date, one of Ruby’s blood tests came back with a value that didn’t give anyone the confidence that the surgery should go ahead on that date. No one expects medically complex patients to have perfect blood results, but one organ that must be functioning well — because of how it is initially “hit” by the immediate aftermath of the surgery — is the kidneys, and her kidney function was not as they would have liked it to be. As one surgeon said, “She would have probably been fine — but probably isn’t good enough.” I take great comfort from the care that they displayed with that decision. I attended the meeting with the surgeons, where the news of cancellation would be confirmed, fully gowned up and in compression socks, because I had to be fully prepared to go, just in case. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Another month passed, and this time, finally, we were good to go. I spent the night before in Ruby’s hospital room and had collected my gown and surgical wash in advance, so that I could spend the maximum amount of time with her before making my way down to be admitted. My surgery was to take place first in the schedule; they would remove the piece of my liver, check that it reflected everything they had on file, and only then would they bring her down to theatre. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;When the time came, once I had kissed Steve goodbye, there was a surprisingly buoyant atmosphere among the surgeons and anaesthetists as they got to work — a bit like what you might find on the morning of a long-anticipated wedding day. I had assumed I would be asked to count down from ten while put to sleep, but instead I was cut off by a deep, chemically induced slumber mid-sentence, telling the medical staff about my job as a yoga teacher. The next thing I remember was being roused energetically, a nasogastric tube being pulled out of my nose as my eyes began to flicker open. It felt as though nothing had happened and no time had passed, but in fact my surgery alone had taken about four hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/uk/healthcare/article/gosh-gene-therapy-granulomatous-disease-8vr6tzhwc" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pioneering gene therapy tricks teen’s cells and transforms his life&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;News of Ruby’s surgery progressing well helped to bring me out of my daze. I was taken to ICU, where I remained pretty much bed-bound. Finally, after two days, I was reunited with my daughter in the PICU. I was pushed up in a wheelchair, and even sitting upright seemed to take all of my energy, but it was worth it to see Ruby. She was intubated, and hooked up to more IVs than I had ever seen, but I felt a wave of calm wash over me, because my mother’s instinct told me in that moment that she was going to be OK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The days and weeks that followed were tough, not least because Ruby’s newly suppressed immune system meant that any virus or infection going latched onto her. Still recovering from my own surgery meant that picking her up to comfort her was a physical challenge. My energy and focus felt significantly depleted; trying to maintain advocacy for a child with a rare and complex condition in hospital asks a lot of you at the best of times, so it was during this period that I found myself truly at my limit. It was worth it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;They say that you get a completely different child post-transplant — but, while the changes are indeed remarkable, I would say that Ruby is more herself than ever before. Inside her previously poorly, undernourished body there had always been a vibrant, funny, kind and curious little girl with an incredibly mighty spirit, and now her body possesses the strength and energy to let her live fully. She is bigger and stronger, having gained two kilos in weight and added length to her frame in just a matter of weeks post-surgery. She feeds better and has much more energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Her cognitive development has accelerated significantly. It is clear that her eyesight has improved and that she is able to engage and interact more. She can now sit independently for short periods, there is a new stability to her spine and core, and as a result she is exploring more movement, thus able to really start embodying her clear curiosity for the world around her. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Although some very exciting and potentially curative treatments are now in trial, this liver transplant, for her, has been the most meaningful step forward in her condition so far, and it places her in the advantageous position of being well enough to really benefit from the many promising potential therapies on the horizon, such as gene therapy and novel work into brain organoids. We, and other families as part of &lt;a href="https://cdg-uk.org/" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;CDG UK&lt;/a&gt;, are working hard to fund and collaborate with numerous research bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;There are still challenges. We were warned that the first year post-transplant is the toughest, as they keep the levels of immunosuppression particularly high to ensure her body doesn’t reject the transplanted liver. This has come with its own complications as she has become more susceptible to catching bugs with the winter months. While seeing her progress developmentally has been a joy, my main hopes for the transplant were that she would not be so frequently unwell and that she would not have to spend so much of her life confined to the four walls of a hospital cubicle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;After some joyful time at home as a family, there has been a lot more hospital time lately. We are looking at Christmas here at Great Ormond Street, which will be our second, as we were able to spend last Christmas at home. However, we know that this is just another bump in the road, of which we’ve endured many, and we are fortunate to have a lot of support from our family and friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/uk/science/article/hopes-rise-of-a-cheap-cure-for-rare-genetic-diseases-ghhzvrx05?gaa_at=eafs&amp;amp;gaa_n=AWEtsqfOqVSoEJwWokOToR3JNfgRPhamHu-ImwNJ3xV8Kr22lUGXdektIOFm4stfuJ8%3D&amp;amp;gaa_ts=69457870&amp;amp;gaa_sig=-qYjTUKjgmIh6qtIXZgxz9D4H0q9D3xplzNtimPhyeSyuo_CNmJed5mOYTjO2IaPw00ASjGzAyN7z5T9gFo8MQ%3D%3D" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hopes rise of a cheap cure for rare genetic diseases&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;As well as having her whole extended family around her, she is supported by an excellent community team of nurses, therapists and play workers, and, when at home, has ongoing outpatient monitoring from GOSH, King’s and University College Hospital. This has not been an easy journey, but one of its many gifts has been to remind me that real human kindness exists and it has introduced me to a wealth of individuals who make it their mission to care for you and to make your life that little bit easier. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;I am frequently met with admiration when people learn that I was her donor, but I am simply doing what any parent would do for their child, given the chance. Fear simply isn’t an obstacle when your child’s life is at stake. On paper, PMM2-CDG can sound bleak, but when you meet my daughter, and all the other children like her, you realise that there is a whole, vital and life-loving person beyond the diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="last-paragraph" class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;&lt;b&gt;You can support children living with PMM2-CDG by visiting &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://cdg-uk.org/support-us/" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;cdg-uk.org/support-us&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; and following &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/projectpmm2/" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;@projectpmm2&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; on Instagram &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxNcHh4aTl0bXl0ZElFSXlWSnBKeDg5SXpRUjZWcGVMT2VBbmNMM2tSWER5T3ltUExBQjVkX0Rxa2dqZnNIVDRDcktkSW85TDJyY295MVFOTmFUWE1XNS1yR0dFTFJlQUlQakNvY1k2V0lfVWxEYTZqRUJ3MVVfdExtekRpN0tsNUJWLWNhTTRoMnZGOGFCUFhUcnVtUV9WTXB0QXhRX2dGTHBUTnBUcDVYRWV5eFhlLS1GdXRHbkVR</guid></item><item><title>隐性感染可能是长期新冠肺炎的缺失环节- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/hidden-infections-may-be-the-missing-link-in-long-covid/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 22:49:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQeTNsc0pXNjF1R3pxbXR1amRTTk1qLUVTUGxROFFpSHpwVVpFQ09iSWpoTExtdnBYMjg5ZlYweW5CcEJDTTlDQ2Y4TWZtdy1tQTRwWWNkb0ZSNXNMdlNiSUg1cXlzeXJodmZLU0FOcE9fWFpyLUpxMUctWUZpX2xRaFpBVEJPd2g2</guid></item></channel></rss>