<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>参议员卡西迪表示，他“非常担心”乙型肝炎疫苗接种时间表可能发生变化- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/bill-cassidy-hepatitis-b-vaccine-schedule-change/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Washington — &lt;/em&gt;Sen. Bill Cassidy, a Louisiana Republican who chairs the Senate Committee on Health, Education, Labor and Pensions, said he's "very concerned" about a potential change to the hepatitis B vaccine schedule for infants, with a key advisory panel set to meet in the coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm a doctor. I have seen people die from vaccine-preventable disease," &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/bill-cassidy-louisiana-senator-face-the-nation-transcript-11-16-2025/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Cassidy told "Face the Nation with Margaret Brennan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;." "I want to make America healthy, and you don't start by stopping recommendations that have made us substantially healthier."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cassidy, a physician whose medical practice focused on hepatitis B, noted that because of the recommended hepatitis B vaccine dose at birth, "we have decreased incidence of chronic hepatitis B by 20,000 people over the last two decades."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The vaccine is safe. It has been established," Cassidy said. "This is policy by people who don't understand the epidemiology of hepatitis B, or who have grown comfortable with the fact that we've been so successful with our recommendation that now the incidence of hepatitis B is so low, they feel like we can rest on our laurels." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Advisory Committee for Immunization Practices, a panel of experts who advise and vote on the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's vaccine recommendations, is set to meet next month. The draft &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/agendas/draft-posted-2025-11-14-508.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;agenda&lt;/a&gt; for the Dec. 4-5 meeting includes discussions of the hepatitis B vaccine, and the meeting could entail votes on recommendations. In September, the panel &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/cdc-vaccine-advisory-panel-covid-19-hepatitis-b-vaccines/" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;voted&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to table a vote on whether to change the pediatric vaccine schedule for hepatitis B to a later date. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cassidy has previously weighed in on the panel. In June, the Louisiana Republican called for a postponement of the vaccine meeting after Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. said he was "retiring" all 17 members of the panel, before replacing the committee members with his own picks. And in August, Cassidy likewise called for the panel to postpone its September vaccine advisory committee meeting amid a slew of departures from the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The moves represented breaks with Kennedy, who was confirmed as the nation's top health official only after winning support from Cassidy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In February, Cassidy delivered the key vote to advance the nomination out of committee after he had expressed misgivings over Kennedy's nomination because of the doubts he had raised about vaccines. But Cassidy ultimately supported Kennedy's nomination, citing "serious commitments" he said he'd received from the administration. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asked by Brennan whether he regrets his vote to confirm Kennedy, Cassidy said "every reporter asks me that."&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"You live life forward," Cassidy added. "Let the day's own troubles be sufficient for the day. And I'll credit the secretary. He's brought attention to things like ultra-processed food that has, frankly, never received this sort of attention before, and people praise him for that. So he and I have publicly disagreed on some matters, but I strongly agree with him on others, and so, so that's how I'll answer your question."&lt;/p&gt;

    

                    
        
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 15:56:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNdjFxY2ZMRXhvemFBY0VJelpGay1zbEtQNkw3N2pzTUs4bDRmX1lMaU1FRm1LWHdPTGVQRWJBS3NrMWlObjJBSTFzODRKQUNocW92NzhhZzBiRWNqMFB0M2xMbE8wQ3NTREU0V3RMbGIxcG8wUDFNVk02OVVXS09fMmpXdHLSAYoBQVVfeXFMTWxReHJQbEZWQ0hKNjMySWRLLUNvb0otUVlfME52OTRmMjJMUXp1VzlMekFxS2R4TW04TUluYXlFQXVXZFVNNUtBeDh3VURRdmhfRFd3dmRuT29xQjdrTllwLUVTUTM4a2lSRUFXSzZDcWlveVlSU1Y2ck9wU0l2enhCTHZQbDlyY3p3</guid></item><item><title>可爱的侏儒金毛猎犬脾气暴躁的脸到处都在融化心-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/adorable-dwarf-golden-retriever-grumpy-152000543.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Some dogs win hearts with smiles, others with sweetness, but there is one &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/grumpy-golden-retriever-human-wont-share-toast" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Golden Retriever;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Golden Retriever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; who has a very unique secret weapon for this breed—his grumpiness. And once you catch a glimpse, you’re done for, because you’ll fall in love very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Born with dwarfism, this pup has the cutest, most unique expression that looks a little cranky but radiates charm. It’s impossible not to fall in love with that perfectly pouty face. Check him out!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;On November 5, TikToker @echogoldenbear shared a video of Echo, a &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/golden-retriever-puppys-bond-with-grandma-is-too-sweet" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:beautiful Golden Retriever;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;beautiful Golden Retriever&lt;/a&gt; who has dwarfism and is known as the "World's Grumpiest Golden Retriever."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It's not typical to see a grumpy Golden Retriever, but that's what is so charming about this guy. His grumpiness has everyone falling in love with him because he's not only short, thanks to his dwarfism, but his smile is hard not to smile back at.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/golden-retriever-fights-to-keep-eyes-open-to-greet-mom" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: Sleepy Golden Retriever Fights To Keep His Eyes Open Just To Greet His Mom;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Related: Sleepy Golden Retriever Fights To Keep His Eyes Open Just To Greet His Mom&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the comments, hundreds of people shared their feelings after watching Echo share his giant, grouchy grin. And it's safe to say people fell in love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;One person wrote, "Hey, there's nothing wrong with being short and mean, sincerely a short and mean girl."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Another shared, "He’s not mean, guys, he just likes to smile a lot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Someone else added, "No matter how many times you do this trend when it pops up, imma like it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Other comments included, "So he has a short temper," "What if he's trying to smile," "Grumpy old man," "His widdo ears," "But he is cute," "He thinks he's tall," and "He’s darling. He’s smiling with attitude. It’s fine."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/dog-face" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐶;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;🐶&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/parade-pets" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP to get “pawsitivity” delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP to get “pawsitivity” delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/paw-prints" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐾🐾;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;🐾🐾&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Dwarfism in Golden Retrievers Isn't Common&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The reason Echo is so short is because he has dwarfism, according to a comment his pet parent left on the video. But according to experts, it's not a common &lt;a href="https://www.mygoldenretrieverpuppies.com/blog/golden-retrievers-dwarfism" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:trait for Golden Retrievers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;trait for Golden Retrievers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;My &lt;em&gt;Golden Retriever Puppies&lt;/em&gt; explains that it's a "rare but notable" condition found in this breed, which causes them to have a smaller stature compared to other pups in this breed. They note that it is typically the result of a "genetic mutation" that impacts their bone growth and is inherited from one or both of their parents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Whether Echo is being &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/grumpy-persian-cat-stand-like-human-begging-for-dinner" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:grumpy;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;grumpy&lt;/a&gt; for real, for fun, or he’s trying to smile, we love that he’s living his best life, and that his community of people obsessed with him either way continues to grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally reported by &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/adorable-dwarf-golden-retrievers-grumpy-face" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade Pets;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Parade Pets&lt;/a&gt; on Nov 16, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Pet News;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Pet News&lt;/a&gt; section. Add Parade Pets as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=paradepets.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 15:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxON0VjcGZkRVlCUjNFZUE2TDAxNjFWMi1iMlRyOTl6TGwyVlF1a1dCVkxWQVB6RXhBU1dlLWQ5TzNQYXg3aGdYejRncTd6Q25OTFk1Y0Fvb0FvZVB3LUR3Z01vMmJ1QlZYU2R6T2lpZXpoNFZkcnloS1NhdktGSUlyeHl2Vkk4UXVaX05nQ29SaDNvYnRNSW9UZjhn</guid></item><item><title>心碎综合症：了解其症状、隐患以及医生如何治疗患者-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/broken-heart-syndrome-know-its-symptoms-hidden-risks-and-how-doctors-treat-the-suffering-patients/articleshow/125344946.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experiencing intense emotional pain, such as the loss of a loved one or sudden trauma, can feel overwhelming, but for some people it can also trigger a profound physical response in the heart. Medically referred to as Takotsubo syndrome or broken heart syndrome, this condition involves a sudden, reversible weakening of the heart’s left or right ventricle and often closely mimics the symptoms of a heart attack. Although initially considered rare and largely benign, recent research shows that broken heart syndrome can lead to serious cardiovascular complications if it is not recognised and appropriately managed. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9821117/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;review published in the Journal of Clinical Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; highlights how stress hormones, hormone levels, and the brain-heart connection create measurable effects on cardiac function and overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does stress affect the heart so strongly?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emerging research indicates that Takotsubo syndrome is frequently triggered by a sudden surge of stress hormones, which temporarily stun the heart muscle and impair its ability to pump efficiently. Activation of the sympathetic nervous system and the release of catecholamines are central features of this response. Other contributing factors include reduced oestrogen levels, particularly in post-menopausal women, altered brain-heart communication, and inflammatory processes involving cardiac immune cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; This intricate interaction between neurological, hormonal, and cardiovascular systems explains why both emotional and physical stressors can precipitate sudden ventricular dysfunction. Takotsubo syndrome demonstrates that the heart is sensitive not only to physical exertion but also to intense psychological stress, making emotional well-being a crucial factor in cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Silent Heart Attack Symptoms Women Often Miss | Spot the Warning Before It’s Too Late | Dr Rajeev Agrawal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Surges of stress hormones can temporarily weaken heart muscle.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Catecholamine release and sympathetic activation are central triggers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduced oestrogen and inflammatory responses increase vulnerability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Emotional and physical stressors can both precipitate the condition.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How do doctors diagnose broken heart syndrome?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The symptoms of Takotsubo syndrome are often indistinguishable from those of a heart attack, including severe chest pain, shortness of breath, and changes in the electrocardiogram or elevated cardiac enzymes. However, patients typically do not have blocked coronary arteries on coronary angiography. Imaging techniques such as echocardiography or cardiac magnetic resonance can reveal the characteristic “apical ballooning” of the left ventricle, giving the condition its informal name of apical ballooning syndrome, highlighting how subtle clinical differences can significantly influence patient care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Differentiating Takotsubo syndrome from acute coronary syndrome is essential because treatment approaches differ substantially. A recent illness, surgery, or intense emotional stress can raise suspicion for Takotsubo syndrome, guiding clinicians toward accurate diagnosis and appropriate management while avoiding unnecessary interventions, ultimately supporting safer outcomes for individuals experiencing severe stress-related cardiac events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Symptoms often mimic a heart attack, including chest pain and shortness of breath.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coronary arteries generally remain unobstructed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apical ballooning of the left ventricle is a hallmark feature on imaging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Accurate diagnosis ensures correct and effective management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What are the hidden risks of broken heart syndrome?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although many patients recover fully, Takotsubo syndrome is not entirely harmless. Complications can include heart failure, cardiogenic shock, irregular heart rhythms, and, in rare cases, left ventricular rupture. Early complications occur in approximately twenty per cent of patients, and mortality rates can approach those seen in acute coronary syndrome. Women, especially those who are post-menopausal, are disproportionately affected, while physical stressors such as surgery or severe illness are nearly as common as emotional triggers. The wide spectrum of potential complications underscores the importance of recognising Takotsubo syndrome as a serious cardiovascular condition rather than a symbolic or purely emotional response. These serious complications highlight the need for early diagnosis, cardiac monitoring, and awareness of risk factors such as stress triggers, hormonal changes, underlying heart disease, and immune responses, which can influence prognosis, recovery time, and long-term cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Takotsubo syndrome can lead to heart failure, cardiogenic shock, arrhythmias, and rare ventricular rupture.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Early complications occur in about twenty per cent of patients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Women, particularly post-menopausal, are most at risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Physical stress can trigger the condition as frequently as emotional events.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How is broken heart syndrome managed and treated?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Management of Takotsubo syndrome primarily involves acute monitoring of cardiac function and treatment of any heart failure symptoms. Physicians may prescribe beta-blockers, angiotensin-converting enzyme inhibitors, or angiotensin receptor blockers based on the patient’s cardiac status and existing comorbidities. Because overactivation of the sympathetic nervous system is a central mechanism, treatment aims to support recovery while limiting additional stress on the heart. Long-term strategies often include stress-reduction techniques, lifestyle adjustments, and follow-up imaging to ensure that ventricular function returns to normal. Continued research into molecular mechanisms may allow for more targeted and precise therapies in the future, improving both recovery and prognosis for affected patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Acute care includes careful monitoring and symptom management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beta-blockers or angiotensin-converting enzyme inhibitors can support heart recovery.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stress-reduction strategies and lifestyle modifications are important for long-term health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Follow-up imaging confirms full recovery of ventricular function.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What remains unknown about broken heart syndrome?&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite advances, many questions about Takotsubo syndrome remain unanswered. The precise interactions of the brain-heart axis, individual genetic susceptibility, and the reasons for recurrence are still under investigation. Some patients continue to experience persistent cardiac symptoms even after apparent recovery. Interestingly, Takotsubo syndrome can occasionally occur after intensely positive emotional events, a phenomenon sometimes referred to as “happy heart syndrome.” Ongoing research into inflammation, microvascular function, and molecular biomarkers may ultimately allow clinicians to predict susceptibility, anticipate complications, and develop interventions that are tailored to the unique pathways involved in this complex condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a healthcare professional before making any changes to your diet, medication, or lifestyle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/why-too-much-matcha-can-strain-your-liver-heart-and-nutrient-levels/articleshow/125344239.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Why too much matcha can strain your liver, heart and nutrient levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 14:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowJBVV95cUxPRU9ZaXJGOThneGVoUnljUlNobFlOZ2tISDcydTVZOG5fR1h3OTFUX1p3UmRhRzloOHNlSTlKVTNaeGFpNzZYaVJQelJIYVRRLUptOUUxd0FyVmNKNlhoaXZWVFdaZllTSHcxRU95OHFoMzZ0R0g3bzU2NTNoTEdkYTRMaUVOeWRzSWptWURQNV9jLUZMeUpiT0xwdnpLTnREbk9zcmx1ZU8yVnRfWHpzUVl6WkpnWHAtNnpZNDFPSFFrOTNVVEhGVnNUeWJBa01PZnNCT3hrY2NTV0M3eDF6TDNGYzBDamhUcUZfa1drVlM2NmJEcTJIZDREbmhoNmFDVjFHYVF0Sl9xRlVWNkUxY3hUN2c3VkJPZTdjNEpRX0FkSk0</guid></item><item><title>为期7天的输水挑战，将降低血糖水平-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/7-day-infused-water-challenge-that-will-reduce-blood-sugar-levels/photostory/125361874.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why combine: A mix brings together gentle botanicals that complement each other. While individual herbs have evidence, a combined approach gives variety and supports a broader metabolic boost.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ingredients to try: Use a small stick of cinnamon, 5 g soaked fenugreek, a few slices of cucumber, mint leaves, and a splash of lemon or lime.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;How to make: Place all in a jug, top up with water, let steep in the fridge for a few hours or overnight. Drink through the day.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9wFBVV95cUxPcDlSS3laLUxHc0pwZUd3aTFRbnl4cVBuV09KQzhZV0xBanFya29IOWlfMW1lM0JkR0JJRnRUYTZxZEdVNjFSYXUwbnR2aFdoWk5fWXhYMXBEb0tZNnFrWEZvb2ZtQWtmZmo2aTZ4alE0aWp3ZnhUSENobVY3cVBpaDRYNXNSdU1mUHR2QkxOWUpreVE0dDQtcU02LTRxZk5CQWhITnF0R2F1QTFNTE9vZmR3U0RNQnUwajVYTnl3WnJoSWxBTG1yNWlRWFo1RERycjBBSE5yQjBXMzFaWXM1UnlBU1dNTngzOWZVbGVvUTRJUFRkVWl30gH_AUFVX3lxTE1la0o5d0hKOEo4Y0dRSUh0YmNZNFZ2WEh1TFNrUF9fRVJkdkxVQUlZa0o3bEdhdWdZZFdIelhSTXZjbXY0UUE4SDJFdlZCOGhLUktsTGNRanNJcEF2amRRb3FVb3FmOXhIcFowWXBmTDlxaktJeFkwa185eF85UHRUbUExN05HUlFiOEtaZzhHc0NGYUdHLWF4aEdYUUl3VVRMQnR1cFNhWHlKUWhzekxkQVZzOWE1OHBPQVFic21CcGhpMWxsajNlaXczRTdINy1lOTNXbVNZQU9TNUxOMmhWNVJ0ajBQSS1mam1JUnJpMkhLQTRnaWdXa3V2VGJaWQ</guid></item><item><title>褪黑激素对你的心脏有害吗？专家解释新发现。- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/is-melatonin-bad-for-your-heart-an-expert-explains-the-new-findings</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A study presented at the American Heart Association's scientific meetings has raised concerns about melatonin, one of Britain's most commonly prescribed sleep  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/hiv" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73049" data-postid="180949" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;aids&lt;/a&gt;. The findings suggest that long-term users face a higher risk of heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the preliminary data demands careful scrutiny before the alarm is sounded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/melatonin-15404"&gt;Melatonin&lt;/a&gt; has been prescribed in the UK for nearly two decades, with 2.5 million prescriptions issued in England &lt;a href="https://openprescribing.net/chemical/0401010AD/"&gt;last year alone&lt;/a&gt;. The drug is a synthetic version of the hormone naturally produced in the brain – the so-called "hormone of darkness" that regulates our sleep–wake cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/humans-used-to-sleep-twice-every-night-heres-why-it-vanished"&gt;Humans Used to Sleep Twice Every Night. Here's Why It Vanished.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, it's been &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/medicines/melatonin/who-can-and-cannot-take-melatonin/"&gt;considered safe&lt;/a&gt; for treating short-term sleep problems in adults and, under specialist supervision, for children with learning disabilities or  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-adhd" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73112" data-postid="180949" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;ADHD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, published only as a &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/circ.152.suppl_3.4371606"&gt;brief summary&lt;/a&gt;, analyzed electronic health records of roughly 130,000 adults with sleep difficulties over five years – half of whom took melatonin and half of whom didn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who took melatonin for at least a year were roughly three times more likely to be hospitalized with heart failure than non-users (19 percent of people who took melatonin versus 6.6 percent of people who did not).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-term users also faced higher rates of heart failure diagnosis and death from any cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers attempted to balance their comparison by matching melatonin users with non-users across 40 factors, including age, health conditions and medications. Yet the study found only an association, not causation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This distinction matters. Correlation doesn't prove that melatonin caused heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The devil, as ever, lives in the missing details. Only a 300-word summary of the study exists so far, meaning crucial information – melatonin dosage, insomnia severity, lifestyle factors – remains unreported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study's methodology raises questions. It relied on electronic medical records rather than direct patient follow-up or interviews, which can leave gaps in the data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research drew from TriNetX Global Research Network, a large international database. But healthcare practices and record-keeping vary wildly between hospitals and nations, potentially skewing results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the UK, melatonin requires a prescription for specific conditions. But in the US, it's sold over the counter – purchases that are often not documented in medical records. This means some people categorized as non-users may actually have been taking melatonin, muddying the comparison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The missing piece of the puzzle&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even assuming both groups were correctly identified and matched, a key question lingers: why did one group receive melatonin while the other didn't?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps those prescribed the drug suffered more severe or disruptive sleep problems – symptoms that might reflect underlying health issues, including heart problems. If so, melatonin might simply be a marker of existing risk rather than the cause of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intriguingly, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/clc.70107"&gt;previous studies&lt;/a&gt; in heart failure patients suggested melatonin may actually protect heart health by improving psychological wellbeing and heart function. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/ehf2.12829"&gt;Other research indicated&lt;/a&gt; it could ease symptoms in people with heart failure and serve as a safe complementary therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the study exists only as an abstract, it hasn't undergone  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/science-peer-review" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73086" data-postid="180949" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;peer review&lt;/a&gt;. And information on the study's methods and results remains limited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the findings are noteworthy and raise legitimate questions about the long-term risks of using this supplement, they're far from conclusive. Further studies are needed to determine whether prolonged melatonin use affects heart health, and if so, how.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors face a familiar balancing act: weighing treatment benefits against potential risks. Poor sleep doesn't just affect the heart; it's linked to &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/sleep-disorders/sleep-and-heart-health#:%7E:text=Sleep%20disorders%20such%20as%20insomnia%2C%20apnea%2C%20narcolepsy%20and,linked%20to%20a%20higher%20risk%20of%20cardiovascular%20diseases."&gt;problems&lt;/a&gt; with metabolism, mental health and the immune system, among others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors typically start with &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/every-mind-matters/mental-wellbeing-tips/how-to-fall-asleep-faster-and-sleep-better/"&gt;lifestyle changes, better sleep habits&lt;/a&gt; and talk therapy. But when these fail to improve sleep quality, short-term medication may be necessary to restore healthy patterns and prevent further health complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The melatonin story isn't over. It's just beginning. Until fuller evidence emerges, panic seems premature.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/269131/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/heba-ghazal-2395642"&gt;Heba Ghazal&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer, Pharmacy, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/kingston-university-949"&gt;Kingston University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/should-you-worry-about-melatonin-and-heart-failure-the-evidence-isnt-clear-269131"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 14:03:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPY0l2QlZiN24zQmQ4SUFOYk5JeUxTY01jTHNjNFQtaHlkUjBUVWJlVkp3bkFMVmpXbEtWTGV4Q0lVM3VYakpXVTZ1SEUxS2FZN2JkMXY1Ti1LQlB0REJ4b01pV1Bub1NJNVQ3dW1WZXBvaUNXYlJQYzE5cWNXbUhUdmg2N2RYcm9fYkJzTmNsN2t2LUNSSmhmdHhmUEU</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现一种可以预防和逆转关键类型心脏病的饮食- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-discover-a-diet-that-can-prevent-and-reverse-a-key-type-of-heart-disease/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:05:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPNTROWnZoSmJWajEtZ3JUSW1lZlM1OVZ0MTEtSk1OUGhJbjZjXzI4WDN2SF9ISW1EclYyZ0RHY1VYV3dXd29JOU13REk3UnFzclEwYzl0MEdLMDR3M1RSN2J0UzRkYW9Xd3BacFNPYzRXeU1URXVaOWR1OHkzaUtFUFVCdDkwQU01V1Zqb1dqNU4yZjFsb2tkTEt5VEJVblBBcTlSLUVlVFc5NmVRTnc</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，养猫可能会使您患精神分裂症的风险增加一倍- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/owning-a-cat-could-double-your-risk-of-schizophrenia-research-suggests</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Having a cat as a pet could potentially double a person's risk of schizophrenia-related conditions, according to an analysis of 17 studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Psychiatrist John McGrath and colleagues at the Queensland Centre for Mental Health Research in Australia looked at papers published over the last 44 years in 11 countries, including the US and the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their 2023 study &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/schbul/sbad168"&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; "a significant positive association between broadly defined cat ownership and an increased risk of schizophrenia-related disorders."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is a need for more high-quality studies in this field," the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/schbul/sbad168"&gt;emphasize&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/adorable-cat-helps-scientists-discover-new-virus-for-second-time"&gt;Adorable Cat Helps Scientists Discover New Virus (For Second Time)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This idea that cat ownership could be linked to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/schizophrenia" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73022" data-postid="181568" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;schizophrenia&lt;/a&gt; risk was proposed in a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/schbul/21.2.167"&gt;1995 study&lt;/a&gt;, with exposure to a parasite called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toxoplasma_gondii"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Toxoplasma gondii&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; suggested as a cause. But the research so far has put forth mixed conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cureus.com/articles/128008-association-between-childhood-exposure-to-pet-cats-and-later-diagnosis-of-schizophrenia-a-case-control-study-in-saudi-arabia#!/"&gt;Studies have found&lt;/a&gt; that being around cats during childhood might make a person more likely to develop schizophrenia; however, &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0225320"&gt;not all research&lt;/a&gt; has found an association.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_149648" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-149648" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/09/DiagramOfToxoplasmaLifeCycleFromCDC.gif" alt="Diagram of toxoplasmosis lifecycle" class="wp-image-149648 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/09/DiagramOfToxoplasmaLifeCycleFromCDC.gif 700w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/09/DiagramOfToxoplasmaLifeCycleFromCDC-642x519.gif 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/09/DiagramOfToxoplasmaLifeCycleFromCDC-513x415.gif 513w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/09/DiagramOfToxoplasmaLifeCycleFromCDC-600x485.gif 600w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-149648" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Toxoplasmosis is only known to reproduce in cats (1), but can be spread to humans through intermediate hosts (2, 5, 7) as well. (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/dpdx/toxoplasmosis/index.html"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some papers also &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1159/000505786"&gt;link cat exposure to higher scores&lt;/a&gt; on scales that measure traits related to schizophrenia – which affects a person's thoughts, feelings, and behaviors – and psychotic-like experiences, but again, other studies &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/psychological-medicine/article/curiosity-killed-the-cat-no-evidence-of-an-association-between-cat-ownership-and-psychotic-symptoms-at-ages-13-and-18-years-in-a-uk-general-population-cohort/75C9A48B669BE36E947AFB0BC5CB00CA"&gt;don't show this connection&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get a clearer picture, McGrath and his team say there's a need for a thorough review and analysis of all the research on these topics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;T. gondii&lt;/em&gt; is a mostly harmless parasite that can be transmitted through undercooked meat or contaminated water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bite from an infected cat, or the cat's feces, can also transmit &lt;em&gt;T. gondii &lt;/em&gt;can also be transmitted through a bite from an infected cat or through the cat's feces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Estimates suggest that &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/toxoplasmosis/about/?CDC_AAref_Val=https://www.cdc.gov/parasites/toxoplasmosis/gen_info/faqs.html"&gt;&lt;em&gt;T. gondii&lt;/em&gt; infects about 40 million people in the US&lt;/a&gt;, typically without any symptoms. Meanwhile, researchers keep finding more &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mind-altering-parasite-may-make-infected-people-more-attractive-study-suggests"&gt;strange effects that infections may have&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once inside our bodies, &lt;em&gt;T. gondii&lt;/em&gt; can infiltrate the central nervous system and influence neurotransmitters. The parasite has been &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-parasite-has-been-linked-to-an-increased-risk-of-rage-disorder"&gt;linked to personality changes&lt;/a&gt;, the emergence of psychotic symptoms, and some neurological disorders, including &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/50-year-old-theory-on-schizophrenias-voices-confirmed-by-recent-study"&gt;schizophrenia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, a link doesn't prove &lt;em&gt;T. gondii&lt;/em&gt; causes these changes or that the parasite was passed on to a human from a cat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_147484" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-147484" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/FuzzyGreyKittenLyingInKittyLitterBoxNextToHouseFurniture.jpg" alt="Cat lying in kitty litter box" class="wp-image-147484 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/FuzzyGreyKittenLyingInKittyLitterBoxNextToHouseFurniture.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/FuzzyGreyKittenLyingInKittyLitterBoxNextToHouseFurniture-514x415.jpg 514w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/12/FuzzyGreyKittenLyingInKittyLitterBoxNextToHouseFurniture-600x484.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-147484" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Cat feces could be the source of toxoplasmosis. &lt;span&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/a-cat-laying-in-a-bowl-on-the-floor-4ZelmqpEcOg"&gt;frosted_vulpes_ferrilata/Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"After adjusting for covariates, we found that individuals exposed to cats had approximately twice the odds of developing schizophrenia," the Australian team &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/schbul/sbad168"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some important things to keep in mind here, like the fact that 15 of the 17 studies were case-control studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This kind of research can't show cause and effect, and it often doesn't account for factors that may have affected both the exposure and the outcome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also highlight the low quality of a number of the examined studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results were inconsistent across studies, but those of higher quality suggested that associations in unadjusted models might have been due to factors that could have influenced the results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0225320"&gt;One study found&lt;/a&gt; no significant association between owning a cat before age 13 and later developing schizophrenia, but it did identify a significant link when narrowing down cat ownership to a specific period (ages 9 to 12). This inconsistency suggests that the critical window for cat exposure is not well defined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0920996413001436?via=ihub"&gt;study in the US&lt;/a&gt;, which involved 354 psychology students, didn't find a connection between owning a cat and schizotypy scores. However, those who had received a cat bite had higher scores when compared to those who had not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1159/000505786"&gt;Another study&lt;/a&gt;, which included people with and without mental disorders, discovered a connection between cat bites and higher scores on tests measuring particular psychological experiences. But they suggested other pathogens, such as &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK557629/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pasteurella multocida&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, may be responsible instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cat-parasite-can-seriously-disrupt-brain-function-study-suggests"&gt;Cat Parasite Can Seriously Disrupt Brain Function, Study Suggests&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before we can make any firm interpretations, the researchers reiterate that we need better and broader research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our review provides support for an association between cat ownership and schizophrenia-related disorders," the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/schbul/sbad168"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is a need for more high-quality studies, based on large, representative samples to better understand cat ownership as a candidate risk-modifying factor for mental disorders."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/schbul/sbad168"&gt;Schizophrenia Bulletin&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in December 2023.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:03:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQdHE5Ty1SQmd5Q2ZsOTJ6Mk9SSFdEQ2xPQ3docFFzUlVNNTJYZWJfeXRSVUItWUpDekdDZzlDRW1Yem1oYnZFZnN5Y05HSGNsQkVMdEJKUUR4VG83MzZ3ekg5NldXNUdBZTJkOEZxeUJwODdoYnhkNWNhbVhWN1N2SUpGeHQwdV9YNldDSkg4U3hJenNKeGUzRUx3bkNrcnFQ</guid></item><item><title>医生说一种高度传染性的病毒现在“失控”。以下是您应该了解的信息。- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/hand-foot-and-mouth-disease-spike-2025-goog_l_69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This fall, multiple states including &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/baltimore/news/maryland-hand-foot-mouth-disease-anne-arundel-county-schools/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Maryland" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cbsnews.com/baltimore/news/maryland-hand-foot-mouth-disease-anne-arundel-county-schools/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Maryland&lt;/a&gt;, Virginia, &lt;a href="https://www.actionnews5.com/2025/10/20/hand-foot-mouth-disease-confirmed-30-schools-daycares-shelby-co/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Tennessee" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.actionnews5.com/2025/10/20/hand-foot-mouth-disease-confirmed-30-schools-daycares-shelby-co/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Tennessee&lt;/a&gt; and Wisconsin have reported outbreaks of hand, foot and mouth disease, a contagious virus that commonly infects children under 5 but can also cause symptoms in older kids and adults, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HuffPost Life delivers practical, reliable advice to navigate life’s challenges and make informed decisions. Support journalism that empowers you — &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support?utm_campaign=in-text-support" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="join our membership program today." data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;join our membership program today.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This year, [cases seem] to be out of control,” said &lt;a href="https://profiles.hopkinsmedicine.org/provider/allison-lorna-agwu/2700537" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Allison Agwu" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://profiles.hopkinsmedicine.org/provider/allison-lorna-agwu/2700537" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Dr. Allison Agwu&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of adult and pediatric infectious diseases at Johns Hopkins University School of Medicine in Baltimore. For example, in Agwu’s state of Maryland, cases are at “four to five times what they saw this time last year,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://directory.hsc.wvu.edu/Profile/88750" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Matthew Thomas" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://directory.hsc.wvu.edu/Profile/88750" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Dr. Matthew Thomas&lt;/a&gt;, a pediatric infectious diseases specialist at WVU Medicine Golisano Children’s in West Virginia, said spikes typically happen in cycles. “Some years you’ll see a lot of cases, like we’re seeing this year, and then it kind of fades away, where you don’t hear about it for a while,” Thomas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;With cases higher than normal, it’s important to know the signs of the virus and what to do if you (or your kids) get sick. Here’s what to know:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As the name suggests, symptoms include blisters on the hands, feet and mouth.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hand, foot and mouth is a virus within the family of enteroviruses, explained &lt;a href="https://profiles.mountsinai.org/jennifer-duchon" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Jennifer Duchon" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://profiles.mountsinai.org/jennifer-duchon" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;Dr. Jennifer Duchon&lt;/a&gt;, an associate professor in the divisions of pediatric infectious disease and newborn medicine at Mount Sinai Hospital in New York.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enteroviruses can present with a range of symptoms. In the case of hand, foot and mouth, “people can have symptoms like a common cold,” according to Thomas. This includes a fever, Agwu added, in addition to respiratory symptoms such as a runny nose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But then a common feature is that they will have a rash, typically on the hands and feet, as well as ulcers or blisters within the mouth,” Thomas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blisters in the mouth are generally at the back of the throat and are often really painful, according to Duchon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the hands and feet, the rash may appear as little red bumps. “Those show up a couple days after the fever,” Agwu noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sometimes people’s hands will start to peel when the rash starts to go away, their feet will start to peel after the rash goes away,” Duchon said. “In really dramatic cases, sometimes your fingernails can fall off.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Jill Lehmann Photography via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Jill Lehmann Photography via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Hand, foot and mouth disease can cause blister-like bumps.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The disease spreads through respiratory droplets and fecal matter and can live on surfaces.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hand, foot and mouth disease is “super contagious,” Agwu said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It spreads through respiratory droplets that go out in the air when someone coughs or sneezes, according to Thomas. It can also spread via the fluid from the blisters or via infected surfaces. So if a child who has the virus drools on toys at daycare, other kids could get sick from those toys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s also spread in stool, so particularly for our infants who are not yet potty trained, someone who’s changing diapers is often putting themselves at risk,” Thomas said. For parents or caretakers changing dirty diapers, good hand hygiene is particularly important. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Most children and adults recover easily at home.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the virus certainly can be gruesome, and often painful, most people do recover at home with the help of symptomatic care such as fever-reducing medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are no specific medications for hand, foot and mouth, and since it’s a viral illness, “no antibiotics are going to get rid of it,” Agwu said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you or your children do get sick, you should “try to avoid spreading it to anyone else,” Thomas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone who is sick with hand, foot and mouth should isolate from others so they don’t pass on the virus, while also hydrating and eating enough nutrients. The virus tends to last for about a week in most people, Thomas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you’re having more severe symptoms, like if you’re having a lot of ulcers in your mouth, it may take up to 10 to 14 days to resolve fully,” Thomas added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some people require additional care, though. If you aren’t able to hydrate, or keep your sick child hydrated, you should seek medical care, Thomas noted. The same is true if whoever is sick isn’t able to eat enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Duchon added, “If you’ve had hand, foot and mouth and afterwards, or towards the end of the illness, you’re feeling really, really tired or having trouble breathing, those are things that are really serious to look for that can mean that the heart has been affected. That’s a very rare but serious complication.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hand-washing is a good way to protect yourself from catching this virus.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are a number of things you can do to keep yourself from getting sick with hand, foot and mouth and other viruses that are currently circulating such as the common cold and &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/news/topic/coronavirus" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="COVID-19" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/news/topic/coronavirus" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The way to prevent it is going to be always the same thing — washing hands ... if you’re touching something that’s problematic, like stool or what have you, making sure you’re doubling down on using good hand hygiene,” Agwu said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re out and about, a “good alcohol-based hand sanitizer” is a fine option, too, but hand-washing with soap and water is ideal, Thomas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s also helpful to avoid touching your face as much as you can, Agwu noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry-support-huffpost-mid-article" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost hidden campaign-cta"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title default-title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Power&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;The&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Truth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost__message--main"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__sub-headline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join HuffPost members who keep fearless, inclusive journalism alive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support?utm_campaign=mid-article-web" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already a member? &lt;a class="js-entry-link-no-impression" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fhand-foot-and-mouth-disease-spike-2025-goog_l_69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69137e92e4b0c374cf511d14" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a general rule of thumb for virus prevention of any kind, staying away from sick people and wearing a mask to protect yourself from virus shed are also good ways to stay healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPTmlsRUtPd0x0M0Y4bm0ycmVHcGhqZVdKc3BjSWNOcjlmZHpDWHd5SkY4R3dINFJBZkRXUzVLZ3FJeXBTSEFSbVRnTVd4TGQ0YkZWU0dlZUdPYm0yMXpPTC1oZ1Y4anMxaVZ3YlZzSzY0b1k1RFR5bnVRZGl3TVhWQ2pYLVBoTWdld3BOeWZ5Uk5iaDN0TDZzV1hKX1B5VGFBT0NB0gGoAUFVX3lxTE5jbk5Wdk1kZVhvVmltU3BFVHlMX3NBZGhycWFxcFNMcXBTNTh1bElHRFdXNWtmV0RRRkFldUNqcVljcGdpTFV0ajN0dm5OZVpmMnZtbTFpa0JZTjNiaGlwMUwtVzE1Q21iYUpNa3BIQUFkUWM4WG1yQjFMUWtObUFCS1c3RU1pS2hZTGFjRjVzdzEwNnVPaXFZMlpqd0hNNTRCcEF0eExadA</guid></item><item><title>新的突破可以帮助预防青光眼的破坏性影响- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/new-breakthrough-could-help-prevent-the-devastating-impact-of-glaucoma</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;There's fresh hope for &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mysterious-form-of-vision-loss-may-brew-inside-the-gut-scientists-say"&gt;early detection&lt;/a&gt; and new treatments of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glaucoma"&gt;glaucoma&lt;/a&gt;, a group of eye diseases that have &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-eye-test-can-detect-glaucoma-4-years-before-current-tests"&gt;devastating effects on vision&lt;/a&gt; – and for which there is currently no cure. A new study has identified two natural molecules that play an important role in these conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The molecules are &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Agmatine"&gt;agmatine&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thiamine"&gt;thiamine&lt;/a&gt; (also known as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="181436" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamin&lt;/a&gt; B1), and their role in protecting against glaucoma was discovered by researchers led by a team from the University of Missouri.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists suggest that agmatine and thiamine could be used as biomarkers for earlier detection of glaucoma, allowing doctors to put preventative measures in place at an earlier stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/space-can-hurt-your-vision-and-now-we-can-predict-the-damage"&gt;Space Can Hurt Your Vision, And Now We Can Predict The Damage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In several cases, people do not find out they have glaucoma until they are older and their eye pressure is elevated," &lt;a href="https://showme.missouri.edu/2025/mizzou-researcher-discovers-natural-molecules-that-may-help-glaucoma-patients/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; ophthalmology researcher Pawan Singh, from the University of Missouri.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The molecules could also help with new treatments: boosting the levels of agmatine and thiamine in mice was shown to reduce inflammation in the retina, protect the retinal ganglion nerve cells (RGCs) that are typically damaged by glaucoma, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/can-eye-exercises-improve-your-vision-an-expert-reveals-the-truth"&gt;improve the vision&lt;/a&gt; of the animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team examined a fluid in the eye called the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aqueous_humour"&gt;aqueous humor&lt;/a&gt; in 19 glaucoma patients and 10 healthy people, testing for 135 different &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Metabolite"&gt;metabolites&lt;/a&gt;. Of those, agmatine and thiamine were found to be especially reduced in people with glaucoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Agmatine and thiamine could be potential immunomodulatory or neuroprotective drugs to treat or prevent neuroinflammatory damage to the retina during glaucoma," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1167/iovs.66.5.28"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_181439" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181439" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/ChemicalLevels.jpg" alt="Chemical level chart" class="wp-image-181439 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/ChemicalLevels.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/ChemicalLevels-600x462.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-181439" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers looked for chemical abnormalities in the eyes of people with glaucoma. (Monu et al., &lt;em&gt;Invest. Ophthalmol. Vis. Sci.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also tested agmatine and thiamine on stressed mouse photoreceptor cells in the lab, finding more positive results: the chemicals &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cocoa-extract-supplements-could-reduce-aging-related-chronic-inflammation"&gt;reduced inflammation&lt;/a&gt; in the cells, and protected them from dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Glaucoma slowly leads to irreversible blindness, caused by damage to the nerves at the back of the eye. It's often, &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/glaucoma/symptoms-causes/syc-20372839"&gt;but not always&lt;/a&gt;, linked to elevated pressure in the eye – something that current treatments focus on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those treatments can only really slow down the disease though. Agmatine and thiamine show promise in stopping the progression of nerve cell &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-eyes-can-shed-light-on-underlying-health-problems"&gt;damage in the eye&lt;/a&gt;, and perhaps reverse some of the damage that's already been done. However, a lot of further study is needed before this can be used to treat humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our long-term goal is to see if doctors could one day do a simple blood test to check for these biomarkers," &lt;a href="https://showme.missouri.edu/2025/mizzou-researcher-discovers-natural-molecules-that-may-help-glaucoma-patients/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Singh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If they can, hopefully they will be able to catch the disease much earlier, before vision loss occurs, so patients can receive treatment sooner."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1167/iovs.66.5.28"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Investigative Ophthalmology and Visual Science&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:53:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOX3g2UDhLclpidjRGWlJwa3R1aGtjN0JjbjdmbnZ2RkVjdmI1dllRM2t5U0tRcVdZaTMzQm1pSFJnMlpPTUp3ZmRIY2ZIdUxYaWw2bV95Z01Xb0VvQk5rdzRPUklrLVN2dTlkXzRxX1ZrNFQyVV82X1lZX2p2TVk0bjBtemZWZlk0VDRCRUJsNHY3QzZ4Z0JIb0xoNE15UGlr</guid></item><item><title>GLP-1s令人惊讶的新用途：酒精和药物成瘾-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/16/glp1-weight-loss-addiction-drug-alcohol/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DN3X723VDRCMJHPFI752VM444E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;MIAMI — When Susan Akin first started injecting a coveted weight-loss drug early this year, the chaos in her brain quieted. The relentless cravings subsided — only they’d never been for food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HITF5E6LGJGZ7NN5RMHJROBUMQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The medication instead dulled her urges for the cocaine and alcohol that caused her to plow her car into a tree, spiral into psychosis and wind up admitted to a high-end addiction treatment center in Delray Beach, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:31:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOdW5lYUhlMlNaOG1kVmtBLW5HdWI4eVBCUE5sQmpNVFJKOXBWR21zRkRYbDltcHR2TXNURVk3TFhTY2ZSNU1pMl9GUjhjWUd3Z3lTVzVDaWVJSGpnS0xEY0RvYUNYZGRDSkM5dnNjdEp0OUdkSTlUc05UaW9GZ2J3aTB0azlZUlZfN3NDdHZRNWpYbkU</guid></item><item><title>多动症与大脑边缘系统的早期和稳定差异有关- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/adhd-is-linked-to-early-and-stable-differences-in-brains-limbic-system/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children and adolescents with attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) appear to show early and stable disruptions in a key brain system involved in emotional and cognitive processing, according to new research published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.bpsc.2025.09.022" target="_blank"&gt;Biological Psychiatry: Cognitive Neuroscience and Neuroimaging&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. The findings suggest that ADHD involves differences in how emotional and cognitive brain circuits are physically wired during development. Although these differences are subtle, they could play a role in shaping the severity of symptoms across childhood and adolescence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ADHD has increasingly been conceptualized as a disorder that affects the brain’s connectivity. Many studies have focused on the brain’s outer cortical regions, such as the frontal lobes, which are involved in attention and executive function. However, less is known about how deeper brain structures, like those in the limbic system, develop in children with ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The limbic system helps regulate emotion and integrates emotional signals with cognitive processes. It is also implicated in behavioral regulation, impulse control, and mood—all areas where people with ADHD often experience difficulties. Emotional dysregulation is especially common in ADHD and can affect quality of life. Given the limbic system’s role in emotion and behavior, the researchers aimed to better understand how its white matter—bundles of nerve fibers that connect brain regions—develops in youth with ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Longitudinal brain imaging research allows scientists to examine how brain structures change over time. By focusing on the limbic system and using more advanced imaging techniques than in past research, the authors of this study hoped to uncover developmental patterns that may help explain why some symptoms of ADHD persist or worsen during adolescence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Most research on ADHD brain development has focused on the outer regions of the brain, especially the frontal and striatal areas linked to attention and control,” said study author Michael Connaughton of the Department of Psychiatry at Trinity College Dublin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We wanted to look deeper – literally – into the limbic system, the brain’s emotional core that connects feeling, motivation, and focus. These regions have been difficult to study because of their complexity and location, but new MRI analysis techniques now let us see them with much finer detail. That opened the door to an important question: how do emotion-related brain pathways mature in ADHD as children move through adolescence?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed brain imaging data from 169 children and adolescents between the ages of 9 and 14. Among them, 72 had been diagnosed with ADHD, while 97 served as a comparison group without the disorder. Each participant underwent advanced diffusion MRI scans at three different time points spaced about 18 months apart. This approach allowed researchers to track changes in brain white matter over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A key strength of this study was that ADHD was confirmed at multiple time points, showing that participants met diagnostic criteria both early and later in development,” Connaughton noted. “This repeated confirmation is crucial for developmental research – it ensures we’re capturing stable features of ADHD rather than temporary fluctuations that can occur as children grow and symptoms change.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers used an advanced brain imaging technique called diffusion kurtosis imaging to examine the structure of white matter in the brain. This method tracks how water molecules move through brain tissue. In healthy white matter, which consists of tightly packed, insulated nerve fibers, water tends to move in a highly organized way. When the structure is less orderly, water movement becomes more random.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One specific measurement, called kurtosis anisotropy, captures this level of organization. Higher kurtosis anisotropy values indicate that the white matter fibers are well-organized and likely well-myelinated, meaning they are coated with a protective layer that helps electrical signals travel efficiently. Lower values suggest that the white matter may be less developed or less efficient at supporting fast communication between brain regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers focused on five major white matter tracts in the limbic system, including the cingulum bundle, which connects regions involved in both cognition and emotion. They also constructed brain network models to assess how different parts of the limbic system were interconnected in each participant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared to the control group, the children with ADHD showed lower kurtosis anisotropy in both the left and right cingulum bundles. These reductions were present across all three time points, suggesting that the white matter differences were not due to temporary fluctuations but instead reflected a stable, early-emerging feature of ADHD. The pattern of white matter development followed a typical trajectory over time, but those with ADHD started out at a lower baseline and did not catch up to their peers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Individuals with ADHD showed stable reductions in limbic system white matter microstructural organisation, specifically lower kurtosis anisotropy in the bilateral cingulum bundle, across childhood and adolescence,” Connaughton told PsyPost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, the overall number and efficiency of connections within the limbic system did not significantly differ between the ADHD and control groups when considered as a whole. However, when the researchers looked at symptom severity within the ADHD group, a clearer picture emerged. Children and adolescents with more severe ADHD symptoms tended to have lower network density and reduced routing efficiency in their limbic system connections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What stood out most was that connectivity within the limbic system network predicted symptom severity rather than diagnosis,” Connaughton said. “This reinforces the view of ADHD as a dimensional condition, existing along a continuum rather than as a categorical divide.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The relationship between limbic system connectivity and symptom severity was not explained by differences in the cingulum bundle, suggesting that both local microstructure and broader network organization may contribute to ADHD symptoms in distinct ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The differences observed in the study were relatively small in size, but they were consistent. “They aren’t large enough for clinical prediction, but in neurodevelopment, small differences across interconnected systems can still influence symptom severity and presentation,” Connaughton explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Overall, the findings indicate that ADHD involves early, stable disruptions in limbic white matter development, particularly within the cingulum, and that reductions in white matter interconnecting limbic regions become more pronounced in individuals with more severe ADHD symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than pointing to a single brain abnormality, the results support the idea that ADHD involves distributed, small-scale differences across multiple systems. These differences may arise early in life and contribute to how symptoms unfold over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These results don’t point to a single ‘ADHD biomarker,'” Connaughton said. “They reflect group- level trends, not diagnostic markers, and should be seen as part of a larger developmental picture that combines genetics, environment, and experience.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study offers important insights but also has some limitations. One issue is that the limbic system does not have a universally agreed-upon anatomical definition. Different studies may include or exclude certain regions, which can complicate comparisons across research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The age range studied was also relatively narrow, focusing on the transition from late childhood into early adolescence. Some individuals with ADHD may show delayed brain development that catches up later in adolescence or early adulthood. Extending the research to cover a wider age range could help clarify whether the differences observed here persist, worsen, or diminish over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We aim to track these developmental changes across the lifespan, extending our work into late adolescence and early adulthood when brain connectivity continues to evolve,” Connaughton explained. “By following individuals over longer periods and integrating imaging with genetic and behavioural data, we can begin to see how early brain differences unfold, stabilize, or adapt over time. The goal is to build a lifespan model of ADHD that helps both patients and clinicians understand why symptoms persist or remit across life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.bpsc.2025.09.022" target="_blank"&gt;Limbic System White Matter in Children and Adolescents with ADHD: A Longitudinal Diffusion MRI Analysis&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Michael Connaughton, Alexander Leemans, Timothy J. Silk, Vicki Anderson, Erik O’Hanlon, Robert Whelan, and Jane McGrath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:05:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxNM3ZiM2VqY1ZwZzNVanM5UjZhOEwzWmQ2RkxRcm80UlZ3TkhTMlNfZU9teDczZV9udmtMRkZTSTdoY01xU1hOMjVXMDBic3ZWdENBT1FKOGE4QnQ4cVRnSXgzSWpDOEVmdVp6eU15bVJnWTc3Smo2Y253NlJZXzRZeVJYMmI5WFQyRVdRek9kalV2MU9SZUNHNHd6bw</guid></item><item><title>加拿大失去了消灭麻疹的地位，美国紧随其后- The Hill</title><link>https://thehill.com/policy/healthcare/5606830-vaccination-rates-decline-americas/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>The Hill</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPTU9TRDdXQ01hemp5M0FaM3VHckFBbGd3MzgtQ3hpZU9uVC0tV2tISUIwaDNudmRjcEtHXzg1UjFGUUN6eVo2TVkxS2hXQWJ0S3pnY2dPZmhsbHA5ZXN3RGhMYkQtQzBxQjF6REtCeVpZWDNILTdwcFdKSVhUckRjaXpEVldmemd30gGOAUFVX3lxTFBmYml1YzJCMzBCcDdSRFVTTWkzalg4MGcxdy1YNFZIYXpFd0NKSVJweHcyOTFEMXBJd2JXUWtUeTdfc0NVbVhuTERpVkktTVJXUVNlYnBXbHlQd1c5NTZ4RFpJQlFNb0NzZGdMeWM2NEY4ZW9JMFpJZGU0RVBHV1doaVRJeXc1NzVPb19WNWc</guid></item><item><title>麻省理工学院发明可注射脑芯片-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/mit-injectable-brain-chip</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;While companies like Elon Musk’s Neuralink are hard at work on brain-computer interfaces that require surgery to cut open the skull and insert a complex array of wires into a person’s head, a team of researchers at MIT have been researching a wireless electronic brain implant that they say could provide a non-invasive alternative that makes the technology far easier to access.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;They describe the system, called Circulatronics, as more of a treatment platform than a one-off brain chip. Working with researchers from Wellesley College and Harvard University, the MIT team recently &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41587-025-02809-3" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;released a paper&lt;/a&gt; on the new technology, which they describe as an autonomous bioelectronic implant.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;As &lt;a href="https://newatlas.com/brain/mit-injectable-brain-chips-treat-disease/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;New Atlas&lt;/em&gt; points out&lt;/a&gt;, the Circulatronics platform starts with an injectable swarm of sub-cellular sized wireless electronic devices, or “SWEDs,” which can travel into inflamed regions of the patient’s brain after being injected into the bloodstream. They do so by fusing with living immune cells, called monocytes, forming a sort of cellular cyborg.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;After they’ve been injected, the SWEDs then follow the “natural trafficking” of the immune cells to &lt;a href="https://www.americanbrainfoundation.org/what-is-neuroinflammation/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;sites of inflammation&lt;/a&gt; in the brain, which play a significant role in many neurological diseases.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Once at the target area, the SWEDs embed in the inflamed part of the brain, where they deliver “electrical modulation” — basically tiny electrical shocks — in an effort to deliver signals that otherwise wouldn’t get through.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;In their paper, the researchers claim Circulatronics could be used in the treatment of Alzheimer’s, multiple sclerosis, strokes, brain tumors, spinal injuries, and more. The team says they’ve successfully implanted the experimental SWEDs in a rodent brain, which they could then control wirelessly to provide electrical stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;If it works out in human patients, the researchers hope Circulatronics could expand treatment of brain regions which are typically expensive, difficult, and dangerous to treat with traditional surgery. (&lt;em&gt;New Atlas&lt;/em&gt; reports that Circulatronics will probably take another &lt;a href="https://orbit.mit.edu/launchpad/ideas/cahira-technologies" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;three years&lt;/a&gt; to even enter clinical trials.)&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The cool part, the study’s lead author Deblina Sarkar explains in a video, is that “this technology is not just confined to the brain, but could also be extended to other parts of the body in the future.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on brain chips: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/brain-implant-companies-data"&gt;Brain Implant Companies Apparently Have an Extremely Dirty Secret&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBWdHlnLWdEekpzYU5lMmxoaUJtZWJ2S0RpOWZ4YXgxMWFKTmNlN21JQVhELVdvbG13bzBoanViUWxtVTNLY2JjME95YjJsLW94ZHkxOU9CdjB5N1lra0FtX3h3VVJFZHdzOFg2WnlwOA</guid></item><item><title>新的研究表明，运动比步行更有效，可以对抗心脏病--《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/exercise-more-effective-walking-heart-health-b2863711.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 bxpovR sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Nearly 1.8 billion adults are at risk of disease from not doing enough physical activity,” a 2024 World &lt;a href="/news/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; Organisation statement reads. At the time of writing, this figure was on the rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lack of physical activity puts adults at greater risk of &lt;a href="/topic/cardiovascular-disease"&gt;cardiovascular diseases&lt;/a&gt; such as heart attacks and strokes, type 2 diabetes, dementia and &lt;a href="/topic/cancer"&gt;cancers&lt;/a&gt; such as breast and colon, the organisation writes. But &lt;a rel="nofollow" data-affiliate="true" target="_blank" href="http://redirect.viglink.com?u=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41467-025-63475-2&amp;amp;articleId=b2863711&amp;amp;key=5b1a6400a3c0d931ed2037885e1a27a3"&gt;new research from the University of Sydney&lt;/a&gt; suggests a certain type of &lt;a href="/topic/exercise"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt; could be more powerful in preventing these conditions than previously thought: vigorous-intensity activity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new data found vigorous-intensity activity to be six times more effective at lowering your risk of cardiovascular disease than moderate-intensity activities like brisk walking, lead author Professor Emmanuel Stamatakis tells me. In other words, for every one minute of vigorous-intensity activity you do, you would need to do six minutes of a moderate-intensity activity to have the same impact on heart health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For diabetes, it’s nine times more effective, and for all-cause mortality and cancer it’s a little bit lower,” Professor Stamatakis adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term “vigorous-intensity activity” is relative – depending on factors such as your age and fitness level, it could mean anything from a swim or cycle to a high-intensity interval training (HIIT) workout. The telltale signs are; your heart is beating fast; you are breathing hard to the point you can’t speak in full sentences; you can’t maintain this intensity for more than a few minutes at a time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you can reach this intensity a few times per week, you can reduce your risk of chronic illness, the University of Sydney’s study suggests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-lq6hxg-0 kcbSyT"&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vigorous-intensity physical activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘The signs of vigorous intensity will be very clear. For a non-athlete aged 30 and up who doesn’t do much exercise, they shouldn’t be able to maintain this intensity for more than two to three minutes without a break. It will be a significant effort, you will be getting out of breath and your heart will be pounding. You should be able to talk, but only say a few words at a time.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderate-intensity physical activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘You will feel slightly out of breath – you can talk and hold a discussion, but you can’t sing comfortably because your respiratory system is quite engaged. There is a certain level of exertion, but you can sustain this for many minutes or even hours.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Light physical activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Light physical activity is any very low-intensity activity where you are moving but your heart rate is barely raised, such as a slow walk.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the science says &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The World Health Organisation recommends adults do at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity physical activity like brisk walking, 75 minutes of vigorous-intensity physical activity like faster running or HIIT, or an equivalent of both. These physical activity guidelines have been widely adopted by the likes of the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/live-well/exercise/physical-activity-guidelines-for-adults-aged-19-to-64/"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this new research, published in the Nature journal, challenges the implicit 2:1 benefit ratio of the two intensities, suggesting you might need less vigorous-intensity activity or more moderate-intensity activity than previously thought to achieve the same health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We make a lot of fuss about the intensity of physical activity in our research because, firstly, different intensities have different health effects, and secondly, the higher the intensity, the higher the health value usually is,” says Professor Stamatakis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His latest study used wearable data from 73,485 UK participants to assess the health impacts of light, moderate and vigorous activity against a selection of specific health outcomes; cardiovascular mortality, major adverse cardiovascular events, type 2 diabetes and cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-lq6hxg-0 kcbSyT"&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health outcome&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amount of vigorous-intensity activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Median equivalence in minutes to see the same response from moderate-intensity activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Median equivalence in minutes to see the same response from light activity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Type 2 diabetes incidence&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 minute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;9.4 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;94 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiovascular mortality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 minute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;7.8 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;72.5 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major adverse cardiovascular events&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 minute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;5.4 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;86.1 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;All-cause mortality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 minute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;4.1 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;52.7 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical activity related cancer mortality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 minute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;3.5 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;156.2 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physical activity related cancer incidence&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1 minute&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;1.6 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;p&gt;5.1 minutes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The obvious conclusion here is that a time-efficient exercise routine should hinge on vigorous-intensity activity. If you prefer moderate-intensity activities like brisk walking, you can use these to obtain similar health benefits, but the time commitment required for the same gains will be considerably greater. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, no amount of light activity, like a slow walk, can replicate “some of the core physiological responses from vigorous-intensity activity”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When it comes to light activity, some movement is better than none,” Professor Stamatakis explains. “Moving around instead of sitting down is good for metabolic disease and energy expenditure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“But when it comes to functional capacity, and cardiorespiratory fitness in particular, you need intensity to challenge your physiology. Vigorous-intensity activity will force the heart to strengthen its muscle, improving its capacity to pump blood. Very few of these things happen with light intensity activity, even in large amounts.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/exercise-intensity-heart-health-b2856019.html"&gt;The thing most people get wrong when exercising – and why it’s costing them results&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 lnqVrP"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/03/8/07/iStock-1097320204.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/03/8/07/iStock-1097320204.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/09/03/8/07/iStock-1097320204.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Walking or running uphill, or up stairs, can be a way to increase the intensity of an activity" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-314624"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Walking or running uphill, or up stairs, can be a way to increase the intensity of an activity&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to exercise for maximum health benefits, based on this research &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Compared to people who don’t do any vigorous-intensity activity as part of their day-to-day routines, introducing anything – even four to five minutes per day – seems to have some effect long term,” says Professor Stamatakis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This relates to another paper he co-authored earlier this year. The research found that five to 10 short daily bursts of vigorous intermittent lifestyle physical activity (or VILPA), such as climbing the stairs or carrying heavy shopping, can significantly lower the risk of cardiovascular disease, cancer and premature death in less active populations. These bouts of VILPA can be accrued through 60-second bursts of physically challenging activities during the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key to achieving lifelong benefits is to make these active behaviours into a habit, Professor Stamatakis asserts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’re not talking about doing it once a week or whenever you remember, we’re talking about a daily behaviour,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those currently living a sedentary lifestyle are the most likely to see significant benefits from introducing short bouts of vigorous-intensity activities into each day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If someone does no vigorous-intensity activity, very little moderate-intensity activity – let’s say 15 minutes or less – and a few hours of light activity per day, that’s a very sedentary individual,” Professor Stamatakis says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Typically, they will do under 5,000 or 6,000 steps per day. A very sedentary non-bedridden person – someone who does no planned physical activity, just essential movements like going to the car to drive to work, going to the supermarket for food or going to the bathroom – will accumulate about 4,000 steps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For such an individual, if they aim to incorporate seven short bursts of vigorous activity per day, or if you go by this study the equivalent is 63 minutes of moderate activity, they will lower their risk of health outcomes like cardiovascular diseases.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/negative-health-effects-of-sitting-down-b2842653.html"&gt;From back pain to heart health – Experts reveal how to counter the negative effects of too much sitting down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bAxvyM"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/05/02/17/55/iStock-1912105812.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/05/02/17/55/iStock-1912105812.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/05/02/17/55/iStock-1912105812.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="The most important factor in securing long-term health benefits is finding a type of exercise you can stick with" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-314625"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;The most important factor in securing long-term health benefits is finding a type of exercise you can stick with&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dealer’s choice, and why vigorous-intensity activity is not for everyone&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The aim of this study is not to impose vigorous-intensity activity across all populations. Rather, it aims to provide people with more strings to their bow when creating an effective and sustainable exercise routine for fending off chronic illnesses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are short on time, vigorous-intensity physical activity can help you maximise exercise efficiency, particularly if you use short bursts of challenging lifestyle activities like climbing the stairs and carrying heavy shopping. These acts can also familiarise you with the feeling of a workout, paving the way for more formal exercise later down the line. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, this approach won’t work for everyone. Pushing people into a type of exercise they don’t enjoy can leave a “bad taste in their mouth”, souring their relationship with movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The higher the intensity, the more discomfort comes with it,” says Professor Stamatakis. “We know this discomfort is a reason why some people quit exercise – because they don’t enjoy it. This is especially true in the population we’re interested in, which is physically inactive people.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this is the case, moderate-intensity activity is a good alternative. You will have to devote more time to it – even more than previously thought, this latest study suggests – but it could be a more sustainable and enjoyable approach for certain people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If someone cannot do vigorous activity, or they can’t integrate it into their day-to-day routine for whatever reason, what is the point of prescribing and advocating vigorous intensity?” Professor Stamatakis asks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It could be that a very sedentary 60- or 70-year-old gentleman may enjoy going to the park with their grandchildren or going for a slow walk with a friend and chatting – that’s absolutely fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You have to be considerate and respectful towards people’s preferences; you have to acknowledge their circumstances and, considering everything, support them in the best possible way to integrate activity into their days. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-us-premium-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The point here is to give people as many options as possible, hoping that one of them will be the option they can stick with. It’s all about establishing habits – not doing things once a week or once a month.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/polyphenols-benefits-and-anti-ageing-effects-b2831125.html"&gt;Experts say including more of this in your diet can help you live a longer, healthier life - and it’s not protein or fibre&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 10:32:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQTWtmbDBJX3NYcUFjLUdCbzZjZ0JnRkgxMy1kTHI4b0dPc29wYVYzS3FadEtjX2hwMGJHemJoU0FsNldaRl9RcmNvbTEzVGczYjhFY2R6VWNmaUVBeHRvRU5iaHNZSEJmZ3VkOFhqb2pNalp0Vkdoc0h6aE9GUlJ6Ym5DRmpDZ0w5aGkwa3pfaXlkay0zWTBjTHFnMC02OVg3TGJvenQxbHBmc0E</guid></item><item><title>饮食不健康和久坐不动的生活方式是导致心脏病发作的主要原因-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/5-things-other-that-eating-unhealthy-and-a-sedentary-lifestyle-which-contribute-majorly-to-heart-attacks-in-most-people/articleshow/125362611.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heart attacks continue to be one of the leading causes of death worldwide, despite advances made in medical treatments and technologies. To help prevent such lethal heart conditions, such as stroke, attack or cardiac arrest, cardiologists usually pay much attention to maintaining blood pressure, cholesterol, and other conventional risk factors within normal limits. According to Dr. Dimitry Yaranov, a well-respected heart transplant cardiologist, the key to preventing heart attacks deserves much greater dedication to fundamental life and holistic health principles. Following are the first things he would never do when it comes to preventing heart attacks, with respect to the management of hypertension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt; Never neglect the cornerstone of heart health&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Yaranov insists that the building blocks of heart health include so much more than just numbers of blood pressure and cholesterol. Among the cardinal rules he lives by is never to disregard key components such as quality sleep, stress management, clean air, and gut health. These are closely related to cardiovascular health and blood pressure. Poor sleep, for example, disrupts the normal nocturnal blood pressure dip, increasing the risk for hypertension and heart disease. Emotional and chronic stress causes inflammation and raises blood pressure, silently hurting the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;What Your Cholesterol Report Is Hiding — The Truth That Could Save Your Heart | Dr Vinayak Agarwal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, ignoring these factors for the sake of medication or isolated lab results does more harm than good. A comprehensive approach to sleep hygiene, mental wellbeing, and environmental quality becomes crucial in the prevention of heart attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Avoid extreme or restrictive diets&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While managing hypertension and heart disease, nutrition plays an important role. Dr. Yaranov cautions against extreme diets, such as very high-protein or carnivore diets, which some might assume are heart-healthy merely because they reduce carbohydrate intake. These diets can elevate LDL cholesterol and provoke systemic inflammation, increasing the risk of artery blockage and cardiovascular events, even in young and otherwise fit individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Instead, his approach advocates for balanced diets rich in nutrients, emphasizing fruits, vegetables, whole grains, lean proteins, and healthy fats. Such diets not only help to regulate blood pressure but also reduce oxidative stress and support the gut microbiome, a vital, often overlooked player in cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt; Never push through chronic stress&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; It is understandable when people today try to "push through" heavy schedules and emotional loads. According to Dr. Yaranov, this attitude is not good for heart health. Stress raises blood pressure temporarily, but frequently enough to cause chronic hypertension and inflammation-major risk factors for heart attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Mindfulness, meditation, physical activity, and adequate rest are some of the effective stress management techniques that he should not miss out on in his heart attack prevention strategy. It is also important to say “no” when overwhelmed and set boundaries to reduce emotional overload.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Effect of gut microbiome&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Emerging research is showing that many aspects of cardiovascular health, including blood pressure, are influenced by gut microbiome. Dr. Yaranov would never neglect gut health in planning heart attack prevention strategies. A diet high in fiber, fermented foods, and prebiotics helps maintain an appropriate gut flora balance to help modulate blood pressure and lower systemic inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Conversely, poor gut health could contribute to hypertension and vascular disease by promoting inflammation and metabolic dysfunction. It is thus important that digestive well-being be prioritized in holistic heart care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Avoid unmonitored medication use&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While moderate consumption of alcohol may have some cardiovascular benefits, binge drinking-even occasionally-can result in subtle vascular damage and sharply raise blood pressure, increasing the risk for heart attacks. Dr. Yaranov says to avoid such patterns at all costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Similarly, unmonitored intake of medications or supplements that raise blood pressure can undermine heart health efforts. The communication between patients with hypertension and their health care providers should be open regarding all drugs taken by them, since certain key medications such as NSAIDs, corticosteroids, and some stimulants may raise blood pressure or lead to fluid retention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;h2&gt; Embracing holistic care&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; By the end of it, Dr. Yaranov's guiding principle is to treat the patients and not to get better numbers on a blood pressure machine. To offer a personalised approach that includes balanced nutrition, lifestyle interventions and promoting sleep and emotional health, judicious use of medication and regular follow-up, all of which are essential for vascular health and heart function&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAJBVV95cUxQUEdMcjJqMkIzbUYxd3pyUVNnZWNweWhsY08yZlFwZ3UySER1dVJPLVVpNGZSOUJ4eXFVZUZQblZJRUk0UE1sWnJSMDkxNmx6eEJBUFRyNG5jbl92aVlzYTdRZmh6TnkwMWhFVHBXS0FHZ3ljOEJLQjRIUm9iY01aeVB3Q2IxLWVKRVcwRmxvc1dlWVpsVUdaVlB0OUFaMFJyeHZMc3hBN29vWkZTLWFsQWNCNGEwZzd1QmJ5WnI3N2dSY19iZU1zbDdlTUxub2tsM1AzcnV6dW4xdWw4LTVZQl93T2FBM0kyd0FIRlJEa2tiakEwanZxdUFGRlRyY1dzUU5PNWJyWWVmeVpjZ1pObjRlNmpOSGphZmk2eWg4RE5TZ1hRbERocGh5NjlJckNo</guid></item><item><title>阿波罗德里内分泌学家解释印度食物中隐藏的糖：即使是idli或poha也是一个问题...... |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/apollo-delhi-endocrinologist-explains-hidden-sugars-in-indian-foods-even-idli-poha-are-problem-when-paired-with-ketchup-101763286808328.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/apollo-delhi-endocrinologist-explains-hidden-sugars-in-indian-foods-even-idli-poha-are-problem-when-paired-with-ketchup-101763286808328.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Ever wondered why you're feeling slaky or &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/feeling-tired-all-day-doctor-warns-it-can-be-a-sign-of-iron-deficiency-suggests-ways-to-boost-iron-levels-101762345266782.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="tired all the time"&gt;tired all the time&lt;/a&gt;? It might not be just the late nights or early mornings; it could be the hidden sugars in your favourite Indian foods. &lt;strong&gt;Also read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-shares-5-indian-food-habits-that-could-increase-your-heart-attack-risk-skip-samosas-jalebis-and-pickles-101758712930028.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Cardiologist shares 5 Indian food habits that could increase your heart attack risk"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cardiologist shares 5 Indian food habits that could increase your heart attack risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/16/550x309/idli_poha_1763287270278_1763287296536.png" alt="Even healthy options like idli or poha can become unhealthy when paired with ketchup or packaged chutneys that have added sugar. (Made using Gemini AI)" title="Even healthy options like idli or poha can become unhealthy when paired with ketchup or packaged chutneys that have added sugar. (Made using Gemini AI)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/16/550x309/idli_poha_1763287270278_1763287296536.png" alt="Even healthy options like idli or poha can become unhealthy when paired with ketchup or packaged chutneys that have added sugar. (Made using Gemini AI)" title="Even healthy options like idli or poha can become unhealthy when paired with ketchup or packaged chutneys that have added sugar. (Made using Gemini AI)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Even healthy options like idli or poha can become unhealthy when paired with ketchup or packaged chutneys that have added sugar. (Made using Gemini AI)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In an interview with HT Lifestyle, Dr Saptarshi Bhattacharya, senior consultant, endocrinology, Indraprastha Apollo Hospitals, shared that many common Indian foods are loaded with added sugars that can push your daily intake beyond healthy limits, leading to &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/diabetes-doctor-shares-magical-tip-to-reduce-sugar-spikes-avoid-scary-complications-why-chew-your-food-at-least-40-times-101753418836284.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="sugar spikes"&gt;sugar spikes&lt;/a&gt; and long-term risks like diabetes, weight gain, and fatigue&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;How sugar hides in Indian foods&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;He said, “When we think of sugar, we usually picture sweets like jalebi, gulab jamun, or laddoo. But sugar is not just in dessert — it quietly hides in many of our everyday Indian foods. From breakfast dishes to snacks and drinks, hidden sugars can easily push your daily intake beyond healthy limits, leading to sudden sugar spikes and long-term risks like diabetes, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/shark-tanks-namita-thapar-48-shares-how-she-copes-with-perimenopause-weight-gain-i-work-out-6-days-a-week-101756099137642.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="weight gain"&gt;weight gain&lt;/a&gt;, and fatigue.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to Dr Bhattacharya, many common foods we eat every day contain more sugar than we realise:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Breakfast items: “Popular choices like &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/kokilaben-hospital-gastroenterologist-explains-how-your-morning-milk-tea-could-silently-harm-your-gut-and-liver-101761880109103.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="chai with sugar"&gt;chai with sugar&lt;/a&gt;, flavoured cornflakes, or sweetened yoghurt can cause you to start your day with 3–5 teaspoons of sugar. Even idli or poha become a problem when paired with ketchup or packaged chutneys that contain added sugar,” Dr Bhattacharya said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Snacks: “Packaged namkeens, biscuits, instant noodles, and bakery items like pav or buns often contain refined sugar to enhance flavour and shelf life,” he added.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Indian gravies: “Many restaurant-style curries and sauces — like butter chicken, paneer butter masala, or korma — use tomato ketchup, cream, or sweetened pastes that add hidden sugar,” he shared&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;⦿ Drinks: Soft drinks, bottled fruit juices, milkshakes, energy drinks, and even 'healthy' packaged lassi or flavoured milk can contain 5-8 teaspoons or 20-30 gm of sugar per serving, as per Dr Bhattacharya.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Street food: “Chaats, samosa chole, and pani puri often use sweet chutneys and syrups. Over time, these sugars add up and cause chronic calorie surplus that results in fat deposition and obesity,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/16/original/Gemini_Generated_Image_jynkdvjynkdvjynk_1763286924347.png" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Eating too much hidden sugar can cause your blood sugar to spike, increasing the risk of diabetes, belly fat, heart disease, and inflammation. (Made using Gemini AI)" title="Eating too much hidden sugar can cause your blood sugar to spike, increasing the risk of diabetes, belly fat, heart disease, and inflammation. (Made using Gemini AI)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Eating too much hidden sugar can cause your blood sugar to spike, increasing the risk of diabetes, belly fat, heart disease, and inflammation. (Made using Gemini AI)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What hidden sugars do to your body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consuming high amounts of hidden sugars can lead to a rapid rise in blood glucose levels, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/doctor-reveals-6-signs-you-might-have-insulin-resistance-increased-belly-fat-cravings-for-carbs-sugar-thirst-101754709377512.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="insulin resistance"&gt;insulin resistance &lt;/a&gt;and type 2 diabetes, and belly fat, heart disease, and inflammation. “Hidden sugars cause a rapid rise in blood glucose levels, followed by a sudden drop that leaves you tired and craving more sugar. Over time, this cycle increases the risk of insulin resistance and type 2 diabetes. Even if you’re not diabetic, excess sugar contributes to belly fat, heart disease, and inflammation,” Dr Bhattacharya said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;How to cut down on hidden sugar&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Bhattacharya, you don’t have to give up your favourite foods — just make small, mindful changes. Here is what he suggested:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Read labels carefully: Packaged foods often list sugar under names like sucrose, glucose syrup, maltose, or dextrose. The shorter the ingredient list, the better.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Limit sweetened beverages: Replace bottled drinks with fresh nimbu pani (lemon water), unsweetened coconut water, or &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/delhi-dietician-reveals-why-herbal-tea-is-better-than-chai-during-pollution-season-suggests-which-ones-work-the-best-101763018962797.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="herbal teas"&gt;herbal teas&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Cook at home: When you prepare your own gravies, you can skip the ketchup or cream and use fresh tomato puree, yoghurt, or nuts for texture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;⦿ Balance your meals: Combine carb-heavy dishes like rice, poha, or chapati with fibre and protein—like vegetables, lentils, or paneer — to slow sugar absorption.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;⦿ Watch portion sizes: Even traditional sweets can be enjoyed occasionally—just limit to small portions and eat them after a balanced meal, not on an empty stomach.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Bhattacharya concluded: “The key isn’t to stop enjoying Indian food — it’s to make it smarter. Choose fresh ingredients, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/analysis/signalling-health-in-packaged-food-space-101756738619194.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="reduce packaged and restaurant meals"&gt;reduce packaged and restaurant meals&lt;/a&gt;, and be conscious of how sugar sneaks into your plate. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;When you take control of what goes into your food, you protect your energy levels, your blood sugar, and your long-term health — one mindful bite at a time.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 10:17:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwJBVV95cUxNVkxmYmdyand2WFdwckVpQTNuTTdoQmhCcGlKT2NfcEtPTTZWdm9NQVNweTU0LUZQc1AwNWlURW01V1JtZ29lZDNyRDlyMGlfUGhVUXIxcjNZQUk3U2dHczFrSjVlQTU0bnI3c1ZnZ010ak83bFFuWUpfZ21JLUk3WlotT1gxbjNyaElMZDMxTUlpaENBeGQyNzIyM3lOMDNpVUhGNkxJUldydERRV29CbEZLdXI4cUhzMWM4alVxOE9SU29USGJLalN1a3lyOTRsRThrZ09ZS3hOQXZMZHZCYUpfRnB1V0lDQzZkSkFYaUJKYnVnUkxRMzFwZmZvZDQwaEJCWENsaDNXM2N6eFZic18yQzRRVXPSAZwCQVVfeXFMTVVKNW00d0Vzdm05UENJMVR4ZUdvaEN1OTd5UnVpdWs2M0J0dU5xY3VQNUZrUkt4eDllYnBBNi1LQUNWMVY3Z19vTnNWVWJjNklVaUdNWWdiVHZjYVhYbndacG12cWpPTEpSZWg1bXJONWw4MWw2M2s2LTZOTlBJMUlwdHFTM19hZUdrYW9tSklaNWl1QU1FSDJScXJLYVlhOG1QVThLY2ZtZjV6NExJVWxOQXMxWTNBVlNuWUNmblFrRDhlS2cwaW95bWc3R3hXU3RlbkNvaTN6eEM4YU51dEtQcGtaamFqN1JvZ1FnWEZVZzlXMnZLMnktWjRtdHBXbXB2OG5xdDlYczV4YzZMTlF6YVRTbXVJSWRLM0I</guid></item><item><title>北卡罗来纳州居民在匹兹堡停留，为肺癌患者辩护- TribLIVE.com</title><link>https://triblive.com/news/health-now/north-carolina-resident-stops-in-pittsburgh-advocating-for-lung-cancer-patients/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="container"&gt;
	
		

				
		
		&lt;a class="logo triblive-logo-link" href="/"&gt;
    		&lt;img src="https://triblive.com/wp-content/themes/TribLIVE2/assets/visuals/images/icons/head/TribLIVElogo.png" alt="TribLive" class="triblive-logo"&gt;
		&lt;/a&gt;
	
		&lt;h1&gt;&lt;i class="fa-solid fa-shield-halved"&gt;&lt;/i&gt; NOTICE OF YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS  IN Virginia &lt;/h1&gt;

		
	
		
	
	
		&lt;p&gt;Because you are coming from a location (Virginia) covered by a Privacy Law, many of the features of TribLIVE.com, like videos and social media elements are disabled.  If you wish to proceed to the site under those conditions (doing so will effectively opt you out of the sale of your personal data) &lt;a href="#" id="setCookieLinkOut" class="setCookieLinkOut"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;. However you will not experience the full features of TribLIVE.com that rely upon third party networks that may require your personal data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="privacy-boxes"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="#" id="setCookieLinkIn" class="setCookieLinkIn"&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to agree to experience the full features of TribLIVE.com and to opt in to the use of your personal data to provide that experience and advertising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			
			
		&lt;p&gt;Bookmark this page to manage your preferences any time in the future. &lt;/p&gt;
	
	&lt;div class="privacy-boxes"&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;If YOU ARE NOT visiting us as a resident of Virginia?  Please update your location to ensure you are presented with the best experience. &lt;/p&gt;
	


		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
		
		
		
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TribLIVE.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxOZExBc3RBYlRRQThoeF9PNkdKVzZCVHkwM1M3RncxeThhajlqWDhwOHZWa0prbEFWVnhrWDBjeUtCOWUtbngwTTdrRHdhdjBnaDcyYnRDNGVldE9PZFN6dUFFMFk1Y2VrU0dkaWpXc2xoSUtTSkhjQzRIOFVUN2RWaHlYel9RcnppXzJlYmtsaHZ3N05CUzhqMnF1MTZsSHFWRzBISkgta0l3aXkyZnRiOHRNdEhESGNO</guid></item><item><title>女性性欲药丸与文化时刻相遇-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/16/style/cindy-eckert-pink-pill-addyi.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 10:00:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5SWHZHakxvc2RfRXVoeVVkaUJJYmw1ay1zLU9KbnBLMEFyQXk0ejhWVTlCSnV1RkVJWVBjWGttV1RNN3UyeXBHQWF1MW9UQm9TT1hnaW9qWW5ubnhsY1UwWHNJSWd3Yi12azJVSUNfdm5WV21IVGxNSXZWNjk3czQ</guid></item><item><title>闻到这种香味可以立即提高注意力，增强大脑的能量，不，这不是咖啡-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/home-remedies/smelling-this-fragrance-can-instantly-improve-focus-and-supercharge-the-brain-and-no-its-not-coffee/photostory/125350607.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peppermint is incredibly easy to add to the daily routine, and even small doses can make a noticeable difference in mental clarity. Use a diffuser with just a few drops of peppermint essential oil to create an energizing environment. Avoid placing the diffuser too close to the face. A warm cup can support alertness and attention. Consume in limited amounts. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: While it’s generally safe, it’s still important to use it mindfully, especially for people with sensitive skin, acid reflux, or allergies. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:13:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwJBVV95cUxNMGFabTBnQklRZnZWYTFfdHBQNU5wQ0JiU2ZGejR2dTZjZFZ6eWNMNVNQQkZ6d0tBNWRPUndYOVhkUUZ5ZHdST1dqM1NUb3I5TVJpd0FqZmxvYlpVWnpMZjhCdVpfMHpfSkxEQlBmVjNpalA1XzFsVnRmOXhvQk1IUFNJUjBVejR2cE5mSTlvOWsxcC1fOEtDZFZzUWMyOERaRVRGWHMxN2hVeWg5M2ZGQXNhYzU0YV9tLTRkVHFOTHVCUkNQZ3hOUTJGbUs0cG1NcW1lQXVzSkVkQ3lJQXJjREFIN2gwV2JQLWd1OWdVakhrUVAwbjNjU2JxNE54R1VLTUoxMUlmeG1EVjA5bDhTaTFtM2N0ZllHRWl1SXhCbDFENHJzMlQ00gGvAkFVX3lxTE9LZ1ZTRk5xajVEZktIQUV6YXNNM01jd19pYTNRN1JOSE56bENSMUtYbjkzTHJxZFFBNHpsY2ZiQTlKbmYtNGF3QlZBSFhoNVB5LURkWFFHdmVKWkc1ZllNbkZtc3Y5dEZYdjZOV2l1QjR5akM5SlY0X2d6WEh1emhMRURxRTZiSTNtVDA4U1dJNjJtVVpwdmt2djJJN0ZvLUVLSnNSQnVsaDJwbFd3aFFsY0xaU0w4WkNUVGxpVzc0d0FjVUZiUHlQS3lqS3RFUm5mUFN2alVXODc5QUhxaV91alA5OWs0LVptMTF1bVI1eW9QUXR6VTgyUWRqd0JTS19nbnpHQXlOVWR5ZGN0d1pRYktBbXB5bV9WdEFLeXh5Q3pscGs2TXc0RFBnT1FIRQ</guid></item><item><title>维生素D ：对健康和长寿的3个潜在益处-今日医学新闻</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/3-ways-vitamin-d-may-boost-longevity-according-to-research-edited</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-7j3c6j"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/pills-blister-pack-table-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/pills-blister-pack-table-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/pills-blister-pack-table-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="eager" src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/pills-blister-pack-table-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="blister pack of vitamin D supplements on blue table" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2F3-ways-vitamin-d-may-boost-longevity-according-to-research-edited&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F11%2Fpills-blister-pack-table-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Vitamin%20D%3A%203%20potential%20benefits%20for%20health%2C%20longevity" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/pills-blister-pack-table-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-y9j4no css-whkgel"&gt;Can vitamin D boost longevity? Here’s what the latest research says. Image credit: Catherine Falls Commercial/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recent research has investigated the potential health benefits of vitamin D, and the role it may play in protecting against certain health conditions. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One study found that vitamin D may have anticancer effects, which could help reduce colorectal cancer risk.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Another piece of research suggests that vitamin D may contribute to longevity and slow aging.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A third recent study also indicates that vitamin D might drastically reduce the risk of experiencing a second heart attack.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/318060" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;vitamin D deficiency&lt;/a&gt; is one of the most common nutritional deficiencies worldwide, with nearly &lt;hl-trusted-source source="PubMed Central" rationale="Highly respected database from the National Institutes of Health"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6075634/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;42%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; of adults in the United States having this deficiency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recommended daily amount for most people is around 15 micrograms (mcg), or 2,000 international units (IU). However, it is important to note that &lt;hl-trusted-source source="PubMed Central" rationale="Highly respected database from the National Institutes of Health"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK557876/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;too much vitamin D&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; can also be harmful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt; looks at three recent studies to examine the possible role vitamin D may have in supporting health and boosting longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent literature review of 50 studies and more than 1 million participants suggest that vitamin D may help decrease the risk of &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/155598" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt; and also improve survival for the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Published in &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/17/8/1351" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nutrients&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in April 2025, the review found that higher serum vitamin D levels were associated with &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/vitamin-d-may-decrease-risk-colorectal-cancer-benefits-improve-survival" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;a reduced risk of colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt;. Additionally, among those with colorectal cancer, higher vitamin D levels were linked to improved survival and reduced mortality.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors of the review suggested that vitamin D helps the immune system and may assist with decreasing inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin D may also possess specific anticancer properties, such as supporting programmed cell death and stopping uncontrolled cell growth. The authors added that vitamin D may be a useful adjunctive option alongside other cancer treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, despite these promosing associations, the researchers noted that more research is still necessary, particularly large-scale, randomized clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;While some research noted that both dietary vitamin D and vitamin D supplements have beneficial effects on colorectal cancer, other studies did not find a significant relationship between vitamin D and colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some studies highlighted that results may differ due to factors such as &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/323586" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;body mass index (BMI)&lt;/a&gt;, sex, and nutritional status. It may be helpful for further research to explore components like how people’s genetics, lifestyle choices, and use of other treatments play a role in vitamin D’s effects on cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/wael-harb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Wael Harb&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a board-certified hematologist and medical oncologist at MemorialCare Cancer Institute at Orange Coast and Saddleback Medical Centers in Orange County, CA, who was not involved in the study, commented to &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For patients with [colorectal cancer], ensuring adequate vitamin D levels may help support immune surveillance and potentially improve outcomes when used alongside standard therapies. Importantly, this review highlights the need for personalized approaches, as individual vitamin D requirements can vary based on genetics, baseline levels, and comorbidities.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hl-trusted-source source="National Human Genome Research Institute" rationale="Governmental authority"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.genome.gov/genetics-glossary/Telomere" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Telomeres&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; describe repetitive DNA sequences that protect the ends of chromosomes, preventing them from damage. Telomere length shortens with age, and telomere shortening is &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8533433/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;associated&lt;/a&gt; with &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/common-elderly-health-issues" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;age-related diseases&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants were randomized, with half receiving 2,000 IU, or 50 mcg, of vitamin D daily, and the remaining receiving a placebo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The findings indicated that in those receiving vitamin D3, telomere shortening in &lt;hl-trusted-source source="National Cancer Institute " rationale="Governmental authority"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/leukocyte" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;leukocytes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;, a type of white blood cells, over the study period was significantly less compared with the placebo. The authors estimated this effect to be equivalent to about a 3-year reduction in &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/chronological-aging" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;biological aging&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further analysis suggested that the effect of vitamin D was more evident in participants who did not have &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/323551" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;obesity&lt;/a&gt;, those not taking &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/cholesterol-medications" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;cholesterol-lowering medications&lt;/a&gt;, and in participants of different ethnicities. Omega-3 fatty acids supplementation appeared to have no significant impact on telomere length.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.medicalofficesofmanhattan.com/our-team/dr-yoshua-quinones/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Yoshua Quinones&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a board-certified internist with Medical Offices of Manhattan and contributor to LabFinder, who was not involved in the study, explained that&lt;em&gt;:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As we know already, vitamin D supports bone, immune system and reduces inflammation, but this study is linked directly with telomere preservation which ties into aging and disease prevention. This [study] gives more of a general idea that vitamin D3 could do more than just helping your bones but actually slowing down the cellular age, impressive!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the researchers acknowledge that the analysis was a post-hoc examination of the VITAL trial, which was not originally designed to look at the effects of supplements on leukocyte telomere length.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, most participants were white and older adults, so it may not be possible to generalize the findings to other groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The TARGET-D trial involved 630 participants, most of which were males with an average age of 63, who enrolled within a month of having a &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/signs-of-a-heart-attack" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;heart attack&lt;/a&gt;. The researchers randomly selected the control group and who would receive targeted vitamin D3 treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;At enrollment, 87% of participants had low vitamin D levels and the average vitamin D level was 27 nanograms/milliliter (ng/ml).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers tailored vitamin D3 supplementation by measuring blood vitamin D levels and adjusting the dose so that individuals reached a target serum level of approximately 40 ng/ml.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers monitored &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/normal-vitamin-d-levels" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;vitamin D3 levels&lt;/a&gt; throughout the trial and would adjust doses to maintain the target level. They also kept track of major &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/cardiovascular-system" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;cardiovascular&lt;/a&gt; events throughout the trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although there was no significant difference between groups in overall cardiac events, the rate of follow-up heart attacks was 3.8% in the vitamin D3 treatment group compared to 7.9% in the control group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overall, while the results suggest that targeted vitamin D3 supplementation may not reduce all major cardiac outcomes, it did cut the risk of repeat heart attacks by more than half.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/cheng-han-chen" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Cheng-Han Chen&lt;/a&gt;, MD, a board-certified interventional cardiologist and medical director of the Structural Heart Program at MemorialCare Saddleback Medical Center, who was not involved in this study, explained that while past research has linked higher blood levels of vitamin D with lower heart disease rates, “it mostly appears that the relationship between vitamin D3 and heart health is that of correlation rather than that of causation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;He noted that vitamin D3 may still offer some cardiovascular benefits, such as “decreasing inflammation and lowering blood pressure.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, he cautioned that the evidence remains mixed. He added that if larger studies confirm the recent finding that targeted vitamin D3 treatment could reduce the risk of recurrent heart attacks, “it would be quite significant.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 06:55:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQb2NseG9iU193alpqMi1ETld6eXpzYngteGVqNmJMNTJwb1hwOXlVQVZzRU54ZEN2ZDJjWW4zWFA1SGtUSEZ0WkFRSjVIOWZtSVhJYXI3VGRvcW9KTUt2U1RNcDFmdzdhelFhcVRpYkZTME9tRWp2SjRFTjdLUzFqalpfYWt6dGhqQkJnMXhGQkZaTEl3bFhZRllZd0owaEEzNVdhZDJWREJQRU0</guid></item><item><title>缓解气体和腹胀的自然方法：在11天内重置肠道的7个技巧-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/natural-ways-to-relieve-gas-and-bloating-7-tips-to-reset-your-gut-in-11-days/photostory/125321598.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gas and bloating have become common digestive issues, leaving the abdomen feeling heavy, swollen, and at times, painful. This discomfort can significantly drain our energy, affect our mood and digestion as well, making everyday life choices crucial. Finding gentle and natural ways to support gut health is important now more than ever.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;To make us more aware of the dos and don'ts of diet, when it comes to bloating and gas, a trusted medical expert, Dr. Sudhanshu Rai, shares tips combined with years of medical and traditional remedies.  Below are seven practical tips to naturally reset the gut over the course of 11 days.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 04:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9gFBVV95cUxQNERERWltSTdETlA3UE1aQk5RYnVHWmR6VHJYNW1aYmhfUlh0YlRWeHZ4elF6NU8yUHh6RG5zTnlOQXp0ZWhqVHM1RHVpZzIzaUNZZFB6c0dmZ3Q4X0xRbGFFblRfdDNHd1RETjl2SUdEMnZDdTA5OEN5bW5CY0JOdjNGWTBWWFl5Z0lLX2RnTFVPWVh6cDJFaVRiTHQzQnlmR1J2YVd3V3VWSzVUVzJlVGZ6M2k2dU1kOWFZaWV5Ti1zVkJLak9fNmR5eHZ5OWRWQ2ROQkNiejRyTXB3cGxEUjhvMHF0TGp3eXR3Umx4VFZPM0VfVkHSAf4BQVVfeXFMTi0tdU9MSlJzUkRSQWxheEhqR2VMNG1TeS05QUV3c3RxbXBXVzZKRGtOaE1kbl9JUWx3OVcyRVBEWVJMcUE2aTNXaFJBUmhNdGV3aW15RndFN0hVS3NpWjNzbFJIVUVyQ0Z6VVp4Y0ZOYk5nQmlrLVZkRWxiRWUwVHB2dFFRdU43Y3RDcXYyeFRuY1Rsd0J0SGRJLV92UWhmSjdmSVNLeGszYlpERjhfM3RjZ25PN1k3Q1YtOFJWY2NEUTFSck9HQXNIRm9YZXR2dzBDaS1JZmpXbzRHOG1DN3VFYW1LeHFHRkJzcGpOZHMwTTNXY2x1SE9WS2ZXWHc</guid></item><item><title>在果冻卷麻疹集群中发现的新病例-布里斯班时报</title><link>https://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/national/queensland/new-case-identified-in-jelly-roll-measles-cluster-20251116-p5nfs6.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="Hy4HP z5wPE" data-testid="body-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A fourth person has been added to a measles cluster emerging from an October concert at the Brisbane Entertainment Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday evening three people who attended American rapper Jelly Roll’s October 24 concert at the Boondall venue tested positive for measles, more than a week since being exposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Queensland Health added a fourth confirmed case on Sunday morning, who had been unknowingly infectious for about a week across locations in suburbs in and around Logan, including Mustang Brothers Football Club, in Chambers Flat, and Logan Hospital’s emergency department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="_72JXS _0SAJQ mSNnk Wnq-J" data-testid="image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="qTXWa"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="_5nQzY"&gt;Logan Hospital (pictured) has been added to the list of potential measles exposure sites following a concert in late October.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;cite class="Zo2UY"&gt;&lt;span class="ALMCC"&gt;Credit: &lt;/span&gt;Dan Peled&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Queensland Health &lt;a href="https://www.brisbanetimes.com.au/national/queensland/brisbane-news-live-two-girls-reported-missing-in-past-few-days-20251112-p5nesm.html?post=p59ip4#p59ip4"&gt;released an initial public health alert on Wednesday night&lt;/a&gt; warning people who attended the October concert to watch for symptoms for up to three weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="Hy4HP z5wPE" data-testid="body-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms include fever, lethargy, runny nose, moist cough and red eyes. After a few days, a red rash will develop, often starting on the face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone who thinks they have measles should organise to get tested but avoid public places.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two other cases unrelated to the show were confirmed in the Central Queensland West Moreton regions across the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, Queensland Chief Health Officer Dr Catherine McDougall said measles cases were on the rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Currently, we’re seeing higher numbers of measles cases not only in Queensland, but across the country. In Queensland, a total of 30 measles cases have been reported this year to date,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Brisbane Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 03:39:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxQVTh0VDVhV0xmT2h5WVd6NWtNSHdoSkN2QjZaU3lLWFFYWnhoNVJzNHhDZC1ZS2hDcFM4azVpQkFnNDFXNkNtQnUtTTFWbkpBNDlqdFRxWDZ6MEw2RGNrREdOd0tSeno0TlM5dGtYUlVybFVwYVRwS25pTk5KRlYyRk9VNWdjd3pRbWJUNnBCZEUtMTNZckM5QVpudzU3V2c4eURPSGNFWXVzOEc1X2g4WEJ2akhMLVJPUkhHSjZ3aXA</guid></item><item><title>我14岁的时候肚子就被钉住了。那次手术没有“治愈”我—远非如此。- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/georgianndavis/weight-loss-surgery-glp1s-fatphobia-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--long__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-1
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139652321" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;285 pounds. Forty-three years old. Summer 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Have you thought about GLPs?” my primary care physician asked as she listened to my heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I laughed nervously. “No, but I am now.” Humor has always been my shield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She didn’t flinch. “Your BMI is over 40. You’re at risk for all sorts of health conditions. Why don’t you look into our weight-loss program?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My labs were fine. But that didn’t matter. My body size alone was enough to warrant a prescription. I left feeling ashamed, reminded once again that medicine sees fatness as a disease in itself — regardless of actual health indicators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This wasn’t the first time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1995, I was 14 years old and weighed 367 pounds when an endocrinologist bluntly told my mother that I would “likely be bedridden by 20.” He described my legs as “enormous” and referred me to bariatric surgery. Soon after, I underwent a stomach stapling procedure that left an eight-inch scar down my chest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time, pediatric weight loss surgery was &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/10733812/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7974834" data-affiliate="true"&gt;quite rare&lt;/a&gt;. But to my doctors, my fat body made it acceptable — even necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The procedure turned eating into a cycle of pain and vomiting. Food lodged in the tiny passage created by the staples left me doubled over until I threw it back up. I became, in effect, a medically induced bulimic — praised, nonetheless, for my weight-loss “success.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within a year, I had lost nearly 100 pounds. Friends, family and even acquaintances congratulated me. No one saw the violence done to my body or the damage it did to my relationship with food. They didn’t know the surgery left me dependent on &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/rossyoder/best-ice-cream-brands"&gt;ice cream&lt;/a&gt;, crackers and mashed potatoes because I could easily chew that stuff down to a pureed consistency to avoid the pain that followed whenever food got stuck in my staples. After the surgery, and even still today, I can’t tolerate most fruit — too acidic — nor many vegetables — too fibrous. Stomach stapling didn’t make me “healthier;” it only made me thinner.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That surgery didn’t even “cure” me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than two decades later, in 2017, weighing nearly 390 pounds, I went under the knife again, this time for a sleeve gastrectomy. By then, I had surrendered to the &lt;a href="https://finance.yahoo.com/news/united-states-weight-loss-market-084700368.html" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7974834" data-affiliate="true"&gt;diet industrial complex, a multibillion-dollar ecosystem&lt;/a&gt; built around the idea that fat bodies are inherently flawed. The pressure was relentless — to fix, shrink and manage a body that medicine had always treated as a problem to solve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And the scrutiny wasn’t limited to exam rooms. In restaurants, on airplanes, at conferences, strangers felt entitled to comment on my body. I’ve been mocked for eating a donut, told loudly in a food court that I was “killing myself,” and subjected to humiliating requests to be reseated on flights. I’ve even overheard cruel remarks in a language people assumed I didn’t understand. Those moments left wounds far deeper than any heat rash or bruise from too-small chairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Society’s obsession with fatness extends well beyond personal interactions. Fat people are &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9125650/" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7974834" data-affiliate="true"&gt;consistently portrayed in the media&lt;/a&gt; as lazy, undisciplined or morally flawed. &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1038/oby.2001.108" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7974834" data-affiliate="true"&gt;Research has documented&lt;/a&gt; how these stereotypes influence health care practices and workplace discrimination. This cultural narrative seeps into medicine, where clinicians — even those with good intentions — can unconsciously perpetuate stigma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, at 44, I’m on Wegovy. Reluctantly. When I started, I told my doctor my goal weight was 250 pounds — a number that, at 5’10”, felt right to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now I weigh 235, down 50 pounds in eight months. My doctor tells me to stay on it. And I’m not sure why I’m listening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Initially approved to treat Type 2 diabetes, GLP-1 medications like Wegovy are now viewed as a &lt;a href="https://www.news-medical.net/health/Wegovy-A-Breakthrough-in-Weight-Loss.aspx" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7974834" data-affiliate="true"&gt;breakthrough&lt;/a&gt; for weight loss, but for me, they feel like another chapter in the same story: doctors offering interventions driven less by my actual health and more by the fear and stigma that surround fatness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why do I take it? Because sometimes it feels easier to live with the physical and emotional side effects of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/B9780080970868640205" target="_blank" data-skimlinks-tracking="7974834" data-affiliate="true"&gt;medicalization&lt;/a&gt; than with the relentless judgment of others — and, most troubling of all for me, with my own internalized fatphobia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s the truth: Fat patients aren’t blank slates waiting for salvation. We know the statistics, the risks, the medical language. What we also know — often more than our doctors — is the crushing weight of fatphobia disguised as medical concern.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 03:31:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOSkZac0ppQXRNNHI0X2p1NHFTY0VzWFlFVkwtSTNNcG01Q0lUZnR3X3AteV8ybUVFMEJ0OTdBQW16MEtqMlVxQVpmUldJTEhrcThDenMtbU5WMDBDT25UWW0wZUlIaE5RdjBUWHVwRDFMMjFCT0d5SUNiRjlvTFJqc09TNWQ0S3lCWWc</guid></item><item><title>研究人员对潜伏在餐桌上的隐患发出警告： “自我毁灭” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/researchers-issue-warning-hidden-hazard-031500079.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Those handy plastic plates, cups, and takeout containers that make mealtime cleanup so easy may be doing more harm than we realize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A new study published in the &lt;a href="https://jnanobiotechnology.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12951-025-03747-7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Journal of Nanobiotechnology;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Journal of Nanobiotechnology&lt;/a&gt; has revealed that tiny plastic fragments, known as microplastics, are showing up where we least expect them: in human semen, reported &lt;a href="https://www.news-medical.net/news/20251015/What-happens-when-microplastics-reach-the-testes-Study-shows-autophagy-and-cell-loss.aspx" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:News Medical &amp;amp; Life Sciences;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;News Medical &amp;amp; Life Sciences&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The discovery has scientists raising concerns about what our daily exposure to these invisible particles might mean for men's health and fertility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Researchers in China analyzed semen samples from 200 men and found microplastics in more than half of them. The main culprits were plastics commonly used in everyday tableware, like polystyrene and PVC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Men who used disposable plastic dishes more often had higher levels of these microscopic particles in their samples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;To better understand the impact, scientists also studied mice exposed to very small plastic particles, the same type found in people. The results were worrying: The mice showed reduced sperm count and movement, and their testicular tissue displayed signs of stress and cell damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;These effects were linked to a specific biological chain reaction that triggered cell "self-destruction" and tissue loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is this concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While the study doesn't mean everyone who eats from plastic plates is in immediate danger, it adds to growing evidence that plastic pollution isn't just an environmental issue; it's a human one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If tiny plastic fragments can make their way into the body and potentially disrupt reproduction, that raises real concerns for communities already facing fertility challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This finding highlights how everyday choices, like reaching for a plastic fork or microwave-safe container, can have unseen health impacts over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What can we do about it?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The good news is that reducing exposure is possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Choosing glass, metal, or ceramic tableware instead of single-use plastic is a &lt;a href="http://guide.thecooldown.com/journeys/use-less-plastic/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:simple start;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;simple start&lt;/a&gt;. Supporting policies that limit microplastic release from packaging and promoting safer materials for food storage can also make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As more research sheds light on how plastics affect the human body, small shifts in how we eat and store food could help pave the way toward a cleaner, healthier future for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/tech-newsletter/?recBqGTV3M4QX85E2" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for weekly updates on the latest innovations &lt;strong&gt;improving our lives&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;shaping our future&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 03:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxPVG5mMjJQZTZtQWdGVGtnSkVHbGlSenhEZVRwWmJ5c2tYWU9ma2Z4M0VXU1V2NXcxM0g1ZFdJaE1EX2xqMVotcVphYmNLdGZNd3RsbkJYa2RwZUtMcGoxMlQxM1FpbXlVbUdYdjlxMXB6VXRtR0pmZFlaUUREYXVpT0haUS1pT2hwMXZZdnZ4Y2RRX2xG</guid></item><item><title>拥有30年经验的纽约心脏病专家分享“10个可以延长10年寿命的简单技巧” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/new-york-cardiologist-with-30-years-of-experience-shares-10-simple-tips-that-can-add-10-years-to-your-life-101763259612120.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/new-york-cardiologist-with-30-years-of-experience-shares-10-simple-tips-that-can-add-10-years-to-your-life-101763259612120.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Want to add a decade to your life? There are certain things you can do daily that can help you ditch the bad habits and kickstart a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/how-to-live-a-long-and-healthier-life-here-are-seven-things-highlighted-by-americans-aged-65-and-older-101762670380082.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="healthier, longer life"&gt;healthier, longer life&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Evan Levine, a cardiologist from Mount Sinai Hospital in New York City, with over 30 years of experience, shared his top 10 recommendations in an Instagram post on November 11 to help people extend their lifespan, starting at age 30.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Also read |&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/the-secret-to-healthy-life-is-hiding-in-our-kitchens-expert-shares-5-superfoods-for-daily-diet-101750682028915.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="The secret to healthy life is hiding in our kitchens: Expert shares 5 superfoods for daily diet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; The secret to healthy life is hiding in our kitchens: Expert shares 5 superfoods for daily diet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/16/550x309/shutterstock_2492441657_1744720954366_1763260011063.jpg" alt="Monitoring your blood pressure and cholesterol levels is crucial for a long and healthy life.(Shutterstock)" title="Monitoring your blood pressure and cholesterol levels is crucial for a long and healthy life.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/16/550x309/shutterstock_2492441657_1744720954366_1763260011063.jpg" alt="Monitoring your blood pressure and cholesterol levels is crucial for a long and healthy life.(Shutterstock)" title="Monitoring your blood pressure and cholesterol levels is crucial for a long and healthy life.(Shutterstock)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Monitoring your blood pressure and cholesterol levels is crucial for a long and healthy life.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;These tips focused on drastically eliminating or reducing harmful substances such as &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/can-smoking-alcohol-and-caffeine-sabotage-fertility-in-men-and-women-doctor-spills-the-beans-101742985541547.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="smoking, alcohol,"&gt;smoking, alcohol,&lt;/a&gt; fast food, sodas, and various stimulants, including marijuana, and even limiting ADHD (attention deficit hyperactivity disorder) medications.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Never smoke, limit booze, ditch fast food&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the video he posted, Dr Levine said: “Starting at the age of 30, 10 simple tips that can add 10 years to your life. Let's begin. I'm Dr Evan, board certified cardiologist. Number one, I would never smoke or be around anyone who smokes. Dozens of known carcinogens, plus increasing your risk of stroke, heart attacks, vascular disease, even aortic aneurysms, and high blood pressure.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Sharing a list of things to avoid, he added, “Number two, no alcohol, or at least stick to less than a few drinks a week. They're cancer-causing. They raise blood pressure. The alcohol industry and its surrogates lie to us. Number three, fast food. Don't open the door. Never walk inside. Toxic, dense calories that poisoned millions. Number four, all drugs and stimulants. I'm including marijuana here. And I'd also include limiting those ADHD meds to the lowest possible doses.”&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/16/original/AI_1763260454561.png" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Make these small changes that can add up to a healthier, happier you. (Made using ChatGPT)" title="Make these small changes that can add up to a healthier, happier you. (Made using ChatGPT)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Make these small changes that can add up to a healthier, happier you. (Made using ChatGPT)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Do any exercise, check your blood pressure&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Levine also advised engaging in regular exercise, aiming for at least 7,000 steps daily, and monitoring key health metrics, such as blood pressure and cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He went on to share what you should ideally be doing for a long life, and said, “Number five, do any exercise. That includes even walking. &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/is-walking-a-good-idea-what-walking-for-30-minutes-every-day-can-do-to-your-health-101728132003995.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Walking is great."&gt;Walking is great.&lt;/a&gt; At least 7,000 steps a day. Pretty easy stuff. Number six, check your blood pressure with a goal of 120 over 80 or less. Number seven, check your cholesterol and treat if that LDL is above 190 with a statin. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Otherwise, with diet and exercise, those coronary artery calcium scans in young patients with heart attacks are often normal, and these tests have limited benefit in this age group.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Ditch stress and toxic people&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cardiologist also highlighted the importance of stress reduction by avoiding toxic individuals and establishing consistent, healthy sleep habits, which lay a foundation for longevity.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He concluded: “Number eight, no sodas or toxic sugar drinks... number nine,&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-explains-if-exercise-can-help-remove-or-prevent-heart-blockage-reduce-stress-lower-blood-pressure-high-bp-101754387406907.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="reduce stress"&gt; reduce stress &lt;/a&gt;and people that cause stress. Build your foundation of friends. Avoid those narcissists, no matter how attractive they may be. And number 10, start a healthy sleeping habit. I hope that helps.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 02:36:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxNZjVJZVROcHFhRUhnVi0xNzQ0RnBSYmVpaHFhN3ZOa19UNXUwQjZtOUNqR0VobnZDY1Y0WDk2NGJONTBvRGJrVGVCeWE3Y2ZKTTlPVTVhQjFycmhGeFlYWG1PTmZJQ1dBbmNENWd2NzBRRkVzSmhFZzZuaTlxTHFTeEtXY3YzcjJUbXRlMW1ab004YVRSTUpzbWJwREYtb1J0T096WGRRYzlOWlExdkdNdEJsaDhWUF90d3dENzlOQUlQblo5NjlaUnNDdlYta2wxNmQ2bHlwWnZqdXk3VHVtbmxOdGpzUmVXQkZCTVhpSjd0eHRQWHdxLWV4VkUzcFVHVldNWmxn0gGLAkFVX3lxTE84dFRxTFIwNkdZY0RndFlkTlZoVms4ZW5aRk5KQUEzbC1BeUdMWl9xQmNVVTRQckJMWVc3T0VjSjJBWWRKOFViQjNfQjN5Um40RE5sNmNSU2N0cHR2c1U5UzQ1M2NFaVd2YXJhMTBYNzFJOFZObVIyaTZlNkJlQklHYjBmaUZGWVFaMVl2a2haTkVaRkl3akRjbE1GazdEdzlzTDlrN05EcEJmcENVY3pYOUxJOHJlZzl6cDNmMHJTMFUzY2ZOZ1BEZGVzUlllSkZ0X1k1bEpYeVFkUzN1MzZHMmV5S05NT2ltWklTeTFyN1ZJcHBaLWhsV2VsMjRsYnVpZ2Jsemc4TURnUQ</guid></item><item><title>4种影响新陈代谢的狡猾事情，每位营养师- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/sneaky-factors-that-affect-metabolism-11850326</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Metabolism does more than affect weight—it's tied to energy, stress, sleep and gut health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stress, sleep, gut health and insulin sensitivity all influence how your body burns energy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protein, strength training and regular meals help support a healthy, efficient metabolism.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When you're feeling sluggish or struggling to maintain your weight, it’s tempting to blame a “slow” metabolism. But metabolism isn’t a simple on-off switch you can flip with a new workout or diet trend. While what you eat and how much you move are important, your metabolism is far more nuanced. It’s actually a complex system—the sum of all the chemical reactions in your body that convert food into energy to power everything from your heartbeat to your thoughts to your daily movement.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While genetics, age and diet do influence how efficiently your metabolism works, many everyday habits also play a role.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; According to dietitians, these often-overlooked factors can &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7937672/how-to-calculate-your-metabolism/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;impact how your body burns energy&lt;/a&gt;. The good news? Small, sustainable shifts may help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-1-dinner-to-eat-for-healthy-metabolism-11792643" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;support a healthy metabolism&lt;/a&gt; over time.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-your-stress-levels"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 1. Your Stress Levels &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Stress isn’t just a mood disruptor—it can also have a big impact on your metabolism. When stress becomes chronic, your body produces &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-to-know-high-cortisol-levels-11762693" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;elevated levels of the hormone cortisol&lt;/a&gt;. In short bursts, cortisol helps your body respond to immediate challenges ("fight or flight" situations). But over time, it can contribute to imbalances that affect how your body uses and stores energy.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “When cortisol stays high, your body holds onto energy instead of burning it,” explains &lt;a href="https://eatswimwin.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Katie Schimmelpfenning, RD&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Cortisol also &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/blood-sugar-effects-from-stress-11830291" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;influences your blood sugar&lt;/a&gt; by increasing glucose production in the liver and reducing insulin secretion.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This makes your body more likely to store fat and less efficient at using energy. Activities like &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8011794/breath-training-lower-blood-pressure/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;deep breathing&lt;/a&gt;, meditation, spending time in nature or regular movement can help calm the nervous system and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-habit-to-break-for-better-metabolic-health-8751700" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;support metabolic health&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-your-sleep-quality"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 2. Your Sleep Quality &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A good night's sleep is not a luxury; it's a biological necessity for a well-functioning metabolism. It plays a vital role in metabolic health. Poor or inconsistent sleep can &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7867303/sleep-might-be-the-reason-you-re-not-losing-weight/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;disrupt hunger and fullness hormones&lt;/a&gt; (ghrelin and leptin), making it harder to manage appetite and energy use.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Your body's circadian rhythm depends on adequate sleep," shares &lt;a href="https://www.soundbitesnutrition.com/about-lisa" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lisa Andrews, M.Ed., RD, LD&lt;/a&gt;. "Lack of sleep may slow down your metabolism and release hormones like cortisol, which impact blood sugar management and weight."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Aim for 7 to 9 hours of high-quality sleep each night to help your metabolism stay healthy.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-your-gut-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 3. Your Gut Health &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The trillions of microorganisms living in your digestive tract, known as the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-your-gut-health-impacts-your-body-8695122" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt;, play a critical role in your overall health, including your metabolism. These microbes help your body &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/288067/3-surprising-reasons-your-gut-health-matters/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;break down food&lt;/a&gt;, absorb nutrients and even produce essential vitamins.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "The microbes you have in your gut play a big role in your overall metabolism," shares &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/taylor-berggren-ms-rdn/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Taylor Berggren, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;. An &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7918818/gut-health-and-weight-loss/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;imbalance in gut bacteria&lt;/a&gt; can hinder your body’s ability to process nutrients efficiently. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Some important strains, called keystones, have been shown to be associated with lower rates of metabolic disease and diabetes, and introducing live probiotic strains can even improve markers of an imbalanced metabolism like A1C and post-meal blood glucose spikes in those with diabetes,” explains Berggren.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A diverse, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/you-just-started-a-high-fiber-diet-recipes-to-make-first-11692499" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber-rich diet&lt;/a&gt; that includes fruits, vegetables, whole grains and fermented foods can help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2059033/best-and-worst-foods-to-eat-for-gut-health/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;nourish a healthy gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-your-insulin-sensitivity"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 4. Your Insulin Sensitivity &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Insulin is a hormone that helps your cells use glucose from your bloodstream for energy. But when your cells become less responsive to insulin, a condition known as insulin resistance, it may &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8053663/the-sneaky-way-diabetes-affects-metabolism-according-to-a-dietitian/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;throw your metabolism out of balance&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "When our cells don’t respond well to insulin, the body has a harder time using glucose efficiently, and fat metabolism slows down. This makes it easier to store fat and harder to burn it," explains &lt;a href="https://datatodiet.com" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Johannah Katz, M.A., RD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Addressing insulin sensitivity through diet, movement, and lifestyle can be just as important as building muscle when it comes to supporting a healthy metabolism."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A balanced diet, regular exercise and maintaining a healthy weight are key strategies for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-nutrient-for-insulin-resistance-8741761" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;improving insulin sensitivity&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-dietitian-recommended-ways-to-support-a-healthy-metabolism"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Dietitian-Recommended Ways to Support a Healthy Metabolism &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While you can't control factors your genetics or stop the clock, you can adopt &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7938737/top-healthy-eating-habits-according-to-a-dietitian/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;habits that support your body&lt;/a&gt;'s metabolism. Here are some actionable tips that are more well-known and equally as important to prioritize:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritize Protein:&lt;/strong&gt; Including an &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290496/this-is-how-much-protein-you-need-to-eat-every-day/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;adequate amount of protein&lt;/a&gt; with every meal and snack is a powerful way to support your metabolism. Your body uses energy to digest and process food, a phenomenon known as the Thermic Effect of Food (TEF). "Protein increases TEF the most, so you burn more calories when you eat protein compared to carbs and fat," explains &lt;a href="https://www.maritaradloff.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Marita Radloff, M.S., RDN, LD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Aim for at least 20-30 grams of protein at meals and 10-15 grams of protein for snacks to support your metabolism and stay full."&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Build More Muscle: &lt;/strong&gt;Strength training helps &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-to-maintain-muscle-mass-while-losing-weight-8706542" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;preserve lean muscle mass&lt;/a&gt;, which burns more calories at rest than fat tissue. Incorporating &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290619/trying-to-lose-weight-heres-why-strength-training-is-as-important-as-cardio/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;resistance training&lt;/a&gt;—such as lifting weights or using resistance bands—even just two times per week, can support a more active metabolism over time.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eat Regular Meals and Snacks: &lt;/strong&gt;Skipping meals can affect your metabolism and how your body regulates blood sugar. One study found that skipping lunch for two days in a row led to a higher blood sugar spike after dinner compared to days when lunch was eaten. Interestingly, skipping breakfast or dinner didn’t have the same effect on blood sugar at the next meal.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; While occasional meal shifts happen, eating regular meals and snacks can help maintain consistent energy and metabolic balance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Metabolism is a complex and highly individual process influenced by much more than just food and exercise. While fueling your body well and moving regularly are foundational, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7872589/habits-healthy-evening-routine/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;supporting your sleep&lt;/a&gt;, managing stress and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/things-you-should-do-everyday-for-better-gut-health-11782347" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;prioritizing gut health&lt;/a&gt; are equally important.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Instead of chasing a quick fix, consider small daily choices that help your body function at its best. These &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/283013/5-ways-to-help-your-diet-become-a-way-of-life/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;sustainable habits&lt;/a&gt; can add up to long-term benefits for your energy, well-being and metabolic health.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 02:05:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBVQnFlUVphZWJ6UW8yekEyRWNEblJOZUF1U1pIUmo2bnpBQmdwTUIwdkJRekNUajFSSkFmdXlFN2l5cWtOaERaOEJPeVpWLXZrWGVmREhfLVJlVXlvQXNhRC1tUFl1Y3pXVktKcmtaX0d2LVJhUzg0VmdRVGdyUQ</guid></item><item><title>肾脏健康：科学家终于找到了一种“简单”的方法来逆转肾脏损伤—何时治愈-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/kidney-health-scientists-finally-found-a-simple-way-to-reverse-kidney-damage-when-is-the-cure-coming/articleshow/125358516.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;One organ that does the most amount of work, without much fuss or chaos — it’s the kidneys. The “silent multitaskers” of the body perform vital, behind-the-scenes work: filtering waste, balancing fluids and salts, producing hormones, and keeping our body chemistry in harmony. And because they work so tirelessly, it’s only natural that without proper maintenance, they’d fall into damage. Now, kidney damage is tricky: it often progresses without obvious warning signs, and by the time overt symptoms appear, substantial injury may already have occurred.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what if there’s a way to reverse that damage?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seems like scientists have finally found one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Don’t Ignore Silent Kidney Damage: How to Detect Issues Before It’s Too Late | Dr Sanjeev Bagai&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Can kidney damage be reversed?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a landmark study published in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.cmet.2025.10.006" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Cell Metabolism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, scientists at the University of Utah Health revealed that they could fully reverse acute kidney injury (AKI) in mice by blocking harmful ceramide molecules. These ceramides, a type of fat, damage the mitochondria — the “power plants” — of kidney cells, triggering the rapid-onset of kidney injury.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acute kidney injury is a dangerous condition often caused by severe stress on the body, such as sepsis or major surgery, and is common in intensive care units. What makes AKI especially alarming is that it can increase the risk of long-term, chronic kidney disease, for which there are very limited treatment options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What does the research reveal?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team, led by Scott Summers, PhD, found that when ceramide production was genetically altered, their genetically modified “super mice” did not develop AKI — even under extreme conditions that normally damage the kidneys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s encouraging is that the researchers also tested a drug candidate developed by Centaurus Therapeutics (a company co-founded by Summers) that mimics this genetic effect. Mice pre-treated with the drug maintained normal kidney function, stayed active, and showed healthy kidney structure under the microscope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under closer examination, the team discovered how ceramides wreak havoc: they impair the mitochondria in kidney cells. Damaged mitochondria lose their shape and efficiency, reducing cellular energy production — a key factor in injury. But when ceramide levels were reduced, the mitochondria remained intact and worked properly, even under stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does this matter?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Firstly, this is the first time researchers have reversed acute kidney damage in this way by targeting metabolism rather than symptoms. The fact that mitochondrial structure was preserved is especially promising because mitochondrial health is central not just to kidney cells but many other tissues, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, ceramide levels also rose quickly in human AKI patients’ urine in earlier studies, suggesting the mechanism may be relevant in people as well. If urinary ceramide becomes a reliable biomarker, it might help clinicians identify patients at risk, for example, before they undergo heart surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What’s next?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, this research surely is promising enough for a possible future where kidney damage can be reversed. However, despite the excitement, experts caution that results in mice don’t always translate to humans. The drug used is still preclinical, meaning it hasn’t yet been tested in human trials. Additionally, safety is a major concern. Even if ceramide-lowering works in people, long-term effects, drug metabolism, and side effects need careful evaluation. The researchers themselves acknowledge this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another challenge is the timing — in the mouse study, the drug was given before injury. It’s not yet clear whether the same approach would work if administered after kidney damage has already started in a clinical setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If human trials succeed, the implications could be huge. The researchers believe that preserving mitochondrial health may not only help treat kidney injury but could also be beneficial in other diseases where mitochondrial dysfunction plays a role, such as diabetes, heart failure, or fatty liver disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it’s also important to remember that scaling from mice to humans is notably complex. What works in a controlled animal model might run into unexpected biological roadblocks in people — differences in drug absorption, immune response, or even how ceramides are metabolized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 01:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwJBVV95cUxONTd1RFpDOTdpM1V6RDlPV3lLYVhFcFR0cEZhejBzNUxFbGJDMlFuSDBHWXBVZVAtZ0ZvU2RVNkU4X1I0UlRVVjJVcUtnWXR5ZE42NW1faG1rZ1BFRzktckNSR2FGQ3BWY1NQTEJONU9YcHRaYnRZQzRiUWJ6NEpvN2JJQ2pvQnZScFBDTnNoNlQ4ejlmTW1KOVhVblpfMnhWdXcyUjVLY2k1cFFpUEE3bk42cnVmQ2tVU0taSWxJa2Jncmc4WFFHRFdaUjFpSHFhb0lVUnYyMjZ5YW5NZFZ0Y042X3NKNXdZaTRmZ3lOT0ZMYk9MRVlnSjFMd1VJWG5lRjd1SFdEdmVXZTFkc0lCbEJYZkVNMV9aQzlQQllsZVBEbEVoOHVj0gGsAkFVX3lxTE42T3FmMFBrR1ptQ1R0Q0NyeENIdDRSQU1Mb0ZXanVfSkl1SFFCTjNWRTF4QUFaT0h6Rjdnazl0RVZybTVxcHVnbWtPTlJ3U081dmxyVWdCdWp5X2dvSmlzLXVVWnFFbVltRkRBaFNPNUVzU0JaSXpuQkxYRXYwYkVXTXRNLXktMmRKbi1XS1l1dXR0dXViMWZ6N0JITzFWbmd5c1FLTFJfREhmSVgyOTVscHluZFJqR0NYdkQxS0JLVWtYRTJTd0pseEZUM19CUDZhWTBMTV9PRXpXb1dQOURybUhIYmxuQ0hqOUtIXzRvVXRTejBCd05pSjREZngya2ZNS0R1dkdlTWZWNDZ4bHJjeGJmWF9tTEdyNzVhOW9kUkxyTVkwdDBzNUlmMA</guid></item><item><title>您有足够的阳光吗？癌症外科医生解释了如何每天获得20分钟的阳光可以降低癌症风险|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/do-you-get-enough-sunlight-cancer-surgeon-explains-how-getting-20-minutes-of-sunshine-daily-can-reduce-cancer-risk-101763220504191.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/do-you-get-enough-sunlight-cancer-surgeon-explains-how-getting-20-minutes-of-sunshine-daily-can-reduce-cancer-risk-101763220504191.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Are you getting your daily dose of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/sunshine" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="sunshine"&gt;sunshine&lt;/a&gt;? Beyond lifting your mood and supporting your body’s &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/office-interiors-can-affect-your-circadian-rhythm-mood-psychiatrist-shares-6-design-tips-to-boost-efficiency-101757930381952.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="circadian rhythm"&gt;circadian rhythm&lt;/a&gt;, sunlight also plays a surprisingly important role in keeping you healthy - including reducing your long-term risk of certain diseases, including cancer!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/15/550x309/sunlight_1763221084942_1763221085232.jpg" alt="This is your sign to go and stand in sunlight for 20 minutes every day - but don't forget sunscreen!(Unsplash)" title="This is your sign to go and stand in sunlight for 20 minutes every day - but don't forget sunscreen!(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/15/550x309/sunlight_1763221084942_1763221085232.jpg" alt="This is your sign to go and stand in sunlight for 20 minutes every day - but don't forget sunscreen!(Unsplash)" title="This is your sign to go and stand in sunlight for 20 minutes every day - but don't forget sunscreen!(Unsplash)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;This is your sign to go and stand in sunlight for 20 minutes every day - but don't forget sunscreen!(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read |&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cancer-surgeon-suggests-6-food-groups-to-protect-against-rising-lung-cancer-risk-due-to-delhi-pollution-101762415846854.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Cancer surgeon suggests 6 food groups to protect against rising lung cancer risk due to Delhi pollution"&gt;Cancer surgeon suggests 6 food groups to protect against rising lung cancer risk due to Delhi pollution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Sudipto De, a robotic cancer surgeon with specialisations in genetics and onco-nutrition, practising at Metro Hospitals, Delhi NCR, has revealed that getting your daily dose of sunlight is actually essential for cancer protection.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; In an Instagram video posted on November 15, the oncologist explains how the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/surgeon-warns-against-vitamin-d-supplements-too-much-can-backfire-and-damage-your-arteries-101761291956952.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vitamin D"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; from sunlight helps fight cancer cells and can even reduce the risk of death due to cancer.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Getting enough sunlight can prevent cancer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;According to Dr De, vitamin D from sunlight may help reduce the risk of certain cancers, making regular, safe sun exposure an important part of cancer prevention.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; He explains, “Vitamin D is not just for bones. It controls cell growth in the body, reduces inflammation, and strengthens immunity. According to research, those who have the right amount of Vitamin D levels have a reduced risk of colorectal, breast, and sometimes &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/prostate-cancer" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="prostate cancer"&gt;prostate cancer&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The oncologist notes that vitamin D supplements are not as effective as sunlight-derived vitamin D. While supplements cannot fully prevent cancer, research suggests they may help reduce the risk of death from the disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/15/original/itamin_d_graphic_1763221442665.png" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="The oncologist suggests these ways to maintain your vitamin D levels.(Image generated via ChatGPT)" title="The oncologist suggests these ways to maintain your vitamin D levels.(Image generated via ChatGPT)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;The oncologist suggests these ways to maintain your vitamin D levels.(Image generated via ChatGPT)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to get enough vitamin D&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;To help meet your recommended vitamin D levels, Dr De suggests getting at least 15 to 20 minutes of sunlight each day - however, don’t forget your sunscreen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; He adds, “Foods like fish (such as &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/doctor-shares-why-you-should-include-fatty-fishes-like-salmon-in-your-diet-boosts-heart-health-reduces-inflammation-101762952360549.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="salmon"&gt;salmon&lt;/a&gt;), eggs, and fortified milk should also be consumed. And if Vitamin D is low in a blood test, one should discuss supplements with a doctor. Keeping your Vitamin D levels between 30 to 50 nanograms per ml is ideal.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;However, the oncologist emphasises that vitamin D is not a magical shield, but it is certainly a powerful part of a healthy lifestyle. So the next time you step out into the sun, think of it as your natural dose of cancer protection.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 01:30:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxQSkFEdDRFWGRVQmIxazVGU0pVbWY2NVJKZWhLazdlYTctX1NyazVFd085V2JMWnNKVEhPTWpBZXJzZjdwU29kRW5TN2lSZHFkWmdyLS1EY3lrTkdnZDkyRGhqdmR5N2tmcTZpVjhqVFBkN3M5N1ZkUG5oVWw2NEZhWW9IME51Mmh4RXNxMGJ0d2VfNWNWLWloOTZrbzRkT3Z2ZXZlR1pnaU0zNGdCQm1NdEt4UHNONlJESktGOXJGc0s5Mkc1XzN2RFZURS1ma3hVSllwMUdrZ3BZR2tCTFdxZ2xoVUxfQk1nTlZtTkFGVmNzTnYwRWhWUXBOUkhCYURqNkhzTWdFdkRVSVpiMllEUdIBlgJBVV95cUxNU19PdkVfUktqb2NFN3ZiLXNuUUViQ0JEOG45bXoyY1p2MUF6TG9yeUFpRC1rb054ZHlfUVgwNHIxb2ZTTEV0WUpsLV9aV3NPT1pmZzZ2WEd5YlJ6b3hFZFJ1VVpUbXJodU0wdS16dWVYbXlIa0Q0cm1ROHBjRWNmRGpDWnFIa2FBLS1qb1NsN2VsdGpTR2ZmX2JIcmNsOEFEUm5pamtfa0Fta0YtcTRHOG5lRU9xdk5YWVpFb2VWUjZOZkw1X2dPQTZiWjJ3WGJSdW5UUl9CRXNnR2FFMWo2MENteVQ0WXN1eHVKaHFRbUZTZms4NTdYQ3FFR3pGdHBod1pXT2V5enNZRG44Mi16WEtoUGFzQQ</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现激素、多巴胺和学习之间缺失的联系- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-discover-a-missing-link-between-hormones-dopamine-and-learning/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 23:13:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxONVZkUkpNMDdPQWU3OWlQM0NHcFNDV1ZEVVdvdzFvQXA5ZHdfNFdoTEJWajBwZmFreGtLTVlyU1hlZC1DWW16SzljaW4tZEdqaHdfODJNT21iSGV3MmJFanhydUI5ZzNISkNvd0Z6NGJ1Wk9VNENvd0U0Rnh5Ui1UOWp0R1I2a1h4UmdNQWtwSXBIcnpuYXpIa3o3LThIZ2Ns</guid></item><item><title>如何永不得癌症？支持身体和降低癌症风险的5种强大方法-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/how-to-never-get-cancer-5-powerful-ways-to-support-your-body-and-lower-cancer-risk/articleshow/125326177.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the central messages is that cancer isn’t just about “bad cells” in isolation, but about the underlying terrain of the body, how well our cellular energy systems (the mitochondria) are functioning, how our metabolism is balanced, and how well our body defences (immune, detoxification) are working. Dr Berg emphasises that supporting mitochondrial health becomes a key strategy in reducing cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When mitochondria are damaged or dysfunctional, cells may revert to abnormal energy pathways, oxidative stress increases, and the environment becomes more favourable for malignant transformation. By contrast, healthy mitochondria contribute to normal apoptosis (cell‑death when needed), stable metabolism, and robust resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding &lt;keyword id="30622074" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="how-cancer-develops" source="Orion"&gt;how cancer develops&lt;/keyword&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer arises when normal cells lose the ability to control growth and division. DNA mutations caused by factors like carcinogens, viruses, chronic inflammation, or inherited genes disrupt the balance of oncogenes and tumor suppressor genes. These changes allow cells to multiply uncontrollably, evade death, and sometimes hide from the immune system. Cancer cells also alter their metabolism, relying on less efficient energy processes to fuel rapid growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Tumors can form and, in some cases, spread to other parts of the body (metastasis). Overall, cancer reflects not just rogue cells but a body environment that enables their survival and growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5 quick tips to avoid getting cancer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;An early point in the video: “Avoid all refined foods.” That means sugar, refined flour, processed snacks, and other “empty‑calorie” items. Why does this matter? Refined foods tend to spike insulin, promote inflammation, feed abnormal cell growth, and put stress on metabolic regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you reduce the intake of these foods, you lessen insulin spikes, reduce the oxidative burden on mitochondria, and create an internal milieu less hospitable to cancerous changes. This strategy aligns with broader research showing that diets high in highly processed carbs correlate with higher cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support mitochondria via diet and fasting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond what you eliminate, Dr Berg advocates for what you do to support mitochondrial health. Two major diet‑strategies he mentions: adopting a low‑carbohydrate (or moderately low‑carb) diet, and using intermittent fasting (or time‑restricted eating). The idea is to reduce metabolic strain, allow cells to repair, reduce oxidative stress, and give mitochondria a chance to “reset”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you go low‑carb, fewer glucose surges occur; insulin demand drops. When you fast or restrict your eating window, your body shifts toward fat/ketone metabolism for periods, which may enhance mitochondrial resilience, trigger autophagy (cellular clean‑up) and reduce inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antioxidants and phytochemicals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another key theme is the role of antioxidants and phytochemicals (plant compounds) in protecting cells and mitochondria from damage. Foods rich in colourful vegetables, berries, herbs and certain spices help neutralise free radicals and lower oxidative stress. Herbs like turmeric, rosemary, green tea extract, and others may support mitochondria and immunologic health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;By making an “anti‑cancer diet” that is heavy on whole, unprocessed plant foods, you provide the raw materials your body needs to defend itself. You improve detox pathways (liver, lymphatic), bolster immune surveillance, and reduce the accumulation of damaged cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Lifestyle factors: Movement, sunlight, fresh air, detoxification&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer prevention isn’t just about what you eat. The video touches on lifestyle factors: daily physical movement, exposure to natural sunlight (for vitamin D), fresh air, and even cold exposure or “stressors” that stimulate mitochondrial adaptation. These practices make the body more robust, optimise circulation, support tissue oxygenation, and enhance immune function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Movement means muscle‑pump, lymph flush, better mitochondrial density. Sunlight signals circadian processes and vitamin D synthesis (important for immune health). Fresh air and decent ventilation reduce indoor pollutants and support respiratory‑detoxification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Minimising iron overload and other hidden risks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A more nuanced point: he mentions avoiding excess iron accumulation. While iron is essential, in excess it can catalyse free‑radical reactions (Fenton chemistry) and thereby damage mitochondria and DNA. So ensuring you’re not overloaded with iron (especially if you’re not using it) can be protective. It signals that cancer‑prevention isn't only “big”, obvious things but also hidden biochemical stressors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other hidden risks include environmental toxins, poor sleep, chronic stress, and impaired gut health all of which may impair mitochondrial and immune health long‑term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This content is for informational and educational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult a qualified healthcare provider before making significant changes to your diet, lifestyle, or supplement routine, especially if you have existing medical conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwJBVV95cUxQZ1g1bEtocXVST2ljYmh2OGR2VmVUaW8tc0ZvMVVmLWpUOTY4NFh5OEZSbGViT01heE55bGZFcU1Sa08xRkM0Z21ZZXVRc2pvSGJ4bnBkTEV6dGl3aEdaMzZoSGszdi1lQzhXLUZoUEdPSkVWc1RtSjg2cUstVzJtLWJiUDFiZDlEQUswaHZ1S3VwM3FCVER6d190ak8yTThDUURkZmxXdktyeWc3RXBEOHVSX291M0VPamlXdEl3RS1qN2g1LUJJX0FLTFNFVGJxZ0JxZ08xdnM0OW9LRnRmMVBZeEZrU1ZTOWFuZkV2dzd5ckdLR3NrT2N5M2MwZFh5RU5DM2ZxUGxhRXBIOXJN0gGUAkFVX3lxTE9OODBvaWRkQTVYMTVsVENrZkxTR3VqcTBmSzFma0hIdmNFOG40eHNUTWRjMlhYZUl4c3k0MHo4WTE3WmU5U19NSUdsTkpQd042UG1fTVY5YlYxbzAxT09mSWlhODBUOWpqTlBGUkMtVTZiVkhyUkFlWHhKcnNTdm5RYTV4RS01MWZiUnpxZzVqcHpOV2V1RmZQc1Y4OExTcHRSNmQ5aHlvN3I5TmdfTGxtRWdQbktRTDRhTVIzN3FjNlJoOVJEMkoyTzZIUG1vZ0EyVHplNVFrTHFZbjJzWEhBWVRRWEhjVEZ6ZnlmLW9UUEtFa0ExNkp4QVpFZnhnUkgxSUI1Z0ZERkEwZmZqT0ZkSzhGdA</guid></item><item><title>如何永不得癌症？支持身体和降低癌症风险的5种强大方法-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/how-to-never-get-cancer-5-powerful-ways-to-support-your-body-and-lower-cancer-risk/articleshow/125326177.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the central messages is that cancer isn’t just about “bad cells” in isolation, but about the underlying terrain of the body, how well our cellular energy systems (the mitochondria) are functioning, how our metabolism is balanced, and how well our body defences (immune, detoxification) are working. Dr Berg emphasises that supporting mitochondrial health becomes a key strategy in reducing cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When mitochondria are damaged or dysfunctional, cells may revert to abnormal energy pathways, oxidative stress increases, and the environment becomes more favourable for malignant transformation. By contrast, healthy mitochondria contribute to normal apoptosis (cell‑death when needed), stable metabolism, and robust resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding &lt;keyword id="30622074" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="how-cancer-develops" source="Orion"&gt;how cancer develops&lt;/keyword&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer arises when normal cells lose the ability to control growth and division. DNA mutations caused by factors like carcinogens, viruses, chronic inflammation, or inherited genes disrupt the balance of oncogenes and tumor suppressor genes. These changes allow cells to multiply uncontrollably, evade death, and sometimes hide from the immune system. Cancer cells also alter their metabolism, relying on less efficient energy processes to fuel rapid growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Tumors can form and, in some cases, spread to other parts of the body (metastasis). Overall, cancer reflects not just rogue cells but a body environment that enables their survival and growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5 quick tips to avoid getting cancer&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;An early point in the video: “Avoid all refined foods.” That means sugar, refined flour, processed snacks, and other “empty‑calorie” items. Why does this matter? Refined foods tend to spike insulin, promote inflammation, feed abnormal cell growth, and put stress on metabolic regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you reduce the intake of these foods, you lessen insulin spikes, reduce the oxidative burden on mitochondria, and create an internal milieu less hospitable to cancerous changes. This strategy aligns with broader research showing that diets high in highly processed carbs correlate with higher cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support mitochondria via diet and fasting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond what you eliminate, Dr Berg advocates for what you do to support mitochondrial health. Two major diet‑strategies he mentions: adopting a low‑carbohydrate (or moderately low‑carb) diet, and using intermittent fasting (or time‑restricted eating). The idea is to reduce metabolic strain, allow cells to repair, reduce oxidative stress, and give mitochondria a chance to “reset”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you go low‑carb, fewer glucose surges occur; insulin demand drops. When you fast or restrict your eating window, your body shifts toward fat/ketone metabolism for periods, which may enhance mitochondrial resilience, trigger autophagy (cellular clean‑up) and reduce inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Antioxidants and phytochemicals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another key theme is the role of antioxidants and phytochemicals (plant compounds) in protecting cells and mitochondria from damage. Foods rich in colourful vegetables, berries, herbs and certain spices help neutralise free radicals and lower oxidative stress. Herbs like turmeric, rosemary, green tea extract, and others may support mitochondria and immunologic health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;By making an “anti‑cancer diet” that is heavy on whole, unprocessed plant foods, you provide the raw materials your body needs to defend itself. You improve detox pathways (liver, lymphatic), bolster immune surveillance, and reduce the accumulation of damaged cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Lifestyle factors: Movement, sunlight, fresh air, detoxification&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer prevention isn’t just about what you eat. The video touches on lifestyle factors: daily physical movement, exposure to natural sunlight (for vitamin D), fresh air, and even cold exposure or “stressors” that stimulate mitochondrial adaptation. These practices make the body more robust, optimise circulation, support tissue oxygenation, and enhance immune function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Movement means muscle‑pump, lymph flush, better mitochondrial density. Sunlight signals circadian processes and vitamin D synthesis (important for immune health). Fresh air and decent ventilation reduce indoor pollutants and support respiratory‑detoxification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Minimising iron overload and other hidden risks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A more nuanced point: he mentions avoiding excess iron accumulation. While iron is essential, in excess it can catalyse free‑radical reactions (Fenton chemistry) and thereby damage mitochondria and DNA. So ensuring you’re not overloaded with iron (especially if you’re not using it) can be protective. It signals that cancer‑prevention isn't only “big”, obvious things but also hidden biochemical stressors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other hidden risks include environmental toxins, poor sleep, chronic stress, and impaired gut health all of which may impair mitochondrial and immune health long‑term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This content is for informational and educational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult a qualified healthcare provider before making significant changes to your diet, lifestyle, or supplement routine, especially if you have existing medical conditions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 21:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwJBVV95cUxQZ1g1bEtocXVST2ljYmh2OGR2VmVUaW8tc0ZvMVVmLWpUOTY4NFh5OEZSbGViT01heE55bGZFcU1Sa08xRkM0Z21ZZXVRc2pvSGJ4bnBkTEV6dGl3aEdaMzZoSGszdi1lQzhXLUZoUEdPSkVWc1RtSjg2cUstVzJtLWJiUDFiZDlEQUswaHZ1S3VwM3FCVER6d190ak8yTThDUURkZmxXdktyeWc3RXBEOHVSX291M0VPamlXdEl3RS1qN2g1LUJJX0FLTFNFVGJxZ0JxZ08xdnM0OW9LRnRmMVBZeEZrU1ZTOWFuZkV2dzd5ckdLR3NrT2N5M2MwZFh5RU5DM2ZxUGxhRXBIOXJN</guid></item><item><title>一人在从西南波特兰公寓窗户大幅坠落后住院- KOIN.com</title><link>https://www.koin.com/news/portland/one-hospitalized-after-significant-fall-from-southwest-portland-apartment-window/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>KOIN.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 21:27:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxQWko4T0p5a1JzMFJxempzeGEzSVFucTFVZGt5R2RTM0UySkpvcVBDQU50S3ZEV29hLVVRc3ItTEJiTUd4Zk1EcVE2YlM3RVFfbUtnNll6eThBNGRBeVFlZUpDODBnUE1LaC11TENjbk8zU01udDcwLVMxcTRhVUNRcHJaLVZLV2JaLVdEYmh5SXBkdjFEWGJyWXJ5Uk1zQnRCdTRCb2duZ0VlT3lYMV9RYkZTSnZSX2vSAbwBQVVfeXFMUExLWmRQa0xKRS16RGtqR0xKaXYxbzlPaENFd0FfS0VnSzRkRFR4cThncWhrM2d5bUlqdXZLeWRJdG82NDhTQXUxYWI5MFBvaWhFb0diX2JfWWVZRkZlM1FRQ1phSGg0WGJRSTNlZXNrU3ktNm1lVkRlMlR6Q0dVNk1tN1ExSzdTSnZkbmRydGlNZDlyenNPT1hNZGhUMEpGRW96S1RzWEc4dzRrUENRNUxTb0prbHlPMzVpa2I</guid></item><item><title>我们对阿尔茨海默氏症治疗的最大希望之一似乎不起作用- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/one-of-our-biggest-hopes-for-alzheimers-treatment-doesnt-seem-to-work</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;For decades, scientists have targeted the sticky protein clumps that amass in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimer-s-disease"&gt;Alzheimer's brains&lt;/a&gt; as a potential way of treating the disease, but they may have been off the mark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study shows that clearing away the amyloid-beta clumps doesn't appear to repair key brain functions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In particular, it doesn't restore the brain's mechanisms for clearing out waste, known as the glymphatic system. This system is &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s11604-017-0617-z"&gt;known to be impaired&lt;/a&gt; in people with  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="181214" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, and would usually help with getting rid of excess amyloid-beta plaques, via &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-discover-hidden-pulse-in-the-brain-that-may-warn-of-dementia"&gt;waves of cerebrospinal fluid&lt;/a&gt; (CSF).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study comes from researchers at the Osaka Metropolitan University in Japan, who tested the new Alzheimer's drug &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-alzheimers-treatment-slows-decline-but-comes-at-a-high-cost"&gt;lecanemab&lt;/a&gt; on 13 people with the disease. &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Magnetic_resonance_imaging"&gt;Magnetic resonance imaging&lt;/a&gt; ( &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/magnetic-resonance-imaging" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73063" data-postid="181214" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;MRI&lt;/a&gt;) scans were used to look at the effects on the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-heart-health-in-middle-age-could-predict-your-later-dementia-risk"&gt;Your Heart Health in Middle Age Could Predict Your Later Dementia Risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Even when amyloid-beta is reduced by lecanemab, impairment of the glymphatic system may not recover within the short-term," &lt;a href="https://www.omu.ac.jp/en/info/research-news/entry-95626.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; medical researcher Tatsushi Oura, of Osaka Metropolitan University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_181217" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-181217" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GlymphaticSystem.jpg" alt="Glymphatic system scan" class="wp-image-181217 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GlymphaticSystem.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/GlymphaticSystem-600x604.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-181217" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A brain scan showing the diffusion of water, which was used to assess how well the glymphatic system was working. (Osaka Metropolitan University)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study highlights yet again the multifaceted nature of Alzheimer's, which is associated with a wide range of potential causes, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-15-factors-are-linked-to-early-dementia-risk-a-major-study-found"&gt;risk factors&lt;/a&gt;, and symptoms. It's not clear exactly how the disease starts, but various triggers are likely contributing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to the buildup of amyloid-beta and another brain protein &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sky-high-levels-of-alzheimers-protein-found-in-newborns"&gt;called tau&lt;/a&gt;, these are tell-tale signs of the disease – and yet scientists are still trying to figure out whether they're causing Alzheimer's, caused by Alzheimer's, or both.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study, lecanemab worked to the extent that it reduced amyloid-beta levels in the brain, but measures of glymphatic system function did not improve after three months. In other words, the drug doesn't seem to reverse the damage &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-may-hijack-your-cells-clocks-hinting-at-new-treatments"&gt;done by Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, at least in terms of the brain's waste recycling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Disease-modifying therapy can reduce plaque burden and slow further cognitive worsening but does not restore lost function, likely reflecting the fact that neuronal damage and clearance system deficits have already been well established," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/jmri.70118"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study adds more nuance to the increasingly complex picture of Alzheimer's, and how it &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-and-cancer-may-soon-be-treated-with-sounds-we-cant-hear"&gt;might be tackled&lt;/a&gt;. It's not the first study to find that &lt;span&gt;clearing plaques doesn't substantially improve Alzheimer's, so some researchers are now suspecting the plaques are a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/there-s-even-more-reason-now-to-stop-blaming-amyloid-plaques-for-alzheimer-s"&gt;consequence of the disease&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-might-been-wrong-what-kills-brain-cells-alzheimer-s-disease-beta-amyloid-tau-protein-app"&gt;not the cause&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-alzheimers-treatment-slows-decline-but-comes-at-a-high-cost"&gt;Past trials&lt;/a&gt; have shown that lecanemab does work at slowing down the steady march of Alzheimer's disease, but the drug functions best when administered at an early stage. That's why researchers are focused on trying to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-sign-deep-inside-your-eyes-could-warn-of-early-dementia"&gt;detect the signs&lt;/a&gt; of dementia &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-test-could-tell-if-you-have-early-signs-of-dementia-with-high-accuracy"&gt;as early as possible&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone size-medium wp-image-181305" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-642x337.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-768x403.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final-600x315.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/health-newsletter-subscribe-promo-final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This short study involved only a small number of people, so the researchers are keen to expand those parameters – looking at how lecanemab affects Alzheimer's &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-disease-harms-the-brain-in-2-distinct-phases-study-reveals"&gt;at different stages&lt;/a&gt;, or when it's administered for longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In the future, we want to look at factors like age, the stage of the disease, and degree of lesions in the white matter to further understand the relationship between changes in the glymphatic system due to lecanemab treatment and the outcome of treatment," &lt;a href="https://www.omu.ac.jp/en/info/research-news/entry-95626.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Oura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This will help understand the best way to administer treatment to patients."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/jmri.70118"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Magnetic Resonance Imaging&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 21:03:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNQUgzc1VJejg1djJwUER2YXFMZmp1MVhCQWtZbmM4Rjh5WktFVjVEQS1oZ0I3eWU4eTA0RGVSelpqRTVKTHM5YjV4cDAzaG5uQ3d0S3ZpVklMaW9OTEg3VXhTX1hJNExBN09KMnFqeXZhVEJIX3pESGlTM19LTEJ0OHI2YlIya1RORHAtd29iZnEtSlExbjd5WkdRZHBRUUE</guid></item><item><title>糖尿病至减肥至心脏防御： Ozempic和Mounjaro可预防中风和心脏病发作， -印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/diabetes-to-weight-loss-to-heart-defence-ozempic-and-mounjaro-protect-against-strokes-and-heart-attacks-finds-study/articleshow/125355781.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two of the world’s most widely used diabetes and weight-loss medications, Ozempic and Mounjaro, may be doing far more than helping people control blood sugar and shed weight. A new study published in&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-025-04102-x" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; Nature&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; Medicine shows that these drugs are also linked to a significant drop in the risk of major cardiovascular events such as strokes and heart attacks. The findings come from researchers at the Technical University of Munich (TUM) and Harvard Medical School, who analysed real-world medical records to understand how these treatments perform in everyday clinical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ozempic and Mounjaro’s benefits that go beyond losing weight&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although Ozempic and Mounjaro are well known for their impressive weight-loss effects, the study found that their heart benefits cannot be explained by weight changes alone. According to lead author Dr Nils Krüger, the protective effects appeared early and seem to involve direct changes in the body’s cardiovascular systems. Exactly how this happens is still being researched.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;What Your Cholesterol Report Is Hiding — The Truth That Could Save Your Heart | Dr Vinayak Agarwal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is important because people with type 2 diabetes face a much higher risk of heart disease than the general population. A treatment that can manage blood sugar, support weight loss and also reduce the chance of a heart attack or stroke could be a major step forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Real-world data shows strong heart protection&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike clinical trials that include carefully selected volunteers, this research used insurance data from thousands of people living with type 2 diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are real patients with different ages, health conditions and lifestyle factors. By studying them, the team could see how semaglutide (Ozempic) and tirzepatide (Mounjaro) actually work in day-to-day medical practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results were encouraging. Semaglutide lowered the combined risk of stroke and heart attack by about 18 percent compared with sitagliptin, a diabetes drug that does not protect the heart. Tirzepatide showed a 13 percent reduction in a broader measure that included heart attack, stroke and death, when compared with dulaglutide, an older GLP-1 medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ozempic versus Mounjaro&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been a lot of talk about which drug is better. Drug companies often suggest their product offers stronger protection, but this study found only small differences between the two. In other words, both appear to work well for heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professor Heribert Schunkert from the TUM German Heart Centre says the findings should reassure doctors. Both medications seem to offer real cardiovascular benefits, not just improvements in weight and blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;A possible turning point in diabetes care&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;GLP-1-based drugs are already changing how diabetes and obesity are treated. Now, with evidence of heart protection as well, these medicines could become key tools in preventing cardiovascular disease, which remains one of the biggest health threats worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;More research and direct comparisons in clinical trials are still needed. But for now, the message from this real-world study is clear. Ozempic and Mounjaro are not just helping people lose weight and control diabetes. They may also be protecting the heart in ways doctors are only beginning to fully understand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 20:53:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwJBVV95cUxQMS1kY2YzZmMybk5DbWt4S1FHdzQtNUFzN1NjVkloMlhndEljMjdjSkJ0WUV4VC1CcXcyVXNraWxsSlhJVEJ6dWZXWGJiWnlwY0hwb19WVHplbEE5SEZ5ZHBQYWNGNnR0NXNyN3JLR0FENXRlVkFsMXpyRlRpRnl5WXV3ZERvWGtuOF9UdFRTN2lLX2E0dGh4a3VMWm5vQVV6SFRRbXp2NU5IcEhvZ000SFlqcnZSUnhDWG5iQzJNMDJhWGdWanJFZWlCQmk2dFZPbkQwclN6VkFmU2ZMaFR1T3N0LTRJcEp2VV9TX2xXSmQ2UlN4LTlzTWFQbXl6dkxmcjRadnhIbFo1ZVJ2OEMzN0RxMnQzblJhdXhSQUVRZXp5d3puOE9JZXVrRlNZRmVHa3BjQlNoYnhqU1E</guid></item></channel></rss>