<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>大脑类器官正在帮助研究人员，但它们的使用也会造成不安- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2026/01/02/nx-s1-5658576/brain-organoids-research-ethics</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-104166" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Cross-section of a two-month old cerebral organoid observed under a fluorescence microscope.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Institut Pasteur-SupBiotech/NASA
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Institut Pasteur-SupBiotech/NASA
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Research on conditions like autism, schizophrenia and even brain cancer increasingly relies on clusters of human cells called brain organoids.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;These pea-size bits of neural tissue model aspects of human brain development as they grow for months and even years in a lab. They also make many people uneasy, in part because the brain is so closely tied to our sense of self.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A group of scientists, ethicists, patient advocates and journalists &lt;a href="https://web.cvent.com/event/f6374d3a-7ab1-477d-8445-265e918699c0/summary" target="_blank"&gt;met for two days&lt;/a&gt; in Northern California this fall to discuss how scientists, and society, should proceed.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Among the questions:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;ul class="edTag rte2-style-ul"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is it okay to place human organoids in an animal's brain?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can organoids feel pain?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Can they become conscious?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Who, if anyone, should regulate this research?&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We are talking about an organ that is at the seat of human consciousness. It's the seat of personality and who we are," says &lt;a href="https://bioethics.hms.harvard.edu/faculty-staff/insoo-hyun" target="_blank"&gt;Insoo Hyun&lt;/a&gt;, a bioethicist at the Museum of Science, Boston, who attended the meeting.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"So it's reasonable to be especially careful with the kind of experiments we're doing," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Societal issues by the sea&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The event was hosted by &lt;a href="https://profiles.stanford.edu/sergiu-pasca" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Sergiu Pașca&lt;/a&gt;, a prominent organoid researcher whose lab at Stanford University used the technology to develop &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2024/04/30/1247900797/timothy-syndrome-genetic-disorder-brain-cells-restored" target="_blank"&gt;a potential treatment&lt;/a&gt; for a rare cause of autism and epilepsy.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Organoids are allowing scientists to study brain cells and circuits that don't exist in animals,&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Pașca says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"For the first time, we have this ability to really work with human neurons and human glial cells," he says, "and ask questions about these really mysterious disorders of the brain."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But Pașca's work has sometimes caused public unease as his lab has &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/04/10/nx-s1-5358410/pain-pathway-in-a-dish-could-aid-search-for-new-analgesic-drugs" target="_blank"&gt;recreated a human pain pathway&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2022/10/12/1128356099/human-cells-in-a-rats-brain-could-shed-light-on-autism-and-adhd" target="_blank"&gt;transplanted&lt;/a&gt; a human organoid into the brain of a rat.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"Of course, there are issues of ethics and societal implications and religious views that have to be taken into consideration," he says. Many of those issues were outlined in a recent &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.aeb1510" target="_blank"&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; by Pasca and others in the journal &lt;em&gt;Science.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;To take the next step, Pașca invited a group to the Asilomar Conference Center on the Monterey Peninsula. It's the spot where, 50 years earlier, another group met to hash out the first &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/10.1126/science.adv3132" target="_blank"&gt;ethical guidelines&lt;/a&gt; for genetic engineering.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Organizers of the organoid event had more modest expectations.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Our goal for this meeting was to just bring everybody together across all these fields and start brainstorming," Pașca says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That happened — in formal sessions, coffee breaks, after-hours social gatherings and even walks on the beach. And participants brought widely varying perspectives.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Risk vs. reward&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Scientists and patient advocates at the meeting often emphasized the need to quickly answer questions and find cures.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Bioethicists were more likely to speak about the importance of guardrails to make sure people consent to having their cells made into organoids, and to discourage any efforts to enhance the brains of animals or humans.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There was consensus, though, on the need to keep the public informed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When people hear about brain organoid research, they tend to have one overarching and quite reasonable question for scientists, says &lt;a href="https://law.wisc.edu/profiles/ralta.charo" target="_blank"&gt;Alta Charo&lt;/a&gt;, professor emerita of law and bioethics at the University of Wisconsin, Madison.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"How far along are they in building organoids that can actually recapitulate something that we associate with human capacities?" she says. "Have we reached a point where we're worried?"&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Not yet, probably. But the prospect seems closer now that scientists are linking multiple organoids to create more brain-like structures called &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40249959/" target="_blank"&gt;assembloids&lt;/a&gt;, Charo says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Pasca's team, for example, has built a network of four organoids to model the pathway that carries pain signals to the brain.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;That sounds disturbing, Charo says, unless you understand that this network of cells lacks the circuitry to feel pain.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The mere existence of the pain pathway, I think, is enough to give a public perception problem that the organoid or the assembloid is suffering," Charo says. "And yet, if the pathway that allows for this emotional aversion doesn't exist, then there's no suffering."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And no ethical issue, for now.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Even so, she says, researchers and regulators should probably be looking ahead, rather than waiting until there is an actual problem.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A perception problem&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Several participants faulted the media for glossing over the current limits on what organoids can do, and for describing these clusters of cells as "mini-brains."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That sort of coverage has led some people to falsely believe there are labs with "brains growing in a petri dish," says &lt;a href="https://www.med.upenn.edu/apps/faculty/index.php/g275/p8945416" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Guo-li Ming&lt;/a&gt;, an organoid researcher at the University of Pennsylvania.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Scientists need to counter that notion and explain how organoid research is helping people with life-threatening diseases, Ming says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Her own lab, for example, is working to customize brain cancer treatment using organoids derived from a patient's own tumor cells. That allows doctors to ensure a cancer drug is effective for the patient's specific tumor.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Ming also thinks it's too soon to worry about organoids becoming conscious because "we're far from mimicking the brain activity in real human beings."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Even so, organoid scientists "definitely need some guidelines," Ming says, because of current public concern and the potential for inappropriate research in the future.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New cells, old issues&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The ethical and societal issues surrounding brain organoids echo those related to stem cell research more than 20 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Back then, there was concern that neural stem cells might give animals human-like cognitive abilities.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It turned out those human cells didn't do well in another species' brain. But organoids, which start out as stem cells, can thrive in animal brains and even integrate with their circuitry.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"So what used to be a very hot issue in stem cell research has now come back," Hyun says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hyun was part of a group that worked on organoid guidelines for the International Society for Stem Cell Research five years ago, when the need for oversight seemed less pressing.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We had a let's wait and see attitude," he says, because it was not clear how long it would take for organoid technology to become concerning. "We've gotten to the point rather quickly."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hyun's immediate concern is protecting research animals from organoid experiments that could cause suffering. But in the long term, he says, it may take guidelines and government oversight to ensure that organoid research doesn't harm, or horrify, people.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The Asilomar meeting suggests many scientists know that, and want help navigating this new scientific frontier.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxOYmdQVXR2dHdTN1E2amZHZkxTWlR3TkpnTnlsNExGMFNiX0VpWUxBY0x0ZklFSjBkRzZHMWJZWnNJQnhCdkloS0pmNWYzeGZpYTUzM256c1M2aWU1bnZWU0hmTFpyTDFIVHU4VmItc0hOVlNMQWtjOFdLWjB5a0Y5aFZGTnZ0RnNnQk9zVWtMOXAyWkhqaUlRbkNxZjR3SXRZSlJhWDB3</guid></item><item><title>一杯橙汁的惊人好处- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251230-the-surprising-health-benefits-of-a-glass-of-orange-juice</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;For instance in &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/microbiology/articles/10.3389/fmicb.2023.1199383/full" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;one study&lt;/a&gt;, 12 overweight women drank 500ml of orange juice every day for four weeks. At the end of the trial period, the women had significantly lower blood pressure. Although the composition of the gut microbiome itself did not change, the bacteria upped their production of chemicals known as short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs) – which are known to reduce inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;&lt;span id="which-orange-juice-is-best?" class="sc-d16436d-0 gCPVhV"&gt;&lt;b id="which-orange-juice-is-best?" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;Which orange juice is best? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, both nutritionists the BBC spoke to were keen to emphasise that whole fruit remains the preferred option and the healthier choice. Not only do oranges contain more fibre, but they also retain more flavonoids that are so beneficial for health. Polyphenols are the wider class of plant compounds to which flavonoids belong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"When you eat a fresh orange, the vitamin C and some of the more oxygen-sensitive nutrients [such as flavonoids] don't oxidise as much because they're still encapsulated within the fibre," says Amati. "Whereas when you juice an orange, you destroy the food matrix and those nutrients become exposed to the air, and so they oxidise, which reduces their potency."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As fibre is so hard to digest, it also helps to carry polyphenols and flavonoids all the way to the colon where they can be feasted on by beneficial microbes, enhancing their benefits. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, if juice is your preferred choice, then freshly squeezed oranges at home or in a restaurant will retain more health benefits than commercially available juice, as more fibre will remain. Industrially produced orange juice, on the other hand, will have been pasteurised and heated – which could kill off some of the more oxygen-sensitive nutrients, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/09637486.2024.2303034" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;such as vitamin C&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPZWVMV3NNN3BXTWo0TlMtZ2hZbjBWekdZNy1UaGtDQ3pkQzM3M1dYMXAwUUhjX3NRUzZJY0hoR1BtUktYX01NRzlScVQyWW94Skdqb2hXVm9VcHRWR1pZSllvOFFMZURmNHhrQzl6RXBDYWJGTzJsOUtqYVE3N2c0WEJsZlRRUmdMNFhoWllBX0RRR25jNzVDa1ZZaFkyc0pJREFr</guid></item><item><title>在欧洲和美国蔓延的“超级流感”是什么？ - wired.com</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/what-is-super-flu-spreading-in-united-states-europe/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spread of &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/tag/flu"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt; became more severe this fall, particularly in the United States and the United Kingdom. The US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/whats-new/2025-2026-influenza-activity.html" target="_blank"&gt;designated the&lt;/a&gt; 2024-25 flu season &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/whats-new/2025-2026-influenza-activity.html" target="_blank"&gt;as the most severe season&lt;/a&gt; since 2017-18. In the UK, the spread has begun earlier than at any time since 2003-04.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Against this backdrop, some media &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cly1rryv2ryo"&gt;outlets&lt;/a&gt; have begun &lt;a data-offer-url="https://theconversation.com/what-is-super-flu-and-other-questions-answered-271959" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://theconversation.com/what-is-super-flu-and-other-questions-answered-271959"}' href="https://theconversation.com/what-is-super-flu-and-other-questions-answered-271959" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;using&lt;/a&gt; the term “super flu.” However, this term is not an official medical term. The actual name is “subclade K,” a new variant of influenza A H3N2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;This variant has multiple mutations in a protein on the surface of the virus called hemagglutinin, making it antigenically different from the variants used in existing vaccines. This allows it to partially evade immunity acquired through previous infection or vaccines, making people more susceptible to infection. Genetic analysis by the UK Health Security Agency has &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12639273/"&gt;revealed&lt;/a&gt; that 87 percent of H3N2 viruses detected since late August 2025 are subclade K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;The Outbreak Began Earlier Than Usual&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The term “super flu” is not necessarily scientifically accurate. The H3N2 strain already caused severe illness in the elderly and children, and the new mutant strain has not made it more deadly. Contrary to the name, the virus's inherent danger is said to be no different from the conventional H3N2 strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In 2025, the US influenza pandemic peaked in early February, with active epidemics occurring in 87.3 percent of the country. For 11 consecutive weeks, more than 50 percent of the country &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/whats-new/2025-2026-influenza-activity.html" target="_blank"&gt;recorded high epidemic levels&lt;/a&gt;, an anomaly that led to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-45.html" target="_blank"&gt;287&lt;/a&gt; child deaths. However, these figures reflect the scale of the epidemic and do not imply an increase in the lethality of the virus itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The influenza epidemic is hitting earlier this year in many parts of the world. While the usual peak in Japan occurs between late December and February, in 2025 the epidemic began in earnest at the end of September. According to the Ministry of Health, Labor, and Welfare, of the 23 H3 virus strains collected in Japan between September and November 5 that could be analyzed, 22 were subclade K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The reason for the early outbreak is thought to be the decline in immunity of the population due to the countermeasures against &lt;a href="https://wired.jp/tag/covid-19/"&gt;new coronavirus infection (Covid-19)&lt;/a&gt;, as well as a decline in physical strength due to the record-breaking heat wave. During the three years of the coronavirus pandemic, the influenza epidemic was largely suppressed. As a result, it is possible that population immunity to the virus was reduced. In fact, with the 2024 influenza pandemic in Australia &lt;a data-offer-url="https://ausvacs.com.au/2025-flu-vaccination-proposal/2024-flu-season-summary/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://ausvacs.com.au/2025-flu-vaccination-proposal/2024-flu-season-summary/"}' href="https://ausvacs.com.au/2025-flu-vaccination-proposal/2024-flu-season-summary/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;at its highest level&lt;/a&gt; since 19 years, it would not be surprising to see a similar trend in the Northern Hemisphere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Existing Vaccines Are Effective&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;There has also been much interest in vaccine efficacy in the face of this virulent strain. The vaccine for the 2025-26 season is based on the conventional J.2 lineage (subclade), which has different antigenicity from subclade K. However, early data from the UK has confirmed that 70-75 percent of vaccinated children and 30-40 percent of adults did not end up visiting the emergency room or being hospitalized after infection. This means that even if the antigenicity is not completely identical, the vaccine remains effective in preventing severe illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The basic prevention measures are the same as for conventional influenza. Vaccination is recommended from October to November before the epidemic, and the effect appears about two weeks after vaccination. It is particularly recommended for people aged 65 and over, people with underlying medical conditions, pregnant women, children aged 6 months to 5 years, and medical workers. In daily life, it is effective to thoroughly wash and disinfect your hands, and wear a mask when in crowds. Ventilation in rooms and maintaining appropriate humidity levels are also important in suppressing viral activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>wired.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNTUZreGUzMWtUY3lzVVRreW1UNE1tZlNOTzdWTmZWRVF5V2FhVFhucVgwYWhfeGhrRlFibmdyaVZvUW03SVpDSTNqa0ZDNEtDaEh4T0trcG1yNHBJS01KaHRPRmNNbmxUdGFGc3hjUHRfVHdrbjJrbkZZTzk0elFfU1V1MGg1RXc</guid></item><item><title>心脏病专家说，这些是他们希望患者尽快更换的3种厨房用品- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/cardiologist-recommended-kitchen-tools-to-avoid-11870842</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;After talking to three different cardiologists, we gathered the best, safer alternatives to concerning kitchen materials such as microplastics and PFAS, including &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Bentgo-Signature-Leak-Proof-Glass-Storage/dp/B0F122SZ82/?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;&lt;u&gt;plastic-free containers&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B087XBR564?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;&lt;u&gt;reusable silicone bags&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Bees-Wrap-Reusable-Beeswax-Extra/dp/B08BWVXP6Y?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;&lt;u&gt;beeswax wrap&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Calphalon-Classic-10-Piece-Cookware-Stainless/dp/B0FQD52NTK?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="4" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;&lt;u&gt;stainless steel cookware&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Lodge-Skillet-Pre-Seasoned-Skillet-Silicone/dp/B00G2XGC88/?tag=eatingwell-onsite-backup-20" data-component="amazon" data-source="affiliate" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="5" rel="sponsored nofollow noskim"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cast-iron cookware&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;All three doctors expressed concern about materials such as microplastics, lead and PFAS. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Doctors want you to remember that swaps should be sustainable, realistic changes based on your budget and specific needs, and encourage you to prioritize your heart health in a variety of ways.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A new year is a great time for change—it’s exactly why resolutions came to be. And if you ask me, 2026 already has a strong theme: Many people want to make better choices for themselves, whether that’s the food they eat or the exercise they commit to. I am the same way, which is why I’ve been reaching out to experts for their advice. &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/cardiologist-recommended-kitchen-gadgets-amazon-11762566" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Cardiologists have some of the most fascinating perspectives&lt;/a&gt;, as cardiovascular health intersects with many different aspects of our well-being. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In light of what was one of the biggest topics of 2025—kitchen toxins &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-to-limit-microplastics-in-your-food-11713723" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;like microplastics&lt;/a&gt;, PFAS (aka forever chemicals), lead and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/banned-flame-retardants-found-in-cooking-utensils-8723612" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;flame retardants&lt;/a&gt;—I asked three cardiologists for their honest advice: Do these materials interact with heart health? What should we &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; avoid and why? And how can we do this in a manageable way? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-cardiologists-1-concern"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Cardiologists’ #1 Concern  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; After polling cardiologists, doctors were most concerned about three well-known toxins: &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/fda-lead-leaching-cookware-replacements-amazon-11833814" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;lead&lt;/a&gt;, plastics, and forever chemicals., Specifically, two out of the three doctors said microplastics were their biggest worry, while one flagged lead and PFAS. What ties these three together is that they can adversely impact heart health, and there are manageable ways to reduce your daily exposure.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “My goal as a cardiologist is not to create fear, but to help people make practical, evidence-based choices that fit into real life and meaningfully support long-term heart health,” says &lt;a href="https://www.houstonmethodist.org/doctor/juan-c-rozo/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nocaes"&gt;Dr. Juan Carlos Rozo, MD, FACC, FASE, RPVI&lt;/a&gt; at Houston Methodist Hospital. “I am concerned, but in a measured, evidence-based way. For Dr. Rozo, his biggest concern is with lead and PFAS since we have the most data to support them, noting that “these [materials] are all well-recognized drivers of cardiovascular disease.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.advancedcvmiami.com/physicians/pedro-martinez-clark" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow nocaes"&gt;Dr. Pedro Martinez-Clark, MD, FACC&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist at Amavita Heart and Vascular Health who has spent 26 years treating heart disease, is “particularly alarmed by recent breakthrough studies that have identified microplastics in human arterial plaques.” If he could choose one material to focus on, it’d be micro- and nanoplastics. “What makes this particularly urgent is that microplastics are nearly impossible to avoid completely; they're in our water (even tap water), food packaging, dust in our homes and the air we breathe. The average person may be ingesting tens of thousands of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/common-products-sources-of-microplastics-11863406" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;microplastic particles&lt;/a&gt; annually,” he notes. &lt;a href="https://bestheartbeat.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="nofollow nocaes"&gt;Dr. Andrew Rudin, MD&lt;/a&gt;, agrees, adding that “these plastics contain chemicals that can disrupt endocrine function as well as cause inflammation and oxidative stress resulting in obesity, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-have-insulin-resistance-8400321" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;insulin resistance&lt;/a&gt;, hypertension, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habit-heart-disease-risk-11833680" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, Parkinson's, Alzheimer's and cancer.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; So, what can we do about it? 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-safer-alternatives-to-consider"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Safer Alternatives to Consider  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Patients can take meaningful action to reduce microplastic exposure more readily than they can address some other &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/forever-chemicals-endocrine-disruptors-expert-kitchen-swaps-amazon-11795890" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;environmental toxins&lt;/a&gt;. This makes it an ideal starting point for those who feel overwhelmed about where to begin," says Dr. Martinez-Clark. We’ve tested a wide range of different &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/50233/must-have-kitchen-tools/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;kitchen gear&lt;/a&gt;, many of which can be considered safer alternatives to products containing microplastics, lead or PFAS. Below are our best recommendations. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-bentgo-signature-leakproof-glass-food-storage-container-set"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Bentgo Signature Leakproof Glass Food Storage Container Set &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_1-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-glass-food-storage-containers-8387775" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;storage containers&lt;/a&gt; are made with glass and silicone. I have been testing them at home for four months, and I really appreciate how durable and airtight they are. Whether I store food in the freezer, refrigerator or pantry, the lid’s seal ensures food stays fresh for days on end. Because there’s no plastic, I never worry about keeping food frozen and stored inside, even if it's for months at a time. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-stasher-silicone-reusable-storage-bag-set-4-pack"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Stasher Silicone Reusable Storage Bag Set, 4-Pack &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_2-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A great alternative to plastic bags, Stasher’s silicone storage options are excellent for keeping ingredients fresh. Use them for sandwiches, snacks, produce and more. We particularly love them for the freezer because of their sturdy material and tight seal—a rarity with plastic versions. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-bees-wrap-beeswax-wraps-for-food"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Bee's Wrap Beeswax Wraps for Food &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_3-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Buying Bee’s Wrap wraps was one of the smartest things I did in 2025. When I was looking for an option to replace most use cases for plastic wrap, I immediately jumped on buying this cut-it-yourself roll. It’s made with organic cotton, beeswax, organic plant oils and tree resin. The sheets seal with the warmth of your hands, and you can wash them with cold water and soap and reuse them time and time again. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-john-boos-chop-n-slice-series-rectangular-wooden-maple-cutting-board"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; John Boos Chop-N-Slice Series Rectangular Wooden Maple Cutting Board &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_4-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Over time, plastic cutting boards get nicked up from your knives, increasing your chances of ingesting microplastics. Investing in a nice &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-wooden-cutting-boards-8639594" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;wooden cutting board&lt;/a&gt; is a great option to grab for most prep, and John Boos makes some of the best on the market. I’ve used these everywhere from professional kitchens to at-home set-ups, and they always hold up. This model is a good starting point for the brand. It’s made with maple wood, is 1 inch thick for durability and lasts for years with proper care. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-calphalon-stainless-steel-cookware-set"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Calphalon Stainless Steel Cookware Set &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_5-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to cookware, reaching for simple materials like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-stainless-steel-cookware-8706088" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;stainless steel&lt;/a&gt; is a great option. We love Calphalon pans for their design, durability and fair price. This set is an excellent choice for many cooking applications. The 10-inch frying pan sears and sautés beautifully, while the 2.5-quart saucepan bubbles sauces and heats food with ease. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-lodge-12-inch-cast-iron-skillet-with-silicone-handle-holder"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Lodge 12-Inch Cast-Iron Skillet with Silicone Handle Holder &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_6-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Our favorite simple &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-cast-iron-skillets-8404277" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;cast-iron skillet&lt;/a&gt; on the market, the Lodge pan, is the one to grab for browning salmon fillets, cooking &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/easy-one-pan-dinners-in-30-minutes-or-less-8580555" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;one-pan dinners&lt;/a&gt; or baking up a tasty dessert. It comes preseasoned and only requires oil maintenance to last for decades to come. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-earlywood-13-in-handmade-wooden-kitchen-cooking-utensil"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Earlywood 13-in Handmade Wooden Kitchen Cooking Utensil &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;figcaption id="mntl-figure-caption_7-0" class="comp mntl-figure-caption text-utility-100 figure-article-caption"&gt; &lt;span class="figure-article-caption-owner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amazon&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When it comes to cooking tools, I always recommend these wooden spatulas for a true multi-tasking option. The slim design and hard edges make it excellent for scraping, tossing, stirring, flipping and more. Once you have one of these, you’ll likely reach for it over every other tool. They’re handmade from wood and have lasted me for years, even with daily use. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Doctors want to reiterate that they don’t want you to make a 180-degree change, and that this isn’t the only way to manage heart health. Always do what works best for you and your budget. “Perfect is the enemy of good. I counsel my patients to focus on high-impact, sustainable changes rather than trying to eliminate every possible risk, which is both impossible and can create unhealthy anxiety,” says Dr. Martinez-Clark.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPNDdSN3NnWWJDUm9ocnFZOXpzN3ZMWGp6MHB3RV9feTI4Qy1RVHZSTlRnYUNmbjdXcGt0RGlnSTZNdnFfdF9FUEJveHpfampZazQyV3E4QzRXdnhtWUZFaHRtYUdGVmh2a25yaFUwMDFWUFhHcHBGMUp3eDl3Mm9fVU1MUTRBWWhBMm0w</guid></item><item><title>主要医生透露，这不是油炸或加工食品，这实际上是对你的大脑最糟糕的食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/not-fried-or-processed-food-this-is-in-fact-the-worst-food-for-your-brain-reveals-leading-doctor/articleshow/126300311.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we think of foods that are good for our brain, we naturally gravitate towards fruits, vegetables, nuts, and good fats. However, what about foods that slowly damage your brain? According to Dr. Austin Perlmutter, MD, it is not refined carbs, or fried food, but something you consume on a daily basis, almost every day—yes, we are talking about sugar, and specifically liquid sugar, aka sugary drinks. Let's take a look...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular consumption of sugar-rich beverages and sweetened foods leads to brain &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40902134/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;damage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; through gradual processes when these items are consumed every day. The brain functions through a few essential elements which include memory, mood, focus and dementia risk assessment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Unhealthy 5 letter foods you should avoid&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;The process of sugar entering your brain system&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consumption of cola, packaged juice, energy drinks and sweet tea leads to fast sugar entry into the blood and brain. Your body needs to produce a large amount of insulin when blood sugar levels rise suddenly, and this process occurs multiple times throughout years which leads to brain insulin resistance. The brain depends on glucose for its operation but requires a continuous and controlled flow of this substance, instead of experiencing rapid increases and decreases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High sugar intake over several years causes brain cell &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11446400/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;damage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; by triggering inflammation and oxidative stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Sweet drinks, kids’ brains, and attention&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early exposure to sugary drinks is especially harmful for young, developing brains. Studies connect high intake of sugar-sweetened drinks in babies and children with more attention and behavior problems later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A large Korean cohort study showed that children who consumed more than 200 ml of sugary drinks daily, before their second birthday developed ADHD at a higher rate than children who drank less. Other studies in Spain and China report that frequent soft drink intake in school-age children links to higher ADHD risk and poorer cognitive performance scores.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Memory loss and thinking problems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prolonged intake of large sugar amounts results in detrimental effects that harm memory functions, learning abilities and information processing capabilities. Symptoms like brain fog and poor focus will appear first before the condition advances to its next stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies based on cohort data show that children who drink too many sugary beverages at a young age, will achieve lower IQ levels as adults based on their cognitive test performance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who drink too much sugar and sweetened beverages, face health dangers that harm their brain function because these drinking habits raise their risk of developing dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Artificial sweeteners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt; do not help much&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Switching from sugar to “zero-calorie” sweeteners may not fully protect the brain. New studies suggest that some artificial and low- or no-calorie sweeteners may also speed up cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research on an 8-year Brazilian study revealed that people who consumed common sweeteners including aspartame, saccharin, acesulfame K, erythritol, sorbitol and xylitol, showed quicker deterioration in their memory abilities, verbal fluency and thinking performance, particularly among participants under 60 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research published in The Neurology journal demonstrated that people who consumed the most sugar substitutes developed mental performance decline at a faster rate than those who used these substances infrequently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Sweetened drinks prove more detrimental to health than sugary foods do&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liquid sugar is particularly bad for the brain because it is easy to overconsume and is absorbed very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drinks do not make you feel as full as solid food, so you can easily add hundreds of “free sugar” calories without noticing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/world-health-organization" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; established two limits for sugar intake: free sugars at 10% of daily calories and 5% for maximum health advantages. One-liter soft drinks exceed the daily sugar limit people should not exceed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Mood swings, cravings, and addiction-like changes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brain's reward system reacts to sugar consumption through the same mechanisms that addictive substances trigger. This is one reason it is hard to stop at “just one” sweet drink.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="82"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;After multiple sugar highs, your brain learns to search for sugar; this develops a pattern leading to a reward cycle that ends with a crash followed by strong hunger and irritability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="84"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The body experiences unstable mood, fatigue and concentration problems when sugar consumption remains high throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How to protect your brain from sugar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="92"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;li&gt;People who drink fewer sweet beverages with added sugar, will protect their memory abilities and concentration skills, which will benefit their &lt;keyword id="20018982" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="brain-health" source="keywords"&gt;brain health&lt;/keyword&gt; in the long run.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The replacement of soft drinks, energy drinks and packed juices should be done by using water and unsweetened tea, along with lemon water, cucumber and herbs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep sweet treats small and occasional, and avoid giving sugary drinks to babies and toddlers to lower their future ADHD and cognitive risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is informational only and not a substitute for medical advice&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="97"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="98"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="100"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="101"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="102"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 06:38:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgJBVV95cUxPRVBacGRHUjZYYS14ZmwtbEU5Wm93MGVPaHctaWQ0dWFCMGUwRldkZFJVRGVXSk1SOGgwcjd0Q3l5Y0xiU2pJU1pOZkFwclRscXQ1Wk50SDBWREYweUY0QkpQOHBUcFo1dUJlekNlNXE3NFNycm1nVmd5STZFUzgya3NsckRLdFBETk43NVFfaXM3Z085a2hpZzQ5dDYwaVd2V01NcmxVemlfU3ZTTkFPcy1BMXczLVk1Tkl2dHFpZ1lDbkFoNVIwS1VLRHctdmZiVkExM3oxQVA3d3ZuQXpSQ3dicEx2NFE3SUJzb1dHSm81V2VwTVpWSGlCMTExUXI3UzVtVXI3dDZ1djVvRnA3WkFB</guid></item><item><title>罕见的食肉感染使蒙哥马利县的企业主留在医院-费城6abc</title><link>https://6abc.com/post/rare-flesh-eating-infection-leaves-montgomery-county-business-owner-hospital/18340382/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;DOYLESTOWN, Pa. (WPVI) -- &lt;/span&gt;A Montgomery County business owner is continuing to recover in the hospital after being diagnosed with a rare flesh-eating bacterial infection, a medical emergency that has kept him hospitalized since mid-December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Peter Atkinson, 49, of North Wales, has been at Doylestown Hospital since Dec. 19 after doctors diagnosed him with necrotizing fasciitis, a rare flesh-eating bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Atkinson said the hospital's swift response saved his life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"If it wasn't for the help of this hospital, I would definitely be dead," Atkinson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Atkinson said his illness initially felt like the flu. He described spiking a 104-degree fever and noticing a mass in his chest area before seeking medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"How did I get this? How did this happen? Apparently, it's rare, but it's not that rare because it happened to me," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He said doctors quickly realized the severity of his condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"I showed them, and it was like, wow, not even five minutes later, he came and said, 'We have to do emergency surgery. We're going to intubate you,'" Atkinson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The infection later progressed to sepsis, and his kidneys began to fail, according to his family. His sister, Marietta Atkinson, said the experience has been especially painful given their family's history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Probably one of the most traumatic events in our life, second traumatic event. In 2016, we lost our sister to sepsis, very similar to what Pete had," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Family members said Atkinson began to show signs of improvement on Christmas. His wife, Sherri Paulson-Atkinson, described the emotional toll of seeing her husband hospitalized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"My husband is a fighter, he's a go-getter, he is always busy, and to see him laying there like that was really hard for me," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Atkinson owns a towing company and is unable to work for the foreseeable future. To help support the family, a friend started a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://gofund.me/7b319da18" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;fundraiser&lt;/a&gt; page that has raised $13,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The amount of people that have touched me just in the last couple of days - I can't fathom the help," Atkinson said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Paulson-Atkinson said the family remains focused on his recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"He does everything for us, and we just need him back," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Atkinson is currently on dialysis. He is scheduled to undergo another procedure and is expected to eventually be moved to a rehabilitation facility to continue his recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2026 WPVI-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>6abc Philadelphia</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:59:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNRnhPdldCUnNTRloxQVNUNkRqbF9sVEk4VVRfUXJ6QXdLMU1mVlFVdlNPSkllR2g0TDY1S29yQm9La0RhbGQwbFRwSEpJazEyVnE4cWFBbDFJUVdyR29PdE9XX3FrWkZ1NHBKRzNXMHJBaUFVY3pDQ3BneUt4dHBHbDJ2OWRFbXZKQjJZazdOaEl6VmZyT0U1ZUxlbWNENGJVajhTaE92c21XZmhf0gGyAUFVX3lxTE1BQjJ3OUFaaXpMOU1lYm8zelBGczVwTHMyaHoyV2NwUUhoOGpoY1VmNl9CYVBwak1aTE9rQ1ROWEhYWTBVLWwxZmRwRzVMNGZhNktmakN6U1NjQVRqNUNHelBhMTJrbHU4Z2I0RmkzSzBMX2lsRWtleWphdWdJWGJ0alpJYzk4a2pJQTdEaGJFSElneS1Ib3lLMExVdG1fMW1DamVlakgwQ29GVXBaSkl6QlE</guid></item><item><title>拥有25年经验的心脏外科医生分享了4种非常规但有效的方法，可以在一夜之间改变您的饮食|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/heart-surgeon-with-25-years-of-experience-shares-4-unconventional-but-effective-ways-to-change-your-diet-overnight-101767322179355.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/heart-surgeon-with-25-years-of-experience-shares-4-unconventional-but-effective-ways-to-change-your-diet-overnight-101767322179355.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As the new year begins, it’s a good time to rethink not just what you eat, but how you make everyday &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/hormone-health-expert-shares-dos-and-donts-fertility-guide-for-him-and-her-food-choices-hormones-timing-101764431372877.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="food choices"&gt;food choices&lt;/a&gt;. Building healthier eating habits doesn’t require extreme diets or drastic restrictions - small, conscious changes can go a long way in improving your &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/nutrition" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="nutrition"&gt;nutrition&lt;/a&gt;, energy levels and overall wellbeing. By making intentional choices and setting up simple systems that support healthier decisions, you can create sustainable food habits that actually last well beyond January.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/02/550x309/eat_1767322681514_1767322681647.jpg" alt="Try out Dr London's recommendations to build healthier eating habits!(Unsplash)" title="Try out Dr London's recommendations to build healthier eating habits!(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2026/01/02/550x309/eat_1767322681514_1767322681647.jpg" alt="Try out Dr London's recommendations to build healthier eating habits!(Unsplash)" title="Try out Dr London's recommendations to build healthier eating habits!(Unsplash)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Try out Dr London's recommendations to build healthier eating habits!(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/heart-surgeon-with-25-years-of-experience-shares-4-smart-hacks-to-protect-yourself-from-flu-in-winter-use-soap-tips-101767149699010.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Heart surgeon with 25 years of experience shares 4 smart hacks to protect yourself from flu in winter: ‘Use soap…’"&gt;Heart surgeon with 25 years of experience shares 4 smart hacks to protect yourself from flu in winter: ‘Use soap…’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Jeremy London, a cardiothoracic surgeon with over 25 years of experience, has outlined four unconventional yet practical strategies to help you build healthier eating habits in 2026.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;In an Instagram video shared on January 2, the heart surgeon explains how small, intentional lifestyle changes at the start of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals/happy-new-year-2026-50-wishes-images-greetings-messages-whatsapp-and-facebook-status-to-share-with-loved-ones-101767096119580.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="new year"&gt;new year&lt;/a&gt; can set the foundation for a healthier, more sustainable way of living throughout the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Change your environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr London recommends thoughtfully reorganising your fridge and pantry so that healthier foods are front and centre and easy to reach, while junk food is kept out of sight, making better choices the default rather than a daily battle of willpower.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; He suggests, “Change your environment. Purge the fridge, the freezer, and the pantry. Make &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/16-year-old-up-girl-death-cause-junk-food-pizza-pasta-burger-neurologist-reacts-to-claims-real-cause-reveals-truth-maggi-101766657776901.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="junk food"&gt;junk food&lt;/a&gt; inconvenient.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Meal prep&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;The heart surgeon advises preparing meals in advance - before you get hungry - so that nutritious options are always within easy reach, reducing impulsive food choices and making it far easier to stick to healthier eating habits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; He explains, “Meal prep before you get hungry. Meal preparation makes healthy choices more convenient rather than using convenience to justify unhealthy choices.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reward yourself&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rewarding yourself for small wins can build motivation and encourage you to keep making healthy choices. Dr London stresses, “Acknowledge when you follow through on the promises you make and reward yourself.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Share your wins&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;The cardiologist explains that sharing even small wins with your loved ones can make the journey more enjoyable while also creating a sense of accountability that helps you stay committed to your goals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; He highlights, “Win with others. Not only is it more fun to share small wins with otherst, but it can help hold you accountable. Focus on progression over perfection. The goal isn't to jump on a short-term diet, but to build a sustainable nutritional plan.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 03:10:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxOa2pCNmhuZS1RZC1fb25UZ0xmZTZ5ZHpwX2hvcnhjSmdiRlowX0QxSTgzdnlzVlZQcW9INTR4SGxkNUV0X1pHQVpqR0pDZ2xidkkwbU42QWFkLWd4bXJ1RWc2T2FfUUR4S3VPUGpLZGVoNy1wekRkaDI1WWxlV0I3UzV2QzFnT0tNajQ1SzR6Nm0xOFlXdzJPRElfZnVXc3lfWVMtVldULXVidzJpY2tnMThxSEtReE4xWFZKUmJuWlNsVkdraEVkTFJZdmJxU0hIbmQwTVR3SW5zN3VaOE5mYVFheXoyNWozNjlfWlRPTmtLWUo3Q19zZ1BlMXdJeTMwdVRmOTZkUm9LZnlnTHZjbdIBlgJBVV95cUxNeW1tXy1UWkU4OGgyQkJENVVTX2ZnWEZYVUpiTW4yT25UcDBvMFhmY2VQMzVXeGFIZUdmbmNfakQ5VkNjamM1V2VCZkVlZjZGeGpSX2didnNWWHNqQkxYMzZNTG5mMl96ZWtEbDRlYnJhWUl6Q0hVUmxBdmtXdDNmVVlHeEtlYnVVWDJJVXVRR081aC1GX2p2Ql85bU9HLUdwd2xrdmRRUnNFMGZyU1F1TzBTSW1rRUMtSUpBOFFrRnMzQmVmR0pqTWRXVEYzUkRMeWl4bkI1d3pfNnlRU2NiZlU0TENNTkNySnB1LWhkQXVzS2NIVHBCdDRiZUJIbURtbWNTVml3cThTT0Fza3pxSVlZaWtxUQ</guid></item><item><title>天主教影响者5岁的儿子在11天的流感战斗后死亡，随后有数千人死亡-福克斯新闻</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/health/catholic-influencers-5-year-old-son-dies-after-11-day-flu-battle-followed-thousands</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;&lt;div class="featured featured-video video-ct" data-v-324c3b57&gt; &lt;div class="contain" data-v-324c3b57&gt;   &lt;div class="info" data-v-324c3b57&gt;&lt;div class="caption" data-v-324c3b57&gt; &lt;p data-v-324c3b57&gt;Fox News senior medical analyst Dr. Marc Siegel joins 'America's Newsroom' to discuss the severe flu season, rising hospitalizations and updated obesity criteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div id="beyondwords-wrapper" class="beyondwords-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="info"&gt;&lt;span class="label-bg"&gt;NEW&lt;/span&gt;You can now listen to Fox News articles!
  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="speakable"&gt;A Catholic influencer announced Thursday that his 5-year-old son had died after an 11-day battle with a &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/respiratory-health/cold-and-flu" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;severe case of the flu&lt;/a&gt;, a loss that unfolded publicly as he shared updates almost daily online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="speakable"&gt;Paul J. Kim, who shares faith-based content with more than 300,000 followers &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DS-hIiekZBe/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;on Instagram&lt;/a&gt;, said his son Micah died on New Year’s Eve. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an emotional video posted Thursday, Kim thanked supporters &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/faith-values/faith" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;for their prayers&lt;/a&gt; and asked for privacy as his family grieves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are so proud of him," Kim said in the video. "I want to thank you from the bottom of my heart, as his dad, on behalf of my family, for all the ways you guys &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/faith-values" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;prayed and lifted us up&lt;/a&gt; during this time. It’s been the hardest thing I’ve ever been through in my life, and it continues to be."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim first shared news of Micah’s illness Dec. 21, when he posted that his son was being taken to a hospital by ambulance after a medical emergency. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/aggressive-new-flu-variant-sweeps-globe-doctors-warn-severe-symptoms" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;‘AGGRESSIVE’ NEW FLU VARIANT SWEEPS GLOBE AS DOCTORS WARN OF SEVERE SYMPTOMS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The young boy was taken by ambulance Dec. 21 to a hospital. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In subsequent updates, Kim said doctors described Micah’s illness as an unusually severe case of the flu. Kim later told followers that Micah had been placed on life support and urged people to pray. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In later updates, he revealed that the flu infection had turned septic and triggered seizures. At the time, Kim said doctors described the case as &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research/rare-diseases" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;rare and serious&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a Dec. 30 update, Kim said his son’s condition had worsened and that Micah was in a coma as doctors and &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/education/parents" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;family members&lt;/a&gt; worked to give him as much time as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/record-breaking-flu-numbers-reported-new-york-state-sparking-warnings-from-officials" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RECORD-BREAKING FLU NUMBERS REPORTED IN NEW YORK STATE, SPARKING WARNINGS FROM OFFICIALS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to recent data, the CDC reported 288 pediatric flu deaths in the recent 2024-25 season.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/media/influencers" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Kim’s posts&lt;/a&gt;, some of which showed Micah in the hospital, were viewed millions of times. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Throughout the ordeal, Kim referred to his son as a fighter and "my hero."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a written Instagram post, he quoted Job 1:21, "The Lord gave, and the Lord has taken away; blessed be the name of the Lord" and said Micah had entered "the never-ending glory, love, and peace of God." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He added that while his family’s hearts are broken, they continue to &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/christianity" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;rely on their faith&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim also asked followers to pray for his family as they learn "how to live by faith and not by sight." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/entertainment/celebrity-trainer-says-tennessee-community-saved-his-5-year-old-daughter-during-cancer-battle" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CELEBRITY TRAINER SAYS TENNESSEE COMMUNITY SAVED HIS 5-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER DURING CANCER BATTLE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="image-ct inline"&gt; &lt;div class="info"&gt;&lt;div class="caption"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kim first shared news of his son's illness Dec. 21. &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;(iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to recent data, the CDC reported 288 pediatric deaths in the 2024-25 season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This has been a record high for a non-pandemic year, mostly among unvaccinated kids, with 70% having underlying conditions like asthma. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition, a new so-called "super flu" strain has emerged this season, a mutation of influenza A H3N2 called subclade K. It's highly contagious and aggressive and is sweeping the nation this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS?pid=AppArticleLink&amp;amp;af_dp=foxnewsaf%3A%2F%2F&amp;amp;af_web_dp=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.foxnews.com%2Fapps-products" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CLICK HERE TO DOWNLOAD THE FOX NEWS APP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On average, around 20,000 children under 5 are said to be hospitalized annually, with younger children (under 6 months) facing the highest mortality risk, highlighting the importance of annual vaccination, according to &lt;a class="H23r4e" href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/highrisk/children.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;the CDC.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kim did not immediately respond to Fox News Digital’s request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fox News Digital's Angelica Stabile contributed to this report.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;div class="article-meta"&gt;&lt;div class="author-bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emma Bussey is a breaking news writer for Fox News Digital. Before joining Fox, she worked at The Telegraph with the U.S. overnight team, across desks including foreign, politics, news, sport and culture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fox News</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 01:36:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxPZ180QXROZGtuZnFnTlExdnUwcXBraGFyQjNwX01pVWNIWXIwRnRlamRuSjJJVktUNTJxNFItQ3ZJYURDcUQ1UjI2aEE1ckszQzVqUWV2SjJWbWFUdHRoUUJ6Y3docE13OXlUY2R4NkVsb2RTeTB2T3oxSWFlQlZQamdha0tZVGlVUG5UMkQ1OEpkVmUwSDNZS1pQUGE4RGw5cWp1cTJUcGxKQmw2VVY4UVlKTzPSAboBQVVfeXFMUFJHMU0wVkM3ZF9sUjFaZHA5dVpyZnVuSWV5NURxR2EwQVVPMHJDVmhiRkZzTEpGNS1IWDE0U0R4NmJ2TjJ2VTl2YVRfWkZqRzlIbGJxMmxQUkUxV01YczYwZE40eE8zN08xSVg1OFRtS3djUEszWGRZRVJYVEc2OEphWWxoVktaekRpX0NXR2o0eEZVcGdESS01QllTLVEtVUJGUG5YS1NfM2RlWXFELV9WX2NGZnNqWGxn</guid></item><item><title>英国各地开始为NHS儿童接种水痘疫苗- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cgexe201n81o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Chickenpox vaccines for young children start across UK&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Philippa Roxby and Smitha Mundasad&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;Health reporters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f527/live/35a82830-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f527/live/35a82830-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f527/live/35a82830-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f527/live/35a82830-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f527/live/35a82830-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f527/live/35a82830-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f527/live/35a82830-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f527/live/35a82830-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A young toddler looks up at a doctor who is holding a vaccine while rubbing a piece of cotton wool on his arm. The toddler is wearing a green and white striped T-shirt and is sitting on his father's knee, who is also wearing a green top." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;All young children in the UK can now be offered protection against chickenpox for the first time on the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The vaccine will be combined with the existing MMR jab, given at 12 and 18 months of age, which already helps protect against measles, mumps and rubella. Children up to the age of six can catch up on doses when invited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Experts say the new, combined vaccine called MMRV, where V stands for varicella - another name for chickenpox - is expected to reduce the many thousands of families affected by the infection each year and prevent the most severe cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Until now, parents have had to pay up to £200 to buy a vaccine privately to protect their children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;From 1 January, the MMRV vaccine will be introduced into the standard list of children's vaccinations in England, Wales and Northern Ireland, with Scotland announcing&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cn0rnqj52y5o" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt; a rollout start date in early January&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Chickenpox is very common in young children. The main feature is an itchy, spotty rash which blisters then scabs over. It can be painful, and cover the body from head to toe. Children often feel unwell for several days, with a fever and muscle aches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It also spreads easily. Some 90% of children under the age of 10 catch chickenpox at some point, and a week off school or nursery is fairly common. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But it can develop into something more severe, warns Dr Gayatri Amirthalingam, deputy director of immunisation at the UK Health Security Agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"For some babies, young children and even adults, chickenpox can be very serious, leading to hospital admission and tragically, while rare, it can be fatal," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Complications can include bacterial infection of scabs, and much more rarely, a swelling of the brain known as encephalitis, lung inflammation known as pnemonitis, and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Young babies and adults are more likely to be seriously ill with the infection. Pregnant women are particularly at risk because of potential complications in both the mother and unborn baby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'My daughter is still living with the pain, 14 years on'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/1fb0/live/da0883f0-e59e-11f0-8bbe-6935d94eeebc.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/1fb0/live/da0883f0-e59e-11f0-8bbe-6935d94eeebc.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1fb0/live/da0883f0-e59e-11f0-8bbe-6935d94eeebc.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/1fb0/live/da0883f0-e59e-11f0-8bbe-6935d94eeebc.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/1fb0/live/da0883f0-e59e-11f0-8bbe-6935d94eeebc.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/1fb0/live/da0883f0-e59e-11f0-8bbe-6935d94eeebc.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/1fb0/live/da0883f0-e59e-11f0-8bbe-6935d94eeebc.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1fb0/live/da0883f0-e59e-11f0-8bbe-6935d94eeebc.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Maria Horton A mum and teenage daughter smiling, sitting in front of a redbrick building, with a window in the background. The mother wears a black and white striped t-shirt and the daughter wears a navy blue t-shirt with white logo. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Maria Horton&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Beth's mum Maria says she would have given her daughter the vaccine if it had been available 14 years ago&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Maria Horton's daughter, Beth, was just two-and-a-half years old when she had a stroke in the weeks after getting chickenpox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She collapsed and her arm and leg went all floppy and then she started to have a seizure," Ms Horton, who lives in Plymouth, said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Beth has had to live with many of the consequences ever since - she can't use her right hand, has speech difficulties and lives in pain, her mother said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I know some people are hesitant about vaccines but if I'd known years ago what I know now, I wouldn't hesitate to give her the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"As a mum, if you could go back in time and stop something catastrophic happening to them, you absolutely would.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"And if I could prevent somebody else from going through what Beth did, that would be amazing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Claire Fuller, NHS England's national medical director, said providing protection against chickenpox was "a hugely positive moment for children and their families".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Health Secretary Wes Streeting urged all parents to take up the offer of the vaccine, describing the rollout as a "historic milestone in protecting our children's health" from a disease that "sends thousands to hospital every year".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The MMRV vaccine has been safely used for decades in other countries such as the United States, Canada, Australia and Germany, which have all seen decreases in the number of people getting chickenpox and fewer serious cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The part of the vaccine which protects against chickenpox has been shown to be very effective - around 97% after two doses - and long-lasting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The UK has been lagging behind for various reasons. There were concerns over the costs of a UK-wide vaccination programme and a potential rise in cases of shingles - when the chickenpox virus is reactivated in adulthood - but that has not been found to be an issue after many years of vaccination in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Recent research also shows the scale of the impact of chickenpox on children and the NHS. An estimated £24 million in income and productivity is lost every year in the UK due to chickenpox in childhood, NHS England says. It also calculates that the vaccine rollout could save £15 million a year in NHS treatment costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;For all those reasons, the Joint Committee on Vaccination and Immunisation (JCVI), which advises UK health departments, recommended the introduction of the vaccine on the NHS in November 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Families will save both time and money - no longer facing lost income from taking time off work or having to fork out for private vaccinations," Streeting said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health said it was "welcome news" that a vaccine was being rolled out across the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Meanwhile the Royal College of GPs said all NHS childhood vaccines were safe and effective, adding that jabs were "some of the most important health interventions parents can make for their children".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;Who can get a chickenpox vaccine, and when?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 GunZh"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d786/live/9613feb0-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d786/live/9613feb0-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d786/live/9613feb0-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d786/live/9613feb0-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d786/live/9613feb0-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d786/live/9613feb0-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d786/live/9613feb0-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d786/live/9613feb0-e5a6-11f0-b84b-6d40b6925787.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Close-up of a spot-covered chest of a young boy with chickenpox - the spots are red and blistered, covering his torso, neck and chin" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Protection against chickenpox is offered in a new, combined vaccine called MMRV, which will replace the current MMR jab. This combined jab helps protect against measles, mumps, rubella and varicella (chickenpox).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;b id="children-born-after-1-january-2026" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;Children born after 1 January 2026 &lt;/b&gt;will be automatically offered two doses of the MMRV vaccine at 12 months and 18 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A catch-up programme will offer one or two doses to older children, depending on their date of birth:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 diUlgm"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;children born &lt;b id="on-or-after-1-january-2025" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;on or after 1 January 2025&lt;/b&gt; will be offered two doses, one at 12 months and one at 18 months&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;children born &lt;b id="between-1-july-2024-and-31-december-2024" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;between 1 July 2024 and 31 December 2024&lt;/b&gt; will be offered two doses, one at 18 months and another at the age of 3 years and 4 months&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;children born &lt;b id="between-1-september-2022-and-30-june-2024" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;between 1 September 2022 and 30 June 2024&lt;/b&gt; will be offered one dose at 3 years and 4 months&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 cRgahm"&gt;children born &lt;b id="between-1-january-2020-and-31-august-2022" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;between 1 January 2020 and 31 August 2022&lt;/b&gt; will be offered a single dose later in 2026&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Children aged six or older on the last day of 2025 will not be eligible for the MMRV because they are likely to already have had a chickenpox infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;GP surgeries will contact families to arrange an appointment when the vaccinations are due.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 00:31:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5YTlh6RHNBeDNSc0V0TWNrSXJ2a0dMLTRfTmJtN211cWhnb0ZHZ2hXX2RCWUpzUkhmQkpSME9GSExWRDJDNF9rZ2dTM2dVMS0xV19wbkZyUjdsQdIBX0FVX3lxTE5CWHI0ekY1XzRGUEowZlMtRUZBQ1VrSVFsekNqN2tBc3ZNZHdmel9hcVM0WnFuOS1ZclIyaHBWTklLRlFzZ2IxR2thMUU3NHhNNTRCcldnNVp0bzZqR3BB</guid></item><item><title>犹他州麻疹病例在全国持续爆发期间上升至156例- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51426212/utah-measles-cases-rise-to-156-amid-ongoing-national-outbreak</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;SALT LAKE CITY — Utah health officials say the state's ongoing outbreak of measles remains on the rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In their latest update on Tuesday, the &lt;a href="https://epi.utah.gov/measles-response/" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Utah Department of Health and Human Services&lt;/a&gt; reported 156 confirmed cases of the highly contagious virus across the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's an increase of just over a dozen infections since their Dec. 23 update. DHHS also noted that 40 Utahns have been diagnosed with measles over &lt;a href="https://www.ksl.com/article/51416341/utah-has-a-115-confirmed-cases-of-measles-with-latest-infection-at-bingham-high" rel="follow" target="_blank"&gt;the past three weeks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Southwest Utah Health District leads the state's case count with 114 confirmed infections, followed by the &lt;a href="https://www.ksl.com/article/51422706/6-new-measles-cases-reported-in-utah-county" rel="follow" target="_blank"&gt;Utah County Health District&lt;/a&gt; with 16, and the Wasatch County Health District, which has a total of 9 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Utah's rise in measles cases is just a glimpse of the virus's impact across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though, the Utah-Arizona border, as well as the upstate region of South Carolina, which have all seen ongoing outbreaks of the virus have continuously added to the dozens of reported cases each week, &lt;a href="https://corecms.ksl.com/tools/cms/article/51425709" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;CNN reports&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Tuesday, there have been 2,065 confirmed measles cases reported in the United States, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;Centers for Disease Control&lt;/a&gt;. A higher annual total of infections than the country had seen in decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Utah-Arizona border accounts for more than 350 cases reported between the two states alone in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the 2,065 measles cases across the U.S., 11% of those have resulted in hospitalizations; with three confirmed deaths due to the illness, the CDC reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last time the country had 2,000 cases of measles reported in one year was in 1992, which was a couple of years after health leaders updated recommendations to say that children should get two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella (MMR) vaccine instead of just one, CNN reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past quarter-century, measles has been considered eliminated in the United States. Since 2000, no outbreaks or other chains of transmission have lasted longer than a year. But now multiple large outbreaks in 2025 may be connected, which puts the elimination status at risk, if cases continue to grow through late January, according to CNN.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC,  measles is one of the most contagious diseases known, but the MMR vaccine offers effective protection. Health officials state that one dose of the vaccine is 93% effective against measles infection and a second dose provides 97% protection against the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the CDC said vaccination rates have been on the decline for several years, especially among young children. During the 2024-25 school year, only 92.5% of incoming kindergarten students have received the MMR vaccine, which is below the 95% threshold, health officials say, is necessary to alleviate outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the 156 individuals in Utah who contracted measles in 2025, the DHHS said 140 of those were not vaccinated. Nine of those were vaccinated and seven patients' vaccination status was unknown, &lt;a href="https://files.epi.utah.gov/Utah%20measles%20dashboard.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;according to the department's website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 23:23:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQOXZrVldDVzk0RXFjOEVjZW1XTHhuMWxqYzJUSHgyQXV1bE1nMVNlSW1FdFgyS0ZFc09lVVBWZTZtOUFOVk8yem5qdERkanZIWW9CYUgzNFhZRXZoNG1CaWlDUF9nNlRrNGt1QmFsSmJPN0E4a19Rc2hSSkx0dy1RVGpISVMtdGI4cng3WnNuVzZHWTZKY3B0NmtfNkxTT2s</guid></item><item><title>营养师制定的7天高蛋白饮食计划，帮助您减掉内脏脂肪- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/7-day-high-protein-meal-plan-to-lose-visceral-fat-11869529</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table-wrapper"&gt;
&lt;table class="mntl-sc-block-universal-table__table"&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;colgroup span="1"&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Day&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;1&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;2&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;3&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;4&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;5&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;6&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;7&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody data-check="0"&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Meals&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; High-Protein Strawberry &amp;amp; Peanut Butter Overnight Oats&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Chopped Salad with Chicken &amp;amp; Creamy Chipotle Dressing&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Sheet-Pan Salmon &amp;amp; Shaved Brussels Sprouts&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; High-Protein Breakfast Casserole &amp;amp; pear&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Spinach &amp;amp; Strawberry Meal-Prep Salad&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Creamy Spinach &amp;amp; Artichoke Chicken Skillet&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; High-Protein Breakfast Casserole &amp;amp; pear&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Spinach &amp;amp; Strawberry Meal-Prep Salad&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Charred Shrimp, Pesto &amp;amp; Quinoa Bowls&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; High-Protein Breakfast Casserole &amp;amp; pear&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Spinach &amp;amp; Strawberry Meal-Prep Salad&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Garlicky White Bean &amp;amp; Kale Stew&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; High-Protein Breakfast Casserole &amp;amp; pear&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Spinach &amp;amp; Strawberry Meal-Prep Salad&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Baked Halibut with Brussels Sprouts &amp;amp; Quinoa&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; Breakfast Beans with Microwave-Poached Egg&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Lemony Orzo &amp;amp; Tuna Salad with Broccoli&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Garlic-Thyme Chicken with Green Beans &amp;amp; Rice&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breakfast:&lt;/b&gt; Breakfast Beans with Microwave-Poached Egg&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Lunch:&lt;/b&gt; Lemony Orzo &amp;amp; Tuna Salad with Broccoli&lt;br&gt;-------- &lt;b&gt;Dinner:&lt;/b&gt; Roasted Root Veggies &amp;amp; Greens over Spiced Lentils&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Daily Totals&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1500&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 72 g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 98 g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 128 g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 32 g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1224 mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1509&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 78 g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 93 g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 118 g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 30 g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1418 mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1475&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 72 g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 92 g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 127 g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 32 g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1578 mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1492&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 66 g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 81 g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 156 g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 41 g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1701 mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1508&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 72 g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 92 g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 137 g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 37 g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1564 mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1478&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 64 g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 84 g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 153 g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 32 g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1626 mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;&lt;b&gt;Calories:&lt;/b&gt; 1516&lt;br&gt;&lt;b&gt;Fat:&lt;/b&gt; 71 g &lt;b&gt;Protein:&lt;/b&gt; 81 g &lt;b&gt;Carb:&lt;/b&gt; 149 g &lt;b&gt;Fiber:&lt;/b&gt; 40 g &lt;b&gt;Sodium:&lt;/b&gt; 1319 mg&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 1 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1500 calories, 72 g fat, 98 g protein, 128 g carbohydrates, 32 g fiber, 1224 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (331 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Morning Snack (186 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (424 calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Afternoon Snack (122 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (436 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,800 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 4 servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dark-chocolate-cashew-clusters-8411318" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Dark Chocolate Cashew Clusters&lt;/a&gt; as an evening snack
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Increase dinner serving to 1 ½ servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/sheet-pan-salmon-shaved-brussels-with-lemon-garlic-drizzle-8769908" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Sheet-Pan Salmon &amp;amp; Shaved Brussels Sprouts&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 2 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1509 calories, 78 g fat, 93 g protein, 118 g carbohydrates, 30 g fiber, 1418 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (411 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Morning Snack (159 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;½ cup plain Greek yogurt, low-fat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 cup raspberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon ground flaxseeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (374 calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Afternoon Snack (95 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (470 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,800 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 4 servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dark-chocolate-cashew-clusters-8411318" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Dark Chocolate Cashew Clusters&lt;/a&gt; as an evening snack
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Reduce raspberries to ½ cup and remove ground flaxseeds from morning snack. Increase dinner serving to 1 ½ servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/creamy-spinach-artichoke-chicken-skillet-8725666" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Creamy Spinach &amp;amp; Artichoke Chicken Skillet&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 3 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1475 calories, 72 g fat, 92 g protein, 127 g carbohydrates, 32 g fiber, 1578 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (411 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Morning Snack (159 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;½ cup plain Greek yogurt, low-fat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 cup raspberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon ground flaxseeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (374 calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Afternoon Snack (95 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_84-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (436 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_87-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_88-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,800 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 4 servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dark-chocolate-cashew-clusters-8411318" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Dark Chocolate Cashew Clusters&lt;/a&gt; as an evening snack
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_89-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_90-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Increase dinner serving to 1 ½ servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/274095/charred-shrimp-pesto-quinoa-bowls/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Charred Shrimp, Pesto &amp;amp; Quinoa Bowls&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_91-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_92-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 4 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1492 calories, 66 g fat, 81 g protein, 156 g carbohydrates, 41 g fiber, 1701 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_94-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_95-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (411 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_96-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_98-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_99-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Morning Snack (184 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_100-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_101-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;½ cup plain Greek yogurt, low-fat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 cup raspberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 tablespoon ground flaxseeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_102-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_103-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (374 calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_104-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_106-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_107-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Afternoon Snack (95 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_108-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_110-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_111-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (428 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_112-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_114-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_115-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,800 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 4 servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dark-chocolate-cashew-clusters-8411318" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Dark Chocolate Cashew Clusters&lt;/a&gt; as an evening snack
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_116-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_117-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Increase dinner serving to 1 ½ servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/garlicky-white-bean-kale-stew-with-lemon-11835743" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Garlicky White Bean &amp;amp; Kale Stew&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_118-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_119-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 5 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_120-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1508 calories, 72 g fat, 92 g protein, 137 g carbohydrates, 37 g fiber, 1564 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_121-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_122-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (411 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_123-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_125-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_126-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Morning Snack (222 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_127-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_128-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;½ cup plain Greek yogurt, low-fat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 cup raspberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 tablespoons ground flaxseeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_129-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_130-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;  &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (374 calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_131-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_133-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_134-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Afternoon Snack (95 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_135-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_137-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_138-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (406 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_139-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_141-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_142-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,800 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 4 servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dark-chocolate-cashew-clusters-8411318" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Dark Chocolate Cashew Clusters&lt;/a&gt; as an evening snack
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_143-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_144-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Increase dinner serving to 1 ½ servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/276964/baked-halibut-with-brussels-sprouts-quinoa/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Baked Halibut with Brussels Sprouts &amp;amp; Quinoa&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_145-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_146-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 6 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_147-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1478 calories, 64 g fat, 84 g protein, 153 g carbohydrates, 32 g fiber, 1626 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_148-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_149-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (364 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_150-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_152-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_153-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Morning Snack (186 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_154-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_156-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_157-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (345 calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_158-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_160-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_161-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Afternoon Snack (122 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_162-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_164-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_165-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (461 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_166-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_168-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_169-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,800 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 4 servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dark-chocolate-cashew-clusters-8411318" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Dark Chocolate Cashew Clusters&lt;/a&gt; as an evening snack
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_170-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_171-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Increase dinner serving to 1 ½ servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/garlic-thyme-chicken-with-green-beans-rice-11710140" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Garlic-Thyme Chicken with Green Beans &amp;amp; Rice&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_172-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-day-7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_173-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Day 7 &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_174-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily totals&lt;/strong&gt;: 1516 calories, 71 g fat, 81 g protein, 149 g carbohydrates, 40 g fiber, 1319 mg sodium&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_175-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_176-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Breakfast (364 Calories)  &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_177-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_179-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_180-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Morning Snack (172 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_181-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_182-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;½ cup plain Greek yogurt, low-fat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;1 cup raspberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons ground flaxseeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_183-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_184-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Lunch (345 calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_185-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_187-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_188-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Afternoon Snack (182 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_189-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_191-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_192-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Dinner (453 Calories)&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_193-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_195-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_196-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 1,800 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Add 4 servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dark-chocolate-cashew-clusters-8411318" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Dark Chocolate Cashew Clusters&lt;/a&gt; as an evening snack
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_197-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_198-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;To make it 2,000 calories&lt;/strong&gt;: Remove ground flaxseeds from morning snack. Increase dinner serving to 1 ½ servings of&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/257758/roasted-root-veggies-greens-over-spiced-lentils/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; Roasted Root Veggies &amp;amp; Greens over Spiced Lentils&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_199-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_200-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-faq mntl-sc-block-universal-faq"&gt;&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-faqs-551c2222-1c76-4c68-80c3-b6655c0d0d1d"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;h2 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__title"&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;noscript id="universal-faq-noscript_1-0" class="comp universal-faq-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-faq__content mntl-accordion js-accordion"&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="1"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_1-0-section-0"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;s it OK to mix and match meals if there’s one I don’t like?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_1-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes! This meal plan is meant to serve as inspiration. It doesn’t need to be followed exactly to reap the benefits. When choosing recipes, we made sure to check the calories, fiber, protein and sodium to align with the parameters of this plan and be within our sodium limits. If you’re making a recipe swap, it may be helpful to choose a recipe with similar calories, fiber, protein and sodium levels. For more inspiration, check out these delicious&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipes/18045/weight-loss-diet/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; weight loss recipes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="2"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_2-0-section-1"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Can I eat the same breakfast or lunch every day?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_2-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Definitely, it’s fine to eat the same breakfast or lunch every day. The breakfasts range from 350 to 400 calories while the lunches span 350 to 400 calories. These ranges are fairly close, though if you’re closely monitoring your calories or other nutrients, like protein, you may want to adjust a snack or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="accordion__item js-accordion-item " data-ordinal="3"&gt;
&lt;p tabindex="0" class="accordion__header js-accordion-trigger" id="mntl-accordion__item_3-0-section-2"&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-chevron accordion__icon"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-chevron" href="#icon-chevron"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;span class="accordion__title"&gt;Why is there not a 1,200 calorie modification?&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="accordion__body"&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-accordion__content_3-0" class="comp mntl-accordion__content"&gt; &lt;div class="faq-accordion__item-answer"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We no longer provide modifications for 1,200-calorie days in our meal plans. The 2020-2025 Dietary Guidelines for Americans suggests that limiting calories to 1,200 per day is too low for most people to meet their nutritional needs, plus it’s unsustainable for long-term health and well-being.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;noscript id="accordion-noscript_1-0" class="comp accordion-noscript mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_201-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-tips-for-healthy-weight-loss"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_202-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Tips for Healthy Weight Loss &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_203-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although adequate protein plays an important role in weight loss, there are other lifestyle factors that work hand in hand to support lasting results. These include:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_204-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_205-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regular exercise&lt;/strong&gt;: While &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-protein-and-its-benefits-11732679" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt; provides the building blocks your muscles need to grow and function properly, exercise is the trigger that stimulates muscle growth and helps your body use that protein effectively. For this reason, it’s recommended to do strength training exercises at least twice a week to boost muscle and metabolic health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; You should also participate in 150 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic exercise each week. This includes walking, dancing, biking or water aerobics.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good quality sleep&lt;/strong&gt;: Diet and exercise may be important, but if you aren’t getting enough sleep, you may not see the weight loss results you desire. Studies show that inadequate sleep is linked to increased cravings, particularly for foods high in carbohydrates and fat.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Aim for at least 7 to 9 hours of sleep each night.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stress management&lt;/strong&gt;: If you feel like you’ve tried everything to lose weight and nothing is working, managing stress may be the missing piece to the puzzle. Chronic stress exposes your body to high levels of cortisol, which is linked to the development of obesity.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Try meditation, breath work, therapy, socialization or getting regular fresh air and sunshine to help reduce stress levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_206-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_207-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-generic" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__heading"&gt;How We Create Meal Plans&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Registered dietitians thoughtfully create EatingWell’s meal plans to be easy-to-follow and delicious. Each meal plan meets specific parameters depending on the health condition and/or lifestyle goal it is targeting and is analyzed for accuracy using the nutrition database, ESHA Food Processor. As nutritional needs differ from person to person, we encourage you to use these plans as inspiration and adjust as you see fit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOQTNJdFUzcWEzZDZMSnhibU43WGJhcmhTYXIzcEo1c0F1Rkd0RUFlNk5HVk5QZm00YW8wUU15TnNPcWNkakhUZkxnQzZiaFNJUGdaRTF2VDU4V3V6c1dGRC05OEgzT2hkQmF1WFVLVDd3bnF1TExjTm1HdG5uRVZqbmstTU14eUFLdXR4R0NR</guid></item><item><title>天主教影响者5岁的儿子在感染流感后死亡- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/catholic-influencers-5-year-old-son-dies-contracting-flu-rcna251834</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1f77b2" class="body-graf"&gt;A Catholic influencer said Thursday that his 5-year-old son died from a severe case of the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a512d4" class="body-graf"&gt;Paul Kim, who posts videos about his Catholic faith and has more than 300,000 followers on Instagram, said in a video on Instagram that his son, Micah, died on New Year’s Eve after “fighting 11 long, hard days.” Previously, &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DS3vY0XjRe-/" target="_blank"&gt;Kim said on Instagram&lt;/a&gt; that his son was hospitalized after contracting a severe case of the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8e0f91" class="body-graf"&gt;“We are so proud of him. I want to thank you from the bottom of my heart, as his dad, on behalf of my family, for all the ways you guys prayed and lifted us up during this time,” Kim said in the video. “This incredibly difficult, impossible time for our family. It’s been the hardest thing I’ve ever been through in my life, and it continues to be.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d12275" class="body-graf"&gt;On Dec. 21, Kim &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DSjAAswjuSX/" target="_blank"&gt;posted on Instagram&lt;/a&gt; that his son was heading to the hospital in an ambulance after “having a medical emergency.” The next day, he posted an update on Instagram saying Micah was on life support and asked for prayers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-670532" class="body-graf"&gt;In an &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/DS3vY0XjRe-/" target="_blank"&gt;update on Dec. 30&lt;/a&gt;, Kim said his son had a severe case of the flu, which caused the child to go septic and experience seizures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1772d5" class="body-graf"&gt;“The doctors are saying it’s one of the most horrific cases of this virus that they have ever seen in their life. It’s very rare, what happened to my son,” Kim said. “Rest assured, he needs a miracle.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0fd335" class="body-graf"&gt;Kim posted updates nearly daily since then, several including videos of the 5-year-old unconscious in the hospital. In Thursday’s video, Kim said his son was in a coma before he died and that “his soul was already with the Lord.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a5511a" class="body-graf"&gt;“In many ways, we were fighting for Micah to buy him as much time as possible, until he passed,” he said. “As a father, that is my duty. I was called to do that. Even if in God’s ultimate will it wasn’t meant for him to recover.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f5dcae" class="body-graf"&gt;Kim said in the Thursday video that his account has been viewed more than 50 million times in the last few weeks since his son’s hospitalization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-62608b" class="body-graf"&gt;The influencer is now asking for privacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4b2a79" class="body-graf"&gt;“Micah is already in heaven at work, seriously. So many testimonies, so many ways in which God is using the light in my 5-year-old to truly save souls and change the world,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f5e3c0" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;The 5-year-old’s death comes as the &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/flu-season-virus-symptoms-surge-nationwide-variants-vaccines-children-rcna251534" target="_blank"&gt;flu surges&lt;/a&gt; across the U.S., with &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/flu-season-states-severity-new-variant-k-vaccines-kids-rcna250056" target="_blank"&gt;young children hit particularly hard&lt;/a&gt; by the respiratory illness. Roughly 3,100 people have died from the flu this season, including five children, according to data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 21:42:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQeWwzS2d5LVFCNVlIVVF4YW5DQUIzalhHM21aQWNCN1VmQWtRcXZGaG5sMkVxX3A1YlRwajdrNmlfRHJVdEd4M3ZoVjdkeGN0Tnp1Q0RoZmw4bFpxZ3AtalhSajBHNkl3V0YxWG8wRzRDSk5iSVFTQTFUZFdkYTZxRVZNdjBtVDMtbGxKejlwWUFGamg2RzQ1NUVRUU9RY0FRc203WnVfUdIBVkFVX3lxTE1SRHJINEk4NDFTTlFtLXduOFF0cmpZY1E2d2k0a09Ecmd1WVJvRU9WbWFXN1pzTkVxb0dvamdfWV9mQXduU1ZaNFNsQU11LVZlZXRQOFpB</guid></item><item><title>天主教发言人保罗·金（ Paul Kim ）的5岁儿子去世-天主教通讯社</title><link>https://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/268791/5-year-old-son-of-catholic-speaker-paul-kim-passes-away</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="col post-content content custom-content-paragraph"&gt;
                      
                    &lt;p class="post-info"&gt;Jan 1, 2026 /
            16:24 pm&lt;/p&gt;
                      &lt;p&gt;Micah Kim, the 5-year-old son of popular Catholic speaker Paul Kim, has passed away, Kim announced in a tearful social media post Thursday afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;Micah died on Wednesday, Dec. 31, 2025, after &lt;a href="https://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/268727/popular-catholic-speaker-pleads-for-a-miracle-amid-son-s-medical-emergency" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow"&gt;more than a week on life support&lt;/a&gt; following a rare medical emergency brought on by a severe case of the flu.&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;“Micah Joseph is beginning the new year basking in the never-ending glory, love, and peace of God,” &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DS-hIiekZBe/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&amp;amp;igsh=MzRlODBiNWFlZA==" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow"&gt;Kim wrote in the post&lt;/a&gt;, which was accompanied by a two-part video. “Micah has been very busy already, as I see the Lord using him and sending him on missions to bring millions of people closer to God.”&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;Kim asked for privacy for his family as they grieve but said he felt he had to provide an update to the millions of people praying for Micah and his family throughout the ordeal. He shared that over the last week and a half, his social media account has been viewed more than 50 million times by people from all over the world offering prayers for the situation.&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;p class="my-4 lightest-grey-bg py-3 body-ad" id="div-gpt-ad-1439931607151-0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;Micah was rushed to the hospital a week and a half ago after experiencing severe internal bleeding and other complications. Kim, a devoted husband and father of six known for his engaging talks on faith and family at Catholic conferences, first alerted followers via social media on Dec. 22: “My son Micah is having a medical emergency right now and headed to the hospital in an ambulance.”&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;By Dec. 24, Micah underwent emergency chest surgery to address the bleeding, which successfully stabilized his heart function. Kim shared on social media that after the surgery, his son’s heart began beating independently and his vital signs remained steady.&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;Doctors gradually reduced life support, with Micah’s lungs showing slow improvement on a ventilator. However, a subsequent MRI revealed severe brain damage, leading physicians to conclude there is “no medical possibility” of recovery.&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;“I couldn’t be a prouder father,” Kim said in his Jan. 1 post. “This reality gives me great joy and hope in the midst of sorrow. Our hearts are broken; but we trust in the Lord. Please pray for my family and me as we learn how to live by faith and not by sight.”&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;p class="my-4 lightest-grey-bg py-3 body-ad" id="div-gpt-ad-1441212700470-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                                    &lt;p&gt;
                
              &lt;/p&gt;
                                              &lt;p&gt;Cardinals, bishops, priests, deacons, and laypeople — including many well-known Catholic media personalities — had messaged Kim and told him they were praying for his son, he said. Kim had prayed the Divine Mercy Chaplet live with followers during the ordeal, and the family had asked for a miracle through the intercession of Venerable Fulton Sheen.&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;In addition to an outpouring of prayer for Micah, a &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/miracle-for-micah-support-the-kim-family" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;GoFundMe campaign&lt;/a&gt; was begun to support the family amid mounting medical costs.&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;“Thank you for all the love, prayers, and compassion that a countless number of you have showed us,” Kim wrote. “May God truly bless you. Your prayers for Micah were answered, but in a different way than what we had all hoped for. God healed and welcomed him into eternal life. He is where we all want to be.”&lt;/p&gt;
                                                          &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Amira Abuzeid contributed to this story.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;p class="my-4 lightest-grey-bg py-3 body-ad" id="div-gpt-ad-1507207562539-0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                                                    
                                
                                &lt;div class="post-author-bottom"&gt;
                              &lt;div class="row"&gt;
                  
                  &lt;p class="col-auto"&gt;Tina Dennelly is senior copy editor for EWTNNews.com. A native of the Chicago area and a graduate of the University of Missouri School of Journalism, during her career she has worked for the Chicago Tribune in its Interactive Media Department, taught journalism classes at Hillsdale College in Michigan, and was copy editor/associate news editor for the National Catholic Register and Faith &amp;amp; Family magazine. After getting married and moving to Long Island, New York, she worked as a freelance copy editor and proofreader for various Catholic book publishers, periodicals, and independent authors while raising four children. She also wrote feature stories for The Long Island Catholic magazine and was a freelance copy editor for CatholicVote. Before joining EWTN in 2022, she was a senior editor of catechetical textbooks for New York-based William H. Sadlier Inc. Tina is currently pursuing a master’s degree in theology from Catholic International University.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Catholic News Agency</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 21:24:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQWFJYRTUxcnNMRWx5YlFGaWFLd0hvTHRyWFNWc09EcWRHMzlVRmFvNVAtNmlPU0VwOURXblQwQXN3bnNoYjkzY0x2WHl2RjdDcm1SSFloQWRNVXozV0d4RDdUY1piRjBDTGZRMExfY0ZZVWdIM0NzS2pnVjhtMlpiem5FY0ZJOFZnSWJ6anFQUDEzZHRzX1JrMnJBTUtac2dDc3JiSNIBqgFBVV95cUxNemVxalJNU25NWm0tTVdvaGVxV2czaEluSWlQZ0lWcVJjZm5OT0lqNm5FMDd2aW9QZksyRHZOVWlHb3kyMGRlQ1VDam14LW1XUzJsSzJNT0xDV25CdEx0TVFZRkFHbjJRTW9tcTNDeEpTLTNzRm5UMG40V3c2WEhRM1QyWTFlQmhRSVVOZDkwbU1xS2RocTVxejhJNVZtVU0tWmROMkFOZm1UZw</guid></item><item><title>粉丝在心爱的VTuber Illy死于囊性纤维化后表示敬意- Dexerto</title><link>https://www.dexerto.com/twitch/fans-pay-respects-after-beloved-vtuber-illy-dies-of-cystic-fibrosis-3299865/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-1"&gt;
&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;Fans of popular VTuber ‘Illy’ are paying their respects after news of the streamer’s death surfaced online from friend and fellow broadcaster ‘Drumsy.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="player-wrapper" class="aspect-16/9 my-4 mb-8 w-full"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;Illy was a well-known Scottish &lt;a class="hover:text-vertical-primary underline decoration-2 underline-offset-4 decoration-vertical-primary" href="https://www.dexerto.com/tag/vtubers/"&gt;VTuber&lt;/a&gt; who was transparent about her struggles with &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow" class="hover:text-vertical-primary underline decoration-2 underline-offset-4 decoration-vertical-primary" href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/cystic-fibrosis"&gt;cystic fibrosis&lt;/a&gt;, a genetic disease that progressively fills the lungs and other organs with mucus, causing breathing problems, infections, and issues absorbing nutrients from food.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;In August 2025, Illy created a fundraiser for her ‘bucket list,’ which included activities like seeing a Vocaloid concert, going to conventions and theme parks, and “throwing a big party” with her friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="mb-[10px] relative"&gt;&lt;p class="Division_custom-division__xywNH wp-block-embed__wrapper external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 id="h-vtuber-illy-dies-after-cystic-fibrosis-struggle-at-23-years-old" class="dark:text-neutral-white font-display font-bold mb-5 external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text text-title-12 lg:text-title-2 wp-block-heading"&gt;VTuber Illy dies after cystic fibrosis struggle at 23 years old&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;On January 1, 2026, fellow content creator Drumsy revealed the news that Illy had died as a result of her cystic fibrosis at 23 years old, saying that she experienced unexpected health complications during the week of Christmas 2025.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;“She was rushed to the hospital,” Drumsy said in a &lt;a class="hover:text-vertical-primary underline decoration-2 underline-offset-4 decoration-vertical-primary" href="https://www.dexerto.com/youtube/"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt; video explaining the situation. “I got a call from her mom letting me know that the doctors said there was nothing else they could do. They kept her medicated and made sure that she wasn’t in pain. She passed away peacefully in her sleep.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="mb-[10px] relative"&gt;&lt;p class="Division_custom-division__xywNH wp-block-embed__wrapper external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;Drumsy went on to reveal that any proceeds from &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow" class="hover:text-vertical-primary underline decoration-2 underline-offset-4 decoration-vertical-primary" href="https://drumsyshop.com/en-usd/products/speed-racing-shirt-white"&gt;the ‘Illy Racing’ shirt&lt;/a&gt; in his merchandise store would go to the Butterfly Trust, a charity that supports sufferers of cystic fibrosis to improve their quality of life and educate the general populace about the condition.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;Illy had wanted to hold a fundraiser for the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow" class="hover:text-vertical-primary underline decoration-2 underline-offset-4 decoration-vertical-primary" href="https://www.butterflytrust.org.uk/about-the-butterfly-trust/"&gt;Butterfly Trust&lt;/a&gt; prior to her death as part of her bucket list, with Drumsy revealing that the organization had paid for her medical treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;Drumsy is also selling a &lt;a target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow" class="hover:text-vertical-primary underline decoration-2 underline-offset-4 decoration-vertical-primary" href="https://drumsyshop.com/products/in-memory-of-illy-poster"&gt;framed poster&lt;/a&gt; of Illy’s VTuber avatar in his store. The proceeds from this poster will go to her mother, who’d been her daughter’s caretaker throughout her life.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;Fans were left heartbroken at the news, sharing their support for Illy’s friends and family and reminiscing on their favorite moments from her broadcasts.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="mb-[10px] relative"&gt;&lt;p class="Division_custom-division__xywNH wp-block-embed__wrapper external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;
&lt;template data-dgst="BAILOUT_TO_CLIENT_SIDE_RENDERING"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;“This was way too soon,” one wrote on YouTube. “I’m sorry, Drumsy. We lost a real one. I hope she’s happy.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;“Illy was by far my favourite because of her personality and doing the dumbest stuff possible with the biggest smile on her face,” another said on X. “Thank you so much, Illy, for being yourself and just doing what you liked and loved.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;To end his video, Drumsy shared an audio recording from Illy during one of their last collaborations together, where she thanked her fans and supporters for rallying around her.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="text-neutral-grey w-full mb-4 text-body-6 md:text-body-5 font-body dark:text-neutral-white external:text-custom-content-text external:dark:text-custom-content-text"&gt;“As dark as things get, and that scary truth that’s looming over me, I can leave something behind thanks to you guys. To the viewers, the producers, the editors, Drumsy… thank you forever.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Dexerto</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 20:13:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQZ2lxX2xqX0Yxd2NKMUd6YzRsTEJjc01zSGl4NHpEc25ia0RDanA1YTV5ZnBzQnlrYXFCUkcyZWpJa2V0Ty1STEdGUkhlTXZvcDM5UnAyVldGTW05RWlGMy1pNUFhU3UwVTJHRW80M1ZFVzFHY2FJcnVzbHQ5ZU1hdzdDNFlLZ0NoSTl3MllaM05URjJhWkFNX29ET04yam9vU2NCR1ZPaXdBRGs</guid></item><item><title>“It Feels Like Me Again” ：世界上第一个手臂外骨骼使中风患者独立-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/it-feels-like-me-again-the-worlds-first-entire-arm-exoskeleton-gives-stroke-patients-independence/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_227565" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-227565" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-227565" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499-1024x629.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499-1024x629.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499-326x200.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499-768x471.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499-356x220.jpg 356w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499-696x427.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499-1068x656.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499-684x420.jpg 684w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499-530x325.jpg 530w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Johanne-Hemnes-using-the-Vilpower-arm-credit-Vilje-Bionics-e1767263816499.jpg 1124w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-227565" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Johanne Hemnes using the Vilpower arm – credit Vilje Bionics&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An exoskeleton for the entire arm has been invented and designed in Norway to help stroke victims recover the use of their arms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It detects and then amplifies tiny movements through the arm and shoulder, and the developers hope to launch it as a fully commercial product this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, more and more people are surviving strokes, and living longer and longer with  disabilities resulting from them. This creates the need for better therapies, accommodations, and regenerative treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://viljebionics.com/vre-brukere"&gt;Vilje Bionics&lt;/a&gt;, the company behind the shoulder-mounted exoskeleton, says that most below-the-elbow prosthetics are for amputees, an few if any exist for victims of partial paralysis—like Johanne Marie Hemnes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2017 Hemnes suffered a brain hemorrhage and collapsed in her living room. The resulting stroke paralyzed her down her left side—usually the result of a stroke in the right half of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All her rehab and focus was on the left leg to ensure she could walk again, and while that was successful, her arm was entirely neglected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I call my arm Jenny, because it feels like it’s not a part of me, because it doesn’t do what I want it to do,” she&lt;a href="https://www.euronews.com/health/2025/11/08/this-is-the-worlds-first-entire-arm-exoskeleton-giving-stroke-patients-more-independence" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; told Euro News&lt;/a&gt;, adding that she even considered cutting it off because it just got in the way. “But when I actually have this on, it feels like me again. It doesn’t just feel like another human being’s arm.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vilje Bionics’ robotic arm assists movements for the shoulder, elbow and hand, which makes it the world’s first exoskeleton for the entire arm. Many of the components were 3D-printed, and Vilje’s founder Saeid Hosseini, says it works by the user “thinking how they’d use their arm.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Because if you think, you make a small movement and then it amplifies that movement,” Hosseini said. “It detects very small movements of a residual movement of a paretic arm and amplifies those movements.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EXOSKELETON INVENTIONS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;40 people have trailed the Vilpower exoskeleton so far, and the company hopes it will be ready in the first 4 to 6 months of 2026 starting in Norway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The robotic arm may be used for rehabilitation purposes in the future, but the company is currently focusing on helping “patients with lasting and significant disabilities to be more independent.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the World Stroke Organization, one in four people will suffer a stroke at some point in their life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hemnes has been able to get used to cutting vegetables and opening bottles again, exactly the kind of independence Hosseini wants his product’s users to be able to reclaim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WATCH the story below… &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
 &lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/VG9doOzB8QQ?si=-8wh2kXYb3Jzbl2I" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt; 
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SHARE This Great Innovation With Your Friends…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 19:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiygFBVV95cUxObjJ6MkpFWkV6VXhmYnVTSFFFTGlsVTYwdllRSUZZbDRQVEp2UnN6cExQQ2tHT2xRSlZuZEE3cUpIbXdDeXVyTk5OWUVzUFRLVzVjbkZlcmItanVaQm9nam13UEdrYXZrRkRJOFhNQkt1czl2QTV6aTJpR1lncUR3dkM3TTA2LXRBQzZvY2hUWm9aa3hlQWZNWE92THhZdHdXNWx6d2hGbnlkRExJMDJBQnYzY3RKQTE3eTREOGhrQXJTa3E1Y3Uwd3pB</guid></item><item><title>在未接种疫苗的旅行者访问Ark Encounter - WDRB后，在肯塔基州检测到麻疹暴露</title><link>https://www.wdrb.com/news/measles-exposure-detected-in-kentucky-after-unvaccinated-traveler-visits-ark-encounter/article_5363a216-76ac-4a0f-b899-b99ea3d42ce1.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;LOUISVILLE, Ky. (WDRB) -- Kentucky health officials are warning the public after a case of measles was confirmed in northern Kentucky earlier this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A post on the Kentucky Department for Public Health's Facebook page said it has "identified potential measles exposures in Grant County, Kentucky." According to the post, the exposure was traced to "an unvaccinated, out-of-state traveler" who stayed at the Holiday Inn &amp;amp; Suites in Dry Ridge from Dec. 28-30. That person also visited the Ark Encounter on Dec. 29.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles, a highly contagious respiratory virus, can cause serious health problems, especially in young children and the elderly. The virus spreads through the air after someone infected coughs or sneezes. It can then linger for up to two hours after the infected person leaves. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virus can also be spread if someone touches surfaces that an infected person has touched.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms include a cough, runny nose and red eyes, followed by white spots that appear on the face and down the body. Two doses of the MMR (measles, mumps and rubella) vaccine is the best protection against measles, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact your healthcare provider if you think you or someone in your family may have been exposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Local News:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/politics/heres-a-look-at-who-s-running-and-what-s-at-stake-in-kentucky-s/article_5d13b267-215a-4a5b-b378-361ab697ff8e.html" target="_blank"&gt;Here's a look at who’s running and what’s at stake in Kentucky’s 2026 elections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="6181" data-end="6433"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/crime-reports/woman-critical-after-shooting-at-american-legion-post-in-parkland-early-thursday/article_4fa05d9b-c356-4f28-946a-23c5e6d8eed9.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woman critical after shooting at American Legion post in Parkland early Thursday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="x_MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/crime-reports/woman-dies-after-shooting-outside-fast-food-restaurant-in-downtown-louisville-near-nulu/article_977afb3b-b61e-4c1c-9330-23d38632bd56.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woman dies after shooting outside fast food restaurant in downtown Louisville near NuLu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="3357" data-end="3568"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/business/contract-details-reveal-when-kentucky-could-seek-repayment-from-blueoval-sk/article_08b61010-b9a6-4b95-aa0a-d26b4948e52d.html" target="_blank"&gt;Contract details reveal when Kentucky could seek repayment from BlueOval SK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="3357" data-end="3568"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/federal-judge-dismisses-consent-decree-meant-to-spark-police-reform-in-louisville/article_1894e619-0355-4d5a-bafb-f0ecb97519cc.html" target="_blank"&gt;Federal judge dismisses consent decree meant to spark police reform in Louisville&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="3357" data-end="3568"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/dozens-of-vacancies-raise-safety-concerns-at-louisville-metro-corrections/article_e7da36c1-ad09-434d-97be-991f733bad68.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dozens of vacancies raise safety concerns at Louisville Metro Corrections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="3357" data-end="3568"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/louisville-doctors-urge-prevention-as-flu-cases-surge-after-the-holidays/article_32d375de-5ee1-4f3d-a6bb-75cf6bb7658d.html" target="_blank"&gt;Louisville doctors urge prevention as flu cases surge after the holidays&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/lmpd-detective-shared-login-to-flock-camera-system-with-dea-agent-conducting-immigration-search/article_03cc732a-3f04-444e-9eee-ad4d2f5dc848.html" target="_blank"&gt;LMPD detective shared login to Flock camera system with DEA agent conducting immigration search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Copyright 2026 WDRB Media. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                &lt;p id="tncms-region-article_bottom_content" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WDRB</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9AFBVV95cUxPTk1XcXhfS1pjS1hQWko0YVBhR05yZVJWeEw5cmY3LVlYaGRoZXY0MTZnUUt5c2Z5TmMxOV92SFFSY1ZNSGlUdnZ5X1BSOVN0TG94MzRoWl9WcVJINWFfWktrY1k3RVZ4Y0x5YkQ3TmFkSi1PN0c4cjZkV3VEVFdUdnZpblpYSFdiWC1sUVpLeFRxdS1QVzZJNUJFMHRQOU4xcXB6Z2FpS1p5b2paRjF6WW5YUkJhQUVFeHg4Z3dGc3BrbUNfdjJRWFk5TU9WNFN0b0tHUTVnZkh4YVMzU3h4ZUFzMnRFU1oyU3kwS3RMdlJjenhh</guid></item><item><title>未接种疫苗的旅客访问Ark Encounter - WDRB后，在肯塔基州检测到可能的麻疹暴露</title><link>https://www.wdrb.com/news/possible-measles-exposure-detected-in-ky-after-unvaccinated-traveler-visits-ark-encounter/article_5363a216-76ac-4a0f-b899-b99ea3d42ce1.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;LOUISVILLE, Ky. (WDRB) -- Kentucky health officials are warning the public of possible measles exposures in northern Kentucky earlier this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A post on the Kentucky Department for Public Health's Facebook page said it "identified potential measles exposures in Grant County." According to the post, the exposure was traced to "an unvaccinated, out-of-state traveler" who stayed at the Holiday Inn &amp;amp; Suites in Dry Ridge from Dec. 28-30." That person also visited the Ark Encounter on Dec. 29.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles, a highly contagious respiratory virus, can cause serious health problems, especially in young children, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/hcp/clinical-overview/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;according to the CDC's website&lt;/a&gt;. The virus spreads through the air after someone infected coughs or sneezes. It can then linger for up to two hours after the infected person leaves. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virus can also be spread if someone touches surfaces that an infected person has touched. Symptoms include a cough, runny nose and red eyes, followed by white spots that appear on the face and down the body. Two doses of the MMR (measles, mumps and rubella) vaccine is the best protection against measles, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact your healthcare provider if you think you or someone in your family may have been exposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More Local News:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/politics/heres-a-look-at-who-s-running-and-what-s-at-stake-in-kentucky-s/article_5d13b267-215a-4a5b-b378-361ab697ff8e.html" target="_blank"&gt;Here's a look at who’s running and what’s at stake in Kentucky’s 2026 elections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="6181" data-end="6433"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/crime-reports/woman-critical-after-shooting-at-american-legion-post-in-parkland-early-thursday/article_4fa05d9b-c356-4f28-946a-23c5e6d8eed9.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woman critical after shooting at American Legion post in Parkland early Thursday&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="x_MsoNormal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/crime-reports/woman-dies-after-shooting-outside-fast-food-restaurant-in-downtown-louisville-near-nulu/article_977afb3b-b61e-4c1c-9330-23d38632bd56.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woman dies after shooting outside fast food restaurant in downtown Louisville near NuLu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="3357" data-end="3568"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/business/contract-details-reveal-when-kentucky-could-seek-repayment-from-blueoval-sk/article_08b61010-b9a6-4b95-aa0a-d26b4948e52d.html" target="_blank"&gt;Contract details reveal when Kentucky could seek repayment from BlueOval SK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="3357" data-end="3568"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/federal-judge-dismisses-consent-decree-meant-to-spark-police-reform-in-louisville/article_1894e619-0355-4d5a-bafb-f0ecb97519cc.html" target="_blank"&gt;Federal judge dismisses consent decree meant to spark police reform in Louisville&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="3357" data-end="3568"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/dozens-of-vacancies-raise-safety-concerns-at-louisville-metro-corrections/article_e7da36c1-ad09-434d-97be-991f733bad68.html" target="_blank"&gt;Dozens of vacancies raise safety concerns at Louisville Metro Corrections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-start="3357" data-end="3568"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/louisville-doctors-urge-prevention-as-flu-cases-surge-after-the-holidays/article_32d375de-5ee1-4f3d-a6bb-75cf6bb7658d.html" target="_blank"&gt;Louisville doctors urge prevention as flu cases surge after the holidays&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/lmpd-detective-shared-login-to-flock-camera-system-with-dea-agent-conducting-immigration-search/article_03cc732a-3f04-444e-9eee-ad4d2f5dc848.html" target="_blank"&gt;LMPD detective shared login to Flock camera system with DEA agent conducting immigration search&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Copyright 2026 WDRB Media. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                &lt;p id="tncms-region-article_bottom_content" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WDRB</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-AFBVV95cUxNOXVvcVV4bFR0Y2M5T1ZFT3dqN2FmWm1iZm1EYW5fX1RrQUctWlBPRTJuV3diMFhCNUpRbXo4MVVRMUdqb29HcWx5amU3UktrTnpUQmx3M0RoeGp1TjdpS1l2NWVNS2NTR0hxX2s5VUJETlpJeW1DMzlQYVRyN1VtZDd6c2RBc0tXaEhuZWF5RXkzQ0Y4OVVXeEVlX2d0SHhLWkZJdS1TVUhzZEJENExmMEFvMG0tZldfWXllcVJReTB6eDZBVW1CM2NFeE5JYmg2RE5SeXk3VzJGUVBnZVlCdm15TTU4U3NKS3d0dzN5aFhoeU9xT0dPSw</guid></item><item><title>适合地中海饮食的5种最佳高蛋白零食- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/best-high-protein-mediterranean-diet-snacks-11874258</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mediterranean-style snacks can support heart health and satiety.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These snacks deliver at least 7 grams of protein per serving.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pairing protein with fiber and healthy fats helps maintain steady energy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When people think of what constitutes a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/our-food-and-nutrition-philosophy-6746110#toc-nutrition-parameters-and-health-considerations" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;, they often imagine a plate full of colorful vegetables, whole grains, and healthy fats, but protein plays an important role, too. While balanced meals are essential to a nutritious diet, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7891453/best-healthy-snacks-according-to-dietitians/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;smart snacking&lt;/a&gt; can contribute key nutrients, help maintain energy levels, and support satiety. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The Mediterranean diet encourages enjoyment and variety while offering several health benefits. Research shows that this way of eating is associated with improved heart health and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/17387/5-tips-to-keep-your-blood-sugar-in-check/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;better blood sugar control&lt;/a&gt;, which are risk factors for conditions like heart disease and type 2 diabetes. Choosing snacks that align with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/291120/mediterranean-diet-for-beginners-everything-you-need-to-get-started/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Mediterranean dietary principles&lt;/a&gt;, which emphasize minimally processed foods, healthy fats, plant-forward ingredients, and lean sources of protein, is a great way to ensure your snack time is nutrient-dense and satisfying.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These five &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/make-ahead-high-protein-snacks-11680376" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;high-protein, low-effort snacks&lt;/a&gt; contain at least 7 grams of protein per serving, and fit seamlessly into the Mediterranean diet (and a busy day!). 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-greek-yogurt-with-berries--walnuts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 1. Greek Yogurt with Berries &amp;amp; Walnuts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Need:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  ½ cup nonfat plain Greek-style yogurt
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  ½ cup berries
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  ¼ cup unsalted walnuts
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein:&lt;/strong&gt; 13–14 grams&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Greek-style yogurt is one of the key components of the Mediterranean diet. It's both high in protein and contains probiotic benefits, which makes it great for snacking. Unlike traditional yogurt, Greek-style yogurt is strained, resulting in a thicker texture and a higher amount of protein. It has also been associated with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290873/how-to-lower-triglycerides-ldl-cholesterol/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;lower levels of triglycerides&lt;/a&gt; and cholesterol, which can decrease the risk of heart disease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Combining the yogurt with other nutritious foods that align with the Mediterranean dietary principles,  such as antioxidant-rich berries and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-nut-for-heart-health-8604884" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;omega-3-packed walnuts&lt;/a&gt;, adds a source of fiber and heart-healthy fats. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-hummus-with-vegetables--whole-wheat-crackers"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 2. Hummus with Vegetables &amp;amp; Whole Wheat Crackers &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Need:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  3 tablespoons&lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/252614/classic-hummus/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt; hummus&lt;/a&gt; (or 1/3 of recipe)
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  2 stalks celery
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  45g reduced-sodium wheat crackers
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein:&lt;/strong&gt; 7–8 grams&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Typically made from chickpeas, tahini, olive oil, and garlic, hummus is a Mediterranean classic. Chickpeas provide a source of plant-based protein and fiber, while tahini contributes healthy fats and minerals. Tahini also contains antioxidants, like sesamin, that have been shown to help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habit-to-break-for-lower-cholesterol-8749670" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;lower both total cholesterol and LDL&lt;/a&gt; (also known as “bad” cholesterol) levels.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Keeping cholesterol levels in a healthy range is important for maintaining heart health and reducing the risk of developing chronic diseases. Pairing hummus with crackers and vegetables also boosts the fiber and nutrient content of this satisfying Mediterranean-inspired snack. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-cottage-cheese-with-tomatoes--herbs"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 3. Cottage Cheese with Tomatoes &amp;amp; Herbs &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Need:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  ½ cup low-fat cottage cheese
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  1/3 cup cherry tomatoes, halved
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  1 tablespoon fresh herbs, chopped
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein:&lt;/strong&gt; 12 grams&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Cottage cheese has grown in popularity due to its versatility. It pairs well with traditional Mediterranean flavors and can easily be transformed into a savory, protein-rich snack. Just a ½ cup of low-fat cottage cheese provides approximately 12 grams of &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/proteins-to-eat-every-week-11684415" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;high-quality protein&lt;/a&gt;, which can help with weight loss and long-term weight maintenance. Because protein takes longer to digest, it helps promote satiety, or feelings of fullness, and may reduce overall calorie intake by keeping hunger at bay in between meals.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Due to their lycopene content, tomatoes regularly may help protect against heart disease by neutralizing inflammation that contributes to plaque buildup in the arteries.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Pairing the cottage cheese with fresh herbs and tomatoes creates a balanced, satiating snack combining protein-rich dairy and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/surprising-antioxidant-rich-foods-you-should-eat-11776388" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;antioxidant-rich vegetables&lt;/a&gt; with flavorful, minimally processed ingredients. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-sardines-on-whole-wheat-toast"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 4. Sardines on Whole-Wheat Toast &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Need:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  1 slice whole wheat toast
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  1 standard can sardine (75g) sardines
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein:&lt;/strong&gt; 22 grams&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://bettrfull.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Nicole Randazzo MA, RD, CDCES&lt;/a&gt; recommends sardines because they provide high-quality protein plus omega-3 fats, specifically EPA and DHA, which support heart health and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-foods-to-fight-inflammation-11762781" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reduce inflammation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “The addition of the whole-grain toast adds fiber for steadier energy,” adds Randazzo. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Sardines are becoming increasingly popular because they’re affordable and minimally processed, making them an accessible way to increase seafood intake. When paired with whole grains, this sardine snack fits perfectly into the Mediterranean diet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-ricotta-toast-with-honey-and-pistachios"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 5. Ricotta Toast with Honey and Pistachios &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Need:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  1 slice whole wheat toast
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  2 tablespoons whole-milk ricotta cheese
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  1 teaspoon honey
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; ·  1 tablespoon chopped pistachios
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein:&lt;/strong&gt; 8-9 grams&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Ricotta cheese provides a creamy texture, a source of protein, and pairs well with both sweet and savory flavors, making it a satisfying base for a Mediterranean-style snack. When spread on whole-wheat toast, it delivers a hearty balance of protein and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290631/what-is-a-complex-carbohydrate/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;complex carbohydrates&lt;/a&gt; that help support steady energy levels. The addition of the pistachios adds a source of heart-healthy monounsaturated fats and plant-based protein, while the drizzle of honey offers natural sweetness without overpowering the dish.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Together, this combination reflects the Mediterranean diet’s emphasis on whole grains, minimally processed ingredients, and nuts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-tips-for-healthy-snacking"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Tips for Healthy Snacking &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Healthy snacking doesn’t have to be complicated; it's all about balance and intention. Start with these simple tips:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_82-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pair protein with fiber:&lt;/strong&gt; Combining protein with fiber-rich foods like fruits, vegetables or whole grains supports fullness and helps to stabilize energy levels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mind portion sizes:&lt;/strong&gt; Remember that snacks are meant to complement meals, not replace them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Include healthy fats:&lt;/strong&gt; Olive oil, nuts, and seeds help to enhance flavor and build out the nutrient profile of your snack.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Plan ahead:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.mycrohnsandcolitisteam.com/writers/683f0deb46c7aa1e0f3349e2" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Avery Zenker, RDN, BASc, MAN&lt;/a&gt; recommends &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/7943165/dietitian-approved-make-ahead-snack-recipes/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;preparing snacks ahead of time&lt;/a&gt; so they're ready to go when you're hungry, which makes healthier choices easier throughout the week. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Include variety:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://holtonnutrition.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="nofollow"&gt;Kara Holton, MS, RDN, LDN, MCHES &lt;/a&gt;suggests "eating a variety of different snacks throughout the week can keep you interested and excited about your food", and can also help you get in all those important nutrients that are helpful for your health overall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_84-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; High-protein snacks can easily fit within the Mediterranean diet when they emphasize whole foods, healthy fats, and variety. From Greek yogurt and legumes to seafood and dairy, these snacks deliver at least 7 grams of protein per serving while supporting heart health and promoting satiety. With thoughtful snack choices, it’s possible to stay energized, support heart health, and enjoy foods that align with the principles of a Mediterranean diet.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNVEF3a3YyLTBuN0dsQnJqMFZWVzduYXhWZEFrWXRrRFQtT1lrNVFESm9TQjZ0b1hKY1p0VFZhMXdVOTlJU29udjBRV3V3R0djM0V0cUJoNTdURll1RXUyTlhEN1ctTXFaWnp0eE5KOG1VVktrWTJvQll6ekZKbTZqZTFPX3p6QQ</guid></item><item><title>流感病例正在上升，导致老年人病情加重-底特律新闻</title><link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/life/wellness/2026/01/01/flu-cases-are-rising-with-a-strain-that-makes-older-people-sicker/87983682007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_dt"&gt;Jan. 1, 2026, 12:59 p.m. ET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Cases of influenza in the United States are rising, driven by a new strain that public health officials worry current vaccines may not protect against as effectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Health officials and researchers say that although the flu season has not reached its peak, the spike in cases is not historically unusual - and they stress vaccines probably still offer protection against the worst effects of the strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The number of hospitalizations, emergency room and outpatient visits, and deaths associated with the flu have shot up, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, although the U.S. isn’t likely to reach peak until early in the year, possibly February.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“It seems to be a bit of a swift increase, but it’s not atypical,” said Jennifer Nuzzo, an epidemiologist and director of the Pandemic Center at the Brown University School of Public Health. “We often see flu seasons come in sort of fast and furious.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Winter creates ideal conditions for airborne viruses such as flu, COVID and RSV to circulate as people gather indoors for long stretches and travel for the holidays. The Northeast is already feeling the surge. On the day after Christmas, New York health officials said the state experienced the highest number of flu cases in a single week since they began tracking the data in 2004.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Since the coronavirus pandemic began in the United States in 2020, winter virus seasons have been marked by waves of covid infections. But COVID in more recent years has become less prevalent during the winter months, researchers say, even if comparing seasons isn’t perfect because fewer patients, doctors and hospitals test for the coronavirus than in years past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The coronavirus does not follow a seasonal pattern, but public health officials urge vaccinations and testing in advance of colder months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Levels of coronavirus tracked in wastewater are lower than during the peak summer wave, said Marlene Wolfe, co-principal investigator for WastewaterSCAN, a private initiative that tracks municipal wastewater data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“There’s plenty of people who are shedding covid into sewer systems when they’re sick, but we aren’t seeing really high levels,” said Wolfe, also an assistant professor of environmental health at Emory University’s Rollins School of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;For the flu, however, the trajectory of cases is expected to keep rising after a sharp uptick in recent weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;It remains unclear whether this winter flu season will rival last year’s, which was considered particularly severe, Nuzzo said. During last year’s flu season, the CDC reported 288 pediatric-influenza-associated deaths, the highest number since the 2009-2010 H1N1 swine flu pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;She said severe flu seasons tend to oscillate, “and that’s probably due to the residual immunity from a previous year.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The CDC estimates there have been at least 4.6 million flu-related illnesses, at least 49,000 hospitalizations and 1,900 deaths this season, which started in late September and may run through March or April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The wrinkle is a new strain of flu. That’s not unusual. The virus constantly mutates through a process known as antigenic drift - the reason vaccine makers reformulate shots each year. The new strain is a version of what is known as H3N2, a type of influenza A, and it’s quickly become the most common one in the U.S., according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The strain has been tied to early and severe flu outbreaks in countries such as Japan, Canada and Britain. Alicia Budd, a CDC epidemiologist who tracks the spread of flu in the U.S., said that while the strain is now common here, flu levels in the U.S. remain within the expected range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“We’re not seeing that increase, that early season that some other countries have seen,” Budd said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The H3N2 strain is typically associated with more flu hospitalizations and deaths in older people. The latest strain popped up during the summer, after U.S. drugmakers finalized their flu shots for the season. Experts worry that means the vaccines could be less effective, leading to more hospitalizations and taxing health systems that must deal with other winter viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In Britain, preliminary data has shown vaccines in that country provide strong protection against the new variant, although shots differ from those in the U.S., experts said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;According to CDC estimates, about 40 percent of U.S. adults have received their flu vaccine, with the number slightly lower for children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Nuzzo, of Brown University, stressed that getting vaccinated remains important, even with the variation. “The flu vaccine may not prevent you from getting flu, but it certainly will keep you out of the hospital and may just reduce the severity of your symptoms or how long you’re sick for,” Nuzzo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In Jacksonville, Florida, pediatrician Pamela Lindor of Bluebird Kids Health has already seen an uptick in children who reported sudden onset of fever, headaches, fatigue and cough while at school. If they are diagnosed within a day or two, she prescribes them antiviral medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Federal health officials under President Donald Trump are casting doubt on childhood vaccine recommendations, suggesting kids receive far too many shots compared with other countries. In early December, Trump ordered a review of the vaccine schedule, questioning the practice of giving children annual flu shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;For years, Lindor said, parents she has encountered have resisted yearly flu shots for their children, even if they agree with other vaccines required by schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“It’s frustrating, in a way, because even though we do see quite a bit of flu this time of year, it could be a lot less if people were more compliant with the flu vaccine,” Lindor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Detroit News</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:59:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0wFBVV95cUxQZFVIX0hVMGtlY0FrSjJZSktfd3U2Ulc0UWg1ekZHaUhyVnBPVy10WUVwdWZZdndORVlmNFpTZjRoZnNhOXc5ampQeVV1c1BOT3hmX190N19jNTBOUDlVajNLVHdBdzlLVmdzZnIyUW1QNEEyNU02V2k2UzV1c1ZPbnJVX1N6bjJyLXNHSmhYVHlIWUFSemczVjZiYnZRYzg2WVBUWWhod1NJVjVBYzRSQUJWMDF6bG1VbFJtODJ4N09EX2xtVFZKdnNoRXozZnJxRndB</guid></item><item><title>麻疹病例达到30年来的最高水平： CDC - NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/measles-highest-level-1992-cdc/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 17:51:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFBnZ0MwODJGaHl4U2JSdEd1cWdpMlk3NUlERUowQVpMTjVGbjYyUFZnUVVsSlJtcjBPMmJOVkRQamU1QjIyT0NPaWNPNWRmNy1tQlBWVUV2VVMzdzExa2ZkNW9ib1E4VDdZc2FKaXpIZ1hiaVFDQkE40gF8QVVfeXFMTkMxclNMQkJXUE1SczlRNUJ1YmExeUZpX1FTeUY0M3NsVEpQcDBsYUd1Q0c4eURqd3RWTE5reS1QWUtMNmJOWXhVVDNHUktPRTNMU2doZ3dlMlhudHhSRHFoNUh5RklGRm1TR08zYzJGVTBVRGlVOEJEaU5QbA</guid></item><item><title>非裔美国人大脑研究中出现了一个关键的阿尔茨海默氏症基因--ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251227004153.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Alzheimer disease (AD) affects African Americans (AA) at roughly twice the rate seen in White or European-ancestry (EA) individuals living in the U.S. Researchers attribute part of this disparity to social and structural factors, including unequal access to health care, differences in educational opportunities, and known biases in cognitive testing. African Americans also have higher rates of health conditions such as cardiovascular disease and diabetes, both of which increase the risk of developing AD.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many previous studies have examined gene expression (measure of the amount of protein encoded by a gene) in brain tissue from people with Alzheimer's compared with those without the disease. However, most of this research focused on EA or mixed-ancestry groups. In many cases, the number of AA participants was either not reported or too small to allow meaningful conclusions about genetic patterns specific to this population.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Largest Brain Study Identifies New Alzheimer's Genes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the largest Alzheimer's study to date using brain tissue from African American donors, scientists at Boston University Chobanian &amp;amp; Avedisian School of Medicine identified numerous genes that behaved differently in people with AD compared with individuals without the disease. Many of these genes had not been previously linked to Alzheimer's by other genetic studies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The strongest signal came from the ADAMTS2 gene. Researchers found that its activity level was 1.5 fold higher in brain tissue from individuals with autopsy-confirmed AD than in tissue from controls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consistent Findings Across Independent Studies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research team analyzed gene expression data from post-mortem prefrontal cortex tissue collected from 207 AA brain donors, including 125 individuals with pathologically confirmed AD and 82 controls. These samples came from 14 NIH-funded AD Research Centers across the United States.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ADAMTS2 stood out as the most significantly differentially expressed gene in this group. It also ranked first in an independent study (&lt;a href="http://medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2024.11.12.24317218v1"&gt;medrxiv.org/content/10.1101/2024.11.12.24317218v1&lt;/a&gt;) conducted by the same researchers using brain tissue from a much larger group of EA individuals. That study compared people with confirmed Alzheimer's pathology who showed clinical symptoms before death with individuals who had the same pathology but remained cognitively resilient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"To our knowledge, this is the first time in similarly designed AD genetics studies that the most significant finding was the same in both white and African Americans," said corresponding author Lindsay A. Farrer, PhD, chief of biomedical genetics at the school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implications for Understanding Alzheimer's Risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers say the findings represent a meaningful advance in understanding the genetic foundations of Alzheimer's risk in African Americans. Previous evidence suggests that most known AD risk variants tend to be population-specific or occur at different frequencies across groups.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Although risk of AD in African Americans has been associated with variants in several genes, the overlap of genes showing association in in EA populations is modest, and even among the overlapping genes the particular variants involved and the size of the effect on AD risk usually differ," explains Farrer. "The fact that expression of ADAMTS2 is significantly and substantially higher in brain tissue from both Whites and Blacks with AD not only points to a shared biological process leading to AD, but also elevates the priority of further research involving this gene which could determine its suitability as a potential therapeutic target."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings were published online in &lt;em&gt;Alzheimer's &amp;amp; Dementia: The Journal of the Alzheimer's Association&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study was supported by National Institute of Health grants R01-AG048927, U01-AG058654, U54-AG052427, U19-AG068753, U01-AG062602, P30-AG072978, U01-081230, P01-AG003949, P30-AG062677, P30-AG062421; P30-AG 066507, P30-AG066511, P30-AG 072972, P30-AG066468, R01-AG072474, RF1-AG066107, U24-AG056270, P01-AG003949 , RF1-AG082339, RF1-NS118584, P30-AG072946; P01-AG003991, P30-AG066444, P01-AG026276, P30-AG066462, P30-AG072958, and P30-AG072978, as well as Florida Department of Health awards 8AZ06 and 20A22. The funding sources had no role in study design, data collection, analysis, interpretation, writing of the article, or the decision to submit it for publication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mark Logue received grants from the NIH and Department of Veterans Affairs. Marla Gearing, Lee-Way Jin, Richard Mayeux, Richard Perrin, Shih-Hsiu Wang and Lindsay Farrer received grants from the NIH. Melissa Murray received grants from NIH, was a paid consultant for Biogen Pharmaceuticals, and served on committees for the Alzheimer's Association and International Conference on Alzheimer's and Parkinson's Diseases. Thor Stein received grants from the NIH and Department of Veterans Affairs, and an honorarium from Brown University. Andrew Teich received grants from the NIH, a contract from Regeneron Pharmaceuticals and an honorarium from Ono Pharmaceuticals, owns stock in Ionis Pharmaceuticals and Biogen Pharmaceuticals, and served on committees for the Department of Defense and the Alzheimer's Association. The effort of Katarnut Tobunluepop and Zihan Wang was supported by NIH grants. Benjamin Wolozin received grants from the NIH, consulting fees from Aquinnah Pharmaceuticals and Abbingworth Ventures, honoraria for several lectures, and owns stock and is Co-Founder and CSO of Aquinnah Pharmaceuticals Inc. Other authors have no competing interests to report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 16:25:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFAyZDBqSmltOFZQcl9scTJZeUtYajVqSjVHR1NKYWZ4ZDNDQjAydV9zUG1VRXRCdDlkSU53bllsNjdyQ1VQb2N3SVBNTWVYeTZVMFEyRTl4S3Z6QzFILVMtbU1PT0hsR1RuV05Na0V2TQ</guid></item><item><title>令人惊讶的面部特征，可以揭示您是否会患上痴呆症-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15425043/facial-feature-dementia-alzheimers-wrinkles-aging.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Wrinkles, especially crow’s feet, may be leading indicators of a person’s risk of developing Alzheimer’s disease later in life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/china/index.html" id="mol-534b97f0-e65f-11f0-8372-cbd839e4644d"&gt;China&lt;/a&gt; determined that looking older than you are created a more than 60 percent higher risk of being diagnosed with dementia, which affects 7 million Americans, over 12 years, even after accounting for factors like health and lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They conducted a second investigation, published in the same report, that found people with the most crow's feet, wrinkles around the eyes, had over double the odds of measurable cognitive impairment than those with the fewest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The perception that old age and wrinkles alone pose a dementia risk may be due to what scientists call Common Pathogenic Mechanisms. The core idea is that facial aging provides a visual estimate of the body's internal biological age and its susceptibility to age-related diseases, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15353809/cause-dementia-risk-Alzheimers-kidney-disease.html"&gt;including those affecting the brain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Looking older than your chronological age is not just about skin-deep wrinkles or sunspots. Instead, it is a visible indicator of your systemic biological age, which may be older than your chronological age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pronounced crow's feet may be a &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15328929/Surprising-new-risk-factor-dementia-discovered-largest-study-33-million-Americans-vulnerable.html"&gt;particularly sensitive biomarker&lt;/a&gt; because they reflect cumulative environmental damage. Heavy sun damage is a source of systemic oxidative stress and inflammation, which are key pathways also implicated in brain aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Crow’s feet also visually represent the skin's biological resilience, or lack thereof. If this thin, vulnerable area shows advanced aging, it may signal that the body's repair mechanisms, such as collagen production and antioxidant defenses, are struggling system-wide, including in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The authors concluded: ‘Facial age (both subjective/perceived and objective) could serve as an indicator and applied into screening strategies for identifying and treating risk population of cognitive decline or dementia in early intervention for older adults.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A major study has found that people who appear older than their actual age face a more than 60 percent greater risk of developing dementia over a 12-year period (stock)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers conducted two distinct studies to build a compelling case. This dual approach was designed to find an initial signal and then validate it, making their conclusion much stronger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the first study included in the report, published in the journal &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11539626/#Sec9"&gt;Alzheimer's Research &amp;amp; Therapy&lt;/a&gt;, researchers used health data of more than 195,000 Brits 60 and up as part of the UK Biobank Study over 12 years on average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the first of two studies, participants in the UK answered the survey question: 'Do people say that you look younger than you are, older than you are, or about your age?'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After accounting for factors like age, health and lifestyle, they found those who reported looking older had a 61 percent higher risk of dementia compared to those who reported looking younger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The link between looking older according to what other people thought and a higher dementia risk was not the same for everyone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The connection was strongest in three specific groups: people with obesity, people who spent more time outside during the summer and people who had a higher genetic risk of developing Alzheimer's disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The risk was elevated across different types of dementia, most notably for vascular dementia, which saw a 55 percent higher risk, as well as unspecified dementia, which saw a 74 percent increased risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The risk of Alzheimer’s and perceived aging, or what other people say about them, was present, though not very strong. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Jana Nelson was 50 when diagnosed with early onset dementia, following severe personality changes and a sharp cognitive decline that left her unable to solve simple math problems or name colors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The connection between looking older than one's chronological age and having an increased risk for dementia and cognitive impairment held true for most people, regardless of their sex, education or many other health factors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those perceived as older by others were more likely to be smokers, men and physically inactive. They also showed higher rates of depressive symptoms and other health conditions than those who felt they looked younger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study also tested participants' current thinking skills and found that those who reported looking older tended to perform worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They scored lower on tests of processing speed and executive function and had slower reaction times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the second study published in the same report, researchers took a different approach. It was conducted in a completely separate study population of around 600 older adults in China. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They showed photographs of participants to a panel of 50 independent assessors who were asked to guess each person's age. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Analyzing this data, they found that for every year older a person was judged to look compared to their real age, their odds of having measurable cognitive impairment increased by 10 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In addition to having assessors guess ages from photos, the researchers used specialized imaging to objectively count and measure wrinkles, particularly crow's feet around the eyes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Rebecca Luna's (pictured here) early-onset Alzheimer's symptoms appeared in her late 40s. She would black out mid-conversation, lose her keys and leave the stove before returning to find her kitchen full of smoke&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The scan shows a brain afflicted with Alzheimer's. The front of the brain is at top in this view from below. The progression of this degenerative disease has caused atrophy in both halves of the brain, but especially at upper right and upper left (lighter brown areas). The ventricles (center, white) have also been affected and are dilated from their normal size &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;First, they counted the total number of wrinkles above the cheeks and around the eyes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Then, they performed the Line Wrinkle Contrast, which measures the visibility or prominence of the wrinkles by analyzing how much they stand out from the surrounding skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of all the measurements taken, the parameters for crow's feet wrinkles, specifically the total number and contrast, showed the strongest and most significant association with cognitive impairment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Measurements from the cheek area and other skin metrics, like hydration and elasticity, did not show as strong a link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The aging process causes a cascade of physiological effects beyond neurological ones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cardiovascular disorders, including heart attack and high blood pressure, type two diabetes, osteoarthritis, chronic obstructive pulmonary disease and many types of cancers share common underlying drivers, including chronic inflammation and cellular aging. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Chronic diseases, as well as accumulated stress, DNA damage, inflammation and hormonal changes, can all be seen on a person’s face, they concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Chronic inflammation plays a leading role in the pathology of dementia. It drives neuronal damage, accelerates brain aging and is a common thread linking many dementia risk factors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This study's findings suggest that facial aging may be a visible sign of this same systemic inflammatory process. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:45:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPN0tVWTJ5TXYtSkVvUnFUaFNfYWhHRGs4eTFYUDRKUnBIU2J6UFB3Y2lPQzQ3LXRWYXRXTFNMYlduTUx4NmhWRlNacVhOR3RMMlI2VWgwUUlqQi1FcDhLN2gzcEN1a1ZUR0pRcS1DbEJUWlZ5R2ZwT1llSUdySk9JRmZoM0xwd1hZSEVFU05zTWs5SWdxcVowSGYtUXJCRDN1LUNhOTVZQlh5Z9IBrwFBVV95cUxPUWhlWEJZNXhmRXMydmNVOGN5VlJZSmloRENyZFpKLWZUMnIzVnZpYXBXS3U1VW82QnZtaWtGWndUb0YzSWtER3ZVb0V0eWVZRE80d3RFVTRjNUlyTk5SczU2amMtUk11VzRURHB5WXNBMjI2RkVadDJjMDdrVlBPZUpWTDloUnlmRVQ3eVExUTZwdjNQakhTWWVGTEZ1SGw4MU03cU5YYTBxR3A3eTlR</guid></item><item><title>你吃东西是为了长寿吗？参加此测验以了解详情。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/interactive/2026/healthy-eating-longevity-quiz/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story relative"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="noscript-warning"&gt;Warning: This graphic requires JavaScript. Please enable JavaScript for the best experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-gxxVqo-dropcap-true wpds-c-foYyTm-ihVwKVo-css component-text" id="MKCMU777WZGYHHVCS5UDYP346Y" data-contentid="MKCMU777WZGYHHVCS5UDYP346Y"&gt;Eating healthy food can add years to your life. It can lower your odds of developing &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/07/28/science-prevent-heart-disease/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template" target="_blank"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, cancer, dementia and other chronic diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css component-text" id="TDK6Q3ZEOZC6LJO7WYBKBGVETE" data-contentid="TDK6Q3ZEOZC6LJO7WYBKBGVETE"&gt;But how do you know if your diet is truly healthy? Are you &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/01/10/foods-health-benefits-diet/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template" target="_blank"&gt;eating the right foods&lt;/a&gt;, and in the right amounts?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css component-text" id="RMVQ3JYMJJG25E7MAHZ2OU46LE" data-contentid="RMVQ3JYMJJG25E7MAHZ2OU46LE"&gt;Experts at the Mayo Clinic developed a survey called the Mini Eating Assessment Tool, or &lt;a href="https://minieat.mayoclinic.org/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template"&gt;Mini-EAT&lt;/a&gt;, that can determine if you’re eating a healthy diet or not. A study &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/JAHA.121.025064?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in the Journal of the American Heart Association found that how you answer the survey’s questions can provide an accurate picture of your diet’s&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;overall state. We spoke to Francisco Lopez-Jimenez, a cardiologist at the Mayo Clinic who developed the survey, to learn more about it. Then we created a quiz based on the survey with his input.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css component-text" id="3DGGJIOJWZBAJPCJBRTZADGNLE" data-contentid="3DGGJIOJWZBAJPCJBRTZADGNLE"&gt;If you want to know if you’re on the right track, answer the following simple questions. If you find that you’re missing the mark, don’t worry. We’ve included science-backed advice to help you spruce up your meals&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;so you can increase your odds of living a long and healthy life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-hSuZRc"&gt;vegetables&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-eNhkpQ"&gt;Serving size examples&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-llABtw"&gt;Diagram shows examples of different types of vegetables at 1 serving size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="PJLV PJLV-ihQhsWy-css"&gt;&lt;div class="pg-graphic fallback-available " data-fallback-image-url="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/fruits-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/2300-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz.png?v=1765386859111"&gt;





&lt;div id="g-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-box" class="ai2html"&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-xxsmall" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="0.561" data-min-width="0" data-max-width="383"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-xxsmall-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/fruits-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-xxsmall.png?v=19" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai0-3" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Sliced yellow &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;bell peppers&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai0-5" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked, &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;chopped broccoli&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-xsmall" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="0.572" data-min-width="384" data-max-width="639"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-xsmall-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/fruits-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-xsmall.png?v=19" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai1-3" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Sliced yellow &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;bell peppers&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai1-5" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked, &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;chopped broccoli&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-medium" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="1.445" data-min-width="640" data-max-width="919"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-medium-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/fruits-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-medium.png?v=19" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai2-2" class="g-Layer_12 g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked, &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;chopped broccoli&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai2-5" class="g-Layer_12 g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Sliced yellow &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;bell peppers&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-large" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="1.482" data-min-width="920"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-large-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/fruits-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/vegetables-healthy-eating-quiz-large.png?v=19" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai3-3" class="g-Layer_12 g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked, &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;chopped broccoli&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai3-4" class="g-Layer_12 g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Sliced yellow &lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;bell peppers&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-igmsXmH-css"&gt;&lt;h2 class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-iTxFAM-level-2 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iHIAaM-css component-heading-2" data-component="Heading" data-contentid="H7LZ4FKYAZGHDPTF2OCRT34DOI" id="H7LZ4FKYAZGHDPTF2OCRT34DOI"&gt;Think about a typical day in your life. How many servings of vegetables do you eat? Fried or starchy veggies such as potatoes don’t count.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-bYzuTg"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-erGbBk"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-iFKWRt"&gt;Drag the slider to mark your answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-hSuZRc"&gt;fruits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-eNhkpQ"&gt;Serving size examples&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-llABtw"&gt;Diagram shows examples of different fruits at 1 serving size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-igmsXmH-css"&gt;&lt;h2 class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-iTxFAM-level-2 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iHIAaM-css component-heading-2" data-component="Heading" data-contentid="BEQG3ZG45BH57E4XLH4F3BPAMQ" id="BEQG3ZG45BH57E4XLH4F3BPAMQ"&gt;In a typical day, how many servings of fresh fruit do you eat? Fruit juice and dried fruit don’t count.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-bYzuTg"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-erGbBk"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-iFKWRt"&gt;Drag the slider to mark your answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-hSuZRc"&gt;legumes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-eNhkpQ"&gt;Serving size examples&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-llABtw"&gt;Diagram shows examples of different types of beans at 1 serving size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="PJLV PJLV-ihQhsWy-css"&gt;&lt;div class="pg-graphic fallback-available " data-fallback-image-url="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/2300-beans-healthy-eating-quiz.png?v=1764966067870"&gt;





&lt;div id="g-beans-healthy-eating-quiz-box" class="ai2html"&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-beans-healthy-eating-quiz-xxsmall" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="0.719" data-min-width="0" data-max-width="383"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-beans-healthy-eating-quiz-xxsmall-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/beans-healthy-eating-quiz-xxsmall.png?v=13" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai0-1" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked black beans&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-beans-healthy-eating-quiz-xsmall" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="0.728" data-min-width="384" data-max-width="639"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-beans-healthy-eating-quiz-xsmall-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/beans-healthy-eating-quiz-xsmall.png?v=13" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai1-1" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked black beans&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-beans-healthy-eating-quiz-medium" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="1.842" data-min-width="640" data-max-width="919"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-beans-healthy-eating-quiz-medium-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/beans-healthy-eating-quiz-medium.png?v=13" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai2-1" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked black beans&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-beans-healthy-eating-quiz-large" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="1.953" data-min-width="920"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-beans-healthy-eating-quiz-large-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/beans-healthy-eating-quiz-large.png?v=13" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai3-1" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked black beans&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-igmsXmH-css"&gt;&lt;h2 class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-iTxFAM-level-2 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iHIAaM-css component-heading-2" data-component="Heading" data-contentid="3ZADVY6C7ZFIZNBM5KEEFTZCYU" id="3ZADVY6C7ZFIZNBM5KEEFTZCYU"&gt;How often do you eat legumes such as beans, peas, lentils or soybeans per week? Hummus and tofu count.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-bYzuTg"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-erGbBk"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-iFKWRt"&gt;Drag the slider to mark your answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-hSuZRc"&gt;nuts and seeds&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-eNhkpQ"&gt;Serving size examples&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-llABtw"&gt;Diagram shows examples of different types of nuts at 1 serving size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-igmsXmH-css"&gt;&lt;h2 class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-iTxFAM-level-2 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iHIAaM-css component-heading-2" data-component="Heading" data-contentid="RFP6CREBNZALLBQ6GQLIFY463Q" id="RFP6CREBNZALLBQ6GQLIFY463Q"&gt;Now tell us where you stand on nuts and seeds. How often do you eat them in a typical week? Nut butters count!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-bYzuTg"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-erGbBk"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-iFKWRt"&gt;Drag the slider to mark your answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-hSuZRc"&gt;seafood&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-eNhkpQ"&gt;Serving size examples&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-llABtw"&gt;Diagram shows examples of different types of seafood at 1 serving size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-igmsXmH-css"&gt;&lt;h2 class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-iTxFAM-level-2 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iHIAaM-css component-heading-2" data-component="Heading" data-contentid="HVYMKDJZH5GMJA7AAFQBM5WD2E" id="HVYMKDJZH5GMJA7AAFQBM5WD2E"&gt;Let’s take a look at your seafood intake. By seafood, we mean fish and shellfish, such as tuna, salmon and shrimp. How many servings do you eat in a typical week?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-bYzuTg"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-erGbBk"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-iFKWRt"&gt;Drag the slider to mark your answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-hSuZRc"&gt;whole grains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-eNhkpQ"&gt;Serving size examples&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="PJLV PJLV-ihwSyul-css"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-llABtw"&gt;Diagram shows examples of different types of whole grain foods at 1 serving size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div aria-hidden="true" class="PJLV PJLV-ihQhsWy-css"&gt;&lt;div class="pg-graphic fallback-available " data-fallback-image-url="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/2300-grains-healthy-eating-quiz.png?v=1764966119607"&gt;





&lt;div id="g-grains-healthy-eating-quiz-box" class="ai2html"&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-grains-healthy-eating-quiz-xxsmall" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="0.688" data-min-width="0" data-max-width="383"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-grains-healthy-eating-quiz-xxsmall-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/grains-healthy-eating-quiz-xxsmall.png?v=10" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai0-1" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked brown rice&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai0-3" class="g-food g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Whole-grain bread&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1 slice&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai0-4" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Whole-grain pasta&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-grains-healthy-eating-quiz-xsmall" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="0.69" data-min-width="384" data-max-width="639"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-grains-healthy-eating-quiz-xsmall-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/grains-healthy-eating-quiz-xsmall.png?v=10" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai1-1" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked brown rice&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai1-3" class="g-food g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Whole-grain bread&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1 slice&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai1-4" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Whole-grain pasta&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-grains-healthy-eating-quiz-medium" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="1.723" data-min-width="640" data-max-width="919"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-grains-healthy-eating-quiz-medium-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/grains-healthy-eating-quiz-medium.png?v=10" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai2-2" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked brown rice&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai2-3" class="g-food g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Whole-grain bread&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1 slice&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai2-4" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Whole-grain pasta&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
	&lt;div id="g-grains-healthy-eating-quiz-large" class="g-artboard" data-aspect-ratio="1.764" data-min-width="920"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;img id="g-grains-healthy-eating-quiz-large-img" class="g-aiImg" alt="" data-src="https://gfx-data.news-engineering.aws.wapo.pub/ai2html/beans-healthy-eating-quiz/AIFWHXHDKZAMHCCB5KSL7AFNIA/grains-healthy-eating-quiz-large.png?v=10" src="data:image/gif;base64,R0lGODlhCgAKAIAAAB8fHwAAACH5BAEAAAAALAAAAAAKAAoAAAIIhI+py+0PYysAOw=="&gt;
		
		&lt;div id="g-ai3-2" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Cooked brown rice&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai3-3" class="g-food g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Whole-grain bread&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1 slice&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;div id="g-ai3-4" class="g-back g-aiAbs g-aiPointText"&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle0"&gt;Whole-grain pasta&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;p class="g-pstyle1"&gt;1/2 cup&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
	&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;




&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-igmsXmH-css"&gt;&lt;h2 class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-iTxFAM-level-2 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iHIAaM-css component-heading-2" data-component="Heading" data-contentid="7DAKNL25PRGUVLKT6JCUEAWFKM" id="7DAKNL25PRGUVLKT6JCUEAWFKM"&gt;Per day, how often do you eat whole grains, such as brown rice, barley, oatmeal, quinoa or whole-wheat or whole-grain pasta or bread?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-bYzuTg"&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV wpds-c-erGbBk"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-iFKWRt"&gt;Drag the slider to mark your answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="PJLV PJLV-ijVPAKx-css"&gt;&lt;h3 class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-eTgREY-level-3 wpds-c-iFKWRt-iiCGobN-css component-heading-4" data-component="Heading" data-contentid="LRZHDRTY6NAW3FCSLTSJ2IH7EE" id="LRZHDRTY6NAW3FCSLTSJ2IH7EE"&gt;Your healthy eating plan&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p data-component="Text" class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-idAgRsb-css component-text" id="RMUNHW52IRCG5GSYPWW3I3ECGU" data-contentid="RMUNHW52IRCG5GSYPWW3I3ECGU"&gt;Congratulations! Whether you scored high or low (or somewhere in between), what matters is that by taking this quiz, you’ve identified where you can make improvements in your diet. Even small changes can have a big impact on your health and life expectancy. And it’s never too late to start. Studies show that no matter how old you are or where you’re at food-wise, you can gain sizable health benefits at any age by cutting back on highly processed foods loaded with salt, &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/interactive/2025/breakfast-added-sugar/?itid=lk_inline_enhanced-template" target="_blank"&gt;sugar&lt;/a&gt; and other additives and replacing them with fruits, vegetables, nuts, beans, peas, lentils, seafood and whole grains. We recommend bookmarking this page and checking back in three months to see how you’ve improved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="PJLV wpds-c-fwOiRn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-czTphm"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-hEgojh wpds-c-hEgojh-idWlhdm-css component-card"&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-iFKWRt wpds-c-iFKWRt-iKuYGR-level-5 wpds-c-iFKWRt-ifepmnN-css component-heading-5"&gt;About this story&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-foYyTm wpds-c-foYyTm-ikHxsIg-css component-text"&gt;Editing by Emily Codik and Theresa Tamkins. Copy editing by Grant Johnson. Graphics editing by Manuel Canales. Design editing by Christine Ashack. Design and development by Junne Joaquin Alcantara.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:31:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQeDhnMkdlUVJrTkxzSzdKY1hwQnFGelJTcENSUHFVMFBuTDkwaFNaRFdFT3dSbUlXT3RNYW44aEczWEJTeTJCWFZDX01KX2pZUFJHTGNmVkFrU3dDUUtUN1JEaVN3S0hGX1NlTDJ6aG9hRVB1X3VxTzZiY3lPdFR3UXdrSElFOTR3MmdVbFlSaHk</guid></item><item><title>医疗专业人士正在揭示您永远不应忽视的“小”健康标志- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-warning-signs-symptoms-december-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-23
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139891589" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;17.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"SOOOOOO much hypertension, arrhythmias, and hyperglycemia. You'll probably get a lot of different answers based on the typical patient population in the area, but the most common things I've seen are &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/hypertension" target="_blank"&gt;hypertensive&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://diabetes.org/living-with-diabetes/treatment-care/hyperglycemia" target="_blank"&gt;hyperglycemic&lt;/a&gt; events for patients who are noncompliant with their medications. Their complaints are usually quite vague (headache, dizziness, weakness, abdominal pain), and the physical examination is unremarkable. Vitals, BMP, UA, and past medical history make it pretty obvious pretty quickly, especially when the patient's previous encounters are already in your system."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;"When asked why they haven't refilled their Metformin or Norvasc since January, many patients will shrug their shoulders. They either changed insurance, lost their insurance, or say they just felt fine and thought they could go without it for a while."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/handsmantis/" target="_blank"&gt;u/handsmantis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxOR280ZWNNY0RUenlRY1Q3RVRxeWNoMGR4Zm14RzIxU1VFdUlhamZWUjZ0MUVVcFZlT2NnZm9QNWFsUDczbnlBQ24yaDJwY0VrRGVldU1WU05vXzVNRE0zSlQzYjhJNGdNdVFoWkcyV3BSZkZ1UlVLUWNiUlB4bHVieks5UUw4dFRGNjcza2NGUEk4azRSdmc</guid></item><item><title>医疗专业人士正在揭示您永远不应忽视的“小”健康标志-雅虎加拿大新闻</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/medical-professionals-revealing-small-health-143102035.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;We recently wrote a post where &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-warning-signs-symptoms-october-2025" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:medical professionals revealed the &amp;quot;small&amp;quot; health signs you shouldn't ignore;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;medical professionals revealed the "small" health signs you shouldn't ignore&lt;/a&gt;. In the comments, doctors, nurses, and other medical professionals shared the warning signs that people often ignore, which could signal a serious health issue. Here's what they had to say:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: Some responses were pulled from &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/medicine/comments/z8mknl/what_warning_signssymptoms_do_you_wish_were_more/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:these;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;these&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/medicine/comments/5hoq9m/what_are_some_oh_no_symptoms_in_your_specialty/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:two;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;two&lt;/a&gt; Reddit threads.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Little &lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/bump-on-gums" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:lumps on your gum;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;lumps on your gum&lt;/a&gt;. Now, it could be a fibroma or a bony growth, but especially in decaying teeth, it could be a dental abscess (where the pulp is infected) and could lead to more serious health conditions, IV drips, and even death if not treated."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—Anonymous&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Sorafilm / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"I specialize in obesity and nutrition: If you lost more than 30% of your weight on a GLP-1 like Ozempic or Wegovy, you likely need other stuff checked out. I've seen multiple instances of cancers missed because we were blaming the Wegovy, and they had &lt;a href="https://www.unitypoint.org/news-and-articles/5-colon-cancer-symptoms-that-are-easy-to-overlook" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:colon cancer.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;colon cancer.&lt;/a&gt;"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—Anonymous, 31, Pennsylvania&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/carolinebologna/12-things-millennials-do-that-gen-z-hates?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:12 Things Millennials Do That Gen Z Says Give Them The Ultimate "Ick";elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;12 Things Millennials Do That Gen Z Says Give Them The Ultimate "Ick"&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Don't ignore sudden severe itching in pregnancy; this can be &lt;a href="https://www.stlouischildrens.org/conditions-treatments/cholestasis-pregnancy" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a sign;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;a sign&lt;/a&gt; of liver disease and may need early delivery of the baby and possible liver transplant eval."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—Anonymous, 31, Pennsylvania&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;4. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"When someone says, 'You know, I lost vision in that eye a couple of weeks ago. But I had another appointment that day, so I waited two weeks to come in.' Or some variation. Happens all the time. If you suddenly lose vision in one eye, get to an eye doctor immediately. Don't wait. It's always less fixable with time."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/eyezontheprize30/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/eyezontheprize30;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/eyezontheprize30&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Lorado / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;5. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/appendicitis/symptoms-causes/syc-20369543" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stomach cramps/abdominal pain;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Stomach cramps/abdominal pain&lt;/a&gt; that can lead to a burst appendix. Usually, it feels like really bad acid reflux."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Arena89/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/Arena89;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/Arena89&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;6. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"MD, Interventional Cardiology. STEMIs, for me. People have had chest pain for six days, but only come in because it still hasn't gone away. Whoops, your entire anterior wall is dead because you came in too late for revascularization. I hope you don't mind wearing an external defibrillator for the next three months."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Onion01/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/Onion01;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/Onion01&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;7. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"I'm in podiatry. Ingrown nails are always a warning sign. I've seen my share of home bathtub nail procedures go south and risk the limb."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/SadFortuneCookie/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/SadFortuneCookie;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/SadFortuneCookie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/fabianabuontempo/surprising-womens-health-conditions-fs?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:21 Things Women Didn't Realize Their Body Was Capable Of Doing Until It Just... Happened;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;21 Things Women Didn't Realize Their Body Was Capable Of Doing Until It Just... Happened&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Wachiwit / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;8. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"The amount of &lt;a href="https://www.pmbc.ca.gov/forms_pubs/diabetes_broch.shtml" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:diabetic feet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;diabetic feet&lt;/a&gt; I see is staggering. Literally 90% (the rest is planned follow-ups for operations) of my wound clinic is people who tried to treat their charcot feet and diabetic ulcers themselves, usually right to the point where the chances of getting away without amputation are slim to none."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/D15c0untMD/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/D15c0untMD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/D15c0untMD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;9. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Like, I've seen patients with vague, intermittent 'dizziness,' that actually has been happening for months. It's always: 'OMG. What's wrong with me? This is so strange; better go to the ER.' But on the other hand, some people wake up and their arm doesn't work, and they're like, 'Hmm, maybe I can ride this one out.'"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/noteasybeincheesy/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/noteasybeincheesy;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/noteasybeincheesy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"&lt;b&gt;I'm always impressed at the people who think they're having a stroke, are in fact&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/stroke/signs-symptoms/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:having a stroke;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;b&gt;having a stroke&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and still wait to see if they feel better the next day before going to the hospital."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—[redacted]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;10. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"'I've been &lt;a href="https://blog.dana-farber.org/insight/2016/09/whats-the-connection-between-night-sweats-and-cancer/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sweating excessively;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;sweating excessively&lt;/a&gt; in the middle of the night.' 'You have been coughing?' Answer = Yes. Time to look for tuberculosis. 'You have been coughing?' Answer = No. Time to look for cancer."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/HermanRV/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/HermanRV;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/HermanRV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Peter Dazeley / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/claudiasantos/hard-truths-challenges-of-aging-fs?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:Older Adults Are Revealing The "Hard Truths" About Aging That No One Prepared Them For, And As A Millennial, I Was Shocked To Hear Some Of These;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;Older Adults Are Revealing The "Hard Truths" About Aging That No One Prepared Them For, And As A Millennial, I Was Shocked To Hear Some Of These&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;11. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"An example with pregnant patients: 'My baby was moving a lot last week, but he hasn't moved or kicked all this week. I'm a bit concerned.' Me: 'OK, let's take a look.' (In my head: WHY DIDN'T YOU COME EARLIER!?)."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/HermanRV/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/HermanRV;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/HermanRV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;12. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"People with minor bite wounds at home sometimes try to glue the laceration shut. This is bad. It turns an ED visit with a few sutures and an augmentin prescription into an inpatient stay."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/thetreece/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/thetreece;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/thetreece&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;13. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Don't ignore pooping yourself while having back pain. Or, being unable to poop or pee properly. I had three patients in the last week with this who wouldn't go to the ER because they didn't want to wait. One osteoporosis-based sacral fracture and two severe cervical stenosis with myelopathy/radiculopathy."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Olyfishmouth/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/Olyfishmouth;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/Olyfishmouth&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Garrett Aitken / Getty Images / iStockphoto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;14. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"I'm honestly shocked at how many new-onset diabetes cases with DKA (Diabetic Ketoacidosis) I see, and the parents didn't think it was abnormal that their kid had lost 20 pounds in two months. &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/symptoms/unexplained-weight-loss" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Unintentional weight loss;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Unintentional weight loss&lt;/a&gt; is never normal. It's almost always associated with something serious, whether it be AIDS, new diabetes, or a malignancy. I feel like this should just be common sense, but it's apparently not."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/halp-im-lost/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/halp-im-lost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/halp-im-lost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;15. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"Never ignore &lt;a href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/gum-disease-may-be-linked-to-plaque-buildup-in-arteries-higher-risk-of-major-cvd-events" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:oral health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;oral health&lt;/a&gt; issues. Visit any cardiology ward, and several patients will have had or are waiting for tooth extractions. Poor oral health can kill you."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/bubblyelephant984" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bubblyelephant984;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;bubblyelephant984&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;16. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"I wish patients would recognize that it's not normal to be coughing all the time and short of breath with minimal exertion...I hate cigarettes."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/fixture94/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/fixture94;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/fixture94&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/scarymouse/old-person-habits-that-make-life-better-2?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;It's Not A Marriage&amp;quot; — 24 People Are Sharing Their Secret &amp;quot;Grandparent&amp;quot; Habits That Actually Make Life Way Better, And I'm Taking Notes For My Future Self;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"It's Not A Marriage" — 24 People Are Sharing Their Secret "Grandparent" Habits That Actually Make Life Way Better, And I'm Taking Notes For My Future Self&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;And finally...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;17. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;"SOOOOOO much hypertension, arrhythmias, and hyperglycemia. You'll probably get a lot of different answers based on the typical patient population in the area, but the most common things I've seen are &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/hypertension" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:hypertensive;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;hypertensive&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://diabetes.org/living-with-diabetes/treatment-care/hyperglycemia" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:hyperglycemic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;hyperglycemic&lt;/a&gt; events for patients who are noncompliant with their medications. Their complaints are usually quite vague (headache, dizziness, weakness, abdominal pain), and the physical examination is unremarkable. Vitals, BMP, UA, and past medical history make it pretty obvious pretty quickly, especially when the patient's previous encounters are already in your system."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"When asked why they haven't refilled their Metformin or Norvasc since January, many patients will shrug their shoulders. They either changed insurance, lost their insurance, or say they just felt fine and thought they could go without it for a while."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/handsmantis/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:u/handsmantis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;u/handsmantis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; PeopleImages / Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: Some submissions have been edited for length and/or clarity.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Doctors, nurses, and other medical professionals, what are some other "small" health signs people should never ignore? Tell us in the comments, or if you prefer to remain anonymous, you can use the form below.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/abbyzinman/doctors-share-health-issues-patients-ignored?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;I Knew Instantly That He Would Be Dead Soon&amp;quot;: Doctors Are Sharing The Biggest Health Issues Patients Ignored Until It Was Too Late, And Whew, I've Been Warned;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"I Knew Instantly That He Would Be Dead Soon": Doctors Are Sharing The Biggest Health Issues Patients Ignored Until It Was Too Late, And Whew, I've Been Warned&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/dannicaramirez/people-diagnosed-with-cancer-share-symptoms?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:19 "Unexpected" Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, Straight From People Who Have Been Diagnosed With Cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;19 "Unexpected" Health Signs You Should Never Ignore, Straight From People Who Have Been Diagnosed With Cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also in Goodful: &lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/haein_jung/people-share-wholesome-stranger-moments?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:&amp;quot;'You Look So Happy Enjoying The Sun'&amp;quot;: People Are Sharing Moments When Strangers Restored Their Faith In Humanity, And It's Just The Wholesome Content We Need In These Trying Times;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;"'You Look So Happy Enjoying The Sun'": People Are Sharing Moments When Strangers Restored Their Faith In Humanity, And It's Just The Wholesome Content We Need In These Trying Times&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-health-warning-signs-symptoms-december-2025?utm_source=yahoo-recirc-links" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read it on BuzzFeed.com;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Read it on BuzzFeed.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:31:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQU2xGZGZvZ1RLbXNGNlRpT2d6ZmV2cHhlc2tpUmZJY2dkVWZBVXUzZlpzbDM4UjJtVHVPenRtdGhGMGNEM0F0OHpWb29EblR2Sm1OWEhkcEQ2SUk2VXUyQ3o5SXFRZnZwank2MUdyc0lCaVFOd1oycVQ5cjJYeGxsaklrSk9XamZRcGxkbW9n</guid></item><item><title>每日一杯茶可以帮助对抗心脏病、癌症、衰老等- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/your-daily-cup-of-tea-could-help-fight-heart-disease-cancer-aging-and-more/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:01:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPS0Y4VGNTVy1yWGNER1RSdlAyelp5d2FYbFl0RjFjZFNVNUctbFpwZXJPdlZhdGxleHhHd21ZRWVMc0FpUjBoaUpGdWFtcnpUQ0UxRG9vY18zdEVyVFgwMEZjeWozN1Q0OUlveURMSEZPTzZGUlhQaWJod2IxdWZPUTdkdDhPSnQ3NjM1a1BJbGdBZ0xvQm41dGFIOG1Xa0RGVnc</guid></item><item><title>这个女人的DNA可能是活过100岁的秘密-印度国防评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/womans-dna-secret-to-living-past-100/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new genetic study published in &lt;em&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/em&gt; has revealed rare biological traits that may explain why &lt;em&gt;Maria Branyas&lt;/em&gt;, one of the oldest recorded humans,&lt;strong&gt; lived to 117 &lt;/strong&gt;with remarkably good health. Based on comprehensive biological samples collected before her passing in 2024, researchers have identified genetic and physiological clues that may reshape our understanding of aging and how to prolong human life.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Inside The Biology Of A Supercentenarian&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Maria Branyas defied the expected trajectory of human aging. Scientists from the Josep Carreras Leukaemia Research Institute in Barcelona conducted a full analysis of her blood, saliva, stool, and &lt;em&gt;urine&lt;/em&gt;, revealing that many of her body’s cellular markers appeared decades younger than her chronological age. The researchers believe her case can unlock vital pathways for healthy aging.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Unlike most people her age, &lt;strong&gt;Branyas &lt;/strong&gt;exhibited low inflammation, excellent cardiovascular health, and an immune system comparable to people several decades younger. Her gut microbiome also displayed strong resilience. The results suggest a rare genomic profile that protected her against age-related decline. The study, published in&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.xcrm.2025.102368" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; &lt;em&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, outlines how Branyas carried rare gene variants linked to healthy brain function, robust immunity, and resistance to chronic disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Extreme human lifespan, exemplified by supercentenarians, presents a paradox in understanding aging: despite advanced age, they maintain relatively good health,” write the researchers, led by epigeneticists &lt;em&gt;Eloy Santos-Pujol&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Aleix Noguera-Castells&lt;/em&gt;. Her &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/dna-reveals-story-of-beachy-head-woman/" data-type="post" data-id="100171"&gt;DNA&lt;/a&gt;, paired with a Mediterranean diet rich in &lt;em&gt;yogurt&lt;/em&gt; and a physically and socially active lifestyle, may have created the perfect storm for exceptional longevity.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Maria Branyas on her 117th birthday. (Family archive of Maria Branyas Morera/Wikimedia Commons/PD)
" class="wp-image-101750" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image.png 642w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-380x355.png 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-520x486.png 520w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image.png"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image.png" alt="Maria Branyas on her 117th birthday. (Family archive of Maria Branyas Morera/Wikimedia Commons/PD)
" class="wp-image-101750" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image.png 642w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-380x355.png 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-520x486.png 520w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Maria Branyas on her 117th birthday. (Family archive of Maria Branyas Morera/Wikimedia Commons/PD)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Why Her DNA Could Change Longevity Research&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;What makes Branyas’ case especially intriguing is that her &lt;em&gt;genomic youth&lt;/em&gt; didn’t match her chronological age. While her telomeres, chromosomal caps linked to aging, were notably short, which is usually a warning sign, she never developed cancer. The researchers theorize that shorter telomeres in this case may have &lt;em&gt;limited cellular overgrowth&lt;/em&gt;, acting as a cancer-prevention mechanism.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In fact, the paradox of her health may turn traditional aging biomarkers on their head. Most aging models suggest that short telomeres mean a shorter life, yet Branyas challenges that view. Her cellular aging may have followed a different, more controlled pathway. This surprising insight could shift how scientists design future therapies for aging and disease prevention.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;blockquote class="wp-block-quote is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The picture that emerges from our study, although derived only from this one exceptional individual, shows that extremely advanced age and poor health are not intrinsically linked,” write the study authors. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research team stresses that broader studies are needed to confirm their findings, but Branyas’ case offers a compelling starting point.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div class="wp-block-image"&gt;
&lt;figure class="aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Younger features and aging features of Maria Branyas. (Santos-Pujol et al.,Cell Reports, 2025)
" class="wp-image-101753" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1.png 768w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1-380x380.png 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1-150x150.png 150w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1-520x520.png 520w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1.png"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1.png" alt="Younger features and aging features of Maria Branyas. (Santos-Pujol et al.,Cell Reports, 2025)
" class="wp-image-101753" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1.png 768w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1-380x380.png 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1-150x150.png 150w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/image-1-520x520.png 520w" sizes="(max-width: 768px) 100vw, 768px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Younger features and aging features of Maria Branyas. (Santos-Pujol et al.,&lt;em&gt;Cell Reports&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What Sets Supercentenarians Apart From The Rest?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Supercentenarians like Branyas represent only a tiny fraction of the population, just &lt;em&gt;1 in 10 people&lt;/em&gt; who reach 100 survive to 110. While her lifestyle certainly played a role, the study emphasizes that &lt;em&gt;genetic architecture&lt;/em&gt; is likely the primary differentiator. Larger studies have also found consistent patterns among long-lived individuals, including higher levels of &lt;em&gt;good cholesterol&lt;/em&gt;, better inflammation control, and unique gut flora compositions.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Her ability to stay &lt;em&gt;mentally, physically, and socially active&lt;/em&gt; into her final years paints a picture of aging that is &lt;em&gt;resilient&lt;/em&gt;, not degenerative. And though this research focused on a single person, its implications are vast. The authors propose using this type of data to identify &lt;em&gt;biomarkers for healthy aging&lt;/em&gt; and develop &lt;em&gt;personalized longevity therapies&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As the global population of centenarians rapidly grows, understanding why some people defy the odds could unlock new strategies to extend not just lifespan but healthspan, the number of years lived in good health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE1nXzlpTlhNejdBZXBrVkNxbHFRUE5Pdko4a1YtcU5uV0RfeS1ZZDJYRU5Hc3NocDdGaXpmc19Sa3VERlRqanJITllqbl9BcFBjenJfRDJxSS1xWW5MYVhWMkcyNGh5R2c4Q2VsdUxGeHJjN2tseE9oNw</guid></item><item><title>根据顶级神经科学家的说法， “永恒的阳光”疗法可以“抹去”糟糕的记忆，并用更好的记忆取而代之-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-15278201/holy-grail-alzheimers-memory.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Memories of past trauma could soon be ‘dialed down’ in the brain so they no longer haunt us, a leading neuroscientist has suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The same techniques could offer tools so that addicts don't crave the drugs that are destroying them - and even reclaim memories lost to &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14197849/longevity-doctor-supplements-reverse-aging.html"&gt;Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt; or amnesia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In his new book, &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://press.princeton.edu/books/hardcover/9780691266688/how-to-change-a-memory"&gt;How to Change a Memory&lt;/a&gt;, Professor Steve Ramirez explored a realm of science so advanced that, until now, it has only existed in sci-fi movies like Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind and Total Recall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And, as he chronicled both his breakthroughs experimenting on the brains of rodents at Boston University, as well as his grief over the death of his lab partner, Xu Liu, he revealed that rewriting human memories could one day become a common part of modern medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ramirez told Daily Mail he has been able to locate memories in mice using brain cells activated by light.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His team has then manipulated them by implanting false memories and reclaiming ‘lost’ ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The results, he said, have been 'pretty amazing,' suggesting the same might be possible in humans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He explained: 'Researchers have been able to successfully restore a memory that was thought to be forever lost, so that really begins shaking the foundations of what we think of when we think of memory.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In a new book, How to Change a Memory, Professor Steve Ramirez explores how emerging science may make it possible to ‘rewrite memories’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Professor Steve Ramirez had memory breakthroughs in mouse experiments (Janice Checchio)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Key to understanding the science is the fact that remembering something is ‘not like hitting "Save" in Microsoft Word,’ he pointed out. Rather, every time you remember something, that memory changes slightly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;'We know that when we recall the memory, it's not a video of the past, but it's a reconstructive process where we pull the book of memory out of the library, and when it's at the forefront of our mind, we inadvertently start sketching details into that memory.'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The next step to manipulate those memories through science, he claimed, is 'pretty simple.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Drugs could be used to target cells holding specific memories, he said. Cognitive behavioral therapy or positive cues could also help make the desired changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'None of that breaks any law of physics. There's just more research we need to get to that point.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He stressed that science will not erase memories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's more than we can start to toggle down the emotional components, which perhaps are the debilitating components. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Or we could even toggle up some of the components, if we wanted to boost the positivity associated with a memory.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He did, however, admit that science has the potential to be abused by malicious parties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'One potential problem is that people might manipulate memories to sell products, just like how, today, that five-second ad you see on social media grows in your head like a seed until it becomes a decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If we know all that information is encoded in the brain,' he added, 'even to the point of guiding behavior, we should hope that this knowledge is used for the greater good - as opposed to for selling products or for marketing.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;In a new book, How to Change a Memory, Professor Steve Ramirez explores how emerging science may make it possible to ‘rewrite memories’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15021993/replacing-levels-common-element-reverse-memory-loss.html"&gt;experiments of his and other labs&lt;/a&gt; are still some way off from understanding exactly what patterns of brain cells are involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But he said: 'If we can study how a traumatic memory is recalled, and we know the nuts and bolts of how it works, then we should be able to intervene with it in a more targeted manner in humans.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists in Geneva have already shown it’s possible to deal with addiction in this fashion, and Ramirez believes similar methods could be used to ‘reset’ the brain back to a healthy baseline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the most powerful benefit, he said, will be the means to reclaim ‘lost’ memories in Alzheimer’s and other conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ramirez said: 'I think that's a kind of mini Holy Grail of this all, to be able to really restore what we once thought was lost, especially something as near and dear as memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There are tremendous amounts of more research we need to get there, but I think that would be what the path forward would look like.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Ramirez’s own understanding of the fluidity of memory helped him deal with the untimely death of his lab partner, Xu Liu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He said: 'For me, I've come to terms with memory being the thing that shaped who I am today, for better and for worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There are certainly difficult aspects of my past, whether it's loss and grief or addiction for that matter, but I wouldn't change it because I've learned to grow my life around it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After Xu Liu's death, Ramirez began obsessively lucid dreaming about him - dreams where the dreamer can control events - and now he believes those dreams were his brain’s attempt to offer him hope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He said: 'It's simultaneously my goal to honor my friend, who is the beating heart of the book, and to do justice to the memories we had together.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;How to Change a Memory: One Neuroscientist’s Quest to Alter the Past by Steve Ramirez is published by Princeton University Press&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:26:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQUTZOejJNRHlsa0hhbWpDNXNYNU9VYzI5ZVV4UHZ3VTI3M091WTU3WERNN0JCcjJ4NXRMZkZ3QmE3NlRlVVNzMjJpQmhwLXJSS1FvVUZSb3ZjNVRpTzlxVXdZZzM1ZzZIZzhoRXo2ck9FOTdUSW1wa1hFc1o2VjhGQlR3TWlMdE02cG1NdzFRYmZXNkJm0gGaAUFVX3lxTE9ETzFJWVgwb1EyZXNJSldLSXZVT1Qyd3dHWFZWR1BmNmJiMmxFT3Z6RTdLRWFZbFNRaTBnd2QySnhva1V0VGpLTllKLXd6WTVVQk5xMUtvNDRMM1J0c3BadUFUd0xVZWk3UFVubmU4TUVTcjAzeUJUamdzYXFRblVBNXRPUEZBajBLbXVYTGtiU2tZQ1VJUVMyRkE</guid></item><item><title>简单的血液测试不匹配可能预测肾功能衰竭、心脏病和死亡- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/a-simple-blood-test-mismatch-may-predict-kidney-failure-heart-disease-and-death/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 13:26:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPQS1KY0NWV0lPVk9zLW9CcGdONXI4ZDFaaHNPY2tkM05aYkhBdkpGaVlMbm45aHAtSUQ1alptazZKM1lxQzZnV1hRTTdaUnZ4NGZpamZNM1BhZDk5LVFNLTFfZG1aTEZnMEVrT0l2VV9ONGZoS0ZORG80ZkpobnBpaU05cnF0dkhQSkJxTXdObUhHYmJiR1BBUWNLN0l3ZEVkSEEzN0tWbWQ</guid></item></channel></rss>