<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>寄生虫困扰着哈德良长城的罗马士兵- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/12/study-roman-soldiers-battled-parasites-at-hadrians-wall/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
                      
                      
          &lt;p&gt;It probably sucked to be a Roman soldier guarding Hadrian’s Wall circa the third century CE. W.H. Auden imagined the likely harsh conditions in his poem “&lt;a href="https://hellopoetry.com/poem/788/roman-wall-blues/"&gt;Roman Wall Blues&lt;/a&gt;,” in which a soldier laments enduring wet wind and rain with “lice in my tunic and a cold in my nose.” We can now add chronic nausea and bouts of diarrhea to his list of likely woes, thanks to parasitic infections, according to a new paper published in the journal Parasitology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2022/02/this-ancient-roman-ceramic-pot-was-probably-a-portable-toilet-study-finds/"&gt;previously reported&lt;/a&gt;, archaeologists can learn a great deal by studying the remains of intestinal parasites in ancient feces. For instance, in 2022, &lt;a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2022/01/intestinal-parasites-plagued-jerusalems-wealthy-elite-toilet-excavation-reveals/"&gt;we reported&lt;/a&gt; on an analysis of soil samples collected from a stone toilet found within the ruins of a swanky 7th-century BCE villa just outside Jerusalem. That analysis revealed the presence of parasitic eggs from four different species: whipworm, beef/pork tapeworm, roundworm, and pinworm. (It’s the earliest record of roundworm and pinworm in ancient Israel.)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later that same year, researchers from the University of Cambridge and the University of British Columbia &lt;a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2022/02/this-ancient-roman-ceramic-pot-was-probably-a-portable-toilet-study-finds/"&gt;analyzed&lt;/a&gt; the residue on an ancient Roman ceramic pot excavated at the site of a 5th-century CE Roman villa at Gerace, a rural district in Sicily. They identified the eggs of intestinal parasitic worms commonly found in feces—strong evidence that the 1,500-year-old pot in question was most likely used as a chamber pot.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Other prior studies have compared fecal parasites found in hunter-gatherer and farming communities, revealing dramatic dietary changes, as well as shifts in settlement patterns and social organization coinciding with the rise of agriculture. This latest paper analyzes sediment collected from sewer drains at the Roman fort at &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vindolanda"&gt;Vindolanda&lt;/a&gt;, located just south of the defense fortification known as &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hadrian%27s_Wall"&gt;Hadrian’s Wall&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An antiquarian named William Camden recorded the existence of the ruins in a 1586 treatise. Over the next 200 years, many people visited the site, discovering a military bathhouse in 1702 and an altar in 1715.  Another altar found in 1914 confirmed that the fort had been called Vindolanda. Serious archaeological excavation at the site began in the 1930s. The site is most famous for the so-called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vindolanda_tablets" data-uri="3b2e6e2a335fbdd9d5b162bf089157b0"&gt;Vindolanda tablets,&lt;/a&gt; among the oldest surviving handwritten documents in the UK—and for the &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/antiquity/article/touch-wood-luck-protection-power-or-pleasure-a-wooden-phallus-from-vindolanda-roman-fort/53F4B0838D23DB65F6A244695624102E"&gt;2023 discovery&lt;/a&gt; of what appeared to be an ancient Roman dildo, although &lt;a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2023/03/remember-that-ancient-roman-dildo-it-might-just-be-an-old-roman-drop-spindle/"&gt;others argued&lt;/a&gt; the phallus-shaped artifact was more likely to be a drop spindle used for spinning yarn.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                      &lt;p class="ars-interlude-container in-content-interlude mx-auto max-w-xl"&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 00:00:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOMFdkZVhyMzEzVTZ4WmlnNVlFTjF4Zlp4V2Y3TW1hcFRLdms2eXVTbXE2QnV2Tml1NDR3ZTNjbXBzZWQwQ2EyWXdWUThxR0NPR2ZVMUR4OWdrdk9sTGpvQzl4cHlKMU14VE5BWWZjMnNtTGNqNDZMeEhLRnBBandOd3RHNURrMUMxMC1BckRVTEFhSTIyRHgwOTZjYXE</guid></item><item><title>历史上打击老年人的流感病毒，儿童重返明尼苏达州- Star Tribune</title><link>https://www.startribune.com/flu-strain-that-historically-hits-elderly-and-kids-hard-is-back-in-minnesota/601548805</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;Vercel Security Checkpoint&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="hide-mobile" data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;|&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;cle1::1766111019-HRfJNst3hEhwcZnrxQLLjaPkpgFkUlUM&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Star Tribune</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 20:06:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxPTVYyeGtNTXpwc1EzSFpZXzh3Z00xU0FTSktRTWotQ0Q1WS1NTk5UMEhHNXFyN3dOQUJ5MDhyRndvYkE2TF9HdFhWMTViT0Uwa0tkSUdUeVB4RXB2WXBnMER6OFllSnFPR2FIVFNiZzZDY2I2VVNCQTVxdlVNYXVoSHJTb2FJcG1yai1uQ2I4Nl8xaW1KV3hWQ0dsSmRJaDE1dnJEZnR3UGdIaEhuanN2SFZoMUc</guid></item><item><title>进行尸体解剖的人正在分享他们在检查尸体时发现的令人震惊的事情- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/abbyzinman/doctors-share-autopsy-stories</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-23
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139869546" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;12.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"When I was in my emergency medical services (EMS) class, my teacher brought in a death investigator and former autopsy examiner to speak to our class. She told us that while she worked as an autopsy examiner, she got this women who at the time mysteriously suffocated after a car accident. Apparently this women was driving, and while she was driving, she grabbed her lighter from her purse and was holding it in her mouth while she fumbled through her bag for her cigarettes. While doing this, she got T-boned. The airbag went off, and on the way to hospital, they kept trying to put tubes down her throat to open her airway, because she was having trouble breathing. But no luck. When they cut open her throat during the autopsy, they found her lighter jammed down there. Apparently when the airbag went off it got jammed down her throat and no one knew."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;–&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/I_Feel_Dizzzy/" target="_blank"&gt;I_Feel_Dizzzy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I often think of this type of airbag problem when I see folks wearing pointed things from their necklace chains and earrings. Pointed objects near the ears, neck, and chest just seem like welcoming signs inviting accidental death. Random? I know. But you can't unsee it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;–&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Wendy28J/" target="_blank"&gt;Wendy28J&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:01:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE1EX2QxVjdDV3h3OHhPUWw0UkVuYlotb0k3SXJpQU1Za1ZULXlUcjBtd2tuQTBmNk1xUmMzYTlUM0VpajdtdGhob1JqUldTUk5NcXpTLVhaY3Rsa3lBamJ5UFNLZE1xazl0NkRrTnpXWk9sMkE</guid></item><item><title>Verge Genomics放弃唯一的临床候选药物，以换取人工智能药物发现的根源- Fierce Biotech</title><link>https://www.fiercebiotech.com/biotech/verge-genomics-drops-sole-clinical-candidate-return-ai-drug-discovery-roots</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="col content"&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;After taking a shot at becoming a neuroscience biotech, buzzy Bay Area AI outfit Verge Genomics is dropping its only clinical asset and returning to its drug discovery roots.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The decision comes after VRG50635, the company’s lead asset for amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), failed a pre-specified efficacy analysis in a &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT06215755"&gt;phase 1 trial&lt;/a&gt;, Effie Bruzik, Verge’s vice president of operations, told Fierce Biotech.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A no-go decision was made,” Bruzik said, so the trial was terminated and did not advance to an open-label extension stage. On clinicaltrials.gov, the reason given for the termination is “lack of risk-benefit data.”&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p class="ad-container"&gt;
      &lt;dynamic-ad-slot pos="14" placeholder-id="nativeAdUnitPos14" :randomize-element-id="true" ad-id="nativeAdUnitPos14" :hide-on-desktop="false" :hide-on-mobile="false" :container-size-map="[[1,1]]" :sizes="[['fluid']]" class="inline-native-ad pos-14" :class="{ 'mobile-ad': false }"&gt;&lt;/dynamic-ad-slot&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
  

      &lt;p class="ad-container"&gt;
      &lt;dynamic-ad-slot :pos="8" :out-of-page="true" placeholder-id="content-embed-one" ad-id="contentEmbedOne" :hide-on-desktop="0" :hide-on-mobile="0"&gt;&lt;/dynamic-ad-slot&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
  

&lt;p&gt;The move away from VRG50635 leaves a preexisting deal with Ferrer in limbo. The Spanish pharma &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/biotech/ferrer-signs-122m-biobucks-deal-ex-us-license-verges-phase-1-als-therapy"&gt;licensed the ex-U.S. rights&lt;/a&gt; to the ALS asset in March 2024 in a pact potentially worth more than 112.5 million euros (then worth roughly $121.7 million).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bruzik did not respond to questions from Fierce Biotech about the status of Verge’s deal with Ferrer. At the time of publication, Ferrer had not responded to Fierce's request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;With no more candidates in the clinic, Verge is pivoting to focus solely on its machine learning drug discovery platform &lt;a href="https://www.vergegenomics.com/approach"&gt;Converge&lt;/a&gt;, Bruzik added.&lt;/p&gt;

      &lt;p&gt;
      &lt;dynamic-ad-slot :pos="11" placeholder-id="ad-slot-2_mobile" ad-id="adSlot2Mobile" :hide-on-desktop="1" :hide-on-mobile="0" :container-size-map="[[1,1]]" :sizes="[[300, 250],[320,50]]"&gt;&lt;/dynamic-ad-slot&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
  

&lt;p&gt;“Recent breakthroughs in AI foundation models has meaningfully increased demand for Verge’s multi-modal human datasets in the last 18 months, and we see a clear opportunity to drive industry-wide impact by enabling partners to improve pipeline success rates,” Bruzik said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verge intends to use a “leaner cost structure” and continued investment in its technology to scale up Converge as a means to achieve “sustainable profitability,” Bruzik explained. The company plans to divulge more details on the “strategic re-focus,” including new hires, early next year, she said. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;VRG50635 itself was originally discovered with Converge, and the tech company’s success at bringing an AI-discovered candidate into the clinic earned Verge a spot on the &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/special-reports/fierce-biotechs-2022-fierce-15#bc74093d-d80b-4bd4-aae8-7df95cee3341"&gt;Fierce 15&lt;/a&gt; list in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Founded in 2015, Verge raised a  &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/medtech/verge-genomics-gathers-32m-to-trial-its-ai-built-neuroscience-drugs"&gt;$32 million series A&lt;/a&gt;  in 2018 and then tripled it to &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/biotech/als-drug-discoverer-verge-genomics-signs-merck-lilly-nearly-100m-oversubscribed-funding"&gt;$98 million&lt;/a&gt; for a December 2021 series B that saw Eli Lilly and Merck pitch in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="omeda-promo-article-inline-after-pos10" class="olytics_injection"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lilly was already a known friend of Verge, dropping &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/biotech/eli-lilly-taps-verge-genomics-als-deal-worth-25m-upfront"&gt;$25 million upfront&lt;/a&gt; on the AI company in July 2021 to pursue new ALS candidates. AstraZeneca &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/biotech/astrazeneca-converges-verges-ai-tech-42m-rare-neurodegenerative-disease-rd-pact"&gt;followed with $42 million&lt;/a&gt; for an R&amp;amp;D pact of its own in September 2023. &lt;/p&gt;




                &lt;/div&gt;
              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fierce Biotech</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 18:09:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQREZTOXlENWV5V2pIanMybTBnY0xMN25fRHR0ZmhOeTNGOTB2SXVzLUNxeExxdzZYOVBNazFnSF9jTUxqVjFNb3Q1NXU1X0VFS0t2MHZNbXN6SFdsYk5WbjNUV2Zkal9zUGp1UldsR1hRLWwtdWRMWjdobmFwZ3hjQ1d1MUo2QWc2ZEhGUGp2YU1GV1BkV2Q0cUpwNTB6VUlJbERWNVpnM01NOVRrSlBJUC1NNA</guid></item><item><title>密歇根州放弃了RFK Jr.联邦小组的疫苗指导-底特律新闻</title><link>https://www.detroitnews.com/story/news/politics/2025/12/18/michigan-moves-away-from-kennedy-appointed-council-for-vaccine-advicemichigan-moves-away-from-kenned/87827679007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_dt"&gt;Dec. 18, 2025, 12:42 p.m. ET&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lansing&lt;/em&gt; — Michigan's top doctor issued a recommendation Thursday, advising health care providers to follow vaccine schedules for children from the American Academy of Pediatrics (AAP) or the American Academy of Family Physicians (AAFP), shifting away from guidance coming from President Donald Trump's administration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The announcement from the Michigan Department of Health and Human Services said the state had "previously looked to the federal Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) for vaccine recommendations."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who has long voiced criticism of vaccines, &lt;a href="/story/news/politics/2025/06/09/rfk-jr-ousts-entire-cdc-vaccine-advisory-committee/84122298007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;removed all 17 members of the committee in June&lt;/a&gt; and picked his own replacements. A "clean sweep" of the board was needed "to re-establish public confidence in vaccine science," Kennedy wrote in a Wall Street Journal guest column.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;But Dr. Natasha Bagdasarian, Michigan's chief medical executive, said on Thursday that public health experts across the country were not in agreement with the recent federal vaccine recommendations issued by the panel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"As the state’s chief medical executive, it is my duty to protect and promote public health, and I find the vaccine schedule recommendations produced by the AAP and AAFP well-evidenced and based on rigorous review," Badgasarian said. "This standing recommendation will help encourage vaccine accessibility and availability in Michigan.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="gnt_em gnt_em_img"&gt;&lt;img class="gnt_em_img_i" fetchpriority="high" data-g-r="lazy" data-gl-src="/gcdn/authoring/authoring-images/2025/11/21/PDTN/87392838007-ap-25316691810361.jpg?width=660&amp;amp;height=440&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp" data-gl-srcset="/gcdn/authoring/authoring-images/2025/11/21/PDTN/87392838007-ap-25316691810361.jpg?width=1320&amp;amp;height=880&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp 2x" decoding="async" alt="Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy, Jr., arrives on stage at the inaugural Make America Healthy Again summit at the Waldorf Astoria, Wednesday, Nov. 12, 2025, in Washington."&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_em_img_ccw gnt_em_img_ccw__cap gnt_em_img_ccw__crd" data-c-caption="Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy, Jr., arrives on stage at the inaugural Make America Healthy Again summit at the Waldorf Astoria, Wednesday, Nov. 12, 2025, in Washington." data-c-credit="Rod Lamkey, AP"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The press release from the state health department specifically referenced a recommendation that all newborns receive the hepatitis B vaccine at birth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Earlier this month, Kennedy’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices voted to end the longstanding recommendation that all U.S. babies get the hepatitis B vaccine, &lt;a href="/story/news/nation/2025/12/05/us-vaccine-advisers-say-not-all-babies-need-a-hepatitis-b-shot-at-birth/87622393007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;according to the Associated Press&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In the state announcement, Dr. Bashar Yalldo, president of the Michigan chapter of the Academy of Family Physicians (MAFP), said routine childhood immunizations, including the hepatitis B birth dose, are supported by decades of real-world data and an exceptional safety record.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"The MAFP encourages parents to follow evidence-based medical guidance and to speak with their family physician about protecting their newborns, families and communities," Yalldo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Michigan is one of more than a dozen states, including New York, Pennsylvania, Maine, and California, that now refer to immunization schedules from the AAP and other national medical organizations, according to the Michigan Department of Health and Human Services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In a statement, clinical leaders from Corewell Health Children's, Mott Children's Hospital, the Henry Ford Health System, Munson Health and other health care providers expressed support for Bagdasarian's recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"By following the AAP's schedule, Michigan providers will be able to confidently administer safe and effective vaccines," their statement said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;cmauger@detroitnews.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Detroit News</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggJBVV95cUxQVmZMeGlWa3FNdVFxa3d5NlZidHN3TUtaTnhxREJ6WmZic0p2RU13a20zclJwWlR1ckxLdHRZMXlIbGJMNmtSLVk5YTI0YnZpbTFwTGw5SmQ5R2Q3eDRId29WbzRZaU5FOTg4LWQyS0huVFFXc2xuU0pZUlVFdWVDbkxzR3NYX00wTWx3UlA5a2M0cU94WXdqZmw1THVfbUFERzNxd2FWY0hsSGFSVjZvd0REeldEazVPZEJJMk1tSzhkVk1NeV9FUmc0R2pPYlVncTNHcXFpeHJxb1FOVVhfOE1JUkNGWGJjRDdQd240Y01rOXliT0Z5RVktRUdFVUY5a3c</guid></item><item><title>两名威斯康星州儿童死于呼吸道疾病，国土安全部证实- 3000频道</title><link>https://www.channel3000.com/news/two-wisconsin-children-die-from-respiratory-illnesses-dhs-confirms/article_6e2f4061-fd53-49e2-a100-53b5cebae7ed.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. -- Two Wisconsin children died from respiratory illnesses, the Department of Health Services confirmed Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One child died from COVID-19 and the other died from influenza. They are the first children to die of a respiratory illness during the current respiratory virus season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a reminder about how serious these viruses can be, but it's not too late to protect yourself and your family by getting vaccinated," DHS Respiratory Disease Epidemiologist Tom Haupt said. "Respiratory vaccines are safe, effective, and the best tool we have to prevent doctor visits, hospitalization, and death for Wisconsinites."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can schedule a vaccine through your primary care provider, local health department, pharmacy or community clinic. The &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/immunization/vfc-parent.htm"&gt;Vaccines for Children program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/immunization/vfa.htm"&gt;Vaccines for Adults program&lt;/a&gt; have also been set up to help those without insurance cover the costs of vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's also important to take steps to stop the spread of germs during the times of year when respiratory viruses are more prevalent. The DHS recommends Wisconsinites:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wash hands often with soap and water for 20 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid touching their nose, eyes, and mouth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay home and away from others if feeling sick.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid being around others who are sick or have flu symptoms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cover their nose and mouth when coughing or sneezing and encourage children to do the same.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wear a high-quality mask around others to prevent the spread of respiratory illness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;​COPYRIGHT 2025 BY CHANNEL 3000. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. THIS MATERIAL MAY NOT BE PUBLISHED, BROADCAST, REWRITTEN OR REDISTRIBUTED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Channel 3000</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:24:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxPLUs2TEg3M0pWZ1EwZFlYaHlMNzlIcGcxTXBpSkxXd1Q4aExIS0FRRURQM0xFUDR3TS1uVHhQUzg1emJWMG1IX3BJNjJUYjlVNjFxUXVVSXdsaXhRV0JTSXZQdUlzRTJtbjZfYnpjNWZTOGNJbUFQdjllWjBneDBCaEFlOWxCZktiMWFTTHM1MG9SRUowQTNHanBVVUNvMHFwMVRJQkpRbWZuS0VIUmZLdy05bUNBcm1UX0U3d1BTVktxNUlZVEZFS1lBYmVMM1AtTTdCUnEwb3JmUmo2V3dKeGIxOA</guid></item><item><title>我怀疑我知道为什么我的妻子有些不对劲……就在下面。她还没有准备好听。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/sex-advice-wife-vagina-something-off.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmknsl0043uum2ha658npx@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Jessica and Rich here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbn4z9a005m3b795eoi3gjh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="114" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbn4ue1005e3b79d722fxj9@published"&gt;I am a 54-year-old man who has been married for 20-plus years to a 50-year-old woman. I had a pretty active sex life before we met, and she had some experience, but mostly just a few hook-ups, that, by her recollection, were mostly her opening her legs and letting the guy finish hurriedly. She claims that her first non-solo climax was with me and that was one reason she continued seeing me, leading to a very deep bond. Similarly, while she wasn’t particularly sexually adventurous, she was open to various positions and, honestly, after experiencing a pretty good sample size, I found her vulva and vagina to feel, taste, and look better than others.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="20" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmlizd00123b79cr861v17@published"&gt;While our frequency has declined over the years, our weekly (sometimes semi-weekly!) sex is generally fine, except for one thing.&lt;/p&gt;

    


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="61" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbni75c006q3b79ga05q5to@published"&gt;Her vagina is too loose now, and I have trouble getting enough friction to cum. This is new to me, because while I am not much longer than average, I had always been told that my erections are much thicker than other guys’ and had always found every partner to be “tight.” Would 25 years of active sex “stretch” her out?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="123" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmlj1200133b79dypujxy3@published"&gt;This has been building for a few years, and yes, now that I am older, it takes a little bit more “action” for me to finish. We’ve tried various positions and some work better than others, but in general, it just gets tiresome thrusting away as she visibly loses interest a few minutes after her orgasm (which happens in all but our most hurried sessions). While she will give some half-hearted licks, she doesn’t like giving oral—especially after penetration—and we tried anal a couple of times, but neither of us is really into that. So most of our sessions end with me jacking off next to her, while she is obviously content and thinking about other things, which sometimes kills the vibe completely.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="115" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmlj3700143b79ofpz18zt@published"&gt;I’ve mentioned to her a few times to “try to squeeze it,” but she just sort of laughs it off, which also tracks with her generally viewing sex as something that the man puts most of the effort into. Plus, while I enjoy taking the lead in bed, I don’t like telling her what to do sexually or otherwise. I don’t want to hurt her feelings, and this isn’t the most important thing, but I’ve had trouble getting the point across that now that we are older, I need her to put a little more effort into it, whether that be Kegels, something to tighten up, or more active participation in our sessions. Any advice?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbn4dwq004k3b793f4plr9z@published"&gt;—Worn Out&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjbn4gdk004r3b79i3rr4aco@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmjbn4nvh00553b79wpety3l7@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjbn4ihw004y3b79x9gqemwd@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="48" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmlj5700153b79df7ue3v9@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica Stoya: &lt;/strong&gt;Oh, boy. His sentence, “And this isn’t the most important thing,” is perfunctory and performative. I feel like the writer had a sense that people might judge the language used and the issue at hand, and felt like he had to say it’s not that important.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="21" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmug2t001b3b792ubt1q29@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich Juzwiak: &lt;/strong&gt;Right. It’s important for our purposes: It’s the focus of the letter, and that’s what we’re here to address.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuhu1001h3b792ulsb8wk@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica:&lt;/strong&gt; It’s also clearly pretty important for him. Would 25 years of sex stretch her out? That’s not how things work. Also, our writer likely had very little opportunity to learn in his lifetime whether that is or is not how things work. But both sexes tend to lose pelvic floor tone as they age, regardless of how much sex they’ve had, how big any penises might have been, whether pregnancy has happened and a woman has given birth, fisting, orgasming, etc. It’s just age. Often, women who have given birth are given access to the tools to maintain pelvic floor function as part of the recovery process.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="94" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuk4f001n3b79u8e59tl9@published"&gt;My biggest concern at the moment is how to get the wife into the kind of doctor who can evaluate whether some pelvic floor therapy needs to happen, regardless of how the sex is going to feel for this guy. When you get into your 60s and 70s, if you don’t have a strong pelvic floor, stuff can start to prolapse, you can have urinary and bowel leakage, it’s not a good scene, and it’s a lot easier to intervene earlier than to be like, “I’m 70, and I can’t control my pelvic floor.”&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="83" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmumhg001t3b798xajsuu2@published"&gt;In order to achieve that, I’m pretty sure he’s going to have to put sexual satisfaction on a shelf and just focus on saying, “I think this is something you should mention to your doctor.” He can do that with the knowledge that it’s likely to help her pelvis tighten back up. But often, in these kinds of discussions, if you portray it as just kind of a sex thing, the person who’s not particularly invested in sex is going to dismiss it.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="103" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuq8m001z3b79zahotwr2@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;Yeah, it’ll just seem selfish and insulting. But that’s why I think the letter writer has to position himself as an expert. There’s nobody who knows the feel of her vagina as he does; they’re monogamous. Also, hormonal changes can create a different kind of effect. What he is feeling in terms of looseness is an estimate; it’s his assessment. He’s not the expert on what’s going on; he’s just the expert in the fact that &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt; is going on. He can tell her that he’s noticed something’s a little bit different, and so she might want to get that looked at.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="33" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmus6h00253b79skjfgg39@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica: &lt;/strong&gt;Also, sometimes penises get smaller or less hard on average as time goes on, so it could be that a portion of the difference in friction is because he’s shrinking a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="137" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmutzn002b3b79codyhevs@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;Exactly. Obviously, a PDE5 inhibitor would be useful in keeping you at full mast. You will shrink sometimes because there’s just not as much blood going into your dick, so if you can get that going using some medication, then you may retain your previous max size, and maybe that would actually give you a change in sensation as well. In a long session like that, especially with a partner who’s kind of just going along for the ride, there can be a distracting element of, “Well, this isn’t ideal in terms of the titillation I’m feeling, so is my erection going to go away?” Then that gets into your head, and it affects the sex. So that’s why the ED drugs are useful beyond the blood flow; they help with the psychology of it sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="127" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuvrj002h3b79zzcbun5h@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica:&lt;/strong&gt; It’s really great that our writer was able to be, it turns out, permanently the person who can help his wife have an orgasm. And I always prefer when men who enjoy sex with women err on the side of prioritizing the woman’s orgasm. That said, in the same way that when I’m having sex with a man, I know once they have an orgasm, my fun is finished, so I kind of factor for that, he might consider trying to aim for sex where she doesn’t orgasm until right before he’s about to, and that’s probably going to result in her staying engaged throughout. Lots of women do have one orgasm and go, “Yeah, I’m done now.” I would roll over and go to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="151" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuxk1002n3b799ux9p3va@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;Right. And I understand that these issues are important for the writer, but look, you’re having regular sex decades into your relationship, and she’s coming. What he describes in terms of her coming and then he’s jacking himself off is a really common thing that happens. I see it a lot myself in my own experiences. In terms of gay male sex, bottoms, if they come, a lot of the time, they can’t keep taking the dick; it’s just too much, and so then the top finishes himself off. Of course, you want people to be engaged and to enjoy that along with you until the end, but there are worse things. The way that they’ve sorted it out is what I would recommend. So yes, this isn’t optimal. I understand you want it to be even better, but a little perspective is called for. It’s still pretty damn good.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="38" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuzby002t3b797t7kz219@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica:&lt;/strong&gt; From the context of a very heteronormative relationship that I’m in now, it’s often a similar experience in those contexts. It’s rare for both people to have the Bridgerton-style, coming at the same time kind of moment.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="102" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv1d6002z3b79al3gdm8w@published"&gt;We can often get these scripts in our heads of how sex is supposed to play out. In the context of a long-term relationship, you can develop a very specific and almost rigid routine. So keep in mind you don’t have to adhere to a routine that isn’t working. You also don’t have to switch to one other routine. Sometimes she finishes, and you’re there jacking off. Sometimes you aim for her to orgasm just before you do. Maybe every once in a while it doesn’t happen for her, that’s probably going to be OK, and sometimes you can do other things.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="101" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv3f200353b7997tuksg9@published"&gt;Then, just to address his thing about positions: My instinct is that positions where her lower back is quite arched in one direction or another, or her legs are pressed together, even crossed, are going to be the positions where there’s more of a sensation of tightness. As much as I really love and support open dialogue, if that’s not going to function or if he needs to not mention sex at all to tell her that it would be a good idea to mention the pelvic floor changes to a doctor, he can  just casually go for positions that feel tighter.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="23" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv55x003b3b7950hqhr4p@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;Yes. But obviously, ideally, talking about this as gently as possible, and not using words like loose, is the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="14" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv6hg003h3b79ubv9iqkt@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica: &lt;/strong&gt;Do not say anything about sample sizes or better or worse than others.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="69" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv89g003n3b79kqn1i41i@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;It’s funny, because a lot of the time, my advice is to use the letter sent in as a template for how to talk about it with your partner. This is one of those letters that’s not the template. You don’t want to go into a lot of this stuff just for the sake of being heard; you don’t want to hurt her feelings and shut her down.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv9sk003t3b79v9ee21r9@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica: &lt;/strong&gt;I would prioritize saying, “It seems like there are some physical changes. I would really love it if you’d mention that to your primary care or gynecologist next time you see them.” Then, when addressing the sex, do your best to make it a neutral issue. Err on the side of it being your own issue. If it’s true that his erections are not as firm as five, 10 years ago, use that, just because this kind of stuff is not easy to hear, especially for women who are aging and don’t really have that much of an investment in sexual pleasure to begin &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;with.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmjbn443e00463b793dgukvn1@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="82" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbn41pg003z3b79feyftsrj@published"&gt;I’m 64 and my husband is 65. We’ve been together for nearly 40 years. He is still crazy about me, thinks I’m beautiful and sensual, and has always had a much higher sex drive than I have. In fact, since my breast cancer surgery seven years ago and the estrogen-blocking medicines I’ve been on, my sex drive is pretty much zero. But he’s loyal and honorable so he’d never have an affair or pay for sex, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/03/husband-fantasy-cheating-sex-advice.html"&gt;so he’s devised a different routine…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmjbmknsl0046uum25c3v2zfb@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE9HWFp2bHBJV0N6TXFDR2M0RUF1MUhfcVQ5Uk5iTHNpQ01IUXpjRTV0YlY1ZDRpVnp0RXVtSDNyN3pjMGxlLURfNWQ5QzBRUXkyb2dHZFBTOVNmX2tabzZxNnB0cGJFazRYdTZBZVp4M1A4Qll1MllTQ1pIME5zMGM</guid></item><item><title>根据专家的说法，所有降低胆固醇的食物- GQ</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/all-the-foods-that-lower-cholesterol-according-to-experts</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. has a &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/what-is-ldl-cholesterol-and-how-do-you-lower-it"&gt;cholesterol&lt;/a&gt; problem. Roughly &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.americashealthrankings.org/explore/measures/High_Chol" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.americashealthrankings.org/explore/measures/High_Chol"}' href="https://www.americashealthrankings.org/explore/measures/High_Chol" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;37% of Americans&lt;/a&gt; have high cholesterol, a statistic that’s likely underreported, considering that, according to &lt;a href="http://google.com/url?q=https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamacardiology/fullarticle/2811350&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;source=docs&amp;amp;ust=1765993289197644&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw2FElvu2xrMvjt8dRON0ocN"&gt;a 2023 study&lt;/a&gt;, many people with high cholesterol don’t know they have it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem specifically is low-density lipoprotein, or &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/what-is-ldl-cholesterol-and-how-do-you-lower-it"&gt;LDL cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;, which clogs arteries when there’s too much of it. This is different from high-density lipoprotein (HDL), which transports cholesterol to the liver, where it’s broken down and excreted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-offer-url="https://findcare.nuvancehealth.org/provider/sunny-s-intwala/1746052" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://findcare.nuvancehealth.org/provider/sunny-s-intwala/1746052"}' href="https://findcare.nuvancehealth.org/provider/sunny-s-intwala/1746052" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Sunny S. Intwala, MD,&lt;/a&gt; a preventive cardiologist with Nuvance Health in New York, says that high cholesterol often flies under the radar. Even if you’re young and in good shape, if your diet and lifestyle habits don’t support healthy cholesterol levels, it will catch up with you. “You can be lean, fit, and young, and still silently be accumulating plaque in your arteries,” Dr. Intwala says. “Your arteries don’t care how good your &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/vo2-max-2"&gt;VO2max&lt;/a&gt; is. Supporting healthy cholesterol levels is about protecting your future health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279318/"&gt;High cholesterol is literally life-threatening&lt;/a&gt;. It increases the risk of heart attack and cardiovascular disease, which is the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/leading-causes-of-death.htm"&gt;number one cause of death in the U.S&lt;/a&gt;. Here’s the good news: It’s completely controllable, and the sooner you have cholesterol-supporting habits in place, the better. A major part of that has to do with what you’re eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to lower cholesterol through diet and lifestyle&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.columbiacardiology.org/profile/corey-k-bradley-md" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.columbiacardiology.org/profile/corey-k-bradley-md"}' href="https://www.columbiacardiology.org/profile/corey-k-bradley-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Corey K. Bradley, MD, FACC&lt;/a&gt;, a preventive cardiologist at Columbia University Irving Medical Center, roughly 20 to 30% of high cholesterol is controllable through diet and lifestyle habits. The rest, she says, comes down to whether you are genetically predisposed to have high cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Bradley says that roughly one in 250 people has a genetic disorder called &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/cholesterol/genetic-conditions/familial-hypercholesterolemia-fh"&gt;familial hypercholesterolemia (FH)&lt;/a&gt;, an inherited disorder leading to extremely high LDL cholesterol and must be treated with medication, along with diet and lifestyle interventions. “You can be the picture of health on the outside, but still have really dangerous levels of LDL cholesterol,” she says, emphasizing that this is why it’s important for everyone to have their cholesterol levels checked at least every couple of years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/how-to-lower-your-cholesterol"&gt;the 20% and 30% that is in your control&lt;/a&gt;, all three cardiologists we spoke to advise a combination of not smoking, &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/how-many-days-a-week-should-you-work-out-2#:~:text=In%20real%20life%2C%20GQ's%20fitness,and%20abilities%2C%E2%80%9D%20he%20says."&gt;exercising regularly&lt;/a&gt;, and following a heart-healthy diet. Dr. Bradley is a big advocate of following the &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/what-is-mediterranean-diet-3"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;, which has been repeatedly scientifically shown to keep LDL cholesterol low. This way of eating prioritizes seafood, lean proteins, vegetables, fruit, and whole grains, while minimizing ultra-processed foods and fatty meats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GQ</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:23:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOT0IxSzRPSThUejN6QURtendVZTM5R1lINzh3YjlsaEJZRGc3ZktJQVhUSEtiS25ZcnRwdW9Wc2tlLUJUWHdiZG1qcmFPUmZIYkxfaGtWNW8zM3o5RXhXX1RzM1ZPMEZObXE2ZmJCeU4tWFZwNGJIZl9VbWRLNWhwZDFXUGd0X2o5cEE</guid></item><item><title>以色列研究：未治疗的妊娠期慢性甲状腺疾病增加儿童自闭症风险-以色列时报</title><link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-study-untreated-chronic-thyroid-condition-in-pregnancy-ups-autism-risk-in-children/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="the-content"&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;Israeli scientists say that women with persistent thyroid hormone imbalance during their pregnancy may be at an increased risk of having children with autism spectrum disorder (ASD).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their new peer-reviewed study tracked thyroid levels in more than 51,000 pregnant women. The study found that children of women with long-lasting, untreated thyroid hormone imbalance during pregnancy had about two to three cases of autism per 100 children, compared with about one case per 100 in the general population.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Women who had a chronic thyroid condition that went untreated and got worse during pregnancy had a greater risk of having children with autism than pregnant women who were adequately treated,” Prof. Idan Menashe of Ben-Gurion University of the Negev, the study’s lead author, said in a phone call.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p id="gpt-passback"&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;However, the scientists found that when a pregnant woman’s chronic thyroid dysfunction was “adequately treated,” there was no association with increased autism risk in her offspring, said Menashe, who is head of Ben-Gurion’s Department of Epidemiology, Biostatistics and Community Health Sciences, and the scientific director of the Azrieli National Center for Autism and Neurodevelopment Research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ben-Gurion researcher Leena Elbedour, May Weinberg of the Meir Medical Center and Tel Aviv University, Analya Michaelovski of Soroka University Medical Center, and Prof. Gal Meiri, also of Soroka University and Ben-Gurion University, collaborated on the study, which recently appeared in &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jcem/advance-article/doi/10.1210/clinem/dgaf596/8339900"&gt;The Journal of Clinical Endocrinology &amp;amp; Metabolism&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter newsletter-article" data-website="timesofisrael" data-from="Israeli study: Untreated chronic thyroid condition in pregnancy ups autism risk in children"&gt;
	&lt;div class="newsletter-article-inner"&gt;
		&lt;p class="newsletter-article-text newsletter-article-part"&gt;
			&lt;span&gt;Get The Times of Israel's Daily Edition&lt;/span&gt;
			&lt;span&gt;by email and never miss our top stories&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="newsletter-article-form-wrapper newsletter-article-part"&gt;
			
			&lt;div class="newsletter-article-terms"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
				By signing up, you agree to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/terms"&gt;terms&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class="newsletter-error newsletter-article-error"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
		
&lt;h3&gt;Thyroid hormones contribute to brain development.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thyroid is a small, butterfly-shaped gland at the front of the neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thyroid hormones regulate the body’s metabolism, which is how the body uses and manages energy. These hormones also play a crucial role in essential processes such as heart rate regulation and the body’s muscle control.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3704008" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/idanMenashe-copy.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-3704008" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/idanMenashe-copy-640x400.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Prof. Idan Menashe, head of the Epidemiology, Biostatistics and Community Health Sciences Department and the Scientific Director of the Azrieli National Center for Autism and Neurodevelopment Research at Ben-Gurion University of the Negev. (Courtesy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thyroid hormones also support the production of myelin, an insulating, fatty coating around nerve fibers. These allow electrical signals to travel between the brain and body more quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;During pregnancy, a woman’s thyroid hormone is essential for the neurodevelopment of the fetus. Studies have shown the association of a woman’s thyroid imbalance with atypical neurodevelopment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the thyroid produces the right amount of hormone, it is considered to be within the normal range, or balanced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a pregnant woman’s thyroid hormone levels are too low, doctors usually prescribe an artificial hormone that safely replaces the missing hormone.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_2905684" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1401898908.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-2905684" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1401898908-640x400.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustrative: a doctor carrying out checks for an autoimmune thyroid disease. (swpispix; iStock by Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Children with autism may have delayed or absent speech, difficulties with social interaction, motor impairment, and repetitive behavior, with a spectrum of severity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Around the world, autism spectrum disorder diagnoses have increased, including in Israel. A recent Israeli &lt;a href="https://www.bgu.ac.il/en/news-and-articles/dinstein-autism-prevalence/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found the number of ASD cases had quadrupled from 2017 to 2021 in two- and three-year-old children, and doubled in older ages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Thyroid imbalance during pregnancy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists have studied the connection between a woman’s thyroid levels during pregnancy and her child’s development. However, most earlier studies checked the thyroid hormone once, usually early in pregnancy, and not throughout the pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;Menashe’s research, done at Soroka Medical Center, followed more than 51,000 births between January 2011 and December 2017 in a retrospective cohort study, with a follow-up through January 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using blood-test data and the women’s medical records, the team divided the mothers into four groups: those with no thyroid problems, those with a chronic thyroid condition whose hormones were balanced in pregnancy, those with thyroid imbalance only during pregnancy, and those who had both a chronic thyroid condition and imbalance during pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This gave researchers the data to compare the women’s thyroid levels during pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What surprised me is that only the last group, those who had both a chronic thyroid condition and were imbalanced during pregnancy, were at risk of having a child with autism,” Menashe said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scientists also observed that the longer the duration of thyroid dysfunction across trimesters, the higher the risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We don’t really know the cause,” Menashe said. “But we know there is a link between them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When asked if he could calculate the specific percentage of risk, the scientist replied, “Not exactly, because this is not the exact way to assess risk. All we can say is that we see an increased risk, or more exactly, untreated thyroid problems are associated with an increased risk of autism.”&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3708009" class="wp-caption  alignright"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/8597643e-4c7b-491e-a8ad-9de121448a75.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-vertical wp-image-3708009" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/8597643e-4c7b-491e-a8ad-9de121448a75-300x480.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Dr. Dorit Shmueli, a specialist in neurology and child development and child development coordinator at Clalit Health Services. (Courtesy/Hagai Shmueli)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Dorit Shmueli, a specialist in neurology and child development and the Child Development Coordinator in Clalit Health Services, told The Times of Israel that research on the safety and importance of balancing hypothyroidism in pregnancy is “essential.”&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;“Optimal maternal thyroid function plays a key role in supporting healthy fetal brain development, and understanding how best to manage it can directly influence the developmental outcomes we see in children, especially autism spectrum disorder,” said Shmueli, who was not involved in the study. “Evidence-based insights from Prof. Idan Menashe’s research are crucial for informing clinical guidance and improving long-term well-being in the populations we serve.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers believe there is “some mechanism where the imbalance in the maternal thyroid hormone affects the neurodevelopment of the fetus,” Menashe said. “Eventually, this abnormal neurodevelopment is translated into autism in the child.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Israeli Medical Association, following international guidelines, recommends that thyroid levels be monitored in pregnant women who are already being treated for thyroid imbalance. However, it does not recommend universal screening because treating mild thyroid problems has not been shown to clearly improve pregnancy or neurodevelopmental outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When asked whether there has been a change in the Health Ministry’s policy about routine thyroid screening, Menashe said, “I don’t think doctors change the protocols based on one study.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Health Ministry did not respond to a query about this issue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Menashe said that more research is needed to “really study these mechanisms in animal models on a molecular level, and to specifically test these hypotheses.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until then, he said, the findings “underscore the need for routine monitoring and timely adjustment of therapy to maintain normal thyroid hormone levels throughout pregnancy.”&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;

				
				

					
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of Israel</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:06:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxOSDU4UEY1Wk5aMWRxdXBOall2UXVpZzFUSEw2MmY1WWJhdm52WkY1RklVdEFLdW9IMjAyMTZXSkZVN2lOMktsWk1PRzdKM0E5QVRKXzhDUWFpbWxiQVJySkwzSWF1LVpKUXdEWHRYMGZQd1VGUkhJbEt3ZFZ1OU02R0dPU2NRZ0xXWndPLW5VN190SmxJWC0wa1ZoTklmeHFZSEZZRlZ5OHdORTZIVWxLRWpGY055Um0tUHI3U1F30gHDAUFVX3lxTE1Hdk1tWHNJLS1udnhqd0N0emxlaWxoaEU4Z0lnLUhjYVByU1FUb3k3MnQ3NWt6MTU5Uy1wSnk4TkRrcUhlODBsN3lld3d2anZzekFnRTNnOVJVZ0J4di1mVFAxNnRuRjRJNDVEYjJxMWF0YUtqZG9KQ2QzZjVaamlzbmVIUF9XcF9tanJDX0Zad1lNYXN1dUw4Yzk0alh3dGkwZjdTb0RvX2EtTm9ZYnhjcmhSSFM1SDJTbVI1b0wweU40WQ</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心为有争议的丹麦研究人员开展的乙型肝炎疫苗研究提供160万$ - CIDRAP</title><link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/cdc-awards-16-million-hepatitis-b-vaccine-study-controversial-danish-researchers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) &lt;a href="https://public-inspection.federalregister.gov/2025-23245.pdf"&gt;has awarded an unsolicited $1.6 million grant&lt;/a&gt; for vaccine research to Danish researchers whose studies &lt;a href="https://health.au.dk/en/display/artikel/randomized-trials-show-no-evidence-of-non-specific-vaccine-effects"&gt;have been challenged&lt;/a&gt; by mainstream scientists but &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/news/the-impact-of-vaccines-on-mortality-decline-since-1900-according-to-published-science/"&gt;championed by anti-vaccine activists,&lt;/a&gt; including Health and Human Services (HHS) Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a notice in the &lt;em&gt;Federal Register&lt;/em&gt; posted yesterday, the CDC is paying the University of Southern Denmark to conduct a single-blind clinical trial of the hepatitis B vaccine in newborns in Guinea-Bissau, a small country in West Africa with exceptionally high rates of maternal and infant mortality, where nearly one in five people &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31746078/#:~:text=Results:%20A%20total%20of%202715,enqu%C3%AAtes%20dans%20la%20population%20g%C3%A9n%C3%A9rale."&gt;are infected with the hepatitis B virus.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC is an agency within HHS. The study aims to assess the optimal timing and delivery of hepatitis B vaccinations, according to the notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;‘Appearance of blatant cronyism’&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study was awarded without any competition from any other scientists, giving it “the appearance of blatant cronyism,” said Angela Rasmussen, PhD, a virologist and professor at the University of Saskatchewan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the federal announcement did not include the names of the researchers, the Danish university’s Bandim Health Project, which has conducted vaccine research in the developing African country for decades, &lt;a href="https://Although%20the%20federal%20announcement%20did%20not%20include%20the%20names%20of%20the%20researchers,%20the%20Danish%20university%E2%80%99s%20Bandim%20Health%20Project,%20which%20has%20conducted%20vaccine%20research%20in%20the%20developing%20African%20country%20for%20decades,%20has%20acknowledged%20being%20awarded%20the%20CDC%20grant."&gt;has acknowledged being awarded&lt;/a&gt; the CDC grant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Bandim project leaders &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/vaccines-have-health-effects-beyond-protecting-against-target-diseases-106383"&gt;have claimed to find “non-specific effects”&lt;/a&gt; from vaccines—some good and some bad—that they say &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10116894/pdf/40264_2023_Article_1295.pdf"&gt;should change how vaccine safety studies&lt;/a&gt; are conducted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their message has &lt;a href="https://www.weekendavisen.dk/samfund/et-daarligt-immunforsvar"&gt;resonated with Kennedy,&lt;/a&gt; a long-time anti-vaccine activist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In June, Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/kennedy-pulls-us-support-gavis-vaccine-efforts"&gt;used a single study&lt;/a&gt; by the Bandim group &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/07/01/g-s1-74752/rfk-jr-vaccines-safety-gavi"&gt;to justify canceling&lt;/a&gt; more than $1 billion in funding for childhood vaccinations in developing countries. The observational study found an increased risk of death in children who received a combined vaccine for diphtheria, tetanus and pertussis (DPT) that hasn’t been used in the United States in three decades. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists say people shouldn’t put too much faith in that study, which is an outlier and conflicts with hundreds of studies showing that vaccines are safe and save lives. Researchers and policy makers normally consider the totality of scientific evidence on vaccines, rather than a single study, which may be flawed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, observational studies, in which scientists merely follow patients but do not randomly assign them to undergo different medical interventions, are not able to prove cause and effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet Children’s Health Defense, the anti-vaccine organization Kennedy founded, &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/research_category/dtap-tdap/#:~:text=Blok%20BA%2C%20de%20Bree%20LCJ%2C%20Diavatopoulos%20DA%2C,van%20Crevel%20R%2C%20Benn%20CS%2C%20Netea%20MG."&gt;cites the Danish group’s research&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/research_tags/diphtheria-tetanus-pertusis-dtp/"&gt;multiple pages&lt;/a&gt; of its website. One article &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/news/the-impact-of-vaccines-on-mortality-decline-since-1900-according-to-published-science/"&gt;praises the Bandim Health’s founder,&lt;/a&gt; Danish anthropologist Peter Aaby, casting him as a martyr who lost his funding when he suggested vaccines cause more harm than good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple scientists have criticized the Bandim group’s methodology and conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A review &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0264410X25012344"&gt;published in &lt;em&gt;Vaccine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; last month found that Bandim Health researchers “have systematically over-interpreted the findings from their randomized trials” for 25 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 23 out of 25 articles, the researchers highlighted secondary findings as support for their theories, but in 22 of these cases the evidence disappeared after proper statistical handling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group “systematically selected and highlighted results that supported their theories, while downplaying the fact that they did not confirm the primary hypothesis the trials were actually designed to test,” said Henrik Stovring, PhD, a professor of biomedicine at Denmark’s Aarhus University who led the new review, &lt;a href="https://health.au.dk/en/display/artikel/randomized-trials-show-no-evidence-of-non-specific-vaccine-effects"&gt;in a press release&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In 23 out of 25 articles, the researchers highlighted secondary findings as support for their theories, but in 22 of these cases the evidence disappeared after proper statistical handling,” said Stovring said, who is &lt;span&gt;also a professor at the Steno Diabetes Center Aarhus&lt;/span&gt;. “When you look at the overall picture, there are almost no real findings left.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two reviews commissioned by the World Health Organization &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/355/bmj.i5434#:~:text=Taken%20together%2C%20the%20two%20systematic,countries%20is%20the%20only%20alternative."&gt;concluded that the evidence for non-specific effects&lt;/a&gt; “remains weak and vulnerable to biases.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Danish media also &lt;a href="https://www.weekendavisen.dk/samfund/et-daarligt-immunforsvar"&gt;have criticized&lt;/a&gt; Aaby and Christine Stabell Benn, MD, PhD, his wife and research partner, for &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/05/19/tracy-beth-hoeg-fda-advisor-marty-makary-vinay-prasad-vaccine-policy/#:~:text=Stabell%20Benn%20and%20her%20husband,results%20of%20the%20observational%20study."&gt;touting the findings of their observational study&lt;/a&gt; while &lt;a href="https://www.sensible-med.com/p/the-false-narrative-of-nonspecific"&gt;failing to publish the results&lt;/a&gt; of a randomized controlled trial—considered the gold standard of medical evidence—on the DPT vaccine, conducted 14 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By commissioning the new vaccine study, the Trump administration’s is trying “to do anything they can to discredit all vaccines,” said Peter Hotez, MD, PhD, endowed chair of tropical pediatrics at Texas Children’s Hospital and co-director of its Center for Vaccine Development. “This is so self-defeating for the country.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Danish researchers have influenced US vaccine policy&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet Aaby and Stabell Benn have found an audience in an influential federal advisory group whose members were handpicked by Kennedy, who fired all of the previous members. The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, which advises the CDC, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-09-18-19/effects-hep-b-vax-summary-508.pdf"&gt;cited the Guinea-Bissau research multiple times&lt;/a&gt; in a presentation at its September meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stabell Benn has &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-09-18-19/01-levi-covid-508.pdf"&gt;served as an expert source&lt;/a&gt; for ACIP and &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/how-the-next-four-years-can-improve-our-evidence-base/id1629371129?i=1000680049921"&gt;has collaborated&lt;/a&gt; on a Substack post and a series of podcasts with a senior leader at the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), Tracy Beth Hoeg, MD, PhD, who attends the committee’s meetings on behalf of agency. Hoeg previously &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/about-fda/fda-organization/tracy-hoeg"&gt;worked as an adjunct associate&lt;/a&gt; professor at the University of Southern Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role="group" class="caption caption-img align-left"&gt;
&lt;img alt="Vaccine needle and vial" src="/sites/default/files/Vax%20needle%20entering%20vial.jpg" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Peter Hansen / iStock&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At an ACIP meeting this month, Hoeg &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-12-04-05/01-Hoeg-Danish-vax-schedule-508.pdf"&gt;presented slides&lt;/a&gt; about vaccination practices in&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Denmark, suggesting that the United States follow that country’s approach. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within hours, President Donald Trump &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/12/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-begins-process-to-align-u-s-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/"&gt;called for the US to align&lt;/a&gt; its childhood vaccination schedule with those of countries such as Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither Stabell Benn nor Aaby responded to a request for an interview by deadline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An HHS spokesman said the study in Guinea-Bissau will fill a vital need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This award supports an independent study designed to answer important questions about the broader health effects of the hepatitis B birth dose,” said Andrew Nixon. “This research aims to fill existing evidence gaps to help inform global hepatitis B vaccine policy and we will ensure the highest scientific and ethical standards are met.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In spite of strenuous objections from three physicians on the committee, ACIP earlier this month &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/anti-science/cdc-advisers-drop-decades-old-universal-hepatitis-b-birth-dose-recommendation-suggest"&gt;voted to abandon&lt;/a&gt; a 34-year-old recommendation to vaccinate all newborns for hepatitis B, a practice that has reduced infections in children and adolescents by 99%. Since 1991, the universal HBV birth dose &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/vaccinating-newborns-against-hepatitis-b-saves-lives-why-might-cdc-panel-stop"&gt;has prevented an estimated&lt;/a&gt; 90,100 childhood deaths. Its safety &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/sites/default/files/searchable-download/Universal%20Hepatitis%20B%20Vaccination%20at%20Birth%202Dec2025.pdf"&gt;has been demonstrated in hundreds&lt;/a&gt; of studies over the past four decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The acting CDC director this week &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/hepatitis/cdc-accepts-acip-s-hepatitis-b-vaccine-recommendations-babies"&gt;followed ACIP advice&lt;/a&gt;, recommending a birth dose of hepatitis B vaccine only for babies who mothers are infected with the virus or whose infection status is unknown. The change &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/cidrap-op-ed-heres-what-removal-hepatitis-b-birth-dose-will-look"&gt;will lead more babies to develop hepatitis B&lt;/a&gt;, which can lead to liver cancer, liver failure and death, wrote Jake Scott, MD, a clinical associate professor of infectious disease and geographic medicine at Stanford University School of Medicine, in an editorial for CIDRAP News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Cherry-picking studies and researchers&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple researchers who spoke to CIDRAP News questioned the need for another study of hepatitis B vaccines, which &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/sites/default/files/searchable-download/Universal%20Hepatitis%20B%20Vaccination%20at%20Birth%202Dec2025.pdf"&gt;have been proven safe and effective&lt;/a&gt; in more than 400 studies over 40 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The data that supports the safety advocacy of the current hepatitis B vaccines is very robust,” said Amesh A. Adalja, MD, a senior scholar at the Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Given the stance of the CDC under RFK Jr’s control, one can assume that the results of this study will be preordained to be against the hepatitis B vaccines,” Adalja said. “Continuing to do studies on a question that is already been answered sufficiently is a waste of resources that could better be used answering new questions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some researchers question where the Trump administration found $1.6 million for the study, given that it &lt;a href="https://www.americanprogress.org/article/mapping-federal-funding-cuts-to-us-colleges-and-universities/#:~:text=According%20to%20the%20Trump%20administration,claiming%20as%20victories%20thus%20far."&gt;has cut billions of dollars&lt;/a&gt; in federal support for science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“NIH is in crisis, grants are being terminated, labs are closing, researchers are being laid off,” Scott told CIDRAP News. “But they found $1.6 million for an unsolicited proposal to study whether we should delay a vaccine we’ve been safely giving for 40 years, in a country where infants are at high risk of infection. The money exists. It’s the priorities that have changed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists said the new study raises ethical concerns on several fronts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Awarding money to an organization without allowing other scientists to compete for the grant is very unusual, Rasmussen said. When this happens, the study protocol typically undergoes rigorous review.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HHS has not released details of the study, noting only that the research will involve a “comparable study of the optimal timing and delivery of … hepatitis vaccinations on newborns in Guinea-Bissau. Activities will include conducting a randomized controlled trial to assess the effects of neonatal hepatitis B vaccination on early-life mortality, morbidity, and long-term developmental outcomes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rasmussen notes that it would not be ethical to provide a birth dose of the hepatitis B vaccine to some babies but not others, given that doctors know the immunization saves lives, both in the early newborn period and decades later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exposing thousands of babies to “a significant risk” of hepatitis B “in a low-income country with limited health care resources” would be “wildly unethical and a disgraceful use of American taxpayer money,” Rasmussen said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers note that Guinea-Bissau, &lt;a href="https://www.afdb.org/en/countries/west-africa/guinea-bissau/guinea-bissau-economic-outlook#:~:text=According%20to%20World%20Bank%20data,an%20estimated%203.9%25%20in%202023."&gt;has a poverty rate of 60%&lt;/a&gt; and a population of 2.2 million, about 150 times smaller than the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you commission research after making a decision, you're not looking for answers—you're looking for validation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Guinea-Bissau study’s findings are unlikely to be relevant to US vaccine policy, given the nation “has very different population demographics from the US and has a health system which is very different from the US,” said Robert H. Hopkins Jr., MD, medical director of the National Foundation for Infectious Diseases (NFID). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott said the study’s announcement suggests that the CDC isn’t truly looking for answers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In evidence-based policy, you gather data and then make a decision,” Scott said. “This is the reverse. CDC made the policy decision and then funded research to back it up. When you commission research after making a decision, you're not looking for answers—you're looking for validation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This story and headline were updated shortly after the story was published after the Bandim group confirmed that they are the recipients of the CDC funding.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:59:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxPWWJCbk8zR2NVbmFydnpQMXg0dGpfbm1FWWVpd1ROTW5EMm13UU1jaDdXZExfOWdfRVVoVy1Leko4RjJSS1h0NERDX0xxazlERkY0QmJLN1NoanZHM0dRWjFqRmxFTGdIX3NHdkxzd2Z1NjlZdG5QeU1OTGN2M2R3SmhHT255MmozVDhtSXNNU1BSTVViNHZZek9RY0VJdWh6ZXhXQnJnYXhwUzdDZWVMa2d2OGpmTFhoak5EbWoyUlhpZThl</guid></item><item><title>咒骂会让你更强壮吗？科学说是。- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/12/does-swearing-make-you-stronger-science-says-yes/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;The result: Only the F-word had any effect on pain outcomes. The team also measured the subjects’ pain threshold, asking them to indicate when the ice water began to feel painful. Those who chanted the F-word waited longer before indicating they felt pain—in other words, the swearing increased their threshold for pain. Chanting “fouch” or “twizpipe” had no effect on either measure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;F@%*-ing go for it&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this latest study, Stephens was interested in investigating potential mechanisms for swearing as a possible form of disinhibition (usually viewed negatively), building on his team’s &lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2018-06780-014"&gt;2018&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35135411/"&gt;2022&lt;/a&gt; papers showing that swearing can improve strength in a chair push-up task. “In many situations, people hold themselves back—consciously or unconsciously—from using their full strength,” &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1110041?"&gt;said Stephens&lt;/a&gt;. “By swearing, we throw off social constraint and allow ourselves to push harder in different situations. Swearing is an easily available way to help yourself feel focused, confident and less distracted, and ‘go for it’ a little more.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In two separate experiments, participants were asked to select a swear word they’d normally use after, say, bumping their head, and a more neutral word to describe an inanimate object like a table. They then performed the aforementioned chair push-up task: sitting on a sturdy chair and placing their hands under their thighs with the fingers pointed inwards. Then they lifted their feet off the floor and straightened their arms to support their body weight for as long as possible, chanting either the swear word or the neutral word every two seconds. Afterward, subjects competed a questionnaire to assess various aspects of their mental state during the task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results: Subjects who swore during the task could support their body weight much longer than those who merely repeated the neutral word. This confirms the reported results of similar studies in the past. Furthermore, subjects reported increases in their sense of psychological “flow,” distraction, and self-confidence, all indicators of increased disinhibition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“These findings help explain why swearing is so commonplace,” &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1110041?"&gt;said Stephens&lt;/a&gt;. “Swearing is literally a calorie-neutral, drug-free, low-cost, readily available tool at our disposal for when we need a boost in performance.” The team next plans to explore the influence of swearing on public speaking and romantic behaviors, since these are situations where most people are more hesitant and less confident in themselves, and hence more likely to hold back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DOI: American Psychologist, 2025. &lt;a href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1037/amp0001650"&gt;10.1037/amp0001650&lt;/a&gt;  (&lt;a href="http://arstechnica.com/science/news/2010/03/dois-and-their-discontents-1.ars"&gt;About DOIs&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:46:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNc3hmZDJieEtZcWs4aDNFVnFxMFZRaVowZjV6X3Jid0xiVklSNWZFWlBMYi1FZUV6aE0tX0FLdEdwelhsQ2RfZkh4Y3N5VDE0Q2h1ZW1nS2tGVHJXenh5ek1BTDdfSy1xWUZtbU03UlFhUElVemJMRGx5dnIxUDVrOUU1WjNlWUQyT05mX21aSE9sSU0</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，不要犹豫，咒骂可以通过降低抑制来提高表现-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/dec/18/swearing-can-boost-performance-lowering-inhibitions-study</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It may not be in keeping with the festive spirit, but if you find yourself dropping the F-word while wrestling a Christmas tree up a flight of stairs, scientists say you could be on to something. A study has found that swearing can enhance physical performance by lowering inhibitions and pushing the brain into a “flow state”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“In many situations, people hold themselves back – consciously or unconsciously – from using their full strength,” said Dr Richard Stephens, a psychologist at Keele University who led the research. “Swearing is an easily available way to help yourself feel focused, confident and less distracted, and go for it a little more.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Previous research found that swearing could increase strength and pain tolerance in tests where participants repeated swearwords while pushing themselves to the limit, such as cycling at maximum effort or holding a hand in icy water. Researchers initially hypothesised that swearing triggered a “fight or flight” response but found no supporting evidence, such as an increased heart rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Instead, the latest research suggests swearing triggers a state of disinhibition. “By swearing, we throw off social constraint and allow ourselves to push harder,” said Stephens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To test this, the researchers ran two experiments involving 192 people. In each, participants were asked to repeat either an expletive of their choice or a neutral word every two seconds while performing chair pushups. After completing the exercise, they answered questions about their mental state during the task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Their answers suggested that swearing boosted self-confidence, improved psychological “flow” and distracted them from the task – important aspects of disinhibition. Confirming earlier findings, the researchers found that swearing increased the length of time people could maintain a chair pushup by 11%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“These findings help explain why swearing is so commonplace,” said Stephens. “Swearing is literally a calorie-neutral, drug-free, low-cost, readily available tool at our disposal for when we need a boost in performance.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Stephens said the power of swearwords was likely to lie in their taboo nature. His team is investigating whether more offensive language produces greater physical gains, in a “dose-response” trial that will test how long participants can tolerate holding their hand in icy water while repeating either mild or strong swearwords.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The team is also exploring whether the confidence boost associated with swearing could help in other contexts, such as public speaking or making a romantic approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There are lots of situations where hesitancy might be to our detriment,” said Stephens. “You could go into a quiet room, go for it swearing for a minute and then go out and give your talk. I bet people do it already.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However, he cautioned that swearing was not an entirely risk-free strategy. “You’re never quite sure when you use a swearword how it’s going to land,” he said. “You have to know your audience and who is around. You could land yourself in hot water if you swear inappropriately.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The findings are published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/amp-amp0001650.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;American Psychologist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOZExSNzdzVlFTZWNvLUN1enRoUzJHc3ZUNTgycGZCdW1qdWhwTVl0Ql9ZTzVYcWZBZ1lubndqWWR6amRDMTVQNEJTMjA4ZXlxT3ZxUkUya0preERwdUxSTy1FU19qUmJ1MGY2TEt2blJtenMyN1g3NWJGeUNwWl9jbHFwdUljXzBSVkgxaDhzdjNBUzRaUHhGaVhWc2RlWHhCV0ZzUHhHakQ</guid></item><item><title>避免在飞机上生病的最佳座位-福克斯新闻</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/best-seat-avoid-getting-sick-plane</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fox News</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:18:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE5fdUZhTWJPdVFPY3IwdVZHbW1jZUVyMnFKejlFcTlFTXR0enVuaGprREhyUko4aVByZWlzRE90ekdIRi16VTVoWXdoVVYwOXdxMnRDRXFFS3FIbFpYSi01SG5iYThMLTE0TG5VNHc0ZVVDTVdqWWxz</guid></item><item><title>为什么女性要支付超过2000 $来逆转“Ozempic阴道” ，因为它变得越来越普遍- UNILAD</title><link>https://www.unilad.com/news/health/ozempic-vagina-explained-labia-puffing-380308-20251217</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main class="article_main__eth__ "&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;p hidden id="S:0"&gt;&lt;template id="P:1"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>UNILAD</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:18:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxPZGVuVzZ1N1BOYlZBRUl3LUxfa0g2SHBJMnpydXBJV2NPSG40MUZMYkp5UmJWWjJxWXlpZUpLVGlwb1JHTkY0SDVJRWFRQjdNVDFZV3JXLU5vT3M5eWYxOEdqdXRRWWthWXRYMGNRUFc0YUtvWlZwQ3FWYU84dGRxakN5WjdZdjg2VG9mazIxUWpHMnc</guid></item><item><title>哪些血液测试可以检测出阿尔茨海默氏症的生物标志物，哪些不能告诉您-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/18/alzheimers-detection-blood-tests/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SABCJW3FRFH7ROGV42QTW5UAXI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;As scientists race to develop simple blood tests that could one day act as an early warning system for Alzheimer’s disease by sounding the alarm before memory problems appear, new research shows tracking shifts in certain protein biomarkers over time is more accurate than relying on a single test result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:01:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOZEVYaXBwenMtT0h0cWJPcFZwNTQ0emJERF95R2JJZU1rNnBEcndteExJOGZESDEwSGRGMnZTWFhlRWhnNzRKbWZER2tlclVvQTVROXc4MGtjTWZYbXJnSmNzOXpxQmFCWDhyRnJabmJwclVpTlJhX0ItMlVQcXI0aGtIMW5DbTdUZWc</guid></item><item><title>流感疫情：您所在地区的医院如何受到影响？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cvgqkvll1yvo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Hospitals across the UK are seeing high levels of flu cases this winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS in England has said it is on "on high alert" after seeing the highest ever number of flu cases in hospital for this time of year, in the week ending 14 December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;You can use our tool below to find out how many flu patients there are in hospitals near you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Figures relating to flu cases in hospitals are collected in different ways in each UK nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In England it is the weekly number of beds occupied by patients with a laboratory confirmed flu case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This data is provided at NHS Trust level. Trusts are organisations which include hospitals, community services and providers of other forms of patient care. You can find which trust your local hospital belongs to on the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/nhs-services" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;NHS England&lt;/a&gt; website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In Scotland the figures relate to the number of patients admitted to hospital with a laboratory confirmed flu case taken between 14 days before the admission date and 48 hours after the admission date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In Wales it is the weekly number of patients in hospital with a laboratory confirmed flu case taken from 28 days before the admission date if tested outside of hospital, or within two days after admission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Figures for Scotland and Wales are provided at NHS Health Board level. Health boards are responsible for all frontline healthcare services. You can find which Health Board your local services belong to on the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhsinform.scot/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;NHS Scotland&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.wales.nhs.uk/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;NHS Wales&lt;/a&gt; websites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In Northern Ireland the figures show the number of new flu cases admitted to hospital that were acquired outside of hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This data is provided at Health and Social Care Trust level. Trusts are responsible for providing local and regional health services. You can find which trust your local hospital belongs to on the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nidirect.gov.uk/information-and-services/health-and-wellbeing/health-services" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;NI direct&lt;/a&gt; website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:37:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE91WGdoVG5XcXplSkZobkRGM2oyLXV0aXN4QmhvMWQzWDNGTDVfNllOT2UzZGJTQU9feGhqX3pyblJIMG1lbEdCZjFsMGxFTnU4cDlvTGd0M1JtQdIBX0FVX3lxTE5FeXZkT1VmRUpNQmpQX2puQUt4dG5naFJpemZhY3c0VFFPOFJuMEVVZm5FbU1WZHE4VEIyWU00TlRMOXloUHh0LTRKazZNVWRSemMwOFlYel9jbmJrVFdn</guid></item><item><title>新的“超级抗生素”在不破坏微生物组的情况下杀死致命的肠道感染- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/new-super-antibiotic-kills-deadly-gut-infection-without-destroying-the-microbiome/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:35:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQNjYzOUw4bjZwSnRNZFpnaUtsQWhkUkRtcnVWMHF2dXlzNC1yOE81WFlXZFE2WHBubEVFOEhaRWtfaVhqeHRLLUNjVks1X0o4UnYwaE1DaGlZY05FbllqQXVaU05yQlVxMWtLS0dqQmxjY0lubXVEdFNqY1VVVFo0STI2LUFDUmNES0dqTlpwTldTanR4WWY3UERQV19xM1liQWw2cWJuLTRKaTA</guid></item><item><title>在为期25年的研究中，奶酪与降低痴呆风险有关- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/cheese-linked-to-lower-dementia-risk-in-25-year-study</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;One of the finest foods available to humanity may carry an unexpected benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study has found that eating 50 grams (1.76 ounces) or more of high-fat cheese a day correlates with a lower risk of developing dementia. That means all cheeses with more than 20 percent fat content, &lt;a href="https://bcpa.eu/factsheets/FatContentOfCheeses.htm"&gt;including&lt;/a&gt; brie, gouda, cheddar, parmesan, gruyere, and mozzarella.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extensive, long-term study followed 27,670 adults in Sweden for around 25 years. The findings establish an association between daily consumption of high-fat cheese and lower dementia risk that is statistically detectable – although more research needs to be done to figure out the potential mechanism behind it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-common-sleeping-pill-could-reduce-buildup-of-alzheimers-proteins-study-finds"&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Common Sleeping Pill Could Reduce Buildup of Alzheimer's Proteins, Study Finds&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For decades, the debate over high-fat versus low-fat diets has shaped health advice, sometimes even categorizing cheese as an unhealthy food to limit," &lt;a href="https://www.aan.com/PressRoom/home/PressRelease/5304"&gt;says nutrition epidemiologist Emily Sonestedt&lt;/a&gt; of Lund University in Sweden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our study found that some high-fat dairy products may actually lower the risk of dementia, challenging some long-held assumptions about fat and brain health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dementia is an umbrella term for &lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/what-is-dementia/types-of-dementia"&gt;several conditions&lt;/a&gt; that impair cognitive function, such as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="186017" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease (the most common form), vascular dementia, and dementia that can develop in disorders like &lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/what-is-dementia/types-of-dementia/parkinson-s-disease-dementia"&gt;Parkinson's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An estimated &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/dementia"&gt;57 million people&lt;/a&gt; were living with dementia in 2021, and an estimated 10 million new cases are diagnosed every year. A 2019 Global Burden of Disease analysis projected that, by 2050, the number of cases could rise &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/s2468-2667(21)00249-8"&gt;as high as 153 million&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since there's a dearth of effective treatments for dementia, some researchers are focusing their efforts on ways of reducing the chances of developing dementia, with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/major-study-links-4-healthy-diets-with-up-to-28-lower-dementia-risk"&gt;diet playing a major role&lt;/a&gt; in these &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-diet-helps-lower-dementia-risk-and-we-may-finally-know-why"&gt;risk mitigation strategies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The so-called MIND diet – a variation of the Mediterranean diet – has &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sticking-to-the-mind-diet-could-reduce-your-risk-of-developing-dementia"&gt;been touted as promising&lt;/a&gt;; however, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s13195-022-00957-1"&gt;findings&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamapsychiatry.2023.0800"&gt;different studies&lt;/a&gt; are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu15010032"&gt;inconsistent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dairy is one particular food group whose association with dementia has been difficult to establish. Studies from &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00394-022-02834-x"&gt;Finland&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s11357-022-00615-2"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-taste-for-cheese-may-reveal-your-future-risk-of-dementia"&gt;Japan&lt;/a&gt;, for example, have looked at different amounts of cheese consumption and found varying results in dementia links.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the new paper, led by nutrition epidemiologist Yufeng Du of Lund University, researchers set out to clarify these inconsistent findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They based their analysis on the &lt;a href="https://www.malmo-kohorter.lu.se/malmo-diet-cancer-mdc"&gt;Malmö Diet and Cancer cohort&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span&gt;a long-running observational study surveying Swedish residents about their diet and tracking health outcomes&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;span&gt;Of the 27,670 participants, 3,208 developed dementia over the course of about 25 years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants recorded their diet at baseline using a 7-day food diary, a food-frequency questionnaire, and a detailed interview about food preparation and eating habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="docos-replyview-body docos-anchoredreplyview-body docos-replyview-body-emoji-reactable docos-replyview-body-emoji-reactable-background" dir="ltr"&gt;The researchers compared people's dementia risk based on their cheese intake. Around 10 percent of those who ate 50 grams or more of high-fat cheese per day developed dementia, compared to about 13 percent of people who ate less than 15 grams a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After adjusting for age, sex, education, and overall diet, people who ate more than 50 grams of high-fat cheese per day had a 13 percent lower all-cause dementia risk compared to people who ate less than 15 grams per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No such association appeared for low-fat cheese or cream, any kind of milk, or fermented milk products such as yogurt and kefir. Butter showed mixed results, including a possible increased Alzheimer's risk at high intake compared to people eating no butter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But before you chow down on cheese with abandon, other researchers point out important issues with the research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"One of the biggest limitations of this study is the cheese consumption as recorded from a food diary and interview at one time point 25 years before the analysis of dementia diagnosis. It is highly likely that diet and other lifestyle factors changed in those 25 years," &lt;a href="https://www.sciencemediacentre.org/expert-reaction-to-study-looking-at-the-association-between-eating-high-fat-cheese-and-cream-and-dementia-risk/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Tara Spires-Jones, Division Lead in the UK Dementia Research Institute, who was not involved in the study.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As nice as it would be, it may not be wise to pin your hopes on any one food to protect yourself against dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1212/WNL.0000000000214343"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Neurology&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:02:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQdlczWVRkSXQyVlA3NDV6enQ2aDdHTmhpZWNYS2FtNGczZGhvRXVndVpMVnkzaXVPTG91Zmx3U016V3dhR2JpVktUU3ZlSjRORnp6d0lmbnJ4LWduOGt1VDBhVWlmV2xRVWtPbjRYNGlpc2NaMWVpNUJNZmpMOFhXVTRkNmNJNW9aWWc</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心官员敦促美国在去年创纪录的儿童死亡后接种流感疫苗-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/dec/18/cdc-flu-vaccination</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Officials are urging doctors to vaccinate their patients and provide flu antivirals after deaths among children reached record highs and as a concerning mutation of the virus circulates in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Influenza activity is increasing in the US. The time to get vaccinated for this season is now,” Timothy Uyeki, the chief medical officer of the influenza division at the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), said in a call with clinicians last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The message comes amid diminishing access to and flourishing rumors about vaccines under Robert F Kennedy Jr, the secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services, who has made &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/01/28/health/rfk-jr-vaccines-autism-video.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;false claims&lt;/a&gt; about the ineffectiveness of flu vaccines and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/dec/06/vaccine-panel-hepatitis-b-change" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;overseen limitations&lt;/a&gt; on routine vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After a year of dramatic cuts to staff and programs at health agencies, CDC officials highlighted the need to continue monitoring variants such as the H3N2 virus subclade K – currently the top strain in the US – as flu season unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s hard to say what will happen throughout the season, and that’s why we need surveillance to really track this,” Uyeki said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A child died of the flu in the week ending 22 November, marking the first known pediatric death this season, the CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-49.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; earlier this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The CDC also reported another child death from flu during last year’s season, bringing the total to 288 – the deadliest pediatric flu season on record outside of a pandemic. Last year, there were an estimated 610,000 to 1.3 million hospitalizations from influenza in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Last season, by all indicators, was a high severity season and one of the highest we have experienced in the US,” Uyeki said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Officials at the CDC on last week’s call highlighted changes in vaccine policy – including a new recommendation against thimerosal, a preservative also known as thiomersal, previously used in a small percentage of flu vaccines. The CDC’s vaccine advisers voted to recommend only flu vaccines without the preservative in a June meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The top regulators of vaccines and drugs at the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) also recently announced changes to how flu vaccines will be approved, which may include &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/dec/11/fda-vaccine-regulations-unconfirmed-covid-deaths" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;extensive trials&lt;/a&gt; each year for children and pregnant people that would put annual vaccination &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/dec/04/us-vaccines-vinay-prasad-memo" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;out of reach&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Children, pregnant people, immune-compromised people, and the elderly are among those at highest risk of illness and death. Vaccines protect against severe complications like pneumonia, cardiac complications, neurological issues, and encephalopathy, or brain dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There were 109 cases of encephalopathy among children last year, with 74% needing intensive care and 54% needing mechanical ventilators. Most (55%) of the children with encephalopathy had no underlying conditions – except for not being vaccinated. Only 16% of the children who were eligible had gotten vaccinated. Nearly one in five (19%) of the children with encephalopathy died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The majority of these are preventable, and this is really, really tragic,” said Uyeki.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This is the highest number of deaths for a seasonal influenza epidemic since we’ve been keeping track, and clearly highlights the fact that we need to do a much better job of preventing influenza and preventing influenza-associated death in children in the United States.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Last year, the vaccine was 63% to 78% &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7406a2.htm" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;effective&lt;/a&gt; at preventing hospitalization among children and 41% to 55% effective against hospitalization among adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In August, the CDC identified the new variant (H3N2 virus subclade K), which mutated from the version of H3N2 included in the vaccine – raising concerns that the flu vaccine might be less effective this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:16,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:4152,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;today-us&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Get the most important US headlines and highlights emailed direct to you every morning&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Headlines US&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Every day&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;We'll send you The Guardian Headlines US every day&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;news&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As the flu season in the US is only beginning now, there is too little data so far to calculate how effective the vaccine is against it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s too early to know what impact exactly this new subclade will have on the influenza vaccine effectiveness for this season,” said Lisa Grohskopf, also a medical officer in the CDC’s influenza division.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It takes a little while before accumulating enough activity and specimens to be able to calculate [vaccine effectiveness].”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Based on early numbers from the United Kingdom, which had an early start to the flu season, vaccine effectiveness is about 70 to 75% for children and 30 to 40% for adults – similar to prior vaccine efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The evidence indicates that “influenza vaccination remains an effective tool in preventing influenza-associated hospitalizations for the season”, Grohskopf said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The flu vaccine is recommended for everyone six months and up, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Providers have been &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/nov/11/pediatricians-vaccines-flu-season" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recommending FluMist more&lt;/a&gt; to patients who are eligible. It’s not a shot, which may assuage vaccine hesitancy. And it may now be given at home by a caregiver or the patient after a major change from the FDA in September 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;​​Antivirals are also a safe and effective way to treat and prevent severe illness, including in pregnancy, and they work best the sooner they can be started.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In recent years, flu antiviral prescriptions have dropped, Uyeki said. Only 35% of children at high risk are prescribed antivirals, and only 32% of children who visited emergency departments because of flu were prescribed antivirals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE5XYjFjM1J0WUxCVWZZcXI3d05pbGRXVzZIUU1wakNYd3pzOWNrNVBoaFFXLWZLdkRXdk9FUjJudG4tMXJ4cHJEQTNDY1VlM3JUbnVsVkdUQm9RVERzak9Hc2Q2TzZKUzJIOUFHVV9mWjJkWl91NkE</guid></item><item><title>尝试治疗喉咙痛的7种家庭疗法-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/18/sore-throat-home-remedies/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N52IDJ4S7RDVJOHY2YI3DAAQGU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Woke up to a sore, scratchy throat? You may want to blame it on dry air, but it’s usually a sign your body is fighting a viral infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SXLK7G6S35H2TC4RAG44PZEQEY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“The top five causes of a sore throat are a virus, a virus, a virus, a virus and a virus,” said Elisabeth Fowlie Mock, a family physician and director at the American Academy of Family Physicians. The culprits that can trigger a sore throat include rhinoviruses (the most common cause of colds), influenza, coronavirus and respiratory syncytial virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:57:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOcWtzYkFrc1V0RHdPVFpEaGo0ZlFKNTZFSHpkbGRCaXVwZl9XVTdJcHlBX0VCaGtncDVSUEw3TllUcVBxY0Z4Um5SOXZkbDNqUEpDYm5QTXR6eFg0NS1jZ0ZOb054YlNJSWk0QzF2SmdEbjdIbkpINFAzenk1YmRIOWdpMA</guid></item><item><title>新药片终于可以在没有口罩的情况下治疗睡眠呼吸暂停- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/new-pill-could-finally-treat-sleep-apnea-without-a-mask/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:25:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxObzdKdzRNTTJXdFdXNU5Mal9VMW9Bd3B2VlVjRnBaNDd6NU1CQ2ZqX1lrTmluS0xjSE0taEpXNm54dTA2aHB4dGZmS19feXVTNWhKUmt2YjhpMklmaHEwdUVfN2I5ZjVuc2xQb19ObzJRbmlyLXdJQUxVWmpFVzhLb0FmX1FDX0Vv</guid></item><item><title>科学家确定了预测痴呆风险的6个关键抑郁症状- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-identify-6-key-depression-symptoms-that-predict-dementia-risk</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Symptoms of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depression" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73097" data-postid="185948" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt; in middle age could point towards &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dementia-risk-declining-with-each-generation-says-promising-new-study"&gt;the likelihood of dementia&lt;/a&gt; later in life, a new study shows, which could perhaps enable &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/6-things-gen-z-should-be-doing-right-now-to-stave-off-dementia-later"&gt;precautions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-existing-vaccine-could-slow-dementia-and-cut-death-risk-by-30"&gt;treatments&lt;/a&gt; to be put in place earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depression and dementia have been &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-is-linked-to-stress-and-depression-and-we-may-know-why"&gt;linked before&lt;/a&gt;, which is part of the reason for the new research, led by a team from University College London (UCL). In this study though, the researchers identified six specific symptoms that may act as warning flags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings show that dementia risk is linked to a handful of depressive symptoms rather than depression as a whole," &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/news/2025/dec/specific-depressive-symptoms-midlife-linked-increased-dementia-risk"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; epidemiological psychologist Philipp Frank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This symptom-level approach gives us a much clearer picture of who may be more vulnerable decades before dementia develops."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/laughing-gas-can-offer-immediate-relief-from-depression-study-finds"&gt;Laughing Gas Can Offer Immediate Relief From Depression, Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed data for 5,811 individuals taking part in a longitudinal study in the UK. Information on patients' mental health was collected between 1997 and 1999, when the participants were aged between 45 and 69 and all dementia free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health of these volunteers was then tracked for around two decades afterwards, on average. Dementia diagnoses &lt;span&gt;recorded in UK health records and registries &lt;/span&gt;up to 2023 were used in the final results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over that time, 10.1 percent of the participants developed dementia – and those who reported five or more symptoms of depression in middle age were found to have a 27 percent &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-roots-of-dementia-trace-back-all-the-way-to-childhood-experts-find"&gt;higher risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, this risk increase was driven by six specific depressive symptoms, out of 30 assessed in total. Those six were losing confidence, difficulty coping with problems, not feeling affection for others, being &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-trial-compares-yoga-and-therapy-as-a-treatment-for-anxiety"&gt;nervous all the time&lt;/a&gt;, having difficulty &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/switching-off-for-a-moment-lets-your-brain-do-something-wonderful"&gt;concentrating&lt;/a&gt;, and not being satisfied with the way tasks are carried out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_185951" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185951" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/DepressionChart.jpg" alt="Depression chart" class="wp-image-185951 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/DepressionChart.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/DepressionChart-600x571.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-185951" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers linked six symptoms of depression with dementia risk. (Frank et al., &lt;em&gt;Lancet Psychiat.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The loss of self-confidence and not being able to deal with problems were particularly significant, with each increasing dementia risk by around 50 percent. Some symptoms, such as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/poor-sleep-can-trigger-a-vicious-cycle-your-brain-cant-break-experts-warn"&gt;sleep problems&lt;/a&gt; and suicidal ideation, showed no long-term correlation with dementia diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the structure of the study doesn't show direct cause and effect, it suggests that certain elements of depression are associated with a higher chance of developing dementia – which may in turn inform research into &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/massive-study-links-15-factors-to-early-dementia-risk"&gt;why dementia takes hold&lt;/a&gt; of some brains but not others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everyday symptoms that many people experience in midlife appear to carry important information about long-term brain health," &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/news/2025/dec/specific-depressive-symptoms-midlife-linked-increased-dementia-risk"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Frank. "Paying attention to these patterns could open new opportunities for early prevention."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know that both &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/some-antidepressants-could-speed-decline-in-dementia-patients"&gt;depression and dementia&lt;/a&gt; are complex and multi-faceted, and different between individuals. That makes trying to establish &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/dad2.70036"&gt;connections&lt;/a&gt; between them challenging – but &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/gps.5711"&gt;not impossible&lt;/a&gt;, as this study shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, there's no guarantee that these results apply universally. The team acknowledges that the research was conducted only in the UK, using relatively healthy civil servants. Dementia was found to be less common in participants in the longitudinal study, compared to the general UK population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More research is needed in more diverse cohorts, especially with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2468-2667(21)00249-8"&gt;dementia expected&lt;/a&gt; to become more prevalent as the growing global population gets older. But it could give scientists a place to start at least, and if a proportion of those cases can be prevented, it could make a huge difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Depression doesn't have a single shape – symptoms vary widely and often overlap with anxiety," &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/news/2025/dec/specific-depressive-symptoms-midlife-linked-increased-dementia-risk"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; epidemiologist Mika Kivimäki. "We found that these nuanced patterns can reveal who is at &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-identify-4-key-factors-that-may-predict-cognitive-decline"&gt;higher risk&lt;/a&gt; of developing neurological disorders."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This brings us closer to more personalized and effective mental health treatments."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2215-0366(25)00331-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Lancet Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:02:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPb3h6Tk9Cekl4cy00UDdEUm9velRBUGRMa3ctN0NoNW93Q1oxV1U2Q3Z1YkVBbE11WkR3V0FqcHNwZzVhOXdjYmV3NjV5YWxWNTlFTGFVX1U3QzJzcWhSQTB4RDFsMGN4NzFVd3JCWjA4YTJUc1RyWENkQXkxd3ZTTVZUcGY1Nm1IZFM0ckxYbWdpU0FlZkJsQVo2SXN1V1pVc1M0</guid></item><item><title>佛罗里达州计划不再需要的四种疫苗是什么？ -坦帕湾时报</title><link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/florida-politics/2025/12/18/florida-vaccine-mandate-explained-ladapo-chickenpox-hepatitis-hib/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="author-bio article"&gt;&lt;a class="author-bio__image--wrapper" href="/author/romy-ellenbogen"&gt;&lt;figure class="author-bio__image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="author-bio__content--role"&gt;Romy Ellenbogen is a Tallahassee correspondent, covering state government with a focus on criminal justice and health. Reach her at rellenbogen@tampabay.com. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tampa Bay Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:01:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxOaTdHelF2enR2RUl3X0xqdzB5TkYxamg4eFdZa2JlLTRDZ2tRRG0yZTVleFFtRFZkdV9TRjE3dHMyZGd2bUhfaWVtX1pld2FKOFd6VFlIYnJwSVBlb2pUNUdKdmRuak1sNjZZclRlVTlLQjhzX2NmYzRDeld1dUI5dzJFaTdrZ2JSNVk5TXFWTlhIWTh4THFVSmdkLVhkM094Tno0em9ncWRxSV9tc0F3OFptWnFsM2ZtS0wtV01FbGFNUQ</guid></item><item><title>人格障碍患者经常以不同的方式使用语言–我们的研究揭示了如何- The Conversation</title><link>https://theconversation.com/people-with-personality-disorders-often-use-language-differently-our-research-reveals-how-271109</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="grid-ten large-grid-nine grid-last content-body content entry-content instapaper_body inline-promos" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Is it possible to spot personality dysfunction from someone’s everyday word use?  My colleagues and I have conducted research that suggests you can, and often sooner than you might expect. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether in a quick text message, a long email, a casual chat with a friend, or a comment online, the words people choose quietly reveal deeper patterns in how they think, feel, and relate to others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone has personality traits – habitual ways of thinking, feeling and behaving. When these patterns become rigid, intense or disruptive, they can cause ongoing problems with emotions, sense of self and relationships. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the more severe end are personality disorders, where these patterns create significant distress and impairment. Common &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/people-with-personality-disorders-are-more-likely-to-sign-up-for-psychology-studies-heres-why-thats-a-problem-201237"&gt;personality disorders&lt;/a&gt; include narcissistic, antisocial, and borderline personality disorder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But not everybody has a full-blown disorder. Personality functioning actually exists on a spectrum. &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/why-are-we-becoming-so-narcissistic-heres-the-science-55773"&gt;We’re all a little narcissistic&lt;/a&gt;, after all. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people you meet – at work, when dating, or online – may show milder difficulties, such as mood fluctuations, negativity, rigid thinking or darker traits like manipulation and callousness. These patterns often &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1146/annurev.psych.54.101601.145041"&gt;slip into how people speak&lt;/a&gt; or write long before they show up in more explicit behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some extreme examples. Linguists &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/forensicsci3010006"&gt;analysing the personal letters of Austrian serial killer Jack Unterweger&lt;/a&gt; – widely viewed as a classic case of malignant narcissism – found unusually high levels of self-focused language, such as “I” and “me”. He also had a notably flat emotional tone. Likewise, letters from Dennis Rader, the BTK killer (bind, torture, kill) displayed strikingly &lt;a href="https://press.uchicago.edu/ucp/books/book/distributed/C/bo44312033.html"&gt;grandiose, detached and dominance-focused wording.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Psychologists have long known that certain linguistic habits reveal how people are functioning internally. For example, people experiencing distress consistently use more &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jrp.2017.02.005"&gt;self-focused language&lt;/a&gt; and more &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.chb.2018.05.035"&gt;negative emotion words&lt;/a&gt;. That’s because they internalise a lot and experience negative affect. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those with darker personality traits often use more &lt;a href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/2983323.2983822"&gt;hostile, negative and disconnected language&lt;/a&gt;, including more swear words and anger words, such as “hate” or “mad”. At the same time, they use fewer socially connected terms like “we”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vitally, these patterns aren’t usually deliberate. They emerge naturally because &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/0261927X09351676"&gt;language tracks attention, emotion and thought&lt;/a&gt;. With computational text analysis, researchers can now analyse these subtle cues at scale, and rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Our research findings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Across four studies using computational text analysis – three of which formed my &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.17635/lancaster/thesis/2215"&gt;PhD research&lt;/a&gt; – my colleagues and I found clear evidence that personality dysfunction leaves a detectable trace in everyday communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In one study of 530 people, published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1521/pedi.2023.37.4.444"&gt;Journal of Personality Disorders&lt;/a&gt;, we analysed written essays about peoples’ close relationships. We also collected data on their levels of personality dysfunction. Those with greater personality dysfunction used language that carried a sense of urgency and self-focus – “I need…”, “I have to…”, “I am…”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was expressed alongside ruminative, past-tense wording. They also had more negative, particularly angry, emotion terms, such as “furious” and “annoyed”. At the same time, they used noticeably less intimate or affiliative language such as “we”, “love” and “family”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a second project, published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jadr.2023.100647"&gt;Journal of Affective Disorders Reports&lt;/a&gt;, we again analysed written essays (530 people), as well as transcribed conversations from 64 romantic couples which included women with diagnosed personality disorders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Across both written and spoken communication, those with more dysfunctional or disordered personalities used more negative emotion words – and a wider variety of them. Even during mundane conversations, their language carried heavier negative affect, indicating a preoccupation with negative feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turning to online communication, in a study recently published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s44184-025-00142-w"&gt;npj Mental Health Research&lt;/a&gt;, we analysed nearly 67,000 Reddit posts from 992 people who self-identified as having a personality disorder. Those who frequently engaged in self-harm used language that was markedly more negative and constricted. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their posts contained more self-focused language and more negations – such as “can’t”. They also used more sadness and anger terms, and more swearing, while referencing other people less. Their wording was also more absolutist, reflecting all-or-nothing thinking, favouring words like “always”, “never”, or “completely”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="align-center zoomable"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://images.theconversation.com/files/707834/original/file-20251210-64-6jtq4l.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;q=45&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=1000&amp;amp;fit=clip"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;figcaption&gt;
              &lt;span class="caption"&gt;Look out for anger and swearing.&lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;span class="attribution"&gt;&lt;a class="source" href="https://www.shutterstock.com/image-photo/angry-furious-businesswoman-working-on-computer-325331660?trackingId=%7B%22app%22%3A%7B%22module%22%3A%22image-search-results%22%2C%22name%22%3A%22next-web%22%2C%22page%22%3A%22ecomm%22%7D%2C%22providers%22%3A%5B%7B%7D%5D%2C%22svc%22%3A%22recommendation-api%22%2C%22strategy%22%3A%7B%22name%22%3A%22INTENT%22%2C%22version%22%3A%221.0%22%7D%2C%22uuid%22%3A%22571603c8-1ddf-405c-aa49-422d54d50e20%22%7D"&gt;pathdoc/Shutterstock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Together, these features created a linguistic picture of emotional overwhelm, negativity, withdrawal and rigid thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, in an ongoing project analysing more than 830,000 posts from the same 992 individuals with personality disorder, plus 1.3 million posts from a general-population comparison group of 945 people, we examined how people express their self-beliefs (“I am …”, “I feel …”, “My …”). Using an &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.18653/v1/2025.acl-long.69"&gt;advanced self-belief classification tool&lt;/a&gt;, we found that people with personality disorders shared self-beliefs on online discussion forums far more often, and their wording differed profoundly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their self-beliefs were more negative, extreme, and disorder-focused, including phrases like “my mental health”, “symptoms”, “diagnosis” and “medication”. They also used more emotional descriptors such as “depressive”, “suicidal” and “panic”. Many self-belief statements centred on pain and trauma – “abusive”, “abandonment”, “hurt”, “suffer”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also frequently referenced childhood or significant relationships (“mother”, “partner”, “relationship”). These patterns arose across a wide range of discussion contexts, suggesting that deeper struggles with identity may surface in language universally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why this matters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding these linguistic patterns isn’t about diagnosing people from their texts. It is about noticing shifts in language that can provide gentle clues. If someone’s messages suddenly become unusually urgent or extreme, emotionally negative, absolutist, inward-focused and socially detached, it may be a sign they’re struggling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And in everyday situations – dating, befriending, online interactions – recognising patterns of hostility, extreme negativity, and emotional and cognitive rigidity can help people spot early red flags. This is particularly for dark personality styles, such as psychopathy or narcissism. For instance, noticeably high use of self-references (“I”, “me”), anger words (“hate”, “angry”), and swear words, combined with a lack of terminology indicative of social connection (“we”, “us”, “our”), may be important language patterns to look out for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But no single word or phrase reveals someone’s personality. People vent, joke, and use sarcasm. What really matters is the pattern over time; the emotional tone, themes and recurring linguistic habits. Subtle linguistic traces can offer a window into someone’s emotional world, identity, thinking patterns and relationships long before they speak openly about their difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noticing these patterns can help us learn about and understand others, support those who may be struggling, and navigate our social lives safely – online and offline – with greater awareness.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

        

        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Conversation</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:01:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxNVkdlbGZPTjVSQUEyU1V2THN1ZndKbUxfX29RRFd4SDFJYkhkRk9uYnhteWVMaHFFeFJuSm9UZUpNT3lHc0JPLXJrUGtWeXNEdDBYOVZKeHZ2bDhxbEg0b0pYZk52bzR0QVgyV3FwbHo1QmcyS2tpMUp0d0VvempqMjNnZndUZWowOFZkb2JaM0laak9zTS1nZDR4TEVhYXFwYUNpMVJ1UlI2bk8tMlBmRW1BWWs5bjczN1ZiTXhjN2lGUQ</guid></item><item><title>当没有人支付奶酪税时，黄金猎犬做出最悲伤的面孔-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/articles/golden-retriever-makes-saddest-face-103207194.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you’ve ever watched a dog clock a snack table from across the room, you’ll understand Bentley immediately. In a video shared by @thespicygoldenn, a full-on house party is happening — people chatting, plates filling up with cheese, good vibes everywhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;And right in the middle of it all sits Bentley, wearing the kind of expression that suggests a deep personal betrayal. The kind of sad that feels very intentional. Bentley, a &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com/dog-breeds/golden-retriever" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Golden Retriever;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Golden Retriever&lt;/a&gt; known online for his permanently unimpressed face, looks around the room like he genuinely cannot believe this is how the night is going.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Video shows Golden Retriever’s sad face saying it all when cheese tax goes unpaid&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The video opens with Bentley planted on the floor as the party swirls around him. The on-screen text explains the problem plainly: no one is paying the cheese tax. The camera zooms in, and Bentley’s face does most of the talking. He glances side to side, as if hoping someone will make eye contact and realize the mistake they’re making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Next, Bentley’s mission for snacks takes him directly to the grazing table, which is loaded with every treat imaginable. He stands there staring at the spread, then looks back at his human with the saddest eyes ever recorded. His look says, “So we’re really doing this?” There’s no aggression here — just hope, fading slowly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the following shots, Bentley upgrades his strategy. He wedges himself between the kitchen island and a guest putting food on a plate. He stands there perfectly still, just in case gravity does the right thing. When even that fails, he presses himself between people at the counter, patiently waiting for someone to crack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Seeing him there (him, the &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/video-golden-retriever-proves-pasta-101816354.html" data-ylk="slk:pasta expert;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;pasta expert&lt;/a&gt;) while everyone ignores him was almost too much for some to handle. The “cheese tax” is a serious matter in his household, and the comments section fully sides with him. Viewers call it “cheese tax evasion,” demand justice, and insist someone get this dog an entire cheese board. Bentley might have left the party hungry, but he certainly won the hearts of thousands of supportive strangers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com/news/199724-golden-retriever-said-cheese-tax-video-instagram" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Golden Retriever Makes the Saddest Face When No One Pays Cheese Tax;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Golden Retriever Makes the Saddest Face When No One Pays Cheese Tax&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:DogTime;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;DogTime&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 10:32:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQckVXN0VRRFp1SGRCeVpvbm1PMFV3blZXLVpOcGFMQzlZV1B3SENnY1VDakVzRHJGLXVhYzBZWUxiM013ZkVLdGZURzZaVnVVMzJZbW0yMWpGWkJDX09FVGppNnJWbWFqdURwTGFlOWdtblFvSlBzdUN5amx6d1Y4bzMxcVVOX2RqUV9KMUlUU2xZVXNwREdPd2tRYw</guid></item><item><title>新的病毒“开关”可能有助于对抗抗生素耐药性-耶路撒冷邮报</title><link>https://www.jpost.com/science/article-880658</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Jerusalem Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 10:29:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiV0FVX3lxTE82ZXRNdHBxY2lLc0VLbG11bmwyRmhrcHRsdVNmZUhpUVFGWUMwM2dsZndkOXJPSjQtV2VlMG9saXZpLVVvMEhkNTRwdWFNZlJkRk52SDRTQQ</guid></item><item><title>南泽西小学的胃肠道疾病爆发使孩子们生病- WHYY</title><link>https://whyy.org/articles/central-elementary-school-haddonfield-new-jersey-norovirus/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="flexible-content-container wysiwyg-styles"&gt;
                                                                                                                                                                                                                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Philly and the Pa. suburbs to South Jersey and Delaware, what would you like WHYY News to cover? &lt;a href="#Section1"&gt;Let us know!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent outbreak of gastrointestinal illness at a South Jersey school has public health experts urging people to take precautions this winter and ahead of the holidays to avoid additional infections.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Camden County officials did not confirm the name of the school, but the outbreak is taking place at Central Elementary School in Haddonfield, according to a CBS &lt;a href="https://central.haddonfieldschools.org/"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exact number of affected students is unknown, but county officials say the school has reported an “unusual increase” in children with nausea, vomiting and other symptoms since Dec. 10.
  &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The scope of the outbreak grew Friday when the school reported an uptick in illnesses to the county’s Department of Health and Human Services.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Gastrointestinal illnesses can be highly contagious, so it is essential that families are aware of the signs and symptoms,” Virginia Betteridge, the department’s commissioner liaison, said in a statement.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms of &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/7040-gastrointestinal-diseases"&gt;gastrointestinal illness&lt;/a&gt; can also include diarrhea, stomach cramps, fever and fatigue. While most people can manage it and recover at home, others including young children, seniors and those with weakened immune symptoms are at risk of dehydration and other complications.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gastrointestinal illnesses are typically caused by bacteria, parasites or viruses like &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/17703-norovirus"&gt;norovirus&lt;/a&gt;, which can survive on high-touch surfaces like doorhandles, keyboards, phones and countertops for days or &lt;a href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/how-long-do-norovirus-germs-live-on-household-and-office-surfaces"&gt;even weeks&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The risk of outbreaks in the winter and during holidays&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cases and outbreaks are more common in the winter as people spend more time indoors and in settings like schools, long-term care facilities and daycares, said Caryelle Lasher, director of the county’s Department of Health and Human Services.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infections caused by norovirus usually spread when people come into contact with fecal matter and then ingest microscopic particles on their hands, on cups or utensils, or in food.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“And that can happen from people not washing their hands well or it can be spread through things contaminated by vomit,” she said. “That’s where we see these really quick spreading, intense outbreaks because it takes so little to make people sick.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schools are especially susceptible for outbreaks, Lasher said, “with young children who may not know to do a really thorough frequent hand washing after the use of the bathroom or before eating or preparing food.”
        &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHYY</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 10:18:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOcEtwYnBvc3RRN2pDY1JmYUVFTnlqLTFrMVlqS0hSMnR2aGVhQVEyRFJVNUJ6Uzc0dndsbkd2U28xOHFDMXNxR0phYk5lalRlYzRsTWNncFdFVkVvQ1g4Ty1tUERoc3RTVzlVRk00cWJyMndjb3YxRllQR2oxVk9rYWY2RW8wcG9hYW83ZGVR</guid></item><item><title>在非洲丛林中与致命疾病作斗争的摩托车手- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251217-the-motorcyclist-fighting-the-worlds-second-deadliest-parasite-in-the-african-bush</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now, she worries about her own children's health. She is in her twenties but unsure of her exact age. People in this part of the world tend to mark the passage of time by rains, rather than calendar years. Either way, she looks older than she really is. In Pokot culture, women bear all the essential burdens of life, from birthing children and fetching water to building houses and cooking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-bc40c3a0-0 kXcvpr"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 jJmNMc"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 160w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 240w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 320w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 480w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 640w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 800w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 1024w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 1376w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Kang-Chun Cheng Ochieng uses a rapid antigen test to help him diagnose people with visceral leishmanaisis (Credit: Kang-Chun Cheng)" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Kang-Chun Cheng&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Ochieng uses a rapid antigen test to help him diagnose people with visceral leishmanaisis (Credit: Kang-Chun Cheng)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ochieng finds that, thankfully, her four young children all appear to be free of the disease. But the risk of visceral leishmaniasis, and poor health exacerbated by poverty, is constant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Selina's family eats just once a day, in the morning: tea, &lt;i id="ugali" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;ugali&lt;/i&gt; (boiled maize meal), and sokoria leaves, which she plucks from a tree. Selina boils them, pounds into a mash and then fries the mixture. "What we can find is what we eat," she says, her toddler clinging to her side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She still remembers the painful injections she received all those years ago. But, to her, that made them more effective than any other kind of medication. It is a common belief here, according to Sagaki – that pain is the best way to deal with disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxOQndlSDJTVGNDckNnS3FkdVpiWWlTc0NYbWNRcHA3ZXI4S3BqNG94U2NJdmtfZWVxeUY0X1FtUGhIaGlVNFlXWWRuSHllcXY1UDRPWUl3bFRnU3dfc0xCY2hGR1hqOU1lNFFOYmUtZkVFUXV4M2p5dWx3UXZ3allrVnlQcXkyTUxpT3pxLU1aczJNaDNjV0lyTkUwMjI0cG42QXhVNkJkTUlwNTBQZ2JqTFVyZng3T20xbk9GMVlLeXZhbmY2</guid></item><item><title>Tracy Leigh Mitchell ， 60岁- Coeur d 'Alene Press</title><link>https://cdapress.com/news/2025/dec/18/tracy-leigh-mitchell-50/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-body font-weight-normal fr-view" id="storycontent"&gt;
	
		
		

			

			
	                        &lt;p&gt;Tracy Leigh Scott Mitchell, a devoted mother, grandmother, sister and friend, passed away Dec. 8, 2025. She will be deeply missed by her loving family and all who knew her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tracy is survived by her children, Shantel Mitchell and Misty Howard; her siblings, Crystal Hill, Janette Jerauld, Denice Duncan and Sheldon Scott; and her beloved grandchildren.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tracy was a kind and caring person who loved her family with all her heart. She will be especially remembered for her warmth, generosity and unwavering support. Her children and grandchildren were the light of her life, and her absence will be deeply felt by all who knew and loved her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tracy is preceded in death by her mother, Annabelle Scott, and her sister, Lenice Kuykendall, with whom she will now rest in eternal peace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A memorial service will be held at a later date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In lieu of flowers, donations may be made to help her children with cremation expenses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Family and friends are invited to sign Tracy’s online guest book at www.coffeltfuneral.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arrangements are entrusted to Coffelt Funeral Services of Sandpoint, Idaho.&lt;/p&gt;
			        	
				
			
		
	

&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Coeur d'Alene Press</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:04:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFAwOWlSLUdiTXRCSU8zNmhYR1ZhV1plWXNQaGI2RmNWcktpQ3B3ZjdjN1JHY0toRl9JTzdIUG54NllBUmN0LUxFZGNuMVZpYnRlWjc2VzlYejlKWUdCY3YzMFA3Rm52ejBQUmJaZGNMcw</guid></item><item><title>大麻化合物有望抵御最致命的癌症之一--SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/cannabis-compounds-show-promise-against-one-of-the-deadliest-cancers/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 04:03:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPbHNGeVZyd2VldGxkX09mREJkYkJnZGZhRWY1RkNtUTNwVFduazVwbVh1TzliazdOb3VpME51aTdTLUtFT0x3S09ldFlGZXZNT0c0YzRtTWFMbHB6NVd3N0dfTUowQnBfX1VFQ0hZSDBzTzdUdkRHbjAyZXBjNXZ0Z21yVlZqMHh0YnNOcnNtUXZWZUNRY082NENR</guid></item><item><title>布朗大学卫生部在呼吸道病毒上升的情况下颁布口罩要求- WJAR</title><link>https://turnto10.com/news/local/brown-university-health-enacts-mask-mandate-rise-respiratory-viruses-transmission-patient-care-visitors-december-17-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="TeaserLink_teaserText__g1DQc"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expert: Sharing unofficial AI-generated images could confuse, hinder Brown investigation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="TeaserLink_galleryIcon__W3OjR"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="TeaserLink_videoIcon__vD91T"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="TeaserLink_teaserSummary__nulFo"&gt;Experts say creating and sharing photos that are generated by AI is an incredibly dangerous game to play and not helpful to the investigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WJAR</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 03:25:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5wFBVV95cUxNMURBbGt5Vk5WaXpZRzlER0ZEWjJzUV9fam1MaVY5a3EyeXJvYVJJdldBR2pCMVhueFlPYTJ2eldYd0NDVGZPTzNHaDNPdXpsTE5hQThXSnlaY0J1YkxuZnR0REFOUDJ3SkZsTExubWV6TEhyMllUdEFBczhiUkhrRDhHVEozLTJxRVM1ZXo0WDdKZ2ZFZUpnOGpJM0o3REQ5QXRqMmV6M3J2akg1eXpTSHpZT1RpY0VmWkRJRGkxTW44NzJQMzduUkNTZ2FJZ1haOURDeDFFNXZtV1p6c3ZMRjJldVFhRm8</guid></item></channel></rss>