<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>碧姬·马克龙（ Brigitte Macron ）在70岁时进行平腹运动- valleyvanguardonline.com</title><link>https://www.valleyvanguardonline.com/brigitte-macrons-go-to-exercise-for-a-flat-stomach-at-70-ampversion/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>valleyvanguardonline.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:10:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPaFA5TGVkNmpzVEFTVzVVSVNWbTZPTWY3T3VoUG9LSUQ1dFpPOUNJRl82bHNRazNrbm13YmxTQmRHUGdaWXNjOThlWFdVRGpHNXF0dUItT1ZLVlg5aDd3VXgtVHFVQWI0SElaMW1RVWZBNU1yQzNxemJiMi02M0xIX0JoaWNabUtqN05UOTItMXdvOVFmczM1Y1pKVDhkZ0FjM2ZpdnNLX3M</guid></item><item><title>每年14,000例新病例：胰腺衰竭的警告信号- valleyvanguardonline.com</title><link>https://www.valleyvanguardonline.com/14000-new-cases-each-year-the-warning-signs-your-pancreas-is-failing/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>valleyvanguardonline.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:05:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxOYllFZ2ZBdzQyZFloVmxUNGh5RUYyajZTZ0NmZmN3OUtFdlpudVFfRmxxMkQzVFk4UW80cVdibnBxcktpb1p6YnpoaDl5NS04TnJjQW9vZ1RsZ0tqTnRveWlFYnJIMkhhNGQySGFwTlZCdUVFa1hlX2o1Tjg1dkdCalVjSWlwdE1EbmhrM1BZSEVHNHlvT1V2ZWlwQUdvZzJ2aFlxeXZFdjByQQ</guid></item><item><title>以下是我对重度抑郁症患者养育子女的了解--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/09/28/parenting-with-major-depression/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6FC7YCBN5NEHHPGHZWGIP63PZM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I was just 11 when I had my first experience with &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/12/01/depression-coping-strategies/" target="_blank"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;. I was feeling alienated at a new school and had body image issues, which were exacerbated by my parents’ divorce. Since then, I have dealt with despondency in cycles. When I experienced heartbreak, a layoff or a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/10/13/friendship-breakup-healthy-relationship/" target="_blank"&gt;friendship breakup&lt;/a&gt;, it affected me in ways that could interfere with my ability to function in my day-to-day life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 13:01:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPZm84QUMzb3Y5emwxUWgteGFIeDFQQ2dzcWpFWHFLeTZkSC1tT3NXSDJSZ2xaWG9odHEwcWJtQ3RuU19iWGpxTGtQZFc1dDVwSEZ6MVkwcXUzekZvcjJRWjNiUkVyUnc2RnN6bHRwMFFuY184YXdTYlpLM0FBdllBby1QNjlMOFVPeGpn</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现肠道-大脑相互作用与心理健康之间的惊人联系- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/scientists-discover-surprising-link-between-gut-brain-interactions-and-mental-health/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study provides evidence that the connection between the brain and the stomach may be linked to mental health in a measurable way. Researchers from Aarhus University in Denmark, publishing their work in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s44220-025-00468-6" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Nature Mental Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, report that a specific pattern of communication between the brain and the stomach reflects how individuals feel emotionally and psychologically. Their findings suggest that these gut-brain interactions can indicate a person’s levels of anxiety, depression, well-being, and overall quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea that emotions are linked to physical sensations in the gut is widely reflected in language. People often talk about having “butterflies in the stomach” when nervous, or feeling “sick to the stomach” when distressed. Yet, despite these common expressions, most scientific attention in the field of brain-body interaction has focused on other organs, such as the heart and lungs. These areas have long been studied for their roles in emotion and mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers were struck by how little was known about how the stomach, in particular, interacts with the brain. While recent studies have explored the influence of gut bacteria and digestion on mental health, very little work had been done on the electrical rhythms of the stomach and how they may directly communicate with the brain’s networks involved in emotion, attention, and cognition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team behind this new study wanted to explore whether a person’s psychological profile might be reflected in how strongly the stomach and brain are coupled during rest. Their aim was not to link a specific diagnosis like depression to a single brain region, but rather to identify patterns across a broad spectrum of mental health experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our interest grew from the long-standing discussion about the role of the body in shaping emotion, a question that has fascinated philosophers and scientists for centuries,” said study author &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/leah-banellis-phd-b192a6a0/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Leah Banellis&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="https://bsky.app/profile/leahbanellis.bsky.social" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;@leahbanellis&lt;/a&gt;), a postdoctoral fellow in Cognitive Neuroscience at Aarhus University. “Yet, while the heart and lungs have received much attention, the stomach has been largely overlooked. This gap struck us as especially surprising, because the link between the stomach and emotional experience feels so intuitive. It is heavily reflected in everyday language, with phrases like ‘butterflies in the stomach,’ ‘sick to our stomach,’ or ‘trust your gut.'”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was part of the Visceral Mind Project, a large-scale initiative that combines data on brain activity, bodily rhythms, and psychological assessments. The team recorded data from 243 people using a method that captures both electrical signals from the stomach (electrogastrography) and brain activity measured with functional magnetic resonance imaging (fMRI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The participants represented a wide range of mental health profiles, from those reporting high well-being to others showing signs of distress, including anxiety, depression, fatigue, and insomnia. To capture this diversity, the researchers didn’t exclude people with psychiatric symptoms or diagnoses. Instead, they aimed for variation, which would allow their models to detect patterns across the mental health spectrum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each participant underwent a series of recordings while lying still in the MRI scanner. At the same time, sensors on the abdomen captured the stomach’s slow electrical rhythm, which cycles about three times per minute. This rhythm, which originates from specialized cells in the stomach lining, is typically involved in coordinating digestion. But the researchers suspected it might also be linked to mental state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To analyze the relationship between stomach and brain activity, the team used a method that looks at how well the two rhythms align over time. This measure, known as phase-locking value, essentially captures the degree of synchronization between stomach signals and brain signals across different regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers then combined this data with results from a comprehensive mental health questionnaire. The battery included 37 different scores across a range of domains—such as anxiety, stress, mood, fatigue, attention, sleep quality, and life satisfaction. Using a statistical method known as canonical correlation analysis, they looked for patterns that linked brain-stomach coupling with the participants’ mental health profiles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis revealed a clear and statistically significant pattern. Stronger coupling between the stomach’s rhythm and brain activity was associated with poorer mental health. Individuals who reported more symptoms of anxiety, depression, stress, and fatigue tended to show increased synchronization between their stomach and brain rhythms. In contrast, those with higher levels of well-being and life satisfaction showed weaker coupling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For the first time, we’ve found a scientific link between your ‘gut feelings’ and your mental health, showing a surprising connection between your stomach’s natural rhythm and your brain,” Banellis told PsyPost. “Specifically, our study revealed that stronger communication between the stomach and brain is linked to worse mental health, such as higher symptoms of anxiety, depression, stress, and fatigue, whereas weaker stomach-brain communication aligns with better mental health reflected in higher overall well-being and quality of life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This stomach-brain signature was not random. It was localized in specific brain networks, particularly those involved in attention, cognitive control, and salience detection. Some of the strongest associations were found in regions like the superior angular gyrus and the posterior frontal and parietal areas—regions often implicated in cognitive tasks and mental health disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, the researchers ran multiple control analyses to ensure the robustness of their findings. They ruled out the possibility that the observed effects were simply due to general brain activity patterns, fluctuations in heart rate or breathing, or basic features of stomach physiology. In other words, the association appeared specific to the coupling between the stomach’s electrical rhythm and particular brain networks—not just a general marker of body or brain state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their approach was designed to detect broad psychological dimensions rather than focus on one diagnosis. The strongest psychological pattern they found was a spectrum ranging from negative affective states (like anxiety and depression) to positive traits (like well-being and quality of life). This result suggests that the stomach-brain connection is not tied to any one disorder but instead reflects a general mode of psychological functioning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Anxiety, depression, stress, and fatigue showed the strongest links to stomach-brain communication,” Banellis explained. “While phrases like ‘butterflies in the stomach’ or feeling ‘sick to your stomach’ are common ways we describe emotional distress, it was surprising to find such consistent and clear evidence across these symptoms. Even more unexpected was the direction of the effect: we might have assumed that stronger alignment between the body and brain would be beneficial. Instead, our findings suggest that heightened stomach-brain communication could act more like a warning signal, an internal alarm system reflecting mental strain rather than harmony.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with all research, there are limitations. The findings are based on resting-state measurements, meaning the participants were not performing any tasks during the brain scans. This leaves open the question of how the stomach-brain relationship behaves during emotional challenges or cognitive demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another limitation is that the study was cross-sectional—it measured participants at one point in time. This limits the ability to determine cause and effect. Longitudinal studies that follow people over time will be needed to see whether changes in stomach-brain coupling can predict shifts in mental health, or whether interventions that alter this coupling can improve well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Despite our study including hundreds of participants, far surpassing the size of previous studies, and using a robust machine learning technique, our study is correlational in nature,” Banellis noted. “Thus, future causal paradigms are needed to understand this mental health associated stomach-brain relationship further.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also note that their measurements relied on surface recordings of stomach activity, which can be affected by noise and variability. Despite extensive quality control, a portion of the data had to be excluded. Future studies using higher-resolution tools or invasive methods in clinical settings might yield even clearer signals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our study raises important questions about causality, whether the stomach is influencing the brain, the brain is influencing the stomach, or both, as well as how stomach-brain communication develops over time and whether it can predict changes in mental health,” Banellis said. “It also opens the door to new treatment approaches targeting the disrupted brain-body connection we identified.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“To build on these findings, we plan to pursue three closely connected next steps: first, case-controlled studies in patients diagnosed with anxiety or depression; second, longitudinal studies to track how stomach-brain communication evolves and whether it predicts mental health trajectories; and third, testing new interventions designed to modulate stomach-brain interactions and evaluate their potential for improving mental health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s44220-025-00468-6" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Stomach–brain coupling indexes a dimensional signature of mental health&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Leah Banellis, Ignacio Rebollo, Niia Nikolova, and Micah Allen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 10:28:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxPdVdqTV8zU1p2NDczWEc0SkhmeFFTanVJV2dsMmdXTlI2UTZjNzBFaGtYdDloUGlEcnA2ajduYk9ta1BfemJsclBEVTR6azA2QXVJamlFdnUxcmY1ZnV0c0lXMy1ZSTRaQm1TQjJ5RjNQWlhGaXBlaXRCMkdQVk1VZFVUM0k5dk9Va2VjVE5Dd3NoMHdMRDBpemFsRVZMTTVXcG8wRDZMTi1sRjl6N1E</guid></item><item><title>泰诺很受欢迎，而且很安全。我们将解释这种药物如何在体内发挥作用-今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/graphics/2025/09/28/how-tylenol-works-nsaids-autism-pain-relivers/86351608007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;On Sept. 22, President &lt;a target="_blank" href="/news/politics/donald-trump/" data-autotag="26f031d1-9924-4f10-b4e6-019d076113d5" rel="noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt; pushed an unproven link between Tylenol and an increase in &lt;a href="/story/news/politics/2025/09/22/autism-tylenol-takeaways-trump-rfk-jr/86293921007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;autism in children&lt;/a&gt;, and he issued an urgent warning to expectant mothers not to take the medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;What do we know about the drug? Tylenol is used to treat a several conditions, such as mild to moderate pain, &lt;a href="/story/news/health/2024/11/22/valley-fever-cases-arizona/76476521007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;fever&lt;/a&gt;, headaches, muscle aches, toothaches, backaches and colds. According to medical experts, when taken as directed, traditional &lt;a href="/story/news/2023/02/03/how-often-can-you-take-tylenol-acetaminophen/11039009002/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;over-the-counter pain relievers&lt;/a&gt; like acetaminophen and nonsteroidal anti-inflammatory medicines (NSAIDs) can be safe and effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Tylenol wasn't widely used until 1950, when Tylenol Elixir for Children, a prescription medication at first, was promoted as an aspirin substitute, according to &lt;a href="https://medicine.tufts.edu/news-events/news/how-does-acetaminophen-work" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Tufts University School of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;. Acetaminophen, &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/01/06/is-tylenol-an-nsaid/77112041007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;often sold under the brand name Tylenol&lt;/a&gt;, had long been considered the safest option for managing headaches, fever and other pain during pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;How does Tylenol (acetaminophen) work in your body?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Tylenol and NSAIDs lower temperature and relieve pain. They are used for treating various types of pain and are part of different drug classes. One significant distinction is that Tylenol does not relieve inflammation; NSAIDs do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Tylenol falls under the umbrella of two other medication classes: analgesics (pain relievers) and antipyretics (fever reducers), says &lt;a href="https://uihc.org/childrens/providers/anureet-walia" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Dr. Anureet Walia&lt;/a&gt;, a pain management specialist with UI Health Care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;To this day, it's still a bit of a mystery how acetaminophen works. What experts do know is acetaminophen works solely on the central nervous system, while NSAIDs work on the brain and the body as a whole. Here's a theory of how acetaminophen works in the body:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unable to view our graphics? &lt;a href="/story/graphics/2025/09/28/how-tylenol-works-nsaids-autism-pain-relivers/86351608007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Click here to see them.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="gnt_em gnt_em_img"&gt;&lt;img class="gnt_em_img_i" fetchpriority="high" data-g-r="lazy" data-gl-src="/gcdn/authoring/authoring-images/2025/09/23/USAT/86308385007-tylenol.jpg?width=980&amp;amp;height=552&amp;amp;fit=crop&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp" decoding="async" alt="Medical experts are challenging President Donald Trump’s autism claims, defending Tylenol’s safety in pregnancy."&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_em_img_ccw gnt_em_img_ccw__cap gnt_em_img_ccw__crd" data-c-caption="Medical experts are challenging President Donald Trump’s autism claims, defending Tylenol’s safety in pregnancy." data-c-credit="Reuters"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;'Use as directed': Comparing Tylenol and NSAIDs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Tylenol and NSAIDs both help with pain perception and fever, but the medications do have one key difference. Distinctly, Tylenol doesn’t have &lt;a href="/picture-gallery/life/health-wellness/2024/11/20/inflammation-food-causes/75996577007/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;anti-inflammatory properties&lt;/a&gt;, meaning it won’t help with swelling or inflammation, says David Mangan, chief pharmacy officer at UMass Memorial Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Like all drugs, the dosage matters. Taking your medication as recommended ensures you will receive its full benefits. Always take your current medical conditions and the sort of pain your body may experiencing into account when choosing between Tylenol and an NSAID.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Here's a comparison on how theses drugs work:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Regardless of the type of pain reliever, it’s important to remember that Tylenol and NSAIDs should &lt;a href="/in-depth/news/health/2022/12/11/pain-america-expensive-complicated-problem-managing-pain/8210733001/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;be taken only for episodic pain&lt;/a&gt;. “If your pain is constant and around the clock, it really should be a discussion with your physician about the source of the pain (and) how to best manage it,” Mangan says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="gnt_ar_b_h2"&gt;No casual link between Tylenol and autism&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The American Psychiatric Association issued the following statement on autism in response to President Trump's announcement:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“It is essential that the administration prioritizes evidence-based support for individuals on the autism spectrum and invests in long-term comprehensive research about the disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"Vaccines do not cause autism. Claims of any such association have been repeatedly discredited in peer reviewed studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;"Autism is a complex disorder, and it is incorrect to imply that a handful of studies have established causation. A strong base of evidence shows that acetaminophen, when taken as directed, is safe for use during pregnancy. Any decisions around a course of treatment should be determined by a patient and their doctor."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The American Academy of Obstetricians and Gynecologists said in a &lt;a href="https://www.acog.org/news/news-releases/2025/09/acog-affirms-safety-benefits-acetaminophen-pregnancy" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;news release&lt;/a&gt; Sept. 22: “In more than two decades of research on the use of acetaminophen in pregnancy, not a single reputable study has successfully concluded that the use of acetaminophen in any trimester of pregnancy causes neurodevelopmental disorders in children.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;&lt;em&gt;CONTIBUTING Caroline C. Boyle, George Petras and Mary Walrath-Holdridge&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 10:21:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNQnpPd3dIWjFWU1ZJaWZ2anVncE1KSm5rTnRuVEpUZVA0LXA1WlhKc3lwbHpJZzFEVGpBLWZ5RVZ3TXliQnk5MGtDVWs5ZFl6Zmd2bFltWDRFQXhPdHpqWmxEaGxlV0tPVVNvbmRhWTVGMkp3QnVSRHdsc1RBd1g5ZmRyTE1pUVR1QXRqUHIwa2hyQkNBWk5HQU9VeUNobVpHMklqVkU4UXJyNHp6ZEE</guid></item><item><title>无花果真的有死黄蜂吗？ - Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/plants/do-figs-really-have-dead-wasps-in-them</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;
&lt;p id="7d341865-008a-4164-a8cd-960f2950a22f"&gt;If you love figs, you may have heard some unsettling lore about them: that every fig hides a wasp, because these insects need to crawl inside and die in order for the fruit to grow. But are there really wasps in the figs we eat, or is this just a myth?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer is somewhere in between. Wasps do play an essential role in the life cycle of many types of fig trees, but most figs from the supermarket are likely bug-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="7d341865-008a-4164-a8cd-960f2950a22f-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.botanicgardens.org.au/teachers-and-schools/teacher-resources/primary-learning-resources/garden-safari-invertebrates-0" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.botanicgardens.org.au/teachers-and-schools/teacher-resources/primary-learning-resources/garden-safari-invertebrates-0" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Fig wasps&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are a group of hundreds of species of small insects that spend much of their life inside figs. They're about the size of a fruit fly, and they're not the same type of wasps that sting humans. Figs and fig wasps have &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/evolution" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/evolution"&gt;&lt;u&gt;evolved&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; alongside each other for millions of years, leading to a special relationship called &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.nhm.ac.uk/discover/mutualism-examples-of-species-that-work-together.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nhm.ac.uk/discover/mutualism-examples-of-species-that-work-together.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;mutualism&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or a link between two species that benefits both of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="068a1ec1-5f44-4831-bfbf-ba02625da19c"&gt;"Fig trees and fig wasps are a great example of a mutualism," &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.uu.se/en/contact-and-organisation/staff?query=N10-1267" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.uu.se/en/contact-and-organisation/staff?query=N10-1267" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Charlotte Jandér&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a plant ecology and evolution researcher at Uppsala University in Sweden, told Live Science in an email. "Other examples of mutualisms include &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/57831-are-trees-vegetarian.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/57831-are-trees-vegetarian.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;trees and the mycorrhizal fungi&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that help the trees take up nutrients, animals and their gut microbes, and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/animals/insects/how-do-insects-know-which-flowers-have-pollen" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/animals/insects/how-do-insects-know-which-flowers-have-pollen"&gt;&lt;u&gt;flowering plants and pollinators&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in general."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="b3e2dafa-7ed7-4521-bad9-948ed0ca5c65"&gt;In the case of figs and fig wasps, the fruit gets pollinated and the wasp is able to reproduce, leading to a mutualism. But this relationship is rather complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What we think of as the fig "fruit" is actually a hollow structure called a syconium filled with tiny flowers. Generally, when a female fig wasp crawls inside a synconium from a female fig tree, she spreads pollen, which the plant needs in order to produce seeds and ripen. The hole that the wasp crawls in is very small, and she may lose her wings and antenna in the process and can even die inside the fig.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, it's possible that some types of figs may have dead fig wasps inside them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that doesn't necessarily mean the figs we eat have wasps inside. Not all types of figs require pollination in order to ripen. Humans eat the fig species &lt;em&gt;Ficus carica, &lt;/em&gt;which has several cultivars that are parthenocarpic, meaning they can produce ripe fruit without pollination — and therefore, without fig wasps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most figs we eat in the US have no wasps inside them," &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://biology.umd.edu/people/carlos-machado" target="_blank" data-url="https://biology.umd.edu/people/carlos-machado" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Carlos Machado&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a biology professor at the University of Maryland, told Live Science in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="eee78aa6-647e-43ea-b4d2-f069e5713eea"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="caption-text"&gt;A female wasp entering a fig. Fig wasps can't sting humans, and they're much smaller than the wasps that do. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Danita Delimont via Alamy)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="c8d9cfa5-2d5b-44e1-95f4-3e43394549d6"&gt;Mission figs and Brown Turkey figs are two commonly-sold fig cultivars that don't require wasp pollination to ripen and produce seeds, Jandér said. This doesn't apply to all figs that humans eat, though; Smyrna figs, Calimyrna figs, and wild figs around the Mediterranean all rely on wasps for pollination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most wild figs do require pollination to produce ripe fruit," Machado explained. That means these types of figs could have a tiny wasp inside them — but it's still not a guarantee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/plants/how-do-plants-with-seedless-fruit-reproduce" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/planet-earth/plants/how-do-plants-with-seedless-fruit-reproduce"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How do plants with seedless fruit reproduce?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just because a wasp was once in the fig, doesn't mean it's still in there by the time the fig is eaten. The synconia of &lt;em&gt;Ficus carcia&lt;/em&gt; have a large enough opening that the fig wasp is sometimes able to leave the structure after entering. If the wasp does die inside, her body generally gets squished and decomposes from the process of the fig maturing, Jandér said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Even if there were remnants of the original pollinator there you probably would not see them," Jandér explained. Any crunchy texture is more likely from the plant's seeds, not wasp remains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-a2342a21-12d9-443f-8dc0-543b01059df7" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="the-fig-wasp-life-cycle-3"&gt;The fig wasp life cycle&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="c50a1ca6-b273-44dc-8b65-d4dafd1b56b6"&gt;Although wasps sometimes die inside figs, these fruits are actually an essential part of their reproduction cycle. Just as most types of figs need wasp pollination to make new fruit, fig wasps couldn't reproduce without the help of fig trees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a female wasp crawls into a fig syconium from a female tree — the type of figs we eat — she only pollinates it, because the flowers inside are too long for her to lay her eggs on. But if she ventures into a synconium from a male tree — which are called caprifigs and generally not eaten by humans — she'll start to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fs.usda.gov/wildflowers/pollinators/pollinator-of-the-month/fig_wasp.shtml" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.fs.usda.gov/wildflowers/pollinators/pollinator-of-the-month/fig_wasp.shtml" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;lay her eggs&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There, the eggs hatch and develop from larvae into young wasps, which mate while still inside the fruit. Generally, the male wasps die inside the caprifig after mating, though they do help chew a tunnel that allows the female wasps to escape, sometimes even offering themselves as bait for the predatory ants that may be waiting outside. Eventually, the fertilized female wasps burst out in search of a new fig to lay their eggs in, carrying pollen from the old caprifig with them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="08c65b1d-ba48-46e7-8edb-88c362c71881"&gt;There are over &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2023/07/unraveling-the-tangled-evolution-of-figs" target="_blank" data-url="https://news.northwestern.edu/stories/2023/07/unraveling-the-tangled-evolution-of-figs" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;850 species of fig trees&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and each one can only be pollinated by a specific species of fig wasp, Jandér said. The relationship between these plants and animals evolved millions of years ago, and both Machado and Jandér pointed to its importance. As a keystone species — an organism that many other plants or animals in the ecosystem rely on to survive — fig trees and their relationship with wasps continue to be of great interest to researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There are other plant-pollinator mutualisms in nature, but the fig-fig wasp mutualism is possibly the most diverse and most consequential of all," Machado said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNTlowejdDR1VqOW92T2UxTHpDTUJFVG9hX0VBZHBDX0JmaTVmVklnRThHS0tSZlJyUG5PV2JaaFBuZDNUU3BmcVlCNW1lb0FERkN6TTBGZWpZQjdhUjVQejNjQXNRV3FOdXh6OE5ia0t6V1J1X25sbmhLYnBXUnNfQV9SMWI3OVlyaFRlZUdQYw</guid></item><item><title>它被称为“噩梦细菌” ，美国的病例正在上升- ClickOnDetroit</title><link>https://www.clickondetroit.com/health/2025/09/28/its-known-as-nightmare-bacteria-and-cases-are-rising-in-the-united-states/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 fURyTV iQviKm articleBody" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NEW YORK&lt;/strong&gt; – It’s known as “nightmare bacteria,” and cases are on the rise in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Infection rates from the drug-resistant bacteria rose almost 70% between 2019 and 2023, according to a new &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-25-02404"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; from Centers for Disease Control and Prevention scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Bacteria that are difficult to treat due to the so-called NDM gene primarily drove the increase, CDC researchers wrote in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7326/ANNALS-25-02404"&gt;an article published Monday&lt;/a&gt; in the Annals of Internal Medicine. Only two antibiotics work against those infections, and the drugs are expensive and must be administered through an IV, researchers said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Bacteria with the gene were once considered exotic, linked to a small number of patients who received medical care overseas. Though the numbers are still small, the rate of U.S. cases jumped more than fivefold in recent years, the researchers reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“The rise of NDMs in the U.S. is a grave danger and very worrisome,” said David Weiss, an Emory University infectious diseases researcher, in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;It’s likely many people are unrecognized carriers of the drug-resistant bacteria, which could lead to community spread, the CDC scientists said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;That may play out in doctors’ offices across the country, as infections long considered routine — like urinary tract infections — could become harder to treat, said Dr. Maroya Walters, one of the report’s authors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Antimicrobial resistance occurs when germs such as bacteria and fungi gain the power to fight off the drugs designed to kill them. The misuse of antibiotics was a big reason for the rise — unfinished or unnecessary prescriptions that didn’t kill the germs made them stronger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;In recent years, the CDC has drawn attention to “ &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/afcee30eb24848d38f9b855fbcc9a4ba"&gt;nightmare bacteria&lt;/a&gt; ” resistant to a wide range of antibiotics. That includes carbapenems, a class of antibiotics considered a last resort for treatment of serious infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Researchers drew data from 29 states that do the necessary testing and reporting of carbapenem-resistant bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;They counted 4,341 cases of carbapenem-resistant bacterial infections from those states in 2023, with 1,831 of them the NDM variety. The researchers did not say how many of the infected people died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The rate of carbapenem-resistant infections rose from just under 2 per 100,000 people in 2019 to more than 3 per 100,000 in 2023 — an increase of 69%. But the rate of NDM cases rose from around 0.25 to about 1.35 — an increase of 460%, the authors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;A researcher not involved in the study said the increase is probably related to the &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/hub/covid-19-pandemic"&gt;COVID-19 pandemic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“We know that there was a huge surge in antibiotic use during the pandemic, so this likely is reflected in increasing drug resistance,” said Dr. Jason Burnham, a Washington University researcher, in an email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The CDC’s count is only a partial picture. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Many states are not fully testing and reporting cases. Even in states that do, cases tend to be among hospital patients sick enough to warrant special testing. Many hospitals also aren’t able to do the testing needed to detect certain forms of genetic resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The CDC researchers did not have data from some of the most populous states, including California, Florida, New York and Texas, which means the absolute number of U.S. infections “is definitely underestimated,” Burnham said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;This is not the first study to report a rise. A CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7423a2.htm"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; published in June noted an increase in NDM cases in New York City between 2019 and 2024. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;This story was first published Sept. 23, 2025. It was updated Sept. 24, 2025, to make clear that Walters said routine infections could become harder to treat rather than become a chronic problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 nALdY copyright"&gt;Copyright 2025 The Associated Press. All rights reserved. This material may not be published, broadcast, rewritten or redistributed without permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ClickOnDetroit</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxNTUctUVFrWEo2TndYNkZmeFVKaVR3X3RaNnpzMVFzLTdFc05faktYZzFaYUw0MHktMVlVd09uLTdJelBqSmZOMEc2V25vdXB6TkxsM2UwNzJsbVVrbzBFRzVPZUtkTEtFT3ZyRGxteUJUQjJSeFVYZlZNQ3RrSS12MVNkcnFuOXV2UmQwTmoxYlFZSmlfRnViSkYxaWo0blVUOXBfaFlLU1dRa1FTMmJrWVQ0M0twdERkbzdZNzZMLXk</guid></item><item><title>“我的眼泪可以帮助人们在脑肿瘤中存活下来” - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cz698z5p84lo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;'My tears could help people survive brain tumours'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Lynette Horsburgh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;North West&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6a97/live/44223430-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Cancer Research UK handout Alex Davies lying in a hospital bed. He has brown stubble with a bandage around his head. He is wearing a black and grey top. Alex is smiling." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Cancer Research UK handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Alex Davies is taking part in the study that could help people get more timely diagnoses&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A father with an incurable brain tumour has donated his tears to a pioneering study that could revolutionise how brain cancers are detected because he wants to "make a difference".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Alex Davies was initially treated for epilepsy but months later scans revealed he had a brain tumour and was told he may only have 12 to 18 months to live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The 49-year-old is now taking part in research at the Manchester Cancer Research Centre exploring if tear fluid can identify glioblastoma, the most aggressive form of brain tumour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He is hoping the study will result in earlier diagnoses and ultimately save lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Davies, from Lostock, Bolton, started suffering seizures in 2023 before later undergoing surgery, chemotherapy and radiotherapy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Follow-up scans initially showed no evidence of cancer but later tests discovered the tumour was growing back and he is now receiving palliative care at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/10ab/live/ca9dd8c0-9a0d-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Cancer Research UK handout Alex, who has brown hair and beard and Emma Davies, with long blond hair, standing outside the entrance to Manchester Cancer Research Centre wearing t-shirts which read Stand Up To Cancer. They are both smiling. It is a sunny day." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Cancer Research UK handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Alex Davies, pictured with his wife Emma&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Davies, who worked at Network Rail before his diagnosis, said he was relatively fit with no health conditions when he "collapsed out of the blue". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It took months to get to my diagnosis and my initial MRI scan didn't spot the tumour," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My symptoms worsened over about three months including severe headaches, my speech became affected as well as my balance and I was getting confused."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The father-of-two continued: "If helping with this research could mean someone like me can be diagnosed sooner, it offers real hope for the future."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Davies' wife Emma said it was a "really horrible time for us". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She said if a simple tear test could be used to bring a diagnosis forward it "would improve that awful time for so many others in the future".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Thanks to nearly £500,000 funding from Stand Up To Cancer - a joint fundraising campaign from Cancer Research UK and Channel 4 - the study led by scientists at the University of Manchester has expanded to include larger-scale trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/94c2/live/e68506b0-9a0f-11f0-8db4-51edddaa67df.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Cancer Research UK handout Left to right: Prof Petra Hamerlik, Alex and Emma Davies in a lab in the Manchester Cancer Research Centre. They are all wearing white coats and smiling. " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Cancer Research UK handout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Prof Petra Hamerlik (left) is leading the study&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Researchers have described the test as a "liquid biopsy" and said the "world-first approach" could pave the way for faster, cheaper and less invasive brain cancer diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If successful, the test could be rolled out to GP surgeries which would allow patients to receive a diagnosis much earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Prof Petra Hamerlik, who lost her father to glioblastoma at a young age, is leading the project. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She said the research had not previously been explored to diagnose brain cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My team is currently developing a tear-protein-based classifier that can differentiate brain cancer patients from healthy volunteers with high levels of accuracy," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If successful, we'll seek further funding to develop a tool that can be rapidly deployed across health services, ultimately helping patients like Alex receive a timely diagnosis and better outcomes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 06:20:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9UV3dlUGFOUnhtR1JUTnhEZWQybjlnaElkb01xXzNUNHE3WDlxcVV1alpLQk9XN1Item05VmN3RFZTUFpkMkE0WVpUZE55VHhPVGtUQnBKZTlwUdIBX0FVX3lxTE1SX2dxREFfaUdZME9meVRIOHhzRlJQOVVDWTNaNGZ4S3pkNnI1ZGdOU0dSaUZoOFBmSHFQNVFtMzdNLWQ2alBfRXl6UWVIMUFUcjk1LTl0TlBxX2RpUG1B</guid></item><item><title>「我的车变成了救护车」--牙买加观察家</title><link>https://www.jamaicaobserver.com/2025/09/28/car-became-ambulance/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="image_caption"&gt;Aiden-Jon Amir Hall was diagnosed with sickle cell anaemia at four weeks old. He passed away in 2022 at the age of five.&lt;/p&gt;				&lt;div class="body content-single-wrap"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PARENTS who each carry the sickle cell trait have a one-in-four chance of having a child with sickle cell anaemia — a painful reality with which Latoya Minott Smikle has had to live.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;During her fourth pregnancy, the now mother of five learnt that her four-week-old baby — Aiden-Jon Amir Hall — had sickle cell disease. At the time, she also found out that she, her partner, and their three other children were carriers of the sickle cell trait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After five-and-a-half years of fighting courageously, Aiden-Jon passed away due to complications with the disease in 2022. Out of that heartache and the battle she waged on his behalf, Smikle established the Aiden-Jon Amir Hall Foundation, which is seeking to raise $1 million this year to provide financial support to six individuals with sickle cell disease. The foundation is also looking to raise awareness about the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smikle recalled that before Aiden-Jon’s birth, she’d lived next door to a family who also had loved ones with sickle cell disease. She told the &lt;b&gt;Jamaica Observer&lt;/b&gt; that she became aware of their late-night hospital runs during a crisis and would hear the anguished cries of pain that echoed through the neighbourhood. Yet, she admitted, she’d never imagined that one day that would also be her reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was after Aiden was diagnosed with the disease that the Sickle Cell Unit in Kingston, which was the unit that reached out to us, they were the ones that looked up my children’s medical records from birth, and then from there they would have discovered that all of them have the trait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Imagine you’re learning that you have a baby with full sickle cell, then you’re finding out that yourself has the trait and all your living children also have the trait. I don’t think I have to tell you how jarring that was. It was very shocking and very jarring, and I think for a moment I became depressed because I would have been four weeks postpartum; that’s not the easiest kind of news to bear at that time,” she told the &lt;b&gt;Sunday Observer&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smikle said subsequent checks would later reveal that it was likely her mother who had the sickle cell trait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sickle cell is a genetic blood disorder that causes red blood cells to become rigid, abnormal cells that block blood flow in small vessels, leading to severe pain. An individual can either have the trait or the full extent of the disease. If an individual is diagnosed with the trait, it means that they inherited one sickle cell gene. The full extent of the disease, sickle cell anaemia, occurs when an individual inherits two sickle cell genes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;September is recognised as Sickle Cell Awareness Month, an annual observance dedicated to raising awareness, understanding, and support for the inherited blood disorder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aiden-Jon was diagnosed with sickle cell anaemia, the most common and severe form of the disease that causes red blood cells to become stiff, crescent-shaped, leading to anaemia, painful episodes, and potentially severe organ damage as the sickle cells block blood flow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like her neighbours, Smikle said late-night hospital visits soon became the norm as she cradled her baby through multiple painful crises. Hospital stays were rarely fewer than seven days, and balancing finances, work, and caring for her other children alongside her husband proved an overwhelming task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At times she had no choice but to take Aiden-Jon with her to work, as her spouse served in the Jamaica Constabulary Force. She recounted one particularly difficult moment when she took him with her as she led a work event in St Ann, only for him to suffer a major crisis before it began — one that ended with another hospital admission. She shared that she was living in Clarendon at the time, but wanted her son to be treated at the specialised Sickle Cell Unit in Kingston to receive comprehensive care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My car had to become an ambulance. I had to be flying like a mad woman from St Ann to get back into town because when a child is in pain; it’s difficult hearing your child cry all the way from St Ann to Kingston. There is nothing that can soothe that pain but whatever is administered to him; for example, morphine and other drugs through IV [intravenous therapy], plus give him the requisite treatment that he needs at the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s very challenging. Sickle cell anaemia is a very challenging situation for parents, especially if you’re not somebody who has a job that pays well; it even becomes a greater challenge because, financially, it is a very stressful situation,” said Smikle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She told the &lt;b&gt;Sunday Observer&lt;/b&gt; that her experience has revealed the gaps that exist in the system as well as the lack of empathy in society for individuals living with sickle cell disease and for parents struggling with their children. While the Sickle Cell Unit, which is located at the University of the West Indies, Mona, serves as a vital pillar by providing testing, resources, and some level of support, Smikle does not believe it is adequately funded to deliver holistic care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She noted, too, that even with assistance from the National Health Fund to cover the cost of medication for loved ones with sickle cell disease, many parents continue to struggle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a country where approximately one in every 150 babies is born with sickle cell disease and one in 10 adults carries the trait, she stressed that greater support and resources are urgently needed. She is hoping the Aiden-Jon Amir Hall Foundation, launched last Saturday, will bring about some of that change.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I believe that God would have known that this would have been my journey and that I would have needed all these life experiences as a tool to help me now to be better able to help other persons, and so, for me, the foundation is to let my son continue to live and continue to impact people, because even though he was five and a half years old, he was such a loving child; people were impacted by him. The testimonies that people shared at his funeral, one would have assumed that he was an adult, but he was just a child and very impactful in such a very small window of time,” she told the &lt;b&gt;Sunday Observer&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“As a Christian, some people would ask me if I don’t ask God why, and why God never healed him, but my faith tells me that God sacrificed his only son through a very brutal death to provide life for me. Whatever my son went through, whatever we all went through as a family with my son, I believe there was purpose behind it to help the forgotten, to help those that are being overlooked, to help those that can’t speak for themselves because they’re in too much pain and because nobody wants to hear anything from them,” she reasoned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Smikle said she has identified six recipients for a grant — a number that reflects how old her son would have been if he had not passed away a month before his birthday in 2022. One of the recipients is the child of a single father who has to undergo surgery to remove his/her spleen. There will be a fund-raising dinner in October to raise $1 million for the recipients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It’s to build a community that can help others who are struggling; for them to understand, ‘You’re not alone.’ For me, most importantly, my child would not have survived, not because there wasn’t effort put forward to making him live the best life he lived, but I want to help someone else’s child to be able to live longer and healthier, and to reach the peak of all that they are able to achieve so that I can smile when I visit my son’s grave; I can smile and say, ‘I did it for him,’ ” said Smikle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="attachment_4435583" class="wp-caption alignleft"&gt;&lt;a href="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591.jpg"&gt;&lt;img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-4435583" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-4435583" ta-src="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591.jpg" alt="Latoya Minott Smikle and her late son Aiden-Jon Amir Hall" ta-srcset="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591.jpg 717w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591-225x300.jpg 225w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_1-591-135x180.jpg 135w" sizes="(max-width: 717px) 100vw, 717px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-4435583" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Latoya Minott Smikle and her late son Aiden-Jon Amir Hall&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="attachment_4435586" class="wp-caption alignleft"&gt;&lt;a href="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348.jpg"&gt;&lt;img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-4435586" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-4435586" ta-src="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348.jpg" alt="A detailed shot of sickle-shaped red blood cells, illustrating the abnormal shape characteristic of sickle cell anaemia." ta-srcset="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348.jpg 1434w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348-300x200.jpg 300w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348-1024x683.jpg 1024w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348-768x512.jpg 768w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_2-348-180x120.jpg 180w" sizes="(max-width: 1434px) 100vw, 1434px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-4435586" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A detailed shot of sickle-shaped red blood cells, illustrating the abnormal shape characteristic of sickle cell anaemia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="attachment_4435589" class="wp-caption alignleft"&gt;&lt;a href="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200.jpg"&gt;&lt;img aria-describedby="caption-attachment-4435589" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="wp-image-4435589" ta-src="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200.jpg" alt="The Aiden-Jon Amir Hall Foundation is set to have a fund-raiser in October to assist parents and individuals living with sickle cell disease. The target is $1 million with six beneficiaries identified." ta-srcset="/jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200.jpg 956w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200-300x300.jpg 300w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200-150x150.jpg 150w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200-768x768.jpg 768w, /jamaicaobserver/news/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/image_3-200-180x180.jpg 180w" sizes="(max-width: 956px) 100vw, 956px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-4435589" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The Aiden-Jon Amir Hall Foundation is set to have a fund-raiser in October to assist parents and individuals living with sickle cell disease. The target is $1 million with six beneficiaries identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Jamaica Observer</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 05:17:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE5vN3RBUHN3RzVvZ2xDcDhpT0p4TXlCeU9FMHRPOWdUa0N3M3A4V1VxdWkzWmJIQzhocXd0bG5iNmRKRU5UOVZyRUpPX2ZvMHJkUnBoV1FMeURfNkNaXy1UOFZFY1R3QTZ4Z2x1MURkTWt1dw</guid></item><item><title>如果有人随便说了这11个短语中的任何一个，他们的挣扎比他们想承认的要多- YourTango</title><link>https://www.yourtango.com/self/someone-says-any-these-phrases-casually-struggling-more-than-admit</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people silently struggle without asking for help. Maybe it's financial problems, relationship issues, or personal pain, but they often walk through life feeling alone. While their behaviors indicate there's a problem, their words sometimes speak louder. Whether it's saying they don't care or acting like they're busy, if someone says any of these phrases casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It isn't always obvious when our loved ones are going through things, but there will sometimes be telltale signs. It could be their tone of voice or dismissive words, but it's up to us to pay close attention. Because when a person is struggling, they may be crying out for help and their words will fall on deaf ears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;If someone says any of these 11 phrases casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. 'I'm fine'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i%27m-fine.png" alt="man telling friend he's fine but secretly struggling" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i'm fine" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;loreanto | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If someone says "I'm fine" casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit. It's unfortunate, but most people who are struggling won't reveal that their mental health is in decline. Filled with guilt and shame, they'd rather cover it up by telling others they are fine, but this can be dangerous and hurtful to those who care about them most.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if they don't see it, their loved ones have a strong desire to connect and be vulnerable with each other. As the &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6125010/" rel="nofollow"&gt;American Journal of Lifestyle Medicine&lt;/a&gt; reiterated, "Humans are wired to connect, and this connection affects our health." So, while it might be tempting to push their feelings to the side, speaking to someone has a big impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/people-who-seem-they-have-their-life-together-often-hide-these-struggles"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People Who Seem Like They Have Their Life Together Often Hide These 11 Struggles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. 'It is what it is'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-it-is-what-it-is.png" alt="young man shrugging saying it is what it is" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit it is what it is" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Krakenimages.com | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some people have been let down so many times, they've learned to be nonchalant about their mental health. As a result, they may shrug and give up. But if someone says "it is what it is," they're struggling more than they want to admit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loved ones might be upset to hear it, but those dealing with mental or emotional health issues may not see it as a big deal. Maybe they were taught to just suck it up and deal with it, or are so tired of trying that they have nothing left to give.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holding everything in might make someone feel more isolated in the long run, causing them to pull away. But talking to loved ones can help and &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/most-powerful-phrase-for-someone-struggling"&gt;provide a safe space to open up&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-habits-tell-other-people-everything-they-need-know-about-you"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8 Subtle Habits That Tell Other People Everything They Need To Know About You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. 'I'm just tired'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i%27m-just-tired.png" alt="tired woman overworked" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i'm just tired" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;CrizzyStudio | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the number of people working overtime to make ends meet, it isn't uncommon to hear people complain about how tired they are. But when someone uses their tiredness as an excuse to avoid doing certain things, like socializing with friends or taking care of their daily responsibilities, it's not a good sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who are struggling are shutting themselves out from seeking help, making their mental health issues worse. And according to a &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/1745691614568352" rel="nofollow"&gt;study published in Perspectives on Psychological Science&lt;/a&gt;, loneliness and social isolation are twice as harmful to someone's physical and mental health as obesity is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/truly-smart-people-usually-avoid-anyone-who-does-these-things"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Truly Smart People Usually Avoid Anyone Who Does These 11 Things&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. 'I don't care anymore'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i-don%27t-care-anymore.png" alt="woman telling friend i don't care anymore" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i don't care anymore" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Pheelings media | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/subtle-signs-not-just-stressed-completely-exhausted-emotionally"&gt;Once someone is completely drained&lt;/a&gt;, everything comes in one ear and goes out the other. Due to their pure exhaustion, they may admit they don't care anymore, even if internally they're not doing well. Because despite how nonchalant they want to be, deep down inside, they're hurting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, due to their stubborn nature, it might be nearly impossible to have a one-on-one conversation about how they actually feel. So used to being closed off, they keep a lid on their emotions until they eventually explode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/wellness/proven-techniques-healing-brain-wound-humans-experience-trauma"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4 Proven Techniques For Healing The 'Brain Wound' Humans Experience From Trauma&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. 'It could be worse'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-it-could-be-worse.png" alt="struggling man telling friend it could be worse" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit it could be worse" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;fizkes | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there's one thing to notice about a person who's struggling, it's that they'll always find a way to demean their own emotions. Like clockwork, they'll compare their issues to someone who is seemingly struggling more than them, downplaying their own pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But just because it isn't as severe as someone else's plight, doesn't make it any less important. As one &lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/doiLanding?doi=10.1037%2Fpas0001155" rel="nofollow"&gt;study from Psychological Assessment&lt;/a&gt; found, people who invalidate their own emotions feel more upset and are more readily activated emotionally. So, once someone is already closed off, it might take a professional to get them to open back up again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health/things-people-used-be-ashamed-of-now-considered-healthy"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Things People Used To Be Ashamed Of That Are Now Considered Healthy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;6. 'I don't want to talk about it'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i-don%27t-want-to-talk-about-it.png" alt="mentally stressed woman saying don't want to talk about it" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i don't want to talk about it" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;StratfordProductions | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When times get tough, it can feel impossible to open up and share what's on your mind. Whether it's from embarrassment or guilt, a person saying they don't want to talk about it is likely suffering in silence. It isn't always their intention to &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/things-people-hide-their-feelings-understand"&gt;shut people out or hide their emotions&lt;/a&gt;, but it might come from a place of fear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, just because it's hard doesn't mean they should give up. Even if it's something small like journaling their thoughts, actively finding a way to vent is the best way to figure out what to say or, at the very least, get those emotions out in a healthy and productive way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/habits-quietly-successful-people-miserable-people-overlook"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 Habits Of Quietly Successful People That Miserable Folks Always Overlook&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;7. 'It doesn't matter'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-it-doesn%27t-matter.png" alt="upset woman telling partner it doesn't matter" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit it doesn't matter" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;simona pilolla 2 | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If someone says "it doesn't matter" casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit. Because the truth is, it does matter to them, they just don't want to express it for one reason or another. Perhaps they don't want to feel like a burden or are prone to overthinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And according to &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/the-mind-body-link/202504/the-hidden-cost-of-overthinking"&gt;psychologist Kyle Davies&lt;/a&gt;, "When we're constantly second-guessing or trying to outthink our emotions, we become disconnected from the deeper signals of clarity, insight, and instinct that reside within us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even so, it's their choice whether they want to share or not. Despite venting being good for their mental health, those who struggle will always do things on their own terms, despite it harming them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/money/people-who-never-struggle-financially-avoid-these-everyday-habits"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People Who Never Struggle Financially Avoid These 11 Everyday Habits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;8. 'I'll figure it out'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i%27ll-figure-it-out.png" alt="woman thinking i'll figure it out" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i'll figure it out" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, people need to figure things out on their own. Despite how difficult the obstacle may be, they can't always depend on others to save them. But this doesn't mean they have to shut everyone out completely. Even if they can't always help, at the very least, people can offer the support needed to keep moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who don't bother asking for help are always going to struggle the most. Even if they can do it all on their own, isolation and the feeling of helplessness are only intensified when they shut down. This is why it's important to let people in. Because nobody does anything alone and comes out the other end successful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/notice-things-someones-house-struggling-more-they-admit"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If You Notice These 11 Things At Someone's House, They're Struggling More Than They Admit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;9. 'I can't complain'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i-can%27t-complain.png" alt="man telling woman i can't complain hiding struggles" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i can't complain" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;MAYA LAB | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people were taught not to complain from a young age. They were told that no matter how difficult life got, there was plenty to be grateful for. And while this might have been said with the best of intentions, never complaining isn't healthy. Holding everything in is bound to mess with a person's mental health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/the-addiction-connection/202312/how-to-stop-intellectualizing-your-emotions"&gt;clinical psychologist Rubin Khoddam&lt;/a&gt; explained, "&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/not-so-subtle-signs-you-might-be-intellectualizer"&gt;Intellectualizing emotions is a defense mechanism&lt;/a&gt; that serves as a shield against the overwhelming intensity of feelings. It's the process of suppressing emotions by overthinking, analyzing, or explaining them away. It can be rooted in our upbringing, societal expectations, or personal coping strategies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/simple-daily-tasks-feel-impossible-when-body-stuck-fight-flight-mode"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Simple Daily Tasks That Feel Impossible When Your Body Is Stuck In 'Fight-Or-Flight' Mode&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;10. 'Same old, same old'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-same-old-same-old.png" alt="woman telling friend same old same old secretly struggling" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit same old same old" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If someone says "same old, same old" casually, they're struggling more than they want to admit because despite wanting people to think that nothing has changed, they're secretly dealing with problems they believe others won't understand. So, they choose to portray everything as just fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While they might not see anything wrong with this, shutting out others is hurtful. After all, feeling abandoned can hurt just about anyone's feelings. Does this mean people have to open up completely? No, but simply saying, "I'm going through something, but I'd rather not talk about it now" is a lot better than keeping them in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/tiny-ways-people-can-tell-you-didnt-shower-even-when-try-freshen-up"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Tiny Ways People Can Tell You Didn't Shower, Even When You Try To Freshen Up&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;11. 'I'm just busy'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-09/someone-says-phrases-casually-struggling-admit-i%27m-just-busy.png" alt="upset woman on phone saying i'm just busy" title="if someone says any of these phrases casually they're struggling more than they want to admit i'm just busy" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;fizkes | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether it's work or family, there's nothing inherently wrong with someone saying they're busy. Likely, it's true. But everyone needs a break now and then, and using being busy as an excuse is never a good sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/your-body-has-something-to-tell-you/202412/the-cost-of-fighting-your-unwanted-emotions"&gt;psychologist Elizabeth Sadock&lt;/a&gt; put it,"Suppressing emotion is like denying hunger: It persists because it serves an essential purpose." So, even if they're not revealing how they truly feel, eventually, it will come back to bite them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/family/quiet-struggles-only-moms-who-financially-provide-for-their-families-will-understand"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Quiet Struggles Only Moms Who Financially Provide For Their Families Will Understand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marielisa Reyes is a writer with a bachelor's degree in psychology who covers self-help, relationships, career, family, and astrology topics.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="midcat-most-popular"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Related Stories From YourTango:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="rc-widget-c743d1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>YourTango</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 03:33:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNYU1pQ1AtVkUyU0pIRUlwTHVick1jdW9vVjZnYWpxc1l6bS1hc05FY3IzTVBaS3IyNzFiV18yamJmSW94V25BNHJER0tuTHg2LXJ5eDJxNmNmLWlCaXlrWl9DMVZGcEVtZlNtcDZIRWZuMlRzZHdxOFpmcFJWb01IYTl4cWJWMGp2TlM1YnNKd1J3Y2g0b1RIS0dzeW5UUQ</guid></item><item><title>8个爱好婴儿潮一代发誓-科学现在说实际上可以延长你的寿命- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/z-8-hobbies-boomers-swore-by-that-science-now-says-actually-extend-your-life/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p data-start="432" data-end="555"&gt;It’s funny—some of the things younger generations teased boomers about actually turn out to have serious health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="557" data-end="755"&gt;Science has been catching up with common sense in the last few decades, and research now shows that several of the hobbies boomers grew up with—or never let go of—are directly linked to longevity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="757" data-end="958"&gt;These aren’t high-tech, expensive pursuits. They’re everyday activities, woven into life without fanfare. And maybe that’s the point: the stuff that really sustains us isn’t flashy, it’s sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="960" data-end="982"&gt;Let’s get into them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="989" data-end="1006"&gt;1. Gardening&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1008" data-end="1098"&gt;Ever wonder why so many boomers spent their weekends pruning roses or planting tomatoes?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1100" data-end="1410"&gt;Turns out, gardening isn’t just about curb appeal or homegrown produce. Studies link it to lower stress, better immune function, and reduced risk of dementia. Digging in the dirt exposes us to microbes that boost serotonin. Plus, gardening keeps you moving in a low-impact way that’s sustainable for decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1412" data-end="1595"&gt;One meta-analysis found that gardening interventions had &lt;a href="https://systematicreviewsjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13643-024-02457-9?.com"&gt;a moderate positive effect on well-being&lt;/a&gt; and mental health across multiple studies. It’s a habit that feeds both the body and the mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1597" data-end="1919"&gt;I’ve noticed this myself when I tend to my balcony plants. Even just ten minutes with my hands in soil resets my stress levels. The quiet focus of pruning leaves feels a lot like meditation—but with tomatoes at the end of it. If you’ve got a yard—or even a few pots—you’ve got a built-in therapy session waiting for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="1926" data-end="1941"&gt;2. Walking&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1943" data-end="2029"&gt;Boomers walked. A lot. They didn’t think of it as exercise—it was just part of life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2031" data-end="2373"&gt;Now, science says it’s one of the best predictors of healthy aging. Walking improves cardiovascular health, supports bone density, and even sharpens memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2031" data-end="2373"&gt;A 2022 genetic study of over 400,000 participants found that brisk walkers had significantly longer telomeres—and suggested that walking faster could&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2022/04/220420133538.htm?.com"&gt; slow biological aging&lt;/a&gt; by the equivalent of about 16 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2375" data-end="2651"&gt;The beauty of walking is its accessibility. You don’t need gear or a gym membership. Just shoes and time. It’s also underrated as a creativity booster. Steve Jobs was famous for his walking meetings, and research backs up the idea that &lt;a href="https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/xlm-a0036577.pdf?.com"&gt;walking helps with divergent thinking.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2653" data-end="2878"&gt;I learned this on a trip to Japan when I joined an older local group on their morning walk. Their energy was contagious, and it hit me: this is a habit you can keep doing well into your eighties. No extreme workouts needed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="2885" data-end="2905"&gt;3. Volunteering&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2907" data-end="3002"&gt;Many boomers made volunteering a staple—whether at church, the library, or community centers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3004" data-end="3208"&gt;Research shows that giving your time doesn’t just help others; it extends your own life. People who volunteer regularly have lower mortality rates, better mental health, and a stronger sense of purpose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3210" data-end="3421"&gt;One prospective study found that adults over 50 who volunteered at least 200 hours per year were about &lt;a href="https://europepmc.org/article/PMC/3804225?.com"&gt;40 % less likely to develop hypertension. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3423" data-end="3669"&gt;Purpose is medicine. And volunteering gives it in spades. It satisfies the psychological need for relatedness, something self-determination theory highlights as essential for well-being. In other words, helping others reminds us that we belong.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="3676" data-end="3712"&gt;4. Playing cards or board games&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3714" data-end="3799"&gt;Friday night poker nights, bridge clubs, Scrabble marathons. Boomers swore by them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3801" data-end="4078"&gt;Now science confirms that regularly playing games protects against cognitive decline. Social interaction plus strategy keeps neural pathways firing. In a French prospective cohort (the Paquid study), regular board game players had about &lt;a href="https://bmjopen.bmj.com/content/3/8/e002998?.com"&gt;15 % lower risk of dementia&lt;/a&gt; over 20 years compared to non-players.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4080" data-end="4321"&gt;Games do something else too: they create shared rituals. That weekly bridge night isn’t just entertainment—it’s community plus mental exercise. The anticipation of the game, the inside jokes, even the competition—all of it feeds longevity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4323" data-end="4532"&gt;I’ve mentioned this before, but when I lived in Spain for a summer, I saw older folks gather nightly in plazas to play dominoes. They weren’t just passing time—they were literally keeping their brains alive.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="4539" data-end="4554"&gt;5. Dancing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4556" data-end="4648"&gt;If you’ve ever been dragged to a boomer wedding, you’ve seen the electric slide in action.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4650" data-end="4938"&gt;Beyond the cheesy moves, dancing is insanely good for you. It combines aerobic activity, balance training, and social connection. Studies show that dancing lowers the risk of heart disease and improves brain health. Some even suggest it &lt;a href="https://montefioreeinstein.org/news/2023/01/05/social-dancing-improve-cognition-reduce-alzheimers-risk?.com"&gt;reduces the likelihood of developing Alzheimer’s.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4940" data-end="5174"&gt;Neurologists point out that dancing challenges the brain in unique ways: you have to coordinate movement, remember steps, and often improvise in rhythm with others. That blend of physical and mental effort is rare outside of sports.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5176" data-end="5359"&gt;Plus—it’s fun. Unlike forcing yourself onto a treadmill, dancing makes exercise feel like joy. No surprise it triggers dopamine release, which is linked to motivation and happiness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="5366" data-end="5389"&gt;6. Cooking at home&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5391" data-end="5445"&gt;Boomers weren’t eating out every night. They cooked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5447" data-end="5652"&gt;Science backs this habit big time. Home-cooked meals tend to be healthier, with fewer processed ingredients and less sodium. Cooking also engages creativity and gives a sense of control over your health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5654" data-end="5882"&gt;One study found that people in Taiwan and Australia who cooked up to five times a week had &lt;a href="https://www.bluezones.com/2018/04/want-to-eat-better-and-live-longer-learn-to-cook/?.com"&gt;a 47 % greater chance of being alive ten years later.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5884" data-end="6157"&gt;I still remember my grandmother teaching me how to make lentil stew. At the time, I thought it was just food. Now I realize it was one of the healthiest “hobbies” she could have passed down. Cooking ties health with tradition, creating a kind of resilience you can taste.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="6164" data-end="6179"&gt;7. Reading&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6181" data-end="6287"&gt;Bookshelves lined with novels, biographies, or how-to guides—that was a common boomer household feature.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6289" data-end="6501"&gt;Reading isn’t just entertainment. It boosts empathy, reduces stress, and improves brain connectivity. A 2016 Yale study found that people who read books regularly&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0277953616303689?.com"&gt; lived almost two years longer&lt;/a&gt; than non-readers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6503" data-end="6679"&gt;Books are also a powerful way to practice “deep focus” in a world that constantly interrupts us. That immersion strengthens attention span, which is protective for the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6681" data-end="6978"&gt;Personally, I find that reading grounds me in a way scrolling never could. I’ll pick up a behavioral science book and suddenly lose hours, not because I’m distracted but because I’m absorbed. That kind of focus is becoming rare—and it might be one of the healthiest mental workouts we have left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="6985" data-end="7024"&gt;8. Bowling and other social sports&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7026" data-end="7097"&gt;Bowling leagues were a thing. So were golf groups and softball teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7099" data-end="7357"&gt;At first glance, they seem like just casual fun. But social sports combine three powerful life-extending elements: movement, community, and routine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7099" data-end="7357"&gt;One longitudinal study found that higher diversity in social activities (e.g. clubs, groups, sports) was linked to &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/psychsocgerontology/article/79/5/gbae021/7609169?&amp;amp;login=false"&gt;lower mortality risk&lt;/a&gt; even after adjusting for health and activity frequency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7099" data-end="7357"&gt;The game matters less than the connection. Whether you’re rolling strikes or gutter balls, you’re winning at health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7479" data-end="7817"&gt;What fascinates me is how these activities create “third places”—spaces outside home and work where people gather. Sociologists argue these places are essential for community health, and boomers knew this instinctively. A bowling alley wasn’t just about pins. It was about friendship, laughter, and rituals that kept people coming back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="7824" data-end="7843"&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7845" data-end="7946"&gt;The hobbies that keep us alive aren’t flashy. They’re simple, social, and woven into everyday life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7948" data-end="8132"&gt;Boomers didn’t need wearables or biohacking apps to tell them what felt good. They trusted habits that gave them connection, movement, and purpose. And now the science backs them up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8134" data-end="8251"&gt;So the next time you’re tempted to dismiss a “boomer pastime,” maybe lean in. It might just add years to your life.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 01:35:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxQbFUxdW05X1FTMlFBU19WdHlYNXg3eUlidUwxb0pxbGU2bE9va1ZWTUdHZUtELU9oOHRLTldxNmI3OWI5NFBkVTVlMTV1c1NGRkczUFEwZ2V6TUdhejNiSHBhRWVNbHRlX0JBaWZmUWxRUVdVLVdtczVvdUV0aTJtQTBXN0Z1XzB4dnprR21XTXEyZmI5TWxDZFZVenBuTUpzZEFpLVZTVks0bl9sVEZqMUFB</guid></item><item><title>这可能是人类第一艘飞往另一个太阳系的多代星际飞船吗？ - Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/possibly-humanitys-first-multi-generational-starship-chrysalis-to-another-solar-system/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new interstellar concept called Chrysalis sketches a 36 mile long rotating habitat designed to carry 2,400 people on a one way, 400 year trip. The destination is &lt;a href="https://www.nasa.gov/image-article/alpha-centauri-triple-star-system-about-4-light-years-from-earth/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Alpha Centauri&lt;/a&gt;, about 25 trillion miles from Earth, a distance that rules out resupply once the ship leaves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The plan treats the vessel as a closed society that must feed itself, educate children, care for the sick, and manufacture what it needs while coasting between stars. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It proposes layered habitats for farms, homes, schools, industry, and storage, all made livable by rotation that supplies gravity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-the-chrysalis-plan"&gt;The Chrysalis plan&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://i4is.org/who-we-are/board-of-directors/#gsc.tab=0" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Dr Andreas Hein&lt;/a&gt; is executive director of the Initiative for Interstellar Studies (&lt;a href="https://i4is.org/"&gt;I4IS&lt;/a&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group convened experts to see whether architecture, engineering, and social systems could be woven into a practical multi-century mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team behind Chrysalis proposes a long training phase on Earth. Early generations would live in isolated Antarctic stations for 70 to 80 years to build the habits, culture, and mental resilience needed for life off planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chrysalis uses a nested shell layout around a central spine. Inner-zones grow plants, fungi, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/living-microbes-found-sealed-inside-2-billion-year-old-rock/"&gt;microbes&lt;/a&gt;, insects, and some livestock in controlled farms, mid layers hold parks, clinics, schools, and libraries, and outer shells host workshops and storage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dwellings sit between community space and light industry to keep daily life close to work and services. The outermost storehouse would be robot heavy to cut human labor and risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-alpha-centauri-and-proxima-b"&gt;Alpha Centauri and Proxima b&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alpha Centauri is the nearest star system, which shortens the voyage by every realistic metric. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The likely landing zone is &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature19106" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Proxima Centauri b&lt;/a&gt;, an Earth-size exoplanet reported to orbit in a temperate zone that could allow liquid water under some conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the ship enters the system, shuttles housed in the central core would ferry crews and equipment to the planet. The design treats that arrival as the beginning of settlement rather than the end of the mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The proposal aims to arrive with full knowledge systems, from agriculture to medicine to materials science. It assumes no external logistics, so onboard manufacturing and repair are treated as basic survival needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-artificial-gravity-and-health"&gt;Artificial gravity and health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chrysalis relies on artificial gravity from steady rotation to keep bodies closer to Earth normal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://technology.nasa.gov/patent/TOP2-311" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Rotation-based gravity&lt;/a&gt; is a studied countermeasure for cardiovascular and musculoskeletal deconditioning, as summarized in a &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/physiology/articles/10.3389/fphys.2018.00716/full"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; that evaluated centrifuge experiments in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spin introduces tradeoffs like &lt;a href="https://oceanservice.noaa.gov/education/tutorial_currents/04currents1.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Coriolis effects&lt;/a&gt; that can disturb balance if rotation is too fast. The nested layout helps tune spin and radius so living areas feel stable while still providing adequate effective gravity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Radiation exposure is another core risk for a centuries long voyage. The concept leans on structure and materials, using mass in the habitat shells to reduce particle flux rather than relying only on specialized shields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health care sits in the communal layer near schools and parks to keep services accessible. That placement supports daily routines and reduces travel time for patients and caregivers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-chrysalis-power-and-propulsion"&gt;Chrysalis power and propulsion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For power and thrust, the team points to nuclear fusion as the long term energy source. Fusion plant concepts and timelines remain under &lt;a href="https://www.iaea.org/publications/15777/iaea-world-fusion-outlook-2024" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;development&lt;/a&gt; and have been mapped and evaluated extensively. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors propose a 20 to 25 year construction window once industry can deliver the required systems. They treat in-space manufacturing as a mission essential capability to replace worn parts and build upgrades during cruise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Energy production, recycling, and life support appear across multiple layers to avoid single points of failure. Heavy maintenance and logistics live at the outer edge where robots can operate with fewer human safety constraints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The population would be planned to hover near 1,500 to balance resources, education, and health. That cap sits below the ship’s maximum berth count to leave margin for emergencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-competitions-like-this-help"&gt;Why competitions like this help&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chrysalis won first place in the 2025 &lt;a href="https://www.projecthyperion.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;competition&lt;/a&gt;, and the jury praised both technical breadth and attention to people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chrysalis impressed the jury with its system-level coherence and innovative design of the modular habitat structure but also overall depth of detail,” wrote the Project Hyperion &lt;a href="https://www.projecthyperion.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;jury&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Chrysalis is a living spaceship where humans, robots and artificial intelligent agents share information, experiences and decision-making processes,” stated the Chrysalis team, explaining that their starship was more than hardware. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We asked participants to integrate architecture, technology and social systems to conceptualise a functional society spanning centuries, and the outcome was beyond expectations,” said Dr Hein executive director of the &lt;a href="https://i4is.org/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Initiative for Interstellar Studies&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concept work cannot replace flight hardware, yet it shapes the questions future engineers must answer. It also documents social and cultural choices that matter as much as engines when people live their whole lives off &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/earths-atmospheric-rivers-have-shifted-towards-the-poles-causing-big-local-weather-changes/"&gt;Earth&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-chrysalis-would-prepare-for-arrival"&gt;How Chrysalis would prepare for arrival&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The core would carry compact shuttles sized for surface hops, cargo, and emergency evacuation. Pilots and maintenance crews would train during the cruise so landings do not depend on a single cohort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Food systems would keep a mix of biomes, from tropical to boreal, to preserve biodiversity and stabilize diets. That diversity lowers the risk that one crop failure cascades across the whole &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/ecosystem-attack-predicting-the-success-of-species-invasions/"&gt;ecosystem&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowledge transfer shows up in how learning is embedded in daily life. Schools would be near labs, workshops, and farms so students practice skills early and keep them across generations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governance would be transparent, with planned births, shared resources, and collaborative decision tools. The aim is to prevent shocks to a small population where every loss hurts community resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 01:19:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxPM2UxR1NrNUdFWlItWDFNYzJHSzBPLWUwWW02OS1LUWJ5LW9XOWdDbFdVTGF2UnYxRGtieXBQc3hxUkRWUGdZLWlfeUJsazFqVU1EU0E0REY3VHB1V0FwMWE2cmd4VXh5RFJSX2FQc1JNLWlZbklxaHJPdFdjU1ZqTk53NWZXaVRUMktkRFc1VzNIUzJuR2Fra0RLZ09UWDVVUTZQSmFGQjd2WV9GVmg3MjNUR04</guid></item><item><title>缓解膝盖疼痛并避免手术的六个简单步骤- dailymail.co.uk</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15139739/ease-knee-pain-avoid-surgery-six-steps.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When keen runner Jon Reeves, 54, began struggling to get down the stairs in the morning, he knew his knee pain was more than just sports injuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The father of two from Oxfordshire had gone from daily runs and regular badminton matches to strapping up his inflamed joints and dosing himself on painkillers just to get through the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2020 doctors confirmed the cause: &lt;a target="_self" href="/sciencetech/osteoarthritis/index.html" id="mol-7df044a0-9ba6-11f0-ac66-c563bb30a77b" class=""&gt;osteoarthritis&lt;/a&gt; – the degenerative joint disease that affects about ten million Britons. More than half of cases strike the knee, with 100,000 people a year ending up on the &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/nhs/index.html" id="mol-7dee96f0-9ba6-11f0-ac66-c563bb30a77b"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; waiting list for joint replacement surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Getting the diagnosis was devastating,’ says Jon. ‘I thought it was an old person’s disease and I was worried it would only get worse.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Initially prescribed anti-inflammatory drugs and exercises that were painful and brought little relief, Jon’s condition worsened until doctors warned him that he would need a double knee replacement. But by combining acupuncture, weight training and a Mediterranean-style diet, he was able to slash his pain level and postpone surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I am now managing amazingly – largely pain-free and back to hiking, swimming, cycling and long walks with my dalmatian Oscar,’ he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say thousands more like Jon could delay or even avoid surgery with simple lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Jon Reeves was diagnosed wth osteoarthritis in 2020. By combining acupuncture, weight training and a Mediterranean-style diet, he slashed his pain level and postponed surgery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The degenerative joint disease affects about ten million Britons. More than half of cases strike the knee, with 100,000 people a year ending up on the NHS waiting list for joint replacement surgery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt; Last week, Mail on Sunday columnist Dr Ellie Cannon wrote she was ‘worried that not enough osteoarthritis patients realise there are steps they can take to avoid knee replacement surgery’. In response she had a flood of letters and emails from readers sharing their own remedies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One, Bill Ellis, 81, from Suffolk, who suffers from osteoarthritis in his knees, said a combination of supplements ‘has certainly made a difference in reducing my pain’ adding: ‘I also do 20 squats every other morning, not too deep I hasten to add, and it keeps the muscles stronger, which helps.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eddie Boyle, 77, from Bedfordshire, swears by capsaicin cream – which contains extracts from chillis – for reducing his pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So from diet swaps to supplements that work and exercises to ease the agony, here is the experts’ guide to managing the pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;1. FOLLOW THE MED DIET &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hailed as a key to longevity, a Mediterranean diet has also been shown to help reduce the symptoms of arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The eating style, common in Greece, Italy and Spain, is focused on fresh fruit and vegetables, fish and chicken, whole grains and olive oil, while cutting back on red meat and sweets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2016 study of more than 4,000 people with osteoarthritis in their knees found those who stuck most closely to the diet were significantly less likely to suffer crippling joint pain. They also scored better on overall physical health and showed fewer signs of depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say the diet’s anti-inflammatory properties can help soothe swollen joints, while also protecting heart health and supporting weight control – two key risk factors for arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the Mediterranean diet won’t ‘cure’ osteoarthritis, scientists suggest it offers a simple, natural way to ease symptoms and improve day-to-day well-being.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘The Mediterranean diet can be really beneficial for patients,’ says Dr Wendy Holden, medical advisor for Arthritis Action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘A diet rich in fruit and veg as well as fish and whole grains, in addition to cutting down on ultra-processed foods, is key to cutting inflammation.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A 2016 study of more than 4,000 people with osteoarthritis in their knees found those who stuck most closely to the Mediterranean diet were significantly less likely to suffer crippling joint pain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Protein intake is another crucial part of the puzzle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘From the age of 40 our muscle mass declines by 2 to 3 per cent per year, so we need to take in more protein from different sources in our diet – ideally at least 40 grams daily,’ says Dr Lucy Donaldson, Director of Research at Versus Arthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘This can be a challenge for many of us, but fortunately our research shows that an essential building block for protein called leucine – found in fish, nuts and legumes – is very potent at stimulating muscle protein levels, helping to maintain skeletal muscle.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other experts argue that the type of diet matters less than weight loss itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘The real benefit to any diet, in relation to osteoarthritis symptoms, is maintaining a healthy weight,’ says Professor Philip Conaghan, an arthritis specialist at the University of Leeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘This is because it reduces the load on the joints, which in turn eases pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘But excess fat also drives inflammation, which makes symptoms worse.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research backs this up. Studies show weight loss reduces levels of inflammatory chemicals released by fat tissue, and can slow cartilage damage even in non-weight-bearing joints such as the hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Anecdotally, doctors say patients who shed excess pounds often report less wrist or finger pain – clear evidence the benefits go beyond simply lightening the load on knees and hips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;2. TRY WEIGHT-LOSS JABS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mounting evidence suggests weight-loss injections may ease the pain of osteoarthritis – and in some cases this may be due to more than just losing excess fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For 54-year-old Sian Rios, who suffers from arthritis in her hip, a private prescription for Mounjaro has meant she can finally ditch her walking stick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Before starting the jabs, the care home manager from Swindon was in such severe pain she was unable to walk more than a few metres. At night the throbbing pain would wake her repeatedly, leaving her exhausted and sleep-deprived.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatRHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-e778e500-9bae-11f0-ac66-c563bb30a77b" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15139739/ease-knee-pain-avoid-surgery-six-steps.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;IT'S A FACT&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Women are 40 per cent more likely to get knee osteoarthritis than men, with an increase in cases during menopause. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Four months on, she has shed six stone to weigh just over 17st.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I feel like it has given me my life back,’ says Sian. ‘Within weeks of using Mounjaro I was suffering from less pain, but now I very rarely have flare-ups and use pain relief far less often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I have lost a lot of weight since May, but what I have really gained is mobility, confidence and hope. I’ve gone from barely being able to walk to taking strolls around the lake. It’s night and day compared with the start of the year.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Her hip replacement scheduled for later this year is now on hold thanks to her progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research backs her experience. A 2025 Taiwanese study of nearly 1,000 patients with osteoarthritis in knees found weight-loss injections reduced the risk of needing joint replacement surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Preliminary studies have suggested there is a benefit to weight-loss injections beyond just weight reduction,’ adds Dr Holden at Arthritis Action. ‘It appears they can help protect cartilage from wear and tear, slowing the progression of disease. The benefits are increasingly being reported by patients, and we are likely to see greater use of the drugs for arthritis going forwards.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Currently, however, arthritis is not included in the prescribing guidelines for weight-loss jabs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;3. BUILD STRENGTH FIRST&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say the key to managing osteoarthritis pain – and preventing it in the first place – is building strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Strictly Come Dancing star Joanne Clifton, 41, who was diagnosed with osteoarthritis in both knees in 2015, is one of those who credits strengthening exercises as preventing her from needing surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Professor Philip Conaghan regularly sees patients aged 40 to 75 with knee, hip or other joint pain, and says muscle weakness is “almost universal”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His advice is simple: ‘First, get strong, then get fit. Just telling people to walk round the block is a bad starting point – because they are weak, they can’t walk at a brisk pace and they’re not getting any benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Strictly Come Dancing star Joanne Clifton, 41, was diagnosed with osteoarthritis in both knees in 2015, and credits strengthening exercises as preventing her from needing surgery&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Once they’ve built some muscle strength, they can start on aerobic fitness, such as on an exercise bike or cross trainer, or swimming. Walking laps in a pool is a fabulous exercise for weak people.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He warns that difficulty undoing a jar, or struggling to get out of a chair or bath, are red flags – even before joint pain sets in – that muscles are weakening and putting too much strain on joints.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The benefits are clear. A review last year in the Annals of Physical and Rehabilitation Medicine concluded there was ‘overwhelming evidence’ that strength training significantly reduces pain and improves function, performance and quality of life in people with knee and hip osteoarthritis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Exercise works because joints depend on the network of muscles and tendons around them. Isaac Selby-Burton, a personal trainer who specialises in arthritis coaching, says: ‘It can be hard for people to take that initial step with exercises, because of the pain the condition causes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘I recommend starting with resistance bands, focusing on range of motion and muscles like the quads, which are vital for people with knee problems.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;4. USE ACUPUNCTURISTS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Many patients swear by acupuncture to manage osteoarthritis pain, saying it allows them to do the strengthening exercises that bring long-term relief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The ancient Chinese therapy involves inserting fine needles into specific points in the body, and is said to encourage the release of natural pain-relieving chemicals, improve circulation and reduce stiffness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatRHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-08b1d6a0-9baf-11f0-ac66-c563bb30a77b" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15139739/ease-knee-pain-avoid-surgery-six-steps.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;IT'S A FACT&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists have found evidence of osteoarthritis in dinosaur fossils, making it one of the oldest known diseases.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The evidence is mixed, but growing. A review in 2025 of 18 studies involving 14,000 people found acupuncture was effective in reducing pain and improving function in osteoarthritis. Other research has shown modest short-term benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘For many people the pain of osteoarthritis has the greatest impact on their lives,’ says Dr Donaldson at Versus Arthritis. ‘Exercise can have very positive effects on pain but isn’t suitable for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Although National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines do not recommend acupuncture for osteoarthritis, rheumatoid arthritis or other inflammatory forms of arthritis, we know many people living with chronic pain and inflammation use it. Our recent survey on complementary treatments found one in two people who tried acupuncture for arthritis reported some level of pain relief.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;5. USE SUPPLEMENTS THAT WORK&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients often swear by supplements to help ease arthritis pain – but experts say the evidence is thin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among the most popular are turmeric (or sometimes just curcumin, the chemical compound that it contains), glucosamine sulphate (which is produced commercially from shellfish exoskeletons) and chondroitin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘There is very little evidence to suggest that these supplements will help relieve osteoarthritis,’ says Dr Wendy Holden, medical advisor for Arthritis Action, who is also honorary consultant rheumatologist at Basingstoke and North Hampshire NHS Foundation trust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The only two supplements with any evidence behind them are cod liver oil and rosehip&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘The issue is that although the compounds themselves may have some benefit, supplements don’t usually contain enough of the key ingredient to make a real difference.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The only two supplements with any evidence behind them are cod liver oil and rosehip – though even here, results are mixed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cod liver oil is rich in omega-3 oils, which are thought to have anti-inflammatory effects, but trials in osteoarthritis have generally failed to show clear benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rosehip powder – which is made from the seed pods of a rose bush – has shown more promise, with several small studies and reviews suggesting it can modestly reduce pain and stiffness, though the effects are limited and further research is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;6. SPECIALIST BRACES CAN EASE SYMPTOMS &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Specialist knee braces can also help to improve osteoarthritis symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2017 study followed 63 patients awaiting total knee replacement who were fitted with an ‘unloading’ or ‘offloading’ brace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After eight years, 40 per cent of those who had worn their brace consistently for two years said they no longer needed surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The brace, made of lightweight plastic and fabric, straps around the knee to apply a gentle sideways pull that helps realign the joint. A hinge on the side absorbs some of the downward force, reducing pressure and allowing patients to be more active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Patients in the trial initially wore the brace almost constantly, before using it selectively for activities needing extra support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Those who wore it for more than six months were half as likely to require surgery as those who gave up within three months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The same model – the Unloader One, made by Icelandic company Ossur – has even been worn by TV star Ant McPartlin, 49.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;McPartlin revealed he turned to it after his struggle with painkiller addiction following his ‘botched’ knee surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>dailymail.co.uk</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:32:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPOUV4cENOblhOQjNSNWtQRWdtTjVnRFFrS1lXZnJROVRLWnNyV3hsS2F0RnhZSndjcFdPTlZ0RkpGbV9jTExwWTkwdWZVUThLTU42SjlRZ2VxUFhjbVJmQlRWTlZDOEJsc3NSTVpYX0NQTDNUZGswcHBXb3pXM1JHZHR6cndNMEEwMXdGeXByb2FwYVVCRXA3RUtCWQ</guid></item><item><title>N70,000艾滋病预防注射分裂尼日利亚人- Punch报纸</title><link>https://punchng.com/n70000-hiv-prevention-injection-splits-nigerians/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Punch Newspapers</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 00:25:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE55d0RQTWN3YVJ5LURqYVhSQTRYcnVJZS02TmhjTFZ6VHRzbjBNcWdMUnJXV01MOXFrUVcwSTdXY0xnbmFlUUJJakU5SUxhdXM2bVlZV2hCQUJocjIxTTFaVWltOHdLSnZiM0QwdVJENXpBZFJwME9HeA</guid></item><item><title>世界视网膜日：医生说，小习惯在保护你的视力方面每天都有很大的回报-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/world-retina-day-doctors-say-small-habits-pay-off-big-in-protecting-your-vision-daily/articleshow/124183315.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;World Retina Day is all about shining a light on the importance of eye health, specifically the retina, that tiny but mighty part at the back of your eye that makes clear vision possible. Without it, things like reading your favorite book, scrolling on your phone, or even recognizing faces would be a real struggle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;We at TOI spoke to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Vitreo-Retina Surgeon, Dr Agarwals Eye Hospital, Sanpada; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Senior Consultant, Ophthalmology, SIMS Hospital, Chennai; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Vitreo - Retinal Consultant, Dr Agarwals Eye Hospital, Bengaluru on common retinal conditions and how to take care of retinal health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Nutrition for healthy eyes: Here's what doctor recommends&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What are the most common retinal conditions you see today, and are cases increasing with lifestyle changes like screen time and diabetes?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Age related vision changes are usually gradually progressive like needing reading glasses(presbyopia), scattering of light especially at night, taking longer time to adjust when going from bright to dark places, fluctuating vision. These are normal age related changes which can be treated with glasses, lubricant eye drops or better lighting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if vision changes are sudden in onset, asymmetric or associated with flashes, floaters, distortion or field loss are warning symptoms and are usually associated with Retina diseases. In such conditions an urgent dilated retinal check-up is needed with an expert. If proven Retina disease then it needs certain tests and immediate treatment as time is extremely crucial in these problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common retina related conditions seen today are related to diabetes and are known as diabetic retinopathy. Yes the cases are increasing to a greater extent with a sedentary lifestyle which most of the middle-aged people are used to it nowadays. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common retinal conditions we see today are diabetic retinopathy, age related macular degenerations and Glaucoma and eye stroke. Lifestyle changes like prolonged screen time renders a person obese, enhancing diabetes. Diabetes mellitus could occur familial or secondary due to co-morbidities, bad dietary habits and sedentary lifestyle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How can people differentiate between normal age-related vision changes and potential warning signs of retinal diseases?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prolonged near work and less outdoor time is leading to higher incidence of minus Glasses called “myopia epidemic.” In children, sustained near focus may accelerate myopia progression leading to gradual increase in glass power. Higher minus power (Myopia) increases risk of several problems like retinal tears &amp;amp; detachments and Myopic macular degeneration. Chronic stress and irregular sleep are risk factors for development of central serous chorioretinopathy, a retinal condition more seen in young and middle aged males. Sedentary lifestyle, obesity and low physical activity can lead to early development of diabetic, hypertension and raised cholesterol levels which secondarily leads Diabetic Retinopathy, Retinal vein occlusion like diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The vision changes due to retinal conditions are usually sudden in onset and are more obvious like appearance of floaters in front of eyes, seeing flashes or beginning to see distorted images, at the same time vision changes related to normal ageing are usually gradual like difficulty in focusing near objects over a period of time like seen in presbyopia or gradual blurring of vision with glare like symptoms seen in cataract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Normal age-related visual changes could be due to receding of reading distance (usually starts in late 30’s or early 40’s) called as presbyopia. Dry eyes causing blurred vision, cataracts causing blurred vision or effective vision. Eye fatigue is common after straining. People cannot differentiate between the normal aging of the eyes and vision disturbances due to retinal diseases unless they become severe and cause a significant amount of vision loss. Hence, regular eye check-ups are mandatory to identify and treat them at the earliest. Retinal diseases symptoms are such as seeing floaters, flashes, loss of vision, loss of central vision, and loss of peripheral vision. Individuals should be mindful that before these symptoms occur a significant amount of retina is affected beyond repair in certain conditions like diabetes, degenerative diseases, glaucoma., etc. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;We hear a lot about diabetic retinopathy—how big of a public health concern is it right now?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Currently India has the second-largest diabetic population in the world and Diabetic Retinopathy is the most common cause of vision loss in working-age adults worldwide. Approximately in India there are 12 million people suffering from Diabetic Retinopathy and 20% of these have variable degree of permanent vision loss. The worst part of Diabetic Retinopathy is no pain, very few subtle symptoms in early stages and by the time patients present with complaints its already advanced stage with some amount of permanent vision loss. Advanced stages of diabetic retinopathy require expensive treatments like lasers, intravitreal injections, surgery). The good news is up to 90% of vision loss from DR can be prevented with timely screening, sugar control and early treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diabetic retinopathy is the leading cause of blindness in the middle aged population. Globally there were 12 crore people suffering from diabetic retinopathy in 2010 and this number can reach upto 20 crores by 2030. Diabetic retinopathy has the potential to cause blindness and with increasing prevalence of diabetes worldwide makes this condition a bigger public health condition which has to to be taken seriously and people should get screened so that the patients are diagnosed early and treated to prevent major vision loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diabetic retinopathy is of major concern in today’s world since the number of cases are increasing despite awareness. It’s a condition which affects the retinal blood vessels and in turn affects the layers of the retina at different stages causing blindness if not treated at the earliest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What role does early detection play in preventing severe vision loss from conditions like macular degeneration or retinal detachment?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Macular degeneration and retinal detachment are two separate diseases but if detected early treatment is simpler and more vision rewarding in both. In case of retinal detachment early detection involves screening for flashes and floaters, detecting peripheral Retinal degeneration/tears which can easily be treated with a quick outpatient laser via major surgery for retinal detachment. Early detection of dry macular degeneration means patients can start lifestyle changes (diet rich in antioxidants, stopping smoking, supplements in select cases) and monitoring which can slow progression of condition to more devastating disease like Wet Macular degeneration. Even in wet age related macular degeneration: If detected early, intravitreal anti-VEGF injections can preserve reading and driving vision whereas detected late (scarred macula), even the best treatment cannot restore useful central vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early detection is crucial in treating any of the retinal conditions as we can minimise the damage caused to the retina and slow the disease progression which in turn preserves the vision. In treating retinal detachment intervention done in hours to days of time will restore maximum vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ingemination to prevent peripheral vision loss due to retinal diseases is a regular eye check up with an ophthalmologist (not optical) and following the investigations and treatment protocols suggested by the doctor without fail. The amount of retinal cells lost in the inadvertence cannot be reverted. All the attempts are to retain the viable tissue for a prolonged period to give some amount of quality of life to the patient. Retinal detachment is realized early by the patient (which is possible by noticing loss of vision suddenly or gradually, floaters and flashes) can be treated well and there is a possibility of patients getting a good quality of vision post-surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;How important is diet and lifestyle in protecting retinal health, and what simple habits can people adopt?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have already discussed the role of bad lifestyle/ diet results in several retina diseases. Now let's see what rectification should be done. In terms of diets, foods rich in antioxidants (green leafy vegetables, coloured fruits) and Omega 3 fatty acids( nuts, chia seeds, fish) should be a regular part of one’s diet. Restrict refined sugars, processed food, alcohol and tobacco / smoking, regular exercise improves blood flow, lowers risk of diabetes &amp;amp; hypertension. Annual/ regular eye check-ups especially in diabetic, hypertensive or highly myopic. Balanced screen use and encourages outdoor activity in children to reduce myopia progression. Stress &amp;amp; sleep management - lowers risk of CSCR and helps overall vascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diets rich in anti oxidants like vitamin A,C,E zinc, lutein and zeaxanthin play a vital role in protecting the retina. They are found in abundance in green leafy vegetables. Also foods like fruits and vegetables support the overall functioning of the eyes. To quit smoking is another major lifestyle modification needed to be adopted as it will reduce the oxidative stress over the retina and prevent its damage. Managing blood sugar and blood pressure levels. Protection of once eyes from harmful UV radiations by using protective glasses, keeping self hydrated, reducing screen time, getting enough sleep and avoiding frequent touching of eyes also plays role in maintaining eye health. Regular eye checkups which should include dilated eye examination for early detection of retinal pathology will avoid severe vision damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="101"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A well-balanced diet is the most important requirement for healthy eyes. Fruits, nuts, green vegetables are all essential for the function of the retina which carries the electrical impulses to the brain which is converted as an image for us to see. Without balanced nutrition the retina degenerates faster. A proper lifestyle is the quintessence of healthy eyes. Cutting down on screen time, having adequate amount of sleep, using the gadgets at a proper distance (60-70cm away) with anti-reflective screen, avoiding reading in dim lights or glaring lights, following the 20/20/20 rule which is only 20 minutes of attention to gadgets at a stretch, blinking every 20 seconds, and looking at objects 20 meters away; this is of utmost importance to prevent dry eyes and eye strain while working. Well balanced nutrition is mandatory, avoiding eye injuries (wearing protective goggles at necessary times) should be borne in mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="108"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What’s one myth about retinal health you wish more people understood correctly?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="110"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Yogesh Patil: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People think that if their vision is good, their retina must be healthy. The truth is early retinal diseases are usually silent. Good vision does not equal a healthy retina. The only way to know is through a regular dilated retinal exam or imaging specially in at risk people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="114"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Krishna Nagaradh: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The major myth which I have heard from many of my patients is that eye check ups need to be done only when they face a difficulty in vision. Regular eye checkups are must especially in diabetics cause early diagnosis and treatment can avoid major eye related complications in future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="117"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dr. Kalpana R: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A common myth about absent retinal diseases is that they can be cured at any time. But the fact is in some individuals the worst outcome can be averted while in some it can be prolonged. Take good care of your eyes and see the colors of the world with a Duchenne smile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="122"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This day is a reminder to check in on your eye health, because conditions like macular degeneration, diabetic retinopathy, and retinal detachment can sneak up without obvious symptoms at first. Regular eye exams are key. A quick visit can help catch problems early and protect your sight long-term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="124"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it’s not just about doctor visits, your lifestyle plays a role too. Eating foods rich in antioxidants (think leafy greens, berries, and fish packed with omega-3s), wearing sunglasses to block UV rays, and keeping your blood sugar and blood pressure in check all support retinal health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="126"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, on World Retina Day, give your eyes some love. Schedule that eye exam, grab a pair of good shades, and maybe even swap the fries for a salad, it’s a small step with a big payoff for your vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="128"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 23:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwJBVV95cUxQTlVfVi14X19rWWYwQ2lPZzhVVmlvUkdhSmRNbS1abEktYzBhdDlYQmJ1ZGZPSlVaSzdQemJPQXdYLVpkdE9POWg3VzdKREFzZk5DOElzVW45SUo5Q2QzRTJneGNNamdKbS1WbzRXTmNnQ0hIMVJDclRDN2hpUTRDWEQxQmkzdzJBWUx6eFRfS2JiR1RPU1ZlRm5GQmdnSnZ1cVJpSjBEMWJ0OXhTZDlkQzBudzkxQ2dNOUhGajNYNEdFaXdZNzRCaDJHX0lqLXpnVzNpbGthQ2R5aHFmVG9rTHJiUi14SFZ2MEFwa21wYW53UG5zcjE1M2I3bWt4emg3bUdLZzZac2ZzU1RCd0ZEQTVOTdIBmAJBVV95cUxPeXNyY0ZtWU52UzJEVGlYazJuOXVZdHlWd01sNjlHRXJwVUZqTklmYllaQzRZSmtsSXBzb2xjM0tNVEJFaGMxbXAyNzAtY2plQ1RoT2x4cHdzODBfMVNaSV9FMXVUSkd3V1JSaWN4Vllwdy1pSGtPNW5NRkVNcXRTaXRIOG02NjRtX3dTcjl4bmVLalVoQ3BxSF9wUGgzdFVzTHNqTkd3c0xnWkNlUmFCX3MySlY2QkpjZGNScTJHak0ydTVVcV9NSnZibURTbHgwSEtyX1owTmxDTl9CN25YRFhhTllLTERvNVVQZ243dk5VUWF4Rzc4LVVQTHVYVm5XMldhOXF2azBOM0xIZTFZZ2VQblhfc0hI</guid></item><item><title>随着卡车驶入数百万只死鸡的潜在垃圾场，巴尔米拉社区感到震惊- TMJ4新闻</title><link>https://www.tmj4.com/news/jefferson-county/palmyra-community-alarmed-as-trucks-pull-into-potential-dump-site-for-millions-of-dead-chickens</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="RichTextArticleBody-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;PALMYRA, Wis. — After TMJ4's &lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.tmj4.com/news/jefferson-county/palmyra-neighbors-brace-for-second-mass-chicken-disposal-as-bird-flu-strikes-jefferson-county"&gt;initial story&lt;/a&gt; on Thursday, the Palmyra community in Jefferson County reached out to the news team concerned about the smell of millions of dead chickens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a class="Link" href="https://datcp.wi.gov/Pages/Highly-Pathogenic-Avian-Influenza-Confirmed-in-Jefferson-County.aspx"&gt;Wisconsin Department of Agriculture, Trade and Consumer Protection&lt;/a&gt;, a commercial flock of chickens were slaughtered after a case of bird flu was discovered in the county. Their bodies are believed to have been dumped in that community Saturday morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zion Rd and County Cl closed on Saturday, but large trucks could be seen driving in and out of the area where neighbor Lisa Eddy said a large egg farm owns property and previously dumped dead chickens in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eddy said trucks have been driving to the dump site all morning, drivers can be seen wearing masks, something she said is a tell tale sign that soon, the smell of millions of dead chickens will once again plague the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="Figure" itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
    
        &lt;div class="Figure-container"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/e8c75ae/2147483647/strip/true/crop/4284x5712+0+0/resize/1080x1440!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F84%2Fe6%2Fa368667d4e1db2d4458a2d97d6ea%2Fimg-1321.jpeg" alt="Lisa Eddy lives near chicken dumpsite in Palmyra" srcset="https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/e8c75ae/2147483647/strip/true/crop/4284x5712+0+0/resize/1080x1440!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F84%2Fe6%2Fa368667d4e1db2d4458a2d97d6ea%2Fimg-1321.jpeg 1x,https://ewscripps.brightspotcdn.com/dims4/default/d96de6c/2147483647/strip/true/crop/4284x5712+0+0/resize/2160x2880!/quality/90/?url=http%3A%2F%2Fewscripps-brightspot.s3.amazonaws.com%2F84%2Fe6%2Fa368667d4e1db2d4458a2d97d6ea%2Fimg-1321.jpeg 2x"&gt;&lt;p class="Figure-credit" itemprop="author"&gt;Marcus Aarsvold&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
        &lt;figcaption class="Figure-caption" itemprop="caption"&gt;Lisa Eddy lives near chicken dumpsite in Palmyra&lt;/figcaption&gt;
    
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's super frustrating, annoying and really impacts your quality of life. You can't be outside, you can't have the windows open and you can't enjoy walks with the dogs or anything," Eddy said. "We're also worried about the groundwater. This is the second time that they're dumping millions of birds. When is it going to stop?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said the first time this happened, the smell lasted for an entire year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class="Link" href="https://datcp.wi.gov/Pages/Highly-Pathogenic-Avian-Influenza-Confirmed-in-Jefferson-County.aspx"&gt;Wisconsin Department of Agriculture &lt;/a&gt;confirmed the bird flu case of a commercial flock in Jefferson County and that they're being depopulated, but did not name the specific farm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;"This story was reported on-air by a journalist and has been converted to this platform with the assistance of AI. Our editorial team verifies all reporting on all platforms for fairness and accuracy."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div class="Form"&gt;&lt;p class="Form-title"&gt;Let's talk:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class="Form-description"&gt;Hey there! At TMJ4 News, we're all about listening to our audience and tackling the stuff that really matters to you. Got a story idea, tip, or just want to chat about this piece? Hit us up using the form below. For more ways to get in touch, head over to tmj4.com/tips. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
        
        
    
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;It’s about time to watch on your time. Stream local news and weather 24/7 by searching for “TMJ4” on your device.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.tmj4.com/apps" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;Available for download on Roku, Apple TV, Amazon Fire TV, and more.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.tmj4.com/reportatypo"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Report a typo or error&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; // &lt;a class="Link" href="https://www.tmj4.com/news/submit-news-tip"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Submit a news tip&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TMJ4 News</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 23:22:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxPcHdMYjVCTXo4ZkVQVjRfLTA5SUVmU01odkNmcmgwcDk1b1BZY3ZTZFFzRGhLR3FGcmo0ZmNMVDQtLVIxUWhBZGFuMHlrNjZLb2hVMkVUZXNzc2psc1VqWlJpM3NLMnF5Wng4RHNCYjZobWJya3NMUXBvT0d1dlZoak94SXRlSGVtQ3hMSkpnMFEtUk1RTXdmbkdaZXFEdVMzZmhDMmhqTmxNNjc2dGVRa3NVWlhMa2ZzQkJZU3BrTUhjM292LVNEcjBoU1VKbkN4OVNQcQ</guid></item><item><title>胶原蛋白补充剂是否有助于减少皮肤衰老的迹象？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cjr5zj12ye1o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Collagen: Do you drink it? Inject it? Rub it on your skin? And does it work?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Ruth Clegg&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Health and wellbeing reporter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f92d/live/0c8a5d50-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Woman applying cream to her face" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;When it comes to collagen - how do you take yours?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;There are parties where people even drink shots of the anti-ageing supplement, often followed by a hefty tequila - though the latter is probably not recommended in the quest for youthful, peachy skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Collagen is the most abundant protein in the body, and forms the scaffolding that helps maintain the structural integrity of our skin and musculoskeletal system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In short, collagen helps to keep our skin plump, our joints and bones strong, and our hair and nails healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It's become so treasured that some dermatologists recommend "banking" it - investing in our collagen supply early so we have surplus when the inevitable happens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Yes. The inevitable. Ageing. Sigh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Our collagen supply naturally starts to decrease, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.uclahealth.org/news/article/should-you-take-collagen-supplements#:~:text=The%20body's%20collagen%20production%20slows%2Cup%20the%20level%20of%20decline." class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;on average around 1% a year, as we reach our mid to late 20s&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The speed of its decline depends on factors like our exposure to the sun, diet, and stress levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But is there credible science to say supplements can replenish our dwindling supply? And if so, what's the best way of getting it into our bodies?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7625/live/25ef5bf0-9ae4-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Kimberlie Smith Kimberlie Smith with long brown hair looking straight into camera" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Kimberlie Smith&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;As a sleep deprived mother, Kimberlie says collagen makes a difference to her skin&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Kimberlie Smith started taking collagen about six months ago. The 33-year-old began using it after a "traumatic year" in 2024. Her son was born prematurely, and as a result of stress, the mother-of-three says her skin took a "huge hit".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She uses marine collagen, the type derived from fish, in a tropical-flavoured gel she drinks every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My skin definitely seems to be brighter and clearer, plus my hair has never looked better since I started taking it," Kimberlie says. "As a sleep deprived mother, it's definitely made a difference."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Emma Wedgeworth, a consultant dermatologist based on London's Harley Street, says while there is some &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.jafc.6b05679" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;research to suggest taking collagen orally has an impact&lt;/a&gt;, she remains sceptical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She says the idea that collagen can make its journey through our body - not the easiest of quests - and land exactly where we need it to be is probably wishful thinking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For a start, it has to get through the gut without being completely broken down. Collagen is a large molecule so companies have now started to break it up into smaller pieces - collagen peptides - otherwise known as hydrolysed collagen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Even though this collagen - now in its smaller form - has a better chance of making its way through the intestinal wall and into the bloodstream, it still has a long way to go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It has to reach the skin to have an impact, and it could just as easily slip off to support other organs in the body. It's a valuable resource.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There is little reliable evidence on this, but there is a theory that because our skin is the organ with the 'fastest turnover' of cells, it might be more likely to use these collagen peptides above other organs."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And that's when you might get an increase in collagen being made in the skin cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'You can't risk stopping'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That all seems very complicated - and uncertain. It may leave you asking: what about using collagen creams? They're going directly onto the skin, so won't they stand more chance of getting where they need to be?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"No," is Ms Wedgworth's simple answer. "The collagen will just sit on the outer layer of your skin, it won't reach the dermis - which is the middle layer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;There are three different types of collagen supplements: marine (from fish), bovine (from cows), and vegan. Of the three, the dermatologist recommends marine if you are taking collagen orally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;This is because it contains more type 1 collagen - the most common of the five types and the one that gives structure to our skin cells, as well as playing a crucial role in the health of our bones, tendons and connective tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Vegan collagen is the least effective, says Ms Wedgeworth. Collagen is an animal-derived protein, so these products are not actually made of collagen, and instead contain a range of amino acids and vitamins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/835f/live/0e8c2f80-9ae2-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Matthew Montgomery Ali Watson at the gym, smiling at the camera and rubbing chalk on her hands 
" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Matthew Montgomery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Ali Watson, a keen weightlifter, originally started to use collagen supplements to help protect her joints&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I'm trapped," Ali Watson tells me as she points to packs of bovine collagen powder in her kitchen. "Yes, this one is for me and well, this one is for Tommy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;I look at the slender brown hound next me, grey whiskers poking out round his nose. He lifts an eyebrow in acknowledgement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ali, a neuroanaesthetist who, by her own admission, "knows a lot about dosing", feels like now she's started taking collagen, she can't stop - and nor can she stop giving it to her dog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I started taking it as a powder a couple of years ago. At first, it wasn't about my appearance, it was about my joints, I wanted to protect them because I do a lot of weight-lifting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ali's not sure that she's noticed any difference with her joints, but she has noticed a change elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My skin feels like it glows more, my hair feels thicker and my nails feel stronger."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;I glance down at Tommy, who seems more interested in his dog bowl than any powdered supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I know, it seems mad," Ali says, "but Tommy seemed a bit slower, a bit less enthusiastic just before summer, so I thought I would try him on dog collagen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I wanted to see if it could help with his joints - he's getting old now. And he is a bit brighter, but that might just be because the weather's got colder again and he's less hot and lethargic."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ali's not completely convinced the supplement is making a difference, and it's costing her £60 a month to ensure she and Tommy get their daily dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Tommy started on collagen a few months ago to help his joints&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But she says she now can't stop dosing them both up. "That's the thing with these supplements," the 46-year-old says, "life does have its ups and downs. You might take them when you're on a down, then things pick up again - and it might have very little to do with the supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"But by that stage, you can't risk stopping."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Professor Faisal Ali, a consultant dermatologist at Mid Cheshire NHS Trust, says one of the issues consumers and clinicians face is the amount of conflicting information and conflicting interests in supplement research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A recent, relatively small, study compared &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002934325002839" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;research funded by the wellness industry&lt;/a&gt; to studies that did not have the same conflict of interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;While industry-funded studies suggested collagen supplements significantly improved skin hydration, elasticity and wrinkles, those that did not receive funding from pharmaceutical companies revealed no effect on skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Prof Ali says industry-funded studies are not "inherently bad", it's just such a varied picture. But he says there is a lack of robust evidence to suggest oral and topical collagen have any substantial effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;So if I could turn back time and start drinking and banking collagen in my 20s, would I have smoother, more youthful skin now, I ask him? Probably not, he says. It doesn't stay in the body for that long - we haven't got a collagen store cupboard that we can just dip into.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3bb2/live/5661bb50-9ae1-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Micro derma facial roller" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Microneedling makes small wounds in the skin which may trigger collagen production&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;However, Prof Ali believes we can potentially boost collagen output and maintain elasticity in our skin by using special techniques&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11499218/#fn-group1" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt; such as laser collagen stimulation and microneedling&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;This means using a number of tiny, specialist needles or a laser to make small wounds to our skin, which then encourage a repair process, triggering new collagen formation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But that's not cheap. You could be paying up to £300 for one session. Is there a less costly alternative?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The best thing you can do for your skin," Prof Ali says, "is using decent sunblock. We know the sun has a huge impact on ageing our skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Sun cream, healthy diet, and if you smoke, stop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"These will have a far greater impact than collagen supplements."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 22:37:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5YYXJORjRDaWc5bXpCYnhia0s5YjVJTUNEMGxtUklhSy11ZnpTcHpsbW40UDZPOHZmYzdFMnd0Qkc3Y2hkaTJGUldGcDJIaWNXS0pmbXY2UUQzZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE9VUnkwTWhPQ0lSNDNRQTYySnIzc2VtSVpjLXdwcXNpUGJBM3g3SU0xdWp3bDJ0dl9DSENNTWk5NDU5UjBtbnlVTnZHbzY4ZUZlWDA5NTlMMXdFSUhfNVNZ</guid></item><item><title>首席拉比敦促在耶路撒冷麻疹死亡后接种疫苗-以色列国家新闻</title><link>https://www.israelnationalnews.com/news/415474</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content-inside article-content" id="articleContent" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;&lt;p id="intext-1" class="sideInf" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s data-v-4bdf62d7&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;Israel’s Chief Rabbis on Thursday issued an urgent call to the public to vaccinate their children against measles virus, following the spread of the disease and the recent deaths that it has caused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;In their official letter, the Chief Rabbis emphasized that “Torah commands us to do everything possible to protect ourselves and our health,” citing the verse, “You shall greatly safeguard your lives,” as a halakhic (pertaining to Jewish law) obligation to vaccinate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;“The responsibility for caring for our body and soul rests upon the individual,” the rabbis wrote. “This applies both to treatment when necessary and during illness, and to preventive care.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="" album="true" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="intext-2" class="sideInf" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s data-v-4bdf62d7&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="" album="true" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;The appeal comes amid the spread of measles cases in haredi communities in and around Jerusalem. Since last weekend, four children, all aged between one and two years of age, &lt;a href="https://www.israelnationalnews.com/news/415473" target="_blank" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;have died of measles.&lt;/a&gt; Only one of those children, a little girl, was vaccinated at all; she had been too young for the measles vaccine when she was infected with the virus. The other three infants were completely unvaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;The rabbis' letter represents a clear halakhic statement from the Chief Rabbinate, emphasizing that vaccination is not only a right but a religious duty. The message is particularly aimed at communities where there is resistance to vaccines for religious or other reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;Meanwhile, the Health Ministry has warned that measles continues to spread, encouraging the public to vaccinate, especially children and communities with low vaccination rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="z396inn" class="" data-v-2a4c3726 data-v-e580db1b-s&gt;



&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Israel National News</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 21:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9uVGFtQlloTGptc1hXNDlBM2ZSaWd1R3hESkk4QksyZFdiSTFLenI5VE1VVVJKM0Y5VUlkTC11Zll1TnB1VWJ1T3Fjc1RISi13Z3QwZTVrTldYZw</guid></item><item><title>哈佛大学为60岁以上的人推荐这项令人惊讶的活动，而不是步行或跑步- valleyvanguardonline.com</title><link>https://www.valleyvanguardonline.com/harvard-recommends-this-surprising-activity-over-walking-or-running-for-people-60/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>valleyvanguardonline.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:27:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxOeWVreW9GQU1aLTdLME5PeVVFNjMwbm82NDVONEtfWFNHRkJfYlJuYU9yUXRyVmtWOFVXemlvM3ZzSmtjY28xTlJMcVFfb205djEwRHZkbjNnclVBTnNJTlAyZ0wyWGNYWUNTWE1ITXJERFg4NDFqUGcxU0x2TFVZdnByT1dweTFXUXRmTGJVeEZVXzJtTG94Y3RvSy1EMWVvU1V5Q3ZzU21Ea3ViMXI5ZjNveWZNVGMwRlFN</guid></item><item><title>女儿发现自己患有严重的遗传性疾病，但当她得知父母隐瞒多年时，她称他们自私，低度接触- TwistedSifter</title><link>https://twistedsifter.com/2025/09/daughter-found-out-she-has-a-serious-hereditary-illness-but-when-she-learned-her-parents-hid-it-for-years-she-called-them-selfish-and-went-low-contact/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article"&gt;
						
						&lt;div id="attachment_609635" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-609635" class="wp-image-609635" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Woman laying in bed crying because she was diagnosed with rare illness" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg 1200w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=150,79 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=300,158 300w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=768,403 768w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=1024,538 1024w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=586,308 586w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-609635" class="wp-image-609635" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg" alt="Woman laying in bed crying because she was diagnosed with rare illness" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg 1200w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=150,79 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=300,158 300w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=768,403 768w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=1024,538 1024w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-Thumb.jpg?resize=586,308 586w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;p id="caption-attachment-609635" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Pexels/Redidt&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finding out you’ve inherited a life-changing illness is devastating enough, but realizing the people who should have warned you chose to stay silent cuts even deeper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mm-player"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, what would you do if your parents knowingly hid a hereditary disease that not only put your own life at risk but also your child’s?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Would you let them keep their secret to avoid tearing the family apart? Or would you inform the other members of your family?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AITAH/comments/1g5o3dh/aita_for_calling_my_parents_selfish_for_having_me/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;following story&lt;/a&gt;, one daughter faces this exact decision and feels everyone has the right to know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s what happened.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;AITA for calling my parents selfish for having me, knowing they’d pass down a hereditary illness, and going LC after they hid it, putting my child at risk too?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I (28F) recently found out I have a serious hereditary illness that’s going to mess up my life, and I am so mad I can barely type this out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s a degenerative illness, no cure, nothing. My body’s just gonna slowly get worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the kicker? My parents have known this could happen my whole life and never said a word.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;This illness runs in my family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A lot of her family members have the same illness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;My dad’s mom had it. His sister—my aunt—died from it a few years ago.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was living overseas when she passed, and my parents told me it was cancer. Cancer. They lied right to my face.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t until I got diagnosed that they finally came clean and admitted she had the same illness I do.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I confronted them, my dad wouldn’t even give me a straight answer. I asked if he had it too, and he dodged every single question, acting like I was overreacting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s where things took a turn for the worse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;My mom, on the other hand, tried to justify it by saying they didn’t want me “living in fear.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you kidding me? I could have been prepared! Instead, they chose to let me walk into this blind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And here’s where it gets worse—I have a 2-year-old son. My child might have this, and they never told me I was at risk. I could’ve had him tested, made informed decisions, anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But no, they took that from me, and now I live in constant fear for him, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then my mom had the nerve to ask me if I would rather not have been born than deal with this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can you believe that? She turned it around on me, like I’m the monster for even thinking it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s how she responded.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;And you know what?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes, I said it. Yes, I would rather not have been born than deal with this disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They made a selfish choice, and now I’m paying for it. They knew the risks and did it anyway, for themselves. They wanted kids, and now I’m stuck with this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I called them selfish, and I meant every word.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, they want her to stay quiet, but she can’t do that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, they’re begging me not to tell my younger siblings. They don’t know about this yet, haven’t been tested, and my parents want to keep it that way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They’re hoping they’ll get lucky, but I’m not going to lie to them. I refuse to let them be blindsided like I was. They deserve to know the truth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve gone low-contact with my parents. I can’t stand to even think about them right now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The guilt trips won’t stop.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;My mom keeps trying to guilt-trip me, saying they were “just trying to protect me.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protect me from what? The truth? No, they weren’t protecting me. They were protecting themselves from the guilt of knowing they passed this on, and now they want me to protect them, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I won’t. I love my son and my siblings too much to lie to them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AITA?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wow! It’s easy to see both sides of this, but the parents should’ve seen it coming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s see what the fine folks over at Reddit have to say about this situation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This person’s family also deals with a hereditary disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609634" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Hereditary Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary.jpg" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary.jpg 520w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary.jpg?resize=150,63 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary.jpg?resize=300,126 300w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609634" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary.jpg" alt="Hereditary Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary.jpg 520w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary.jpg?resize=150,63 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary.jpg?resize=300,126 300w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this person, the parents took away all of her choices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609633" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Hereditary 1 Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-1.jpg" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-1.jpg 572w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-1.jpg?resize=150,58 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-1.jpg?resize=300,117 300w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609633" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-1.jpg" alt="Hereditary 1 Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-1.jpg 572w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-1.jpg?resize=150,58 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-1.jpg?resize=300,117 300w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This reader thinks it’s probably Huntington’s Disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609632" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Hereditary 2 Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-2.jpg" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-2.jpg 562w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-2.jpg?resize=150,79 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-2.jpg?resize=300,159 300w" data-lazy-sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609632" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-2.jpg" alt="Hereditary 2 Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-2.jpg 562w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-2.jpg?resize=150,79 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-2.jpg?resize=300,159 300w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s someone who tells her to do it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609631" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Hereditary 3 Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-3.jpg" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-3.jpg 506w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-3.jpg?resize=150,65 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-3.jpg?resize=300,129 300w" data-lazy-sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609631" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-3.jpg" alt="Hereditary 3 Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-3.jpg 506w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-3.jpg?resize=150,65 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-3.jpg?resize=300,129 300w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this reader, what the parents did is abuse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609630" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/plugins/lazy-load-0.7/images/1x1.trans.gif" alt="Hereditary 4 Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" data-lazy-src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-4.jpg" data-lazy-srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-4.jpg 533w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-4.jpg?resize=150,63 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-4.jpg?resize=300,126 300w" data-lazy-sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignnone wp-image-609630" src="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-4.jpg" alt="Hereditary 4 Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact" srcset="https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-4.jpg 533w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-4.jpg?resize=150,63 150w, https://twistedsifter.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/09/Hereditary-4.jpg?resize=300,126 300w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" title="Daughter Found Out She Has A Serious Hereditary Illness, But When She Learned Her Parents Hid It For Years, She Called Them Selfish And Went Low Contact"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She should tell them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you enjoyed this story, check out this post about a &lt;a href="https://twistedsifter.com/2023/12/daughter-invited-herself-on-parents-40th-anniversary-vacation-so-they-can-babysit-the-kids-so-dad-tricks-her-and-travels-to-another-place-entirely/?utm_source=IN-ARTICLE&amp;amp;utm_medium=IN-ARTICLE&amp;amp;utm_campaign=IN-ARTICLE" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;daughter who invited herself to her parents’ 40th anniversary vacation for all the wrong reasons&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

						
						 	
						

						
												
						
						
						
					&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TwistedSifter</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:25:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwJBVV95cUxNaFhuQnhVRFhIa1hoS2N4bkxPbXFJcUhOUlFYSks0Z2NGS0RhcG4tN3NTZDRvc3VLQjFlM1NsaFFWWUY5LUJEZS1EQ1FrbmpkbTdCeFNObzVPRWlvZmRMUEVyVWtYbW0yczdOZ0gxVlh3RWVGMldmUmhySzJ4ZGFOUHpLYXQ2RUlEbWE0N00wdzA1bU1zLWpDaE41SW53QVljUXdUY0xWd2laeUM0aktjZ3FRS0tMUjB2SnZYTnc4RjZ6RWdkVmlYVGFGaWp3Y3lSbEdOd2VyNUJ0Qkc4a01hODYwOEcxX1hWaTlTSUNVbWxoY0xPMm9FWmU5cUdVcW9pYUFHX0p5OXRSVW8tbkpCT0h3TQ</guid></item><item><title>嗅、嗅、滴。如何在纽约市接种流感、新冠疫苗。-高谭市民</title><link>https://gothamist.com/news/sniff-sniff-drip-how-to-get-flu-covid-vaccines-in-nyc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="streamfield-paragraph rte-text"&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="jvfnn"&gt;It's finally fall, and with that also comes respiratory viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="9v7nc"&gt;Dr. Michelle Morse, acting health commissioner and chief medical officer of the New York City Department of Health and Mental Hygiene, recently discussed the flu and COVID-19 vaccines with All Things Considered host Sean Carlson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="aemh2"&gt;Her guidance in a nutshell: “It’s time to get your COVID flu and RSV vaccine if you're eligible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="70kr4"&gt;Here is a lightly edited transcript of their conversation:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 data-block-key="c5o6o"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sean Carlson: Who should get the COVID and flu vaccines right now?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="55jo9"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dr. Michelle Morse:&lt;/b&gt; It is a source of confusion and I am here to try to make it plain for New Yorkers and your listeners. First and foremost, for anyone who's 6 months old and above, there are zero safety concerns about the COVID vaccine. We are recommending that everyone 6 months and above get an updated COVID shot this fall to protect them as much as possible for the upcoming respiratory viral season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="47rba"&gt;There are a few groups that we are really strongly encouraging to get vaccinated: People who are above the age of 65 and anyone who is pregnant or considering being pregnant. And we're also encouraging our babies, the age group of 6 months to 24 months. Those groups in particular will benefit tremendously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 data-block-key="1ik7l"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Centers for Disease Control’s Vaccine Advisory Board is recommending that people consult with their doctor before getting a coronavirus shot. That is a shift from previous federal policy that made vaccines widely available to almost all Americans older than 6 months for free and without question. What does it mean to consult with a clinician?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="1tge1"&gt;Unless you have a special or unique medical situation that requires you to have further consultation with your physician, there is no need for consultation. For the COVID vaccine, specifically, I want to underline again that there has been no new data presented about any safety concerns about the COVID vaccine. Again, my recommendation and the city's recommendation, in partnership with New York State health commissioner, is that those 6 months and over should go ahead and get that vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="5c4d4"&gt;I do worry that the very confusing messaging that is coming from our vaccination advisory council at the CDC, as well as the current U.S. health secretary, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., are going to make people confused and concerned. We are in a position to say very, very clearly that it is recommended that New Yorkers 6 months old and above get the updated COVID vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 data-block-key="cheq4"&gt;&lt;b&gt;How can New Yorkers get the vaccine at a pharmacy? Do they need to get a prescription for it?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="3p0i6"&gt;Luckily, because of action by Gov. Kathy Hochul and the executive order that she signed a couple of weeks ago, New Yorkers do not need a prescription. In fact, the New York City Health Department just relaunched our New York City health map — &lt;a href="https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/index.page" rel="noopener" target="_blank"&gt;nyc.gov/health&lt;/a&gt; — with updated information about where you can get the COVID vaccine. It lists not only geographically lists any specific community you're in, it also lists by insurance. We also list a number of places where you can go if you do not have insurance or you can't afford to pay for a vaccine, a COVID vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 data-block-key="5rh49"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Now, this summer it seemed like a lot of people were getting sick with COVID, and according to the City Health Department COVID data, there was a steady increase of known COVID cases in August. So, if someone recently had COVID, do they still need to get a vaccine?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="96eev"&gt;In recent weeks we did see a slight uptick in both emergency room visits and hospitalizations for COVID, and we still see that uptick actually for people who are very young and for people over the age of 65. So, COVID is definitely out there and circulating. The evidence suggests that if you just had COVID, it is generally recommended that you wait around three months, at least, after your episode of COVID to get the vaccine. But really you are eligible to get the vaccine really anytime after you're no longer feeling ill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="dcri7"&gt;And if you have more questions about that, you can certainly also talk to your primary care doctor about what the ideal timing is for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 data-block-key="7brpi"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What about insurance? Does that cover the vaccine?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="6u6i9"&gt;We are also very excited to be able to say that all of the insurers across New York City and New York State have agreed to make sure that the COVID vaccine is covered by health insurance. That is incredibly important because no one should have to pay for vaccines. Vaccines are safe and effective. They benefit you and your community and your family. And in many cases they are lifesaving, as we learned very clearly during the height of the emergency phase of the COVID pandemic. Unfortunately last flu season was also one of our worst flu seasons in recent history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="dgfo3"&gt;RSV is also circulating. So we want there to be as few barriers as possible to people getting their respiratory viral vaccines. We do have those guarantees from insurers that those vaccines will be covered. It is right about the perfect time for everyone listening to go ahead and get out there and get your COVID flu and RSV vaccine if you're eligible for RSV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 data-block-key="6h0s7"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What if somebody doesn't have insurance? What recourse do they have?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="dt98g"&gt;At the City Health Department, part of what we do is, we ensure that no matter if you can pay, no matter where you live, no matter your documentation status, no matter any of those things, we want to make sure that you have access to lifesaving vaccines and healthcare. The NYC Health map lists several places here you can get these vaccines for respiratory viral season, even if you do not health insurance and are unable to pay out of pocket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 data-block-key="arj7s"&gt;&lt;b&gt;We've talked about the guidance from the federal government and how some people might be confused about new recommendations as it relates to vaccines. As a local city health official, how do you take what's being said from the federal government and then shape vaccine policy here in New York City?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="b6aii"&gt;This is one of our greatest challenges right now. Under normal circumstances, the federal government and the CDC are our partners in really making sure that accurate information is out there in the public. That is not the case right now, and that is incredibly challenging for us. So part of what we do and, and what we will continue to do, no matter what happens at the federal level, is push out information through our social media channels, through talking on the radio with folks like you, Sean, through videos and, and all kinds of different communication approaches to make sure that the message is clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="234oc"&gt;Again, respiratory viral season is here. It’s time to get your COVID flu and RSV vaccine if you're eligible. They are safe and effective. That has not changed. And we will do our very best to make sure that those vaccines are free and accessible for everyone who's ready to get them, especially for the groups that are at highest risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4 data-block-key="eofnh"&gt;&lt;b&gt;That's New York City Health Commissioner, Dr. Michelle Morse. Commissioner, as always, thanks for joining us.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="dtqe5"&gt;Thanks for having me, Sean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gothamist</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:22:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxPY3JtMThCM0JNY2M1TVZWS3V0aVdYLTZrZFMwRnJIZ3Q1c2JvbUhpcmtodE1nT1BQOEVQNFpGejNQWlRwWlRHWHVYRDZfUG1qZGZXT1BleXl3RUFBSzFWc0s2aXFuMU9kNzloeTNSYXNsUldyM0h1NUpIVGt0b2FkcHJMNi1ZSFk</guid></item><item><title>在奥斯威戈县废水中检测到麻疹，州警告- Syracuse.com</title><link>https://www.syracuse.com/news/2025/09/measles-detected-in-oswego-county-wastewater-state-warns.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AOTFJF5VF5BMRGUMEXWVKHM26E"&gt;Oswego, N.Y. - Low levels of the measles virus were detected in a wastewater sample collected earlier this week from an Oswego County treatment facility, according to the state Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BNK7A34GXJD3RBUGVYAVSO2SZI"&gt;The treatment facility serves parts of the City of Oswego and surrounding areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HCEWM5UFRBHCTGQLCHVW5R43TM"&gt;The results may indicate that at least one person with the virus was in the county, according to a news release issued Saturday by the health department. No measles cases have been reported in the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AZI54TNCJNBILJC35NL6TRPC4U"&gt;“This detection does not mean there is an outbreak,” state Health Commissioner Dr. James McDonald said. “It is, however, a timely reminder to make sure you and your family are up to date on the MMR vaccine and to keep an eye out for symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="F2F6VVR6EZGWJIOQFD4J2S6FWU"&gt;In Oswego County, 87.8 percent of children under two years old are immunized for measles, mumps and rubella (MMR), leaving some children and adults susceptible to infection, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TVUTYOEMRVG77D2T7ZRUHDMOMY"&gt;In Central New York, the immunization rate is 87.1%, according to state health department data. In Onondaga County, the rate is 89.2%&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OM5EL7VCDVF4JCM7Q6YE3TAD7Y"&gt;Statewide, the immunizations rate is 81.2%. The lowest rates reported are Yates County at 55.8% and the highest is Niagara County at 89.3%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="223HCRLC4NHUFBFXL4GKWCWAAI"&gt;Measles is one of the most contagious diseases known, and even small groups of under-immunized people can allow the virus to spread, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EDIBSWFYSRGULFRZLEVIMR72A4"&gt;About 1 in 10 people with measles require hospitalization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VWSHQCI3OBDKFPHPQBAJKPGK4U"&gt;People can protect themselves from obtaining and spreading the virus by checking their vaccination status and knowing the symptoms, officials said. Measles typically begins with a fever, cough, runny nose and red, watery eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7V23GAAGU5DONF37CXX3YK7V4Q"&gt;A rash typically appears several days later, starting on the face and spreading across the body, and it may come with a fever that can spike above 104 degrees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="S7K2SM2WBBGWZCYECOLXONH56M"&gt;Measles spread through the air when an infected person coughs or sneezes, and the virus can linger in the air for up to two hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WNBH4JMH5RBS5GEZFCCSS7632E"&gt;Measles can be transmitted four days before the rash appears and until four days afterward, according to the release. The incubation period is typically between seven and 14 days, but symptoms can appear up to 21 days after exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LLEVBKHGKRDOTPZPGR5VKXTUN4"&gt;Most people born before 1957 are considered immune to measles because they were likely exposed to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="C3CKLJ3BCFEYNCZM4B4PJX6XAY"&gt;Anyone who is unsure of their vaccination status should contact their health care provider or local health department, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XSXRC4CQE5F75EVFODNV5FBMAQ"&gt;The health department urges people to be fully vaccinated against measles, particularly before international travel or travel to areas of the U.S. experiencing outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RUMDYXCL6NER5MU3VIAEUU23LI"&gt;The detection was from one of two locations tested by the national commercial company, WastewaterSCAN, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HY656257UNE2PJ57DN7ZBPSHWQ"&gt;The state’s Wadsworth Center has routinely tested for measles in wastewater samples from locations around the state since October 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EMSJ5W5FOBDNZDDKKWGQICZBYA"&gt;The detected sample was above the national program’s reporting threshold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4MNAJ44SB5GQPI2PKKBZU74ILA"&gt;Further testing will be performed by both the WastewaterSCAN and the Wadsworth Center next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FYQWI6LU3VEVLP7RJGRHYETWXU" data-fusion-component="FYQWI6LU3VEVLP7RJGRHYETWXU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rawhtml"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FYQWI6LU3VEVLP7RJGRHYETWXU" data-fusion-component="FYQWI6LU3VEVLP7RJGRHYETWXU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Syracuse.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 20:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxQUHkxUW03alFscFNZX0RFODNmMTcwNWR0Q3JnWFlQNTA2TjdJd1ZKemlVT2tyczNSajNCRVlhVUFGa0pkaWpZMFdQMEE4QWJIRHRuczQ5Z2JpQUZ2c2kxWDNCVnJEYUdvUlJGc1dQZDNaRDd0OXE5SHdRUUtaYlU3cHpzZ0EyM0RiM2otZXg3cE5Wb1VuVmpYa2dCLWdqRy1w0gG0AUFVX3lxTE15Z2dPVkM4emZkN0ZfZWJaaDFDY1dBNmRPMWRKYVRFY1l0NnptOEJMdXpyV2czeE5wbnd3aDBHelZYcHlBcFI4cUV3d2oxTEo3OExXaUVqTGNYLVFwSVEtVnNkZ3VvY1ZJSUI5N2M3eFJacW9URjkzamtnbkw4RzdSS056cUYwOEhKeF8wTm9CSkd0SkRKZmJBTjNwejVCbGdGRjhvX0syTVRuOUZ2UHBKbFU3cQ</guid></item><item><title>噩梦细菌，超级细菌在加利福尼亚州崛起-补丁</title><link>https://patch.com/california/across-ca/nightmare-bacteria-superbugs-rise-california</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="styles_Section__card__4Uoov"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infection rates from drug-resistant “nightmare bacteria” have spiked across the United States and in California at the same time a fungal superbug is spreading in the Golden State, according to a new &lt;a href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/ANNALS-25-02404" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt; from Centers for Disease Control and Prevention scientists and state health officials. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Case of “nightmare bacteria” rose almost 70% in five years the United States, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported. In California, state health officials have already reported hundreds of cases between January and July, according to preliminary data provide to Patch by the California Department of Public Health. Just a few years prior, the bacteria was considered rare in the state.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Double Whammy&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;The alarming rise in anti-biotic resistant bacteria is happening at the same time the state is battling the spread of another drug-resistent superbug. C. auris is a deadly species of fungus that does not respond to common antifungal treatments, according to the California Department of Public Health. The deadly fungus has been rampant in the Southern part of the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="ContentBlocks_CardDetail__SubscribeBlock__4zBcQ ContentBlocks_CardDetail__SubscribeBlock--mobile__18tT_"&gt;&lt;section class="styles_SubscribeForm__0dj5n"&gt;&lt;h2 class="styles_SubscribeForm__title__F_olP"&gt;Find out what's happening in Across California&lt;span class="styles_SubscribeForm__title--nextLine__FTO3K"&gt;for free with the latest updates from Patch.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;California saw 11,711 cases of harmful superbug fungus from September 2022 to May 2025, according to the California Department of Public Health. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Several California counties have reported thousands of cases of candida auris, a species of fungus that does not respond to common antifungal treatments and can be deadly, according to the California Department of Public Health. From January 2017 to May 2025, Los Angeles County saw 5,745 cases of Candida auris, Orange County saw 3,575, and San Bernardino County saw 1,254 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="ContentBlocks_CardDetail__SubscribeBlock__4zBcQ ContentBlocks_CardDetail__SubscribeBlock--desktop__oN6vv"&gt;&lt;section class="styles_SubscribeForm__0dj5n"&gt;&lt;h2 class="styles_SubscribeForm__title__F_olP"&gt;Find out what's happening in Across California&lt;span class="styles_SubscribeForm__title--nextLine__FTO3K"&gt;for free with the latest updates from Patch.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img data-image="24074589-1758734703" alt title data-src="https://patch.com/img/cdn20/users/24074589/20250924/012502/styles/raw/public/processed_images/Screen%20Shot%202025-09-24%20at%2010.24.46%20AM.png" data-sizes="(min-width: 780px) 726px, 100vw" data-srcset="https://patch.com/img/cdn20/users/24074589/20250924/012502/styles/raw/public/processed_images/Screen%20Shot%202025-09-24%20at%2010.24.46%20AM.png?width=640 640w, https://patch.com/img/cdn20/users/24074589/20250924/012502/styles/raw/public/processed_images/Screen%20Shot%202025-09-24%20at%2010.24.46%20AM.png?width=726 726w"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Source: California Department of Public Health&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; &lt;h3&gt;'Nightmare Bacteria'&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;While C. auris represents a fungal threat, a new CDC report published Monday in the Annals of Internal Medicine draws attention to a different kind of superbug: carbapenem-resistant Enterobacteriaceae, or CRE, is a family of bacteria that are resistant to many common antibiotics.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Nationwide, they increased 70% between 2019 and 2023, according to a new report from Centers for Disease Control and Prevention scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In California, there were 632 cases of CPOs with an NDM gene reported to CDPH in 2024, and 317 cases reported in 2025 from January through July, the most available data. The year before, the state record 632 cases.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The bacteria can also cause infections in patients with existing serious medical problems, or who are undergoing operations or other invasive procedures, according to UCLA hospital officials. In 2015, more than 100 patients at UCLA Medical Center were exposed to the superbug, which may have been responsible for two deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bacteria that are difficult to treat due to the so-called NDM gene primarily drove the increase, CDC researchers said. Only two antibiotics work against those infections, and the drugs are expensive and must be administered through an IV, researchers said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bacteria with the gene were once considered exotic, linked to a small number of patients who received medical care overseas. Though the numbers are still small, the rate of U.S. cases jumped more than fivefold in recent years, the researchers reported.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The rise of NDMs in the U.S. is a grave danger and very worrisome,” said David Weiss, an Emory University infectious diseases researcher, in an email.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It's likely many people are unrecognized carriers of the drug-resistant bacteria, which could lead to community spread, the CDC scientists said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That may play out in doctors’ offices across the country, as infections long considered routine — like urinary tract infections — could become harder to treat, said Dr. Maroya Walters, one of the report’s authors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antimicrobial resistance occurs when germs such as bacteria and fungi gain the power to fight off the drugs designed to kill them. The misuse of antibiotics was a big reason for the rise — unfinished or unnecessary prescriptions that didn’t kill the germs made them stronger.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In recent years, the CDC has drawn attention to “ nightmare bacteria ” resistant to a wide range of antibiotics. That includes carbapenems, a class of antibiotics considered a last resort for treatment of serious infections.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They counted 4,341 cases of carbapenem-resistant bacterial infections from those states in 2023, with 1,831 of them the NDM variety. The researchers did not say how many of the infected people died.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The rate of carbapenem-resistant infections rose from just under 2 per 100,000 people in 2019 to more than 3 per 100,000 in 2023 — an increase of 69%. But the rate of NDM cases rose from around 0.25 to about 1.35 — an increase of 460%, the authors said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A researcher not involved in the study said the increase is probably related to the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We know that there was a huge surge in antibiotic use during the pandemic, so this likely is reflected in increasing drug resistance,” said Dr. Jason Burnham, a Washington University researcher, in an email.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The CDC’s count is only a partial picture.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Many states are not fully testing and reporting cases. Even in states that do, cases tend to be among hospital patients sick enough to warrant special testing. Many hospitals also aren’t able to do the testing needed to detect certain forms of genetic resistance.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The CDC researchers did not have data from some of the most populous states, including California, Florida, New York and Texas, which means the absolute number of U.S. infections “is definitely underestimated,” Burnham said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is not the first study to report a rise. A CDC report published in June noted an increase in NDM cases in New York City between 2019 and 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;— &lt;em&gt;The Asssociated Press contributed to this report. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k SubscribeCTABlurb_SubscribeCTABlurb__M_Azu"&gt;Get more local news delivered straight to your inbox. &lt;a target="_blank" href="/subscribe" class=""&gt;Sign up for free Patch newsletters and alerts.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="MuiBox-root css-0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Patch</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 19:20:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxObnR5LUI3Tm9mOFRqSzJTVmVSeHJMdmZ0WEp2d0tLcFI4cmZxVThzVGRiN1hFc3RnTTMxNW5rSVhPM1hVaXJGWXk3SlN0Q2FTUmktWHMxN3RhQzF1RzVnQ3BqQUZpN0ZNSjZCaTFXUXoyaEpXLURhbEtuTThMZW9Tek44YWZtdTZReklR0gGqAUFVX3lxTFBrTEJLVlMxT3Q4VmIteEt5bnV6b2tDbmtRdFctUHJrdTNHNWlTTUhTdHRLVTFVMnJXTnNCZHZnZGpveGc5d2xOcDdyLVNxWWp4Y2UxMmdvTGZEYkY0ZkVZdkI5OFF5cTNaV3FMWTc5b3J5ZU5YdEhza3JWQk55bXhvbVdFajJzWFdTRWdEQjdYNmx3N1NabGtfb2M5dXdmbENLSTZWaWRyN3dR</guid></item><item><title>睡眠障碍预测未来几年的帕金森氏症或痴呆症-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/sleep-disorders-parkinsons-dementia-29744/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Two landmark international studies show that brain biomarkers can predict whether people with REM sleep behaviour disorder (iRBD) will develop Parkinson’s disease or dementia with Lewy bodies (DLB). MRI scans revealed that reduced glymphatic system function signals higher risk for Parkinson’s, while increased free water in the basal nucleus of Meynert predicts progression to DLB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings come from the largest imaging studies ever conducted in patients with confirmed iRBD. The results pave the way for earlier diagnosis, targeted monitoring, and preventive treatments before irreversible brain damage occurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Parkinson’s Predictor:&lt;/strong&gt; Reduced glymphatic fluid circulation doubled Parkinson’s risk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DLB Predictor:&lt;/strong&gt; Higher free water in the basal nucleus of Meynert raised DLB risk 8-fold.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clinical Impact:&lt;/strong&gt; First tools to differentiate disease outcomes years before symptoms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University of Montreal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An international research team led by Université de Montréal medical professor Shady Rahayel has made a major breakthrough in predicting neurodegenerative diseases.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to two complementary UdeM studies, scientists are now able to determine, years in advance, which individuals with a particular sleep disorder will develop Parkinson’s disease or dementia with Lewy bodies (DLB).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The studies focus on isolated REM sleep behaviour disorder (iRBD)—a condition in which people yell, thrash, or act out their dreams, sometimes violently enough to injure a bed partner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not just restless sleep—it’s a neurological warning sign,” said Rahayel, a neuropsychologist and researcher at the Centre for Advanced Research in Sleep Medicine at Sacré-Cœur Hospital in Montreal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roughly 90 per cent of people with this sleep disorder will go on to eventually develop Parkinson’s disease or DLB. Until now, however, it was impossible to know which disease would occur—or when.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First biomarker: predicting Parkinson’s&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first study, led by UdeM doctoral student in neurosciences Violette Ayral and published in &lt;em&gt;Neurology &lt;/em&gt;on September 16, involved 428 participants from five countries: Canada, the United States, France, the United Kingdom and Czechia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It examined the brain’s glymphatic system—a network that clears metabolic waste during sleep, including proteins linked to neurodegeneration. When this system is impaired, waste accumulates, potentially triggering diseases like Parkinson’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using an advanced MRI technique known as DTI-ALPS, researchers measured fluid circulation in specific brain regions in 250 patients with iRBD and 178 healthy control subjects, with an average follow-up of six years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key finding: patients with a lower DTI-ALPS index in the left hemisphere of the brain (indicating reduced fluid circulation) were 2.4 times more likely to develop Parkinson’s disease in the years that followed. No such link was found for dementia with Lewy bodies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This asymmetry mirrors what we see clinically in early Parkinson’s, where motor symptoms often start on one side of the body – it may mark the very earliest stage of the disease,” said Ayral.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the first evidence that glymphatic function, as measured by MRI, can predict progression to Parkinson’s—and the largest international study ever conducted on this topic among patients with polysomnography-confirmed REM sleep disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Second biomarker: predicting DLB&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second study, led by UdeM doctoral student in neuropsychology Celine Haddad and published in &lt;em&gt;Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia&lt;/em&gt; on September 19, focused on 438 participants from the same five countries as the first study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It took a different approach to predict the onset of DLB —a condition combining Parkinsonian symptoms (tremors, rigidity) and Alzheimer-like symptoms (cognitive impairment, confusion, hallucinations). It’s the second most common degenerative dementia after Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers measured the amount of “free water” — water not bound by brain cells and able to flow freely between them — in the basal nucleus of Meynert, a key region for thought and reasoning. This free water is a sign of early microscopic changes, such as inflammation or cell loss, and serves as an indirect marker of neuronal degeneration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a median follow-up of 8.4 years, the results were striking: individuals who developed DLB had significantly higher levels of free water in this brain region, making them eight times more likely to convert to this form of dementia. This method proved more sensitive than traditional approaches based on brain atrophy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What’s fascinating is that this marker picks up very early changes—even before symptoms emerge,” said Haddad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toward precision medicine&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These studies represent the largest international imaging research ever done on patients with polysomnography-confirmed iRBD, and pave the way for personalized screening tests to predict which disease will develop before symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clinicians will be able to tailor medical monitoring to each patient’s trajectory and better target clinical trials for preventive treatments, the researchers say, adding that their early intervention model could transform care for neurodegenerative diseases by addressing them before irreversible damage occurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We already knew that isolated REM sleep behaviour disorder is a warning sign for these diseases,” said Rahayel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we didn’t know was who would develop what. Thanks to these complementary studies, we now have tools to better predict and personalize care.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this sleep and Parkinson’s disease research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#412b6f222e33252420346c26203b20282d2d2401342c2e2f353324202d6f2220" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Julie Gazaille&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://umontreal.ca" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of Montreal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Julie Gazaille – University of Montreal&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://www.neurology.org/doi/10.1212/WNL.0000000000214042" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;DTI-ALPS associates with differential phenoconversion in patients with isolated REM sleep behaviour disorder: a multicenter MRI study&lt;/a&gt;” by Shady Rahayel et al. &lt;em&gt;Neurology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DTI-ALPS associates with differential phenoconversion in patients with isolated REM sleep behaviour disorder: a multicenter MRI study&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Background and Objectives&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Isolated REM sleep behavior disorder (iRBD) is the strongest prodromal marker of synucleinopathies, including Parkinson disease (PD) and dementia with Lewy bodies (DLB). Identifying brain biomarkers that predict progression and distinguish phenoconversion trajectories remains a challenge. The glymphatic system is involved in interstitial waste clearance, and its dysfunction has been associated with pathologic protein accumulation and neurodegeneration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diffusion tensor imaging along the perivascular space (DTI-ALPS) has been proposed as a noninvasive proxy for glymphatic function. The aim of this study was to determine whether patients with iRBD show a reduced DTI-ALPS index compared with controls and whether a lower DTI-ALPS index predicts future phenoconversion to PD or DLB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Methods&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We conducted a longitudinal, multicenter cohort study using brain MRI scans from patients with polysomnography-confirmed iRBD and healthy controls recruited across 5 international centers. All participants underwent T1-weighted and diffusion-weighted MRI. DTI-ALPS indices were computed from diffusivity along projection and associative fibers adjacent to the lateral ventricles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The primary outcome was time to phenoconversion to synucleinopathy. Linear models assessed baseline group differences and clinical correlates, and Cox proportional hazard models assessed the predictive value of DTI-ALPS for time to phenoconversion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Results&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;A total of 250 patients with iRBD (mean age: 66.5 ± 6.8 years; 87% male) and 178 controls (65.7 ± 6.8 years; 81% male) were included. Patients with iRBD showed a lower left DTI-ALPS index compared with controls (mean difference = −0.034, 95% CI −0.067 to −0.001; &lt;em&gt;p&lt;/em&gt; = 0.043). Of 224 patients with iRBD followed for a mean of 6.1 ± 3.5 years, 65 phenoconverted to a synucleinopathy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Converters had a lower left DTI-ALPS index than nonconverters (mean difference = −0.050, 95% CI −0.098 to −0.003; &lt;em&gt;p&lt;/em&gt; = 0.038). Lower left DTI-ALPS index was associated with an increased risk of conversion to PD over time (hazard ratio = 2.43, 95% CI 1.13–5.25; &lt;em&gt;p&lt;/em&gt; = 0.012). Other diffusion metrics inside periventricular masks, namely fractional anisotropy, diffusivity metrics, and free water, did not differ between groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Discussion&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients with iRBD exhibit a reduced DTI-ALPS index, suggesting altered glymphatic function. This reduction was associated with future phenoconversion to PD, supporting the DTI-ALPS index as a potential prognostic MRI biomarker of progression in prodromal synucleinopathies.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 19:08:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE94VlFfUzBpU0tLdm5sSXB1dkxWalNuQmRDbUVCU0ZLbzc0eTFFNDBUbkZrT1dUazN0Z2V6MmRfa09fYkJMREM2U3RHZmxtajVFRlRDVjFpeWtiSkdRVktRcmxsZTNuN3VOMWUwNTB1MmFuRjdlUmdDbHVVQQ</guid></item><item><title>慢性失眠可能引发引发痴呆症的大脑变化- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/chronic-insomnia-may-spark-changes-in-the-brain-that-trigger-dementia</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Staring at the ceiling while the clock blinks 3am doesn't only sap energy for the next day. A large, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12425456/"&gt;long-running US study&lt;/a&gt; of older adults has now linked chronic insomnia to changes inside the brain that set the stage for &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/dementia-283"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers, from the Mayo Clinic in the US, followed 2,750 people aged 50 and over for an average of five and a half years. Every year the volunteers completed detailed memory tests and many also had brain scans that measured two telltale markers of future cognitive trouble: the buildup of amyloid plaques, and tiny spots of damage in the brain's white matter – known as white-matter hyperintensities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants were classed as having chronic insomnia if their medical records contained at least two insomnia diagnoses a month apart – a definition that captured 16 percent of the sample.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-identify-a-trait-in-speech-that-foreshadows-cognitive-decline"&gt;Scientists Identify a Trait in Speech That Foreshadows Cognitive Decline&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared with people who slept soundly, those with chronic insomnia experienced a faster slide in memory and thinking and were 40 percent more likely to develop mild cognitive impairment or dementia over the study period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the team looked more closely, they saw that insomnia paired with shorter-than-usual sleep was especially harmful. These poor sleepers already performed as if they were four years older at the first assessment and showed higher levels of both amyloid plaques and white-matter damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By contrast, insomniacs who said they were sleeping more than usual, perhaps because their sleep problems had eased, had less white-matter damage than average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why do both amyloid plaques and blood-vessel damage matter?  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="175187" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease isn't driven by &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d42473-024-00275-0"&gt;amyloid alone&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7477392/"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt; increasingly show that clogged or leaky small blood vessels also speed cognitive decline, and the two disease states can &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-3425/13/2/218"&gt;magnify each other&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;White-matter hyperintensities disrupt the wiring that carries messages between &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39611374/"&gt;brain regions&lt;/a&gt;, while amyloid gums up the neurons &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4135182/"&gt;themselves&lt;/a&gt;. Finding higher levels of both in people with chronic insomnia strengthens the idea that poor sleep may push the brain towards a double hit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study's models confirmed the well-known effect of carrying the ApoE4 variant; the strongest common genetic risk factor for late-onset Alzheimer's. Carriers declined more quickly than non-carriers, and the insomnia effect was large enough to be comparable to the effect of having the gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists suspect ApoE4 amplifies the damage of sleepless nights by &lt;a href="https://molecularneurodegeneration.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s13024-016-0138-8"&gt;slowing the overnight clearance of amyloid&lt;/a&gt; and making blood vessels &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-020-2247-3"&gt;more vulnerable to inflammation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, these findings add to a growing body of research, from &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-021-22354-2"&gt;middle-aged civil servants in the UK&lt;/a&gt;, to community studies in &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/aging-neuroscience/articles/10.3389/fnagi.2022.1037650/full"&gt;China&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28228567/"&gt;US&lt;/a&gt;, showing that how well we sleep in midlife and beyond tracks closely with how well we think later on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic insomnia appears to accelerate the trajectory towards dementia, not through one pathway but several: by boosting amyloid, eroding white matter and probably raising blood pressure and blood-sugar levels too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That sounds like an obvious next step, but the evidence is mixed. The Mayo Clinic researchers found no clear benefit, or harm, from the sleeping pills its participants were taking. Trials of newer drugs such as orexin blockers have hinted at reductions in Alzheimer-related proteins in spinal fluid, but these &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36897120/"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; are tiny and short term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive behavioral therapy for insomnia, delivered in person or digitally, remains the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33164742/"&gt;gold-standard treatment&lt;/a&gt; and improves sleep in around &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9802437"&gt;70% of patients&lt;/a&gt;. Whether it also protects the brain is still unproven, although &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29220627/"&gt;one small trial&lt;/a&gt; in people with mild cognitive impairment showed sharper executive function after this type of talk therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the relationship is unlikely to be as simple as "treat insomnia, avoid dementia". Poor sleep often co-exists with  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depression" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73097" data-postid="175187" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;, anxiety, chronic pain and sleep apnea – all of which themselves hurt the brain. Unravelling which piece of the puzzle to target, and when, will take rigorously designed long-term studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Prevention starts early&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The participants in Mayo Clinic study were, on average, 70 years old at the start of the study, but &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-021-22354-2"&gt;other research&lt;/a&gt; has shown that routinely sleeping less than six hours a night in your 50s is already linked to higher dementia risk two decades later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That suggests prevention efforts shouldn't wait until retirement. Keeping an eye on sleep from midlife, alongside blood pressure, cholesterol and exercise, is a sensible brain-health strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleepless nights are more than a nuisance. Chronic insomnia appears to accelerate both amyloid buildup and silent blood-vessel damage, nudging the brain toward cognitive decline – especially in people who already carry the high-risk ApoE4 gene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good quality sleep is emerging as one of the modifiable pillars of brain health, but scientists are still working out whether fixing insomnia can truly head off dementia, and at what stage of life interventions will have the greatest payoff.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/265216/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/timothy-hearn-1439589"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Timothy Hearn&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, Senior Lecturer in Bioinformatics, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/anglia-ruskin-university-1887"&gt;Anglia Ruskin University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/poor-sleep-may-nudge-the-brain-toward-dementia-researchers-find-265216"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 19:04:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNQ1ZqYVZrcUlWTjZtWi05T0ZRY3QyX2dWVVdIbXlxM3ZlMjZpQkxsd2dsZzRva0oxMHVENUZIUVVWNWVJcnRQZHQwLU96SzNfVEpONlhhbDdFSl9QT3g0clhGZmVGcG04R29CSzNFWFF2aTByZnJldmxlZm9PSlM0NzJHU1dURXIwdTI2X0xuZFg2QzZiNFlnTzdDVjF3RTQ</guid></item><item><title>在Atrium Health Floyd进行的突破性前列腺手术- Coosa Valley新闻</title><link>https://coosavalleynews.com/2025/09/groundbreaking-prostate-surgery-performed-at-atrium-health-floyd/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content entry-content"&gt;
									
&lt;p&gt;A Harbin Clinic surgeon has been the first in northwest Georgia to perform an innovative robotic surgery that offers relief to men with enlarged prostates. The surgery was completed at Atrium Health Floyd Medical Center.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Aquablation therapy uses a real-time, ultrasound-guided, robotic-assisted, heat-free waterjet to remove excess prostate tissue. The combination of the camera and ultrasound allows a doctor to see the entire prostate in real time for a precise procedure.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The surgery uses the AI-powered HYDROS Robotic System, which is clinically proven to provide significant relief for men with benign prostatic hyperplasia (BPH) while helping preserve urinary (continence) and sexual function.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“This is another surgical procedure at Atrium Health Floyd Medical Center that uses robotics to provide better outcomes and improve the patient experience,” said Dr. Ken Jones, chief physician officer.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Common symptoms of BPH include the need to urinate immediately or urgently, urinating more often than normal and urinating frequently at night.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It is estimated that half of men between the ages of 51-60 have BPH and 99%  of men say it impacts their quality of life. The HYDROS waterjet technology allows surgeons to create a personalized treatment plan that precisely targets which prostate tissue to remove and which to preserve.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Without timely treatment, BPH can lead to permanent bladder or kidney damage, bladder stones and incontinence.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Aquablation brings precision to BPH treatment, allowing men to reclaim their lifestyles and find relief from symptoms while not having to worry about sexual side effects,” said Dr. Robert Williams, a urologist at Harbin Clinic who performed the surgery.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Recovery time is about one week.&lt;/p&gt;
																	&lt;/div&gt;
														&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Coosa Valley News</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:53:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQSGFrZ0l2TUNCQ1Y3T2RjM3pvMVA5bURTZFEtX01oTkdDRUdHYnNwWW9GYllSOURkY3doZGR0OGd4ejN2cTdIN1JOTUlrd3pqNUE3VDFYR0xiMW9NNTlGV2pLaVIwbVFWT1E2U0dxaFRON2tUb0NCcmNwc3V5ZzQtQ1IxeU4xQzd6OG9NX0pQWjFIMUtHZkUtSjJhWGxtSXdySExZ</guid></item><item><title>研究人员揭示了呼吸如何诱导意识状态的改变- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/researchers-shed-light-on-how-breathwork-can-induce-altered-states-of-consciousness/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new scientific investigation finds that altered states of consciousness induced by fast-paced breathing are linked to specific changes in brain blood flow and the body’s autonomic nervous system. The research, published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0329411" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;PLOS One&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;, offers a biological explanation for the profound subjective experiences reported by practitioners of this technique.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breathwork is a general term for practices that involve consciously controlling one’s breathing. Some forms, known as high ventilation breathwork, involve increasing the rate or depth of breathing, often guided by evocative music. These practices can produce powerful shifts in perception and emotion, creating experiences that practitioners describe as being similar to those from psychedelic substances, including feelings of bliss, unity, and emotional release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite growing popularity as a therapeutic tool, the biological processes behind these effects have remained largely unexamined. A team of researchers, led by first author Amy Amla Kartar, sought to fill this gap by exploring what happens in the brain and body during these intense breathing sessions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The investigation involved a total of 31 unique, experienced breathwork practitioners who participated across three interconnected experiments, with some individuals taking part in more than one session. The first study was conducted remotely over a video conferencing platform with 15 participants (average age 43, 5 female) to see if the subjective effects could be reliably produced in a home setting. A second study used a special type of magnetic resonance imaging that measures blood flow in the brain with 19 participants (average age 44, 7 female). The third experiment took place in a psychophysiology lab with 8 participants (average age 41, 2 female) where researchers measured changes in the autonomic nervous system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the laboratory and imaging sessions, participants listened to pre-recorded audio instructions paired with evocative ambient music. The session would begin with a period of normal breathing, after which the music’s tempo would progressively increase to encourage the fast-paced breathing. The audio track provided specific guidance, such as: “Mouth wide open, pulling on the inhale, that’s it. No pauses at the top of the inhale, or the bottom of the exhale. Full body breaths. Breathing in to your whole body.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The instructions also encouraged participants to surrender to the experience: “The music is going to keep on rising, so fall into the rhythm and let your breath guide you. Your job is just to keep breathing… Whatever sensations you’re feeling, let them come, let them rise, enjoy them. Stay focused.” In all settings, participants completed questionnaires before and after the breathwork to document their emotional state, any panic-like symptoms, and the nature of their altered state of consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across all three settings, the researchers found that high ventilation breathwork was safe for experienced practitioners and consistently produced altered states of consciousness. Participants did not report significant increases in fear or any panic attacks, although there was a slight increase in reported physical discomfort. Negative feelings and emotions tended to decrease after the sessions. The most commonly and intensely reported experience was a state the researchers call “Oceanic Boundlessness,” which includes feelings of bliss, spiritual connection, and a sense of unity with one’s surroundings. This particular experience was chosen as the key subjective measure to compare against the biological data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brain imaging results from 13 of the 19 participants revealed significant changes in cerebral blood flow. Overall, the fast-paced breathing caused a widespread reduction in blood flow to the brain, which is an expected physiological response to lowered carbon dioxide levels in the blood. The scientists discovered a specific relationship between this change and the participants’ subjective experiences. They found that a greater reduction in blood flow in a brain region known as the left posterior insula was associated with more intense feelings of Oceanic Boundlessness. This part of the brain is thought to be central to interoception, which is the perception of the body’s internal state, including signals from the heart and lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further analysis of this brain region showed that the blood flow reduction was specifically linked to the components of Oceanic Boundlessness described as “experience of unity” and “blissful state.” This suggests that changes in how the brain processes internal bodily signals may contribute to these profound feelings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also identified another key finding when they compared blood flow from the beginning of the breathwork session to the later, more sustained phase. In a region that includes the right amygdala and hippocampus, areas linked to emotion and memory processing, blood flow actually increased for those who reported the most intense experiences. This localized increase, happening against a backdrop of overall reduced blood flow, may indicate heightened neural activity related to processing emotional memories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the laboratory experiment focusing on physiology, the researchers observed that high ventilation breathwork activated the body’s sympathetic nervous system, the system responsible for the “fight or flight” response. This was measured by a decrease in heart rate variability, a marker that indicates the heart is beating in a more regular, less variable pattern typical of an aroused state. The specific pattern of change in heart rate variability over the course of the session was directly related to the intensity of the participant’s reported Oceanic Boundlessness. This finding connects the profound psychological state to a distinct signature of bodily arousal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study has some limitations. The number of participants in each experiment was small, and they were all experienced practitioners, so the results may not apply to individuals new to the practice. The research did not include a control condition, such as listening to the music without performing the breathwork, which makes it difficult to isolate the effects of breathing alone. The authors noted that they chose to study the practice as a whole, including the musical component, because that is how it is typically used. Future research could explore these effects in a larger and more diverse population, including novices and individuals with specific mental health conditions, to better understand its therapeutic potential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Conducting this research was a fantastic experience,” Kartar said. “It was thrilling to explore such a novel area – while many people anecdotally recognize the health benefits of breathwork, this style of fast-paced breathing has received very little scientific attention. We are very grateful to our participants for making this work possible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alessandro Colasanti, a principal investigator on the project, also commented on the findings. “Breathwork is a powerful yet natural tool for neuromodulation, working through the regulation of metabolism across the body and brain. It holds tremendous promise as a transformative therapeutic intervention for conditions that are often both distressing and disabling.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0329411" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Neurobiological substrates of altered states of consciousness induced by high ventilation breathwork accompanied by music&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Amy Amla Kartar, Toru Horinouchi, Balázs Örzsik, Brittany Anderson, Lottie Hall, Duncan Bailey, Sarah Samuel, Nati Beltran, Samira Bouyagoub, Chris Racey, Yoko Nagai, Iris Asllani, Hugo Critchley, and Alessandro Colasanti.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:15:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPT3dUZHBtaWZnVGJuS3pKZ0QyWTJnamRZYzlEUUNkUThCak11QVdsV2I0VnZtZ1RoQnAxQTROZEhPSC14Um5MY2Z4bjdLaEtEcnhaMFNXZjZHZEN1V0V3TEFnc2szR2J3dnFZUGhBdUJDOVMzczlkbHphdkVybFdEbUVTb2t3UkJ1YjJmMU9uZl91YW91OTRjU0RBM1FyZ0FZczhfcGx3TlQxNVA5</guid></item><item><title>金毛小狗在可爱视频中成为“牛奶马车的指定召唤师” - AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/golden-retriever-puppy-becomes-designated-141000881.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every family has &lt;em&gt;that one&lt;/em&gt; member who knows how to get what they want, and in this adorable TikTok clip, a tiny &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/dogs/golden-retriever-overnight-playdate-with-4-pups-instantly-cant-hang" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Golden Retriever;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Golden Retriever&lt;/a&gt; puppy has officially claimed the title of “Designated Summoner of the Milk Wagon.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The video opens on a scene of peak puppy drama: a little golden fluffball flopped on a blanket, softly whining with the type of urgency only baby animals and snack-deprived humans can master. But don’t be fooled, this isn’t just aimless noise. No, this pup is on a mission. And clearly, it has a system that works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within seconds, Mom arrives on cue like a doting room service cart, and it’s game on. The puppy dives in like it’s been wandering the desert, and milk has never existed before this moment. Siblings gather around, but it’s obvious who made the magic happen, this little summoner started the snack stampede.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best part? That tiny, pitiful whine that somehow manages to sound both demanding &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; adorable. It’s not a cry for attention, it’s a call to action. And it’s working. The internet has already dubbed this pup the "Snack Siren,” “Milk Mage,” and our personal favorite: “The Chosen Chugger.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s the kind of video that hits all the right notes: fluffy ears, and the sheer power of a puppy who knows how to get results. Whether you're a dog lover, a parent of a similarly dramatic toddler, or just someone who appreciates a well-executed summon, this clip is guaranteed to brighten your scroll.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes all it takes is one determined little voice to make the milk (or magic) happen. Whether you're summoning snacks, motivation, or Monday morning coffee, let this golden go-getter be your inspo: whine with purpose and believe the milk wagon will come. 🐾🍼&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;P.S. If we could bottle that puppy power, we’d never wait for snacks again.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Every pack has a voice!&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, it’s the tiniest one that leads the charge. Whether it's a puppy calling for milk or someone speaking up for what matters, this video is a sweet reminder that &lt;em&gt;confidence isn’t about size — it’s about knowing you belong&lt;/em&gt;. So go ahead, make a little noise. You might just inspire others to speak up, too. 🐾💛&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/dogs/golden-retriever-overnight-playdate-with-4-pups-instantly-cant-hang" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: Golden Retriever Has Overnight Playdate With 4 Pups and Instantly Can't Hang;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Related: Golden Retriever Has Overnight Playdate With 4 Pups and Instantly Can't Hang&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally reported by &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/dogs/golden-retriever-puppy-becomes-designated-summoner-of-milk-wagon-in-cute-video" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade Pets;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Parade Pets&lt;/a&gt; on Sep 27, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/dogs" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dogs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dogs&lt;/a&gt; section. Add Parade Pets as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=paradepets.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:08:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOdlpWR1Y4WU4zWjdFRExoMEtNeVlIU1JFbkpoc2JHb3p1cVp6aGZWTmY4Y1FXbWVsSklOZ0Fha3FuZUhGcmpIX1ZLSHJCZWlvWS1jSDU0THI5LTlhYXY0enhsUEN6ckExUlQ2YzVUU0hjTE5kdWhlTXdBYkhuYlRsT3MzVGF0Um8tamVtOGFR</guid></item><item><title>延迟孩子的注射？这就是为什么专业人士说这是个坏主意。-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/delaying-child-shots-why-professionals-174219799.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As vaccine hesitancy increases around the country, some parents are choosing to delay routine shots for their children rather than skip them altogether. But that’s a perilous decision that could jeopardize the health of infants, weaken protection against debilitating diseases and lead to outbreaks, medical experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Childhood vaccination rates are backsliding across the country, a trend professionals widely attribute to misinformation about the safety of shots. Those fears have been amplified by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy and President Donald Trump, who this week encouraged parents to break up childhood vaccinations into multiple doctors visits and postpone some altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://subscribe.washingtonpost.com/newsletters/#/bundle/postmost?method=SURL&amp;amp;location=YAHOO&amp;amp;initiative=feed" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Subscribe to The Post Most newsletter for the most important and interesting stories from The Washington Post.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Subscribe to The Post Most newsletter for the most important and interesting stories from The Washington Post. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Trump criticized the current federal recommendation schedule as a “disgrace” that overwhelms young children with shots and leads to lasting harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Overstating the risk of vaccines sows distrust overall,” said Ari Brown, a pediatrician in Austin. “It is very easy to scare people, and very difficult to un-scare them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Scientific data show that getting several vaccines at once is safe, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. Combination vaccines have been used in the United States since the mid-1940s. Ignoring the long-standing federally recommended vaccine schedule for infants can have severe and lasting consequences if ignored, according to public health professionals and advocates, who say Trump’s health advice is dangerous and not grounded in science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Here’s what medical specialists say about delaying or postponing childhood vaccines:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;- - -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;What is the recommended immunization schedule?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The childhood immunization schedule is a federal recommendation for all the shots kids need as they grow and develop. It’s a carefully crafted timeline that considers when certain vaccines can best protect a child from debilitating diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Babies and young children are often given several shots at the same time to reduce the amount of visits to the doctor. That process is designed to protect them as quickly as possible, and also save parents time, money and reduce trauma on the child. Some vaccines - like the one for measles, mumps and rubella (MMR) - are given as a combination to reduce the number of shots administered during a single visit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The CDC currently recommends parents vaccinate their child before the age of 2 against more than a dozen infectious diseases, including measles, chicken pox, hepatitis B, tetanus, whooping cough and polio. A Washington Post-KFF poll conducted this summer found that 1 in 6 parents have delayed or skipped some vaccines for their children, excluding for coronavirus or flu, and about a quarter of parents (26 percent) said the CDC recommends “too many” childhood vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Trump’s remarks - the latest in his administration’s embrace of anti-vaccine rhetoric - come as immunization rates fall across the country and measles cases rise to their highest in over 30 years. Public health experts worry vaccination rates will decline even further under the current administration, as the president and health secretary use their platform to amplify misinformation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In August, the Department of Health and Human Services revived a long-defunct task force that was initially created in 1986 as part of broader legislation to address childhood vaccine safety. According to HHS, the task force will make recommendations focused on developing and refining childhood vaccines that result in “fewer and less serious adverse reactions,” among other things. The task force will send its first report for Congress within two years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;- - -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;What happens if I delay shots for myself, or children?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Delaying a shot outside the recommended schedule leaves children vulnerable to diseases when they are most at risk of getting ill, developing serious complications - or dying - if they contract it. That’s because their bodies and organs are still developing, and their immune systems aren’t yet equipped to handle certain infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“There is a lot of work that goes into figuring out what the optimal scheduling timing is and when we should vaccinate,” said James Campbell, a pediatric infectious-disease specialist at the University of Maryland Children’s Hospital and School of Medicine. “If you’re making up your own schedule, you don’t have backing from the data.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If an infant catches a vaccine-preventable disease like pertussis, commonly known as whooping cough, they have a much higher risk of severe acute disease, hospitalization or death, Campbell said. Others, like hepatitis B, leave a higher risk of developing health complications later in life. That means the risk of complications are higher than the risk of serious vaccine side effects, which are extremely rare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The vaccine for human papillomavirus is recommended for children at ages 11 or 12, typically before they’re exposed to the virus through sexual activity. It’s also an age when they are most likely to generate the most amount of antibodies. The HPV vaccine has the potential to prevent more than 90 percent of cancers caused by the virus, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;- - -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Do multiple vaccines at once overwhelm the immune system?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;No. Vaccines don’t overwhelm the immune system, but instead help it recognize and fight specific diseases, according to medical experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Vaccines contain antigens - or tiny parts of viruses or bacteria - that spark an immune response when introduced into the body. The amount of antigens in a vaccine is much lower than what the child would experience if exposed to the disease itself, so the shots do not induce serious illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Brown, the pediatrician in Texas, said that while the majority of parents choose to vaccinate their children, those rates are dropping. According to the CDC, 92.5 percent of kindergartners received their MMR vaccines last school year, with lower rates in some parts of the country. More than 95 percent of a community needs to be vaccinated against measles to achieve herd immunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“That is really scary and troublesome,” said Brown, the pediatrician in Texas. “As vaccination rates go down, you will start to see these diseases return.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Related Content&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/interactive/2025/toxins-tech-tumors-is-modern-life-fueling-rise-cancer-millennials/?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=nss_yahoo" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:What researchers suspect may be fueling cancer among millennials;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;What researchers suspect may be fueling cancer among millennials&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2025/09/25/drew-lynch-comedian-heart-attack-hospital/?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=nss_yahoo" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Comedian spots man in cardiac arrest during show, finishes set at hospital;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Comedian spots man in cardiac arrest during show, finishes set at hospital &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/entertainment/2025/09/24/jimmy-kimmel-returns-late-night/?utm_source=yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=nss_yahoo" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Jimmy Kimmel advocates for free speech, slams FCC chair in late-night return;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Jimmy Kimmel advocates for free speech, slams FCC chair in late-night return&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 17:42:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOYWVzMi1GM004czRpUmhTX2dlR0tnLVllMmJBNGY1VGpGU2k2MGVhazloQkdHNXFDeENxQlZOdVc4cGUzajlKQ01KV2o5aGVMOWdvMEE1N0xoZmFrRU9NWkpYcWFfcms1MnhaOElhTGlYTnAwY2t3NmJoRXI4RFZwSndJZzB2Zkg2U0l6b2RFZ041MjQ</guid></item></channel></rss>