<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>即使在挫折之后，如何在任何年龄改善您的健康状况-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/2025/09/29/older-adults-regaining-well-being/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NMCIVBSCEJD77OZUBTIMEQABNI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When Florene Shuber was around 82 years old, she noticed that sometimes she’d trip and fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZS4UXQ4JC5FY7EJYDIM5EKPWPI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“One thing that old people don’t realize when they fall, is they don’t know they’re falling until they’re about this far from the ground,” she said, holding up her fingers an inch apart. “I found it pretty frightening. It happened two or three times. And I thought, I have to do something about this.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 13:34:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxPTU5DclpPQlNQYnhOaldYM1pkUmhvemlvamNXY18yQlJHZjU4Mm5LenlSTVRUR1ZtOUpfTDRCUERkdmh0QkQ4eTMxZkc0MmIxUm9IVFhsVEY5TjZGM204S0VZQVJZeVhoZVVybndYX2UwenJIc3dRQ1ZFQlVPdFZWUTVtNHk5OXJhWFpGTGc4aw</guid></item><item><title>得益于创新的耳部手术，当地幼儿园首次实现清晰听力- WRAL.com</title><link>https://www.wral.com/lifestyle/family/kindergartener-hears-first-time-innovative-ear-surgery-2025/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
					
						&lt;p&gt;Imagine spending five years hearing everything as if your head was underwater with a pair of headphones on. You can feel the vibrations, but you’re unable to make out anyone’s words clearly.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;That was five-year old Eliza Fowler’s reality. Now, with the help of creative technology, she is able to start kindergarten with new ears.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
								
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Eliza was born with a rare ear condition called bilateral microtia. Commonly known as "small ear syndrome," microtia is an underdeveloped outer ear and ear canal. Researchers estimate that one in every 3,800 babies in the United States has this birth defect, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/birth-defects/about/anotia-microtia.html"&gt;according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/birth-defects/about/anotia-microtia.html"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Eliza’s mother, Jennifer Fowler, explained, “She doesn’t have an ear canal, and I always say it looks like a butterfly wing.”&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;There are four classifications of microtia, and conditions range from having a small or underdeveloped ear to having no ear at all. The ear drum and ear canal may be partially formed or completely absent, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/health-library/diseases-and-conditions/m/microtia-ear-reconstruction.html"&gt;Cedars-Sinai&lt;/a&gt;, a nonprofit hospital and research center in Los Angeles, California.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Eliza has grade three microtia - known as severe microtia, where the ear is small and peanut-shaped. Patients often have a partial earlobe, but there is no external ear canal or ear drum. This is the most common form of microtia. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;At only nine days old, Eliza had her first surgery. Soon after, the family was introduced to &lt;a href="https://lewinear.com/"&gt;Lewin Ear Reconstruction&lt;/a&gt;, a California practice that specializes in microtia. The family used FaceTime to speak with Dr. Sheryl Lewin, a plastic surgeon who uses the &lt;a href="https://giveanearfoundation.org/microtia-treat/"&gt;Porus Implant Ear Reconstruction (PIER) technique&lt;/a&gt; developed by the surgeon herself. The surgery helps to minimize scarring and create more natural appearing ears.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/lifestyle/family/kindergartener-hears-first-time-innovative-ear-surgery-2025"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/lifestyle/family/kindergartener-hears-first-time-innovative-ear-surgery-2025/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Most surgeons will not perform reconstructive surgery until the ear is fully developed, which happens around age five or six. So, for the past five years, Eliza has used a bone-anchored hearing aid, known as a &lt;a href="https://www.cochlear.com/us/en/home"&gt;BAHA&lt;/a&gt;, under a headband she wears daily.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;In preparation for Eliza's big surgery, mother and daughter made several trips to California to see Lewin.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;In June, after surgery to rebuild her ear, Eliza received a cochlear &lt;a href="https://www.chicagoear.com/our-services/hearing-implants/page-10/"&gt;Osia implant.&lt;/a&gt; The implant sits under the skin, directly on her skull. It sends sound vibrations through the bone, bypassing the middle ear, and allows her to hear. The surgery took 10 hours to complete.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The moment Eliza heard her mother’s voice clearly, it brought tears to her eyes, and her family and surgical team sang happy birthday to her new ears. Eliza said sometimes she misses her headband, though.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;“She loves her new big ear,” Jennifer Fowler said. “She’ll look at it all the time. She checks on it every day. She’s like oh my gosh, it’s just so beautiful.”&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/lifestyle/family/kindergartener-hears-first-time-innovative-ear-surgery-2025"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/lifestyle/family/kindergartener-hears-first-time-innovative-ear-surgery-2025/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Eliza said she’s able to hear sounds more clearly, saying “S, ssss, snake.” Her mother said higher frequency sounds are something she is still getting used to.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Jennifer Fowler said one of the most impactful moments after surgery was Eliza taking a bath. She said her daughter started splashing in the tub, and her face lit up.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;According to her mother, Eliza exclaimed, "Woah, I really like this!"&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;"I was like, oh my gosh, you have never heard that because you couldn’t wear your BAHAs in the water,” Jennifer Fowler explained.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, and I can play with my Barbies in the bathtub," Eliza added,  finally being able to hear as her mermaid dolls glided through the water.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
								&lt;p id="nativo-0001"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p id="nativo-0002"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p id="nativo-0003"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Eliza has two dogs, Luna and Lincoln, whose barks she is able to hear more clearly after receiving her implant. She also has a lot of hobbies that she has recently had to put on hold due to her medical traveling and healing.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Eliza loves horseback riding, ice cream and playing on her iPad. Her implant can directly link with her iPad, so she doesn’t have to wear any additional headphones. Her mother said Eliza can’t wait to get back to horseback riding soon.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Eliza has two siblings that traveled with her on some of her surgery stays.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Jennifer Fowler, who worked night shifts as a remote OBGYN triage nurse until May, said between coordinating her work schedule with her husband’s and family appointments, the travel became difficult. She said she is grateful to be able to take a step back.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Eliza’s second and final surgery is scheduled for Oct. 16, when the family plans to stay in California for 11 days. Jennifer Fowler credits finding community and building relationships with navigating her daughter’s diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/lifestyle/family/kindergartener-hears-first-time-innovative-ear-surgery-2025"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/lifestyle/family/kindergartener-hears-first-time-innovative-ear-surgery-2025/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt; Eliza said she would like to become a doctor who helps kids with broken bones, or a veterinarian, when she is older.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRAL.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 11:18:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQRzJaR3BpeXZyMEhSaC0zRS14QlZDTVJvUDcyU1pSVDZxZmtadDZkOVpmNl9OQlpucTJqc3BOeUVpb05sODJPUUpJWGE5REhMTEpfNWVvNXdLUkRHMm5pMzZDZWZZb1RvUWxjQnEwd1hjNUJGbTNJLWdNR3RuWTZ2X3IzTkQtVXJvUlBjZEFnYzZEMXczSWRmbGRDRzFOX3c</guid></item><item><title>“智能尘埃已经无处不在” ：微型间谍传感器跟踪您的位置，而科技公司则永远隐藏监控革命-能源记者</title><link>https://www.energy-reporters.com/news/smart-dust-is-already-everywhere-microscopic-spy-sensors-track-your-location-while-tech-companies-hide-the-surveillance-revolution-forever/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Energy Reporters</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 09:57:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAJBVV95cUxOeG9lT0x6LW9FT09yOXRJZFM0VG9xdDFESVpYdUc0LXpVM2FwR3EtM1VmZkdQb1oyUkVnSy1tb2tCaUh4UnVoYkJiTm1GNkpXOUlaVFFsVXhNMklOdTdQZFVFbnNSQzI4ZTVDeDRWQms1MlUtaDZvZXpScnp6UDZ2SjM0M0otVDAzWTVmWGNKNW1rN2VQUWxSZ2pVcEhaamtuY2RORC1ONXladWIyY0hQTllCWVlObFM5UlhfNkd0Z1VlVF80TUJvemFOLXkxb1l4SzJDVmJnaF80ekhFVHdsZUoyeXlrRDdISDl5enl3TVNQLXFwLVg3dGpqTDYtWkFRd25scjdWWGk</guid></item><item><title>有异常症状的被忽视型糖尿病终于有了自己的名字- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/09/29/g-s1-90669/neglected-form-of-diabetes-with-unusual-symptoms-finally-gets-its-own-name</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-90690" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Researchers say that with ongoing malnutrition crises in many countries, they expect to see more cases of Type 5 diabetes emerging. Pictured here is a patient receiving a blood glucose test for diabetes in a door-to-door screening program in India's Haryana state.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Prashanth Vishwanathan/Bloomberg/via Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Prashanth Vishwanathan/Bloomberg/via Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;In the early 1950s, British physician Philip Hugh-Jones was flummoxed by 13 patients who showed up at the diabetes clinic he ran near Kingston, Jamaica.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;At the time, researchers broadly recognized two kinds of diabetes, known today as Type 1 and Type 2. Hugh-Jones himself coined those terms in a study of hundreds of patients published in 1955.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Most of his patients fell into those two buckets, but that group of 13 people didn't fit into either category, says &lt;a href="https://uwi.edu/caihr/faculty/pg-boyne.php" target="_blank"&gt;Michael Boyne&lt;/a&gt;, an endocrinologist at the University of the West Indies, where Hugh-Jones did his research.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"They were relatively young, thin and kind of undernourished looking," says Boyne.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Normally, that would point to Type 1 diabetes, where individuals are unable to make their own insulin and can become underweight. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But these 13 patients never experienced a common symptom of Type 1  — ketoacidosis. That occurs when the body runs out of insulin and starts burning fat for fuel, which can lead the blood to become dangerously acidic.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Even though they were thin, they never developed keto[acidosis]," says Boyne, seemingly ruling out &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2019/10/14/763948647/researchers-try-a-genetic-diabetes-test-to-prevent-emergency-hospitalizations" target="_blank"&gt;Type 1 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;. But they didn't seem to be Type 2 diabetics either, who tend to be overweight.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"So he said, 'Huh, these guys are different. They don't fit Type 1 or 2,'" says Boyne. "So he called them Type J." That's "J" for Jamaica. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The name didn't stick. Subsequent names didn't stick either, despite cases of this unusual form of diabetes continuing to surface, especially in areas afflicted with malnutrition. Now, 70 years later, an international team of researchers is trying to formalize a new name — Type 5 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The time is ripe" to recognize this disease that could impact as many as 25 million people," says Dr. &lt;a href="https://einsteinmed.edu/faculty/1982/meredith-hawkins" target="_blank"&gt;Meredith Hawkins&lt;/a&gt;, a diabetes researcher at Albert Einstein College of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In April, the International Diabetes Federation adopted the new name. Now, in a perspective published in &lt;em&gt;The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Lancet Global Health&lt;/em&gt;, Hawkins and an international team of researchers are &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/langlo/article/PIIS2214-109X(25)00263-3/fulltext" target="_blank"&gt;urging other entities&lt;/a&gt;, including the World Health Organization, to get on board too.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"It is important, from a scientific perspective, to give it a name," says &lt;a href="https://www.cmcendovellore.org/nihal-thomas-php/" target="_blank"&gt;Nihal Thomas&lt;/a&gt;, an endocrinologist at the Christian Medical College in Vellore, India, who is part of the effort. "And patients will benefit a lot," he said, since some are getting treatment that can be deadly.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;The dangers of not having a name&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;After Hugh-Jones published his 1955 paper, researchers around the globe started noticing similar cases that didn't fit Type 1 or Type 2.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It had a variety of names over time, but they were all generally describing the same thing," says Boyne. "And in Southeast Asia, India and Africa, they really noticed a strong connection with malnutrition in early life."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hawkins herself first saw this unusual form of diabetes while working in Uganda in the early 2000s.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"A lot of very impoverished patients that were coming in from rural areas, very thin and malnourished, very high blood sugars," she says. They'd exhibit classic symptoms of diabetes, including frequent urination, excessive thirst or hunger, and even nerve damage.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;To most clinicians, including Hawkins at the time, such patients seem like classic Type 1 cases. The standard treatment would be to send them home with a lot of &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2018/09/01/641615877/insulins-high-cost-leads-to-lethal-rationing" target="_blank"&gt;insulin&lt;/a&gt;. But she and her colleagues soon learned that this approach could be lethal.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Basically, in many cases, committing them to a death sentence from low blood sugar," if they didn't have enough food to eat at home, she says. Insulin is a hormone that helps shuttle sugar from the blood into cells, where it can be used for energy. Too much insulin, coupled with too little food, can result in dangerously low blood sugar, she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Seeing such cases of "young people who had died from low blood sugar because they weren't being appropriately treated really motivated our research," says Hawkins.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;What makes Type 5 diabetes different&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Since then, she and other researchers have learned that physiologically, people with Type 5 diabetes &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35522035/" target="_blank"&gt;look different&lt;/a&gt; from those with Type 1 or 2. Those differences seem to be shaped by malnutrition.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"These individuals have generally had malnutrition from the time they were in utero," says Hawkins. "They're malnourished as toddlers, as children, as adolescents and as adults. These are the ones that don't catch up. They just stay very thin, and that makes them different than other forms of diabetes."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;One key difference is the pancreas, where insulin gets produced. Evidence suggests that malnutrition in early development harms the ability of the pancreas to pump out insulin.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Their pancreas is crap," says Boyne. "It's not as bad as Type 1, but it's really crappy."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That leaves people with Type 5 diabetes in a weird spot. They can produce some insulin and their cells respond to it (unlike people with Type 2 diabetes, whose cells are often resistant to insulin), but they can't make quite enough to normally regulate their blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We felt very strongly that if this was a separate entity, it needed separate treatment," says Hawkins. Figuring out the best treatment will take more research, she says, something she hopes the new name can galvanize.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Not everyone in the diabetes research community is convinced that Type 5 diabetes is a distinct entity or that it deserves a new name.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Formal classification risks codifying what may be a spectrum of poorly characterized Type 2 diabetes rather than a discrete entity," says Anoop Misra, an endocrinologist at the Centre of Nutrition &amp;amp; Metabolic Research in New Delhi. He says the existing data isn't enough to definitively establish a distinct form of diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The International Diabetes Federation disagrees, though, and launched a &lt;a href="https://idf.org/news/new-type-5-diabetes-working-group/" target="_blank"&gt;working group&lt;/a&gt; aimed at developing better diagnostic criteria and treatment guidelines for Type 5 diabetes. (It chose the name Type 5 as uncontested territory, since there are ongoing efforts to label other forms of diabetes as Types 3 and 4.) Advocates hope recognition by other health authorities, including the World Health Organization, could help that effort, at a time when cases are poised to rise in some parts of the globe.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Food crises in &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/08/22/g-s1-84600/famine-is-declared-in-gaza-what-does-it-take-to-make-this-pronouncement" target="_blank"&gt;Gaza&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2024/12/25/nx-s1-5238230/hunger-experts-say-the-severity-of-the-famine-in-sudan-has-worsened" target="_blank"&gt;Sudan&lt;/a&gt;, the Democratic Republic of Congo, Nigeria and Yemen could be setting up a generation for increased risk of Type 5 diabetes, says Boyne.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's really heart-rending," he says. "This is something that's preventable — it's preventable by food."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1wFBVV95cUxQSHVEZXJPM3BmNW5XWkU2SnpYYkxoTDlKOXBZNThwOW8xVkRuVFlEMHFiZzJhd21lenFPeFBPbTVlQnB3ZW8xbFFXeHhhVnJSMkYwdjBiWGJlU2txR0FoQ0xjVDZrb1YxRnh1NDhBWnl6eXBUUDdKaWRZWU5pODY1VFlOZHRRRW5Ucm9JU0c0WlBQUTVJdkdFVENzc1J5QnhtU3RLZzJfVUU0a1k3bkVKLUtYX3YzaUluZFhCdUNPRER0MUV2dFhlUHZ5Uk9UdF9Jb2pmMkROcw</guid></item><item><title>容易患冬季抑郁症？现在开始光疗可以有所帮助- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/09/29/nx-s1-5546611/seasonal-depression-light-therapy-mental-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-90756" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Light boxes or sunlight simulator lamps need to emit 10,000 lux of light to be effective. If used correctly a light box can help combat the effects of Seasonal Affective Disorder.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Daniel Wischenbarth/E+/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Daniel Wischenbarth/E+/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Have you noticed you're sleeping a little longer? Maybe you're experiencing a shift in appetite — craving more sweets or pasta. In autumn, our bodies sense the change in light as the dark winter months approach, which can help explain what you are feeling.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;As daylight diminishes, you may find your mood dimming, too. About 1 in 20 adults have&lt;a href="https://www.psychiatry.org/patients-families/seasonal-affective-disorder" target="_blank"&gt; Seasonal Affective Disorder &lt;/a&gt;— which is &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2018/12/21/678342879/scientists-find-a-brain-circuit-that-could-explain-seasonal-depression" target="_blank"&gt;seasonal depression&lt;/a&gt;. And millions more experience a milder form of "winter blues."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;One way to fend it off is by using a light box, beginning in the fall.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"A lot of research has shown that using bright light therapy in the morning can be extremely helpful to reverse some of the symptoms of seasonal depression," says &lt;a href="https://www.feinberg.northwestern.edu/faculty-profiles/az/profile.html?xid=34411" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Dorothy Sit&lt;/a&gt;, a psychiatrist and Associate Professor at Northwestern University, who has studied bright light therapy.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Typically, people sit in front of a light box, which emits bright light, every morning, for about 30 minutes, give or take. Sit says making it part of a morning routine is key. "If people use a light box every day they can experience an enduring effect throughout the fall and winter," she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Sit points to an often-cited study that found light therapy is &lt;a href="https://psychiatryonline.org/doi/10.1176/ajp.2006.163.5.805" target="_blank"&gt;on par with standard anti-depression medications&lt;/a&gt; in relieving symptoms. Some people do both, taking medication and using a light box, and research shows the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31600678/" target="_blank"&gt;combination can be helpful&lt;/a&gt;. Studies point to improvements in symptoms within one week of starting light therapy.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Understanding our body clocks&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Our bodies can be quite &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2017/10/02/555054483/how-messing-with-our-body-clocks-can-raise-alarms-with-health" target="_blank"&gt;sensitive to changes in daylight &lt;/a&gt;because we rely on it to regulate our &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2024/10/30/1211597510/1a-10-30-2024" target="_blank"&gt;circadian rhythms&lt;/a&gt; and our sleep-wake patterns.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;And because our internal body clocks don't keep a perfect 24-hour cycle, the master clock in our brains needs a daily reset. "Light through the eyes," is the cue for the reset, explains Michael Terman, a retired professor of clinical psychology and psychiatry at Columbia University.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's why &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2024/11/07/nx-s1-5178149/light-exposure-circadian-rhythms-sleep" target="_blank"&gt;exposure to morning light &lt;/a&gt;is so important. "What we are doing is resetting that drifting circadian clock to synchronize with the outdoor world," Terman explains.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Terman is also President of the non-profit organization, &lt;a href="https://cet.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Center for Environmental Therapeutics,&lt;/a&gt; which aims to educate healthcare professionals and the public about therapies to improve mood and health, focusing on non-medication treatments, including light boxes.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Terman says some models of light boxes sold online are either too small or don't emit enough bright light. His organization offers&lt;a href="https://cet.org/how-to-select-a-light-box/" target="_blank"&gt; guidance on how to select a &lt;/a&gt;light box, and recommends purchasing models that meet the standards of devices tested in clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A few things to keep in mind when starting use of a light box: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;ol class="edTag rte2-style-ol"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Purchase a light box that emits &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/seasonal-affective-disorder/in-depth/seasonal-affective-disorder-treatment/art-20048298" target="_blank"&gt;10,000 lux of light&lt;/a&gt;. (Lux is a measure of brightness.) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Larger screens are better, according to the Center for Environmental Therapeutics, because screen size influences light exposure."Smaller sizes increase the likelihood that small head movements reduce the 10,000 lux dose," the group says. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adjust the angle of the light box. The light box should project downwards towards the eyes at an angle. This will help avoid a glare.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Start with 30 minutes in front of the light box and make adjustments based on how you feel. If you only get a little spurt of additional energy, you may want to increase to 45 minutes. Or if you feel jittery, that may be too much.  "Just as with a drug, light has to be dosed," Terman says. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"I think bright light is still an underrecognized treatment option," says psychiatrist Dorothy Sit. And you don't need to be clinically depressed to benefit. Light therapy can be quite helpful for people who even have "milder forms," she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So, If you're one of the many people who feels a dip in mood and energy beginning in fall, you may want to consider a light box, Sit says. But she also recommends that you talk to a healthcare provider about symptoms and treatment options.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Also, keep in mind that a lack of light is not the only trigger of a low mood. If it's cold and snowy, people tend to go out less, says &lt;a href="https://profiles.stanford.edu/jamie-zeitzer" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Jamie Zeitzer&lt;/a&gt; of Stanford University. "That can be depressing." He says light therapy won't help with the blues caused by social isolation, so remember to reach out to friends and stay engaged in activities that bring you into contact with others.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;When it comes to feeling good in the coming darker months, we need light, as well as&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/09/19/1200223456/depression-anxiety-prevention-mental-health-healthy-habits" target="_blank"&gt; a handful  of habits&lt;/a&gt; that can help boost our moods, including laughter, friendship, a healthy diet,&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/01/05/nx-s1-5247787/depression-walking-step-count-fitness-tracker#:~:text=%22Studies%20like%20these%20are%20encouraging,some%20cases%2C%20exercise%20worked%20better." target="_blank"&gt; physical activity&lt;/a&gt; and exercise.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxQTjFOUGw1ZVJIZlU1WTB1N05ZY1NDcUFEQXpUTGtPZUg2OHNJV3R0S0lXQVNvVkxWeG1Ub1JRLUhfSEo5LXN4OEpERGhVMU1nVWdWTnJwWUl4YUJSa2JDaUpwTHByLUNyc0ppUEpSU1pobG0tTzFXdjlnaHp4clo4bmR6ZWpSeHl3RmY2ZFJwRW5mN18zNFVr</guid></item><item><title>您应该采取哪些措施来降低患痴呆症的风险？询问Richard Sima。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/09/30/dementia-prevention-questions-answers/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-krqlHC"&gt;&lt;h1 id="main-content" data-qa="headline" data-testid="headline" class="wpds-c-eRlesA wpds-c-eRlesA-dHdMuz-isOnSplitTopper-false wpds-c-eRlesA-bAbYzz-isStyle-false wpds-c-eRlesA-iPJLV-css"&gt;What should you do to reduce your risk of dementia? Ask Richard Sima.&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;p data-qa="subheadline" data-testid="subheadline" class="wpds-c-ckOSsQ wpds-c-ckOSsQ-iPJLV-css"&gt;Brain health expert Richard Sima will answer your questions during a live chat on Tuesday at 11 a.m. Eastern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-testid="timestamp" class="wpds-c-bEimne wpds-c-bEimne-dyECYW-theme-default"&gt;&lt;time data-testid="updated-and-published" datetime="2025-09-30T15:00:17.900Z" class="wpds-c-gRBhEF wpds-c-gRBhEF-ihakyQ-css overrideStyles"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="display-date" class="wpds-c-bASIGw overrideStyles"&gt;September 30, 2025 at 11:00 a.m. EDT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 08:18:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxPVlV4dmsxMTFLT1lWUk9ES19YeDR3aWJOSWxYNm9EbS1leU5UazdKc0g0anQxbEVhbno2M1IzVWZqeVZnV1ZwMVItZEZnaDhzSGdKN3hpbEtKMjMwVFIzenVaYk9wcDVLODd4NUpoekh4elRSeVFKY0FCNmp4TV9jdGp2WjRaalZUaGVPV2VJVGRYWHc</guid></item><item><title>减肥注射如何将肥胖变成财富问题- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cre5xp83394o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;How weight-loss injections are turning obesity into a wealth issue&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-6 ioiEdf"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Nick Triggle profile image" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Nick Triggle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Health correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC A pound sign etched out with a tape measure " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;b id="three-years-ago,-a-fashion-editor-friend-returned-from-milan-fashion-week-bursting-with-a-story-to-tell." class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;Three years ago, a fashion editor friend returned from Milan Fashion Week bursting with a story to tell.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Most fashion editors stayed at the same hotel, she explained, and each bedroom had its own mini fridge. After checking out, en route to the airport, a stylist in her party cried out that he'd left "an important package" in his fridge and telephoned the hotel, pleading with them not to throw it away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Turns out he'd forgotten his Ozempic," my editor friend whispered. We were baffled. Ozempic?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Back then, Ozempic was not part of the common lexicon. But quietly, in certain circles, this injectable drug, which is licensed for the treatment of type 2 diabetes, was being prescribed privately and off-label for weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Flash forward to today and the picture is vastly different. "So many fashion people are on it," she tells me today. "And now they're very vocal." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Serena Williams, Elon Musk and Whoopi Goldberg have all spoken about using weight-loss injections. Some are now prescribed by the NHS, including Wegovy and Mounjaro, generating scores of headlines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Really, this should have made it a great leveller. In theory, anyone struggling with obesity can - without the expense of a private doctor - get help to manage their weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Only that's not the full picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="AFP via Getty Images Models walk the runway wearing white and black
" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;AFP via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;'So many fashion people are on it and now they're very vocal,' says one London-based fashion editor (Milan Fashion Week is pictured)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Thousands of NHS patients are believed to be missing out. And with the NHS tightly restricting access, some working in the field warn a two-tier system around weight-loss drugs is developing - one that's benefitting the most well-off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Martin Fidock, who is UK managing director of Oviva, which provides Wegovy and lifestyle support to NHS patients, claims that thanks to varying thresholds of eligibility in different regions, NHS prescriptions are a "postcode lottery".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;An estimated 1.5 million people in the UK use these drugs - but more than nine in 10 are believed to pay privately. Prices vary but it generally costs between £100 and £350 a month, depending on the dose and lifestyle support. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Then, last month, it was reported that pharmaceutical giant Eli Lilly was expected to &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cvg3ykg4jrro" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;increase the list price of Mounjaro&lt;/a&gt; by as much as 170%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;They have since done a deal for UK distributors, meaning rises are likely to be less, and the rises don’t affect the cost to the NHS - but it has still caused concern in some quarters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's scary," says Brad, a tech company worker in his 40s. He has been taking Mounjaro for a year and worries he may not be able to afford to continue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I've lost 20kg and want to keep using it, but it's a lot of money. It's unfair."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images (R) AFP via Getty Images (L) Two images of Elon Musk" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images (R) AFP via Getty Images (L)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Wegovy was called the 'Viagra' of weight-loss drugs - the huge interest around it is partly fuelled by social media buzz and celebrity users, including Elon Musk&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Nutritionists and GPs I spoke to have also expressed concerns about the broader system, and in particular whether existing health inequalities could worsen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We cannot allow good health to become a luxury for the wealthiest by limiting access to weight-loss drugs to those who can pay privately," argues Katharine Jenner, executive director of Obesity Health Alliance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;So could it really be that weight-loss injections - for all of their benefits - are turning obesity into a wealth issue?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;The NHS 'postcode lottery'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Weight-loss drugs have been available on the NHS for some time, but the landscape changed significantly with the introduction of some newer medications - among them, semaglutide, marketed under the brand name Wegovy, and tirzepatide, sold as Mounjaro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Wegovy was first prescribed for obesity by the NHS in 2023, while Mounjaro followed earlier this year. They work in part as an appetite suppressant by mimicking a hormone, which makes people feel fuller. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Studies have suggested patients can lose as much as a fifth of their body weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;They are licensed for people with a BMI of 27 or more for those with a health condition or above 30 for those without (adjusted for certain ethnic groups). But tougher NHS criteria are being applied, and in England and Wales the drugs are mostly restricted to those with a BMI of over 35.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Plus there are more restrictions too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For Wegovy, local areas are making their own decisions on access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Martin Fidock claims that in recent months a third of regional health boards have increased the BMI threshold, which he says has resulted in fewer people being able to get it. (The BBC has been unable to verify this data.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A spokesperson for Novo Nordisk, the pharmaceutical giant that makes Wegovy, told the BBC it is "concerned about the growing disparity" in access to NHS specialist weight management services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"This has led to a large proportion of people needing to pay out of pocket, an option which is out of reach in areas of deprivation where obesity rates are significantly higher."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;NHS England has said the differences could be related to different levels of need and other providers being more active in certain regions, but confirmed it was up to local areas to decide how much to spend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Reuters Blue Ozempic injection pens lined up" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Reuters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;While Ozempic is intended for those with type 2 diabetes, Wegovy is prescribed specifically for weight loss&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For Mounjaro, NHS England has started it for people with a BMI above 40 who also have certain health conditions. The NHS roll-out officially began in June, but a report published earlier this month suggests that not all general practices had started offering it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Just 18 out of 42 NHS boards across England confirmed that they'd begun prescribing it in line with the roll-out plan, according to data obtained by freedom of information requests published in the BMJ. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The NHS has previously said it is supporting the phased rollout for eligible patients and that "these represent brand-new services in primary care that are being established and scaled up over time".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But Mr Fidock believes we are seeing a "postcode lottery".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We have got an obesity epidemic and these drugs provide us with an opportunity to tackle it in a way we have never been able to do before. But your ability to benefit is dependent largely on whether you have the means to pay."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Adding to the challenge is the fact that more people from deprived areas struggle with obesity in the first place: more than a third of people in the most deprived areas are obese – twice that of more affluent neighbourhoods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Beyond the physical health risks - and there are many, including higher risks of cancer and heart disease, plus mental health problems - there may be social consequences too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;One US study found that obese men with a bachelor's degree earn 5% less than their thinner colleagues, while those with a graduate degree earn 14% less. For obese women it is worse still, earning 12% and 19% less respectively, based on data concerning 23,000 US workers, published in The Economist in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;NHS GP Matthew Calcasola, who is also involved in a service Get a Drip, which offers weight-loss drugs privately, has his own concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We're concerned health inequality will build," he says. "GPs worry about this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Private patients priced out&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Meanwhile, a booming private market has emerged. Sara de Souza, a business analyst from Nottingham, is among those delighted that it has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Following the birth of her son Vito in 2023, she put on 30kg. "I got to 96kg," she recalls. "Me and my husband both got into bad habits. We were so busy, we were eating junk food and having chocolates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I was always tired and struggled to pick up my baby. But I just couldn't lose the weight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Sara tried dieting and went to see her GP who referred her to a lifestyle diet and activity programme. But still the pounds stuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At her heaviest her BMI was 37.5, but she wasn't eligible for NHS access and paid £200 a month for the drug through an app called Juniper, which also gave her diet and lifestyle advice. Within a year she had lost the full 30kg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Sara says the cost didn't impact her. 'Even if it had, I'd have carried on, because of the benefits'&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It completely changed my life. I felt like a new person, alive again. It's not just how I look, it's how I feel and being able to keep up with my son."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Sara says the cost didn't impact her. "Even if it had, I'd have carried on, because of the benefits."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Not everyone feels the same. Some 18% of overweight Britons would be willing to pay for weight-loss drugs - but if they were available on the NHS, 59% said they would be keen on using them, according to new polling by communications agency Strand Partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And some of those willing to pay privately fear they could find themselves being priced out following the proposed price spike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A pen prepared for weight loss injection 
" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;'Some people can't move on to the higher doses because of cost,' says the UK head of an online pharmacy, speaking about weight-loss drugs in general&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If I'd had to pay £300 or even more, I would have really struggled to afford it," says Pete Beech, 57, from Southampton. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He weighed 18 stone and paid £160 a month for a prescription of Mounjaro to help him lose weight to qualify for an ultrasound treatment as part of his treatment for prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The way the NHS is rationing these drugs has consequences beyond just obesity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;James O'Loan, head of online pharmacy Chemist4U, has already observed some people stretching themselves financially to get hold of weight-loss drugs - some have asked for payment plans, which they cannot offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Some people can't move on to the higher doses because of cost," he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images for ESSENCE Serena Williams looking serious with her hands on her hips
" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images for ESSENCE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Serena Williams has spoken out about using weight-loss drugs - she says, to lift 'stigma' around them&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Then there are concerns about a weight-loss drug black market, or unscrupulous dispensing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Some services are desperate to dispense the stuff and don't care what happens," claims Professor Richard Donnelly, editor of medical journal Diabetes, Obesity and Metabolism. "People are just asked to fill in a quick questionnaire. There's no proper medical assessment or follow up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He also stresses that they should not be seen as a quick fix. "They're not there to lose a bit of fat around the tummy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Whilst generally well tolerated, there are risks of certain side effects — including nausea, constipation and diarrhoea. A study into potential serious side effects of weight loss jabs has also been launched after hundreds of people reported &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/c4ged0r1n3wo" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;problems with their pancreas. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The NHS advises people never take a medicine for weight management if it has not been prescribed for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'Not a magic bullet'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Some argue that the answer is, simply, to widen NHS access. The issue, of course, comes in part down to cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Michael Shah, senior analyst at Bloomberg Intelligence, believes that this could start to resolve itself in time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There are more than 160 weight-loss drugs in clinical development," he says. Once available, he predicts that the competition could push costs down across the board.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"NHS bargaining power should improve as additional players and treatments enter the space."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Kevin Mazur/WireImage via Getty Images Whoopi Goldberg attending the 90th Annual Academy Awards " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Kevin Mazur/WireImage via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Actress Whoopi Goldberg has said: 'I weighed almost 300 pounds... I was on all this stuff and one of the things that has helped me drop the weight is Mounjaro'&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Earlier this year the Tony Blair Institute suggested that the drugs should be offered to everyone with BMIs over 27, arguing that it costs even more to deal with the consequences of obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Obesity is estimated to cost the economy £98bn a year, according to research commissioned by the think tank, once you take into account lost productivity as well as the NHS treatment costs and the impact on the individual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The Institute suggests a means-tested system with those entitled to free prescriptions getting it free and others self-funding or encouraging employers to share the cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;NHS England has said it is looking at an option to "accelerate roll out to even more people in the future". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But it also pointed out that weight loss drugs should not be seen as a "magic bullet".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Are we medicalising a social issue?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;All of this begs a broader question - that is, in medicalising debates around tackling obesity, do we risk overlooking the wider social issue?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"By thinking we have a treatment for obesity we lose focus and stop thinking about the more difficult issues around the food industry and regulation, which are the root cause of this," warns Greg Fell, president of the Association of Directors of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I do have concerns about equity of access," he adds. "But I think the NHS has carefully thought about this and probably is, more or less, in the right place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Bin overflowing with junk food packaging" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Obesity was rare In post-war Britain due to food shortages - there wasn't the convenience food culture of today either&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In post-war Britain, obesity was rare due to food shortages and physically demanding lifestyles – lower-income groups were more likely to suffer from malnutrition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Only since the 1980s have obesity rates risen across all social classes, with a growing disparity between rich and poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It is driven by several interconnected factors. Katharine Jenner argues there needs to be more done to address one of them in particular: our "broken food system".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"People in poorer areas are surrounded by junk food advertising, more unhealthy takeaways, and face bigger barriers to buying healthy food," she says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Without investment in prevention, health will get worse, inequalities will widen, and the costs will fall on all of us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;How to effectively achieve that is perhaps the biggest question of all. But whatever the answer - and regardless of whether the onus really should be on the state or as others argue, the individual - it runs far deeper than the cost of a weight-loss jab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We live in a society that prizes freedom of choice and expression, values material wealth and tolerates vast inequality," argues Chris Rojek, sociology professor at City St George's, University of London. "In such a system, casualties are inevitable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It would be naïve — or even pious — to claim we can simply solve this. The answer is complex and touches the very fabric of our society."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;i id="top-picture-credit:-onzeg/-getty-images" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;Top picture credit: Onzeg/ Getty Images&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/bbcindepth" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;&lt;i id="bbc-indepth" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;BBC InDepth&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="is-the-home-on-the-website-and-app-for-the-best-analysis,-with-fresh-perspectives-that-challenge-assumptions-and-deep-reporting-on-the-biggest-issues-of-the-day.-and-we-showcase-thought-provoking-content-from-across-bbc-sounds-and-iplayer-too.-you-can-send-us-your-feedback-on-the-indepth-section-by-clicking-on-the-button-below." class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt; is the home on the website and app for the best analysis, with fresh perspectives that challenge assumptions and deep reporting on the biggest issues of the day. And we showcase thought-provoking content from across BBC Sounds and iPlayer too. You can send us your feedback on the InDepth section by clicking on the button below.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 07:02:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBaeWZjd25EamxWeldhZFlSamd4R3o1Z0dHVHczVUMxRlpRQzIyMjdUODVHYmtremJpTEVDUWtXX0tKV29BcTRGZkVGYXdrbEwyRnNpRkFYb1ZpUQ</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，微塑料可能会削弱您的骨骼- WIRED</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/microplastics-could-be-weakening-your-bones-research-suggests-osteoporosis/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;Microplastics could be&lt;/span&gt; a factor in driving up cases of osteoporosis worldwide, according to &lt;a data-offer-url="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00198-025-07580-4" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00198-025-07580-4"}' href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00198-025-07580-4" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;recently published research&lt;/a&gt;. The study reveals that when these tiny plastic particles enter the body, they disrupt the functioning of bone marrow stem cells, which are essential for maintaining and repairing bone tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Throughout your life, your bones are replenished. Osteoporosis is a condition where this process goes wrong, with the breakdown of bone outstripping the rate at which it is replaced. This leads to bones weakening over time and becoming more likely to fracture. The condition &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/osteoporosis/symptoms-causes/syc-20351968"&gt;has many risk factors&lt;/a&gt;—age, sex, medications, diet, smoking and drinking, and genetics are all known to influence it—with the disease developing slowly over time. Often people don’t realize they have the condition until they break a bone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;This new analysis, published in the journal Osteoporosis International, adds exposure to microplastics as a potential new risk factor. The research reviewed 62 scientific articles that had run various laboratory and animal tests on the possible effects of micro- and nanoplastics on bone. Analysis of lab experiments showed that microplastics stimulate the formation of osteoclasts, cells created by stem cells in the bone marrow that degrade bone tissue to promote resorption, the process in which the body breaks down and eliminates old or damaged bone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The study also found that, in relation to bones, plastic particles can reduce the viability of cells, induce premature cellular aging, modify gene expression, and trigger inflammatory responses. The combination of these effects generates an imbalance in which osteoclasts destroy more bone tissue than is regenerated, causing an accelerated weakening of bone structure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;When then looking at animal studies, the researchers found that the accumulation of microplastics in the body decreases the white blood cell count—which is suggestive of alterations in bone marrow function. In addition, these animal studies suggested that the impact of microplastics on osteoclasts may be associated with deterioration of bone microstructure and the formation of irregular structures of cells, increasing the risk of bone fragility, deformities, and fractures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“In this study, the adverse effects observed culminated, worryingly, in the interruption of the animals’ skeletal growth,” said coauthor Rodrigo Bueno de Oliveira in a &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1098938"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt;. “The potential impact of microplastics on bones is the subject of scientific studies and isn’t negligible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Oliveira, who is the coordinator of the Laboratory for Evaluation of Mineral and Bone Disorders in Nephrology at the State University of Campinas in Brazil, is now working with his team to further prove in practice the relationship between exposure to microplastics and bone deterioration. This research will begin by evaluating the effects of microplastic particles on rodents’ femurs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“Although osteometabolic diseases are relatively well understood, there’s a gap in our knowledge regarding the influence of microplastics on the development of these diseases. Therefore, one of our goals is to generate evidence suggesting that microplastics could be a potential controllable environmental cause to explain, for example, the increase in the projected number of bone fractures,” Oliveira said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Microplastics and nanoplastics are small fragments of plastic—some so small that they’re invisible to the naked eye—that become detached from everyday objects when sunlight, wind, rain, seawater, or abrasion degrade them. The main difference between the two lies in their size: microplastics measure from 1 micrometer (one-thousandth of a millimeter) to 5 millimeters, while nanoplastics are smaller than 1 micrometer. These particles have been detected &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/the-microplastic-crisis-is-getting-exponentially-worse/"&gt;all over the world&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/microplastics-are-polluting-the-ocean-at-a-shocking-rate/"&gt;natural environments&lt;/a&gt;, as well as throughout the &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/this-startup-promises-to-clean-your-blood-of-microplastics-clarify-clinics/"&gt;human body&lt;/a&gt; and in meat, water, and various agricultural products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Studies have started to show that this type of plastic contamination can &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0013935124004390"&gt;damage health&lt;/a&gt;. Experts argue that this means the world urgently needs to reduce its use of plastics. Every year more than 500 million tons of the material are produced worldwide, but only 9 percent is recycled, with much of the remainder spreading into the environment and degrading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This story originally appeared on&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://es.wired.com/articulos/la-cantidad-de-fracturas-en-el-mundo-podria-dispararse-a-causa-de-los-microplasticos"&gt;WIRED &lt;em&gt;en Español&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;and has been translated from Spanish.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPMnctQWNVYWhOYWpmUV9UUzUtUWZ2OFNnWDJQV0dmbkthRFBzOEVlOUFQSWRNWmhWNThiQURyS0pfV0FpdF9rVzhGUTZicEpfU2VLcFlmZ2RQUGN2TmdpdFB4LUF1THJmTTl2WVdxLVN1aTJTa3VmMEgxTlZxT2w3dFJNbV9KWTBUdmFJcFBpdUdaZkQtUTVhM1hXNTJqeHV3NG8wNnZ3</guid></item><item><title>根据医生和护士的说法， 13种严重破坏您健康的“坏”习惯- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/lizmrichardson/doctors-worst-health-mistakes-bad-habits</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-12
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139375732" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;9.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"I work with patients in end-stage kidney failure. Turmeric supplements &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/wellness-and-prevention/turmeric-benefits" target="_blank"&gt;can potentially be very damaging&lt;/a&gt; to the internal structure of your kidneys. While turmeric's anti-inflammatory properties can benefit some, turmeric pills and supplements can potentially act as vasodilators, lowering &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0939475323002727" target="_blank"&gt;blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;. If you don't have high blood pressure, a vasodilator can restrict blood flow in the delicate internal structure of the kidneys, essentially choking them off. Most over-the-counter turmeric supplements are poorly regulated. If you want to benefit from turmeric, it's best to consume it in a pure form, rather than the mystery amalgamation you get from supplements."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;"The overuse (more than directed on the bottle, or over a great length of time) of Advil and other over-the-counter painkillers can do the same thing. &lt;b&gt;Protect your kidneys, folks!!!&lt;/b&gt; Dialysis is not a fun process, and once your kidneys go, your only option is dialysis or transplant."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.buzzfeed.com/strangerthanitseems"&gt;strangerthanitseems&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 03:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQb3V3RzJacUM5YU02NFVYSjUxei1FQTVnYjYwZG0wSkJDcnA5NU9Ncl9EX2NSOVFITFJuSWZlcm5CUkhmZU5pZVU3TXktNEsxMDZKX0ZJX2YyYldJalp4NnlXbkYzanJQTXRaVURHQmJTX3JoZ3Z4cE5fY29pUV90bHNLMzI4b28</guid></item><item><title>让我不想再上网的几个WTF事实- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/crystalro/maura-murray-kenneth-mcduff-that-got-dark-september-28</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz__description
  "&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Do you have a weird, creepy, or shocking story you want to share? Perhaps there’s a strange Wikipedia page you want to talk about? Tell me all about it at thatgotdark@buzzfeed.com, and who knows, maybe it’ll be featured in a future edition of&lt;/i&gt; That Got Dark&lt;i&gt;! &lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:02:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOb1Fwbm10eWVMX00tVTBnQ1pwV2YzcVh3bFR6NUZSVzRJTlNvUGppLWFmN3JVUlhJaUkzT2RVdXU0eWpZaWkxS1lKZ1F4N19GNU13VENNYnJlOVpnZ2d0dGdHS2hxZXRKZmhrSkFCdzdhX0NRZ0N0Q2IyckpsYmVfZ1pKdkRCTTdqY3FZdVBIRmRLTnM</guid></item><item><title>科学家说，这种受欢迎的饮食似乎可以减少牙龈疾病- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/this-popular-diet-seems-to-reduce-gum-disease-scientists-say</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;There's something rather special about the Mediterranean diet: already associated with a lower risk of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-diet-can-lower-genetic-risk-for-alzheimers-scientists-discover"&gt;Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/mediterranean-diet-linked-to-23-lower-risk-of-death-in-women"&gt;early death&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-food-choices-can-fuel-anxiety-and-depression-heres-how"&gt;poor mental health&lt;/a&gt;, and more besides, a new study links the diet to better gum health too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, carried out by researchers from King's College London and the University of Catania in Italy, involved 195 participants with an average age of 49, who were given a health check-up and quizzed on their &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-mediterranean-lifestyle-really-can-help-you-live-longer-study-shows"&gt;dietary habits&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those participants who stuck more closely to the plant-rich Mediterranean diet were less likely to have &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/gum-disease-isnt-only-a-problem-for-your-mouth-heres-what-to-know"&gt;gum disease&lt;/a&gt;, the data showed – especially those who didn't eat much red meat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-diet-helps-lower-dementia-risk-and-we-may-finally-know-why"&gt;This Diet Helps Lower Dementia Risk, And We May Finally Know Why&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, the healthier diet was also associated with fewer inflammatory markers in the blood – biological indicators that the body is under stress or being damaged. It's another health win for eating &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-diet-helps-lower-dementia-risk-and-we-may-finally-know-why"&gt;in the Mediterranean style&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings suggest that a balanced, Mediterranean-type diet could potentially reduce gum disease and systemic inflammation," &lt;a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/news/mediterranean-diet-could-reduce-gum-disease"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; periodontist Giuseppe Mainas, from King's College London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_174437" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-174437" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/MedDiet.jpg" alt="Mediterranean diet" class="wp-image-174437 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/MedDiet.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/MedDiet-621x415.jpg 621w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/MedDiet-600x401.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-174437" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Eat like the Mediterraneans – your gums might thank you. (&lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/green-salad-on-white-plate-d825JrXvun8"&gt;Mike Kenneally/Unsplash&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mediterranean diet gets its name from the part of the world where it's habitually eaten, and it favors fruits, vegetables, whole grains, and fish. &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ultra-processed-food-is-harming-mens-health-in-three-key-ways"&gt;Processed foods&lt;/a&gt;, too much dairy, and red meat are limited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to bear in mind that this study didn't track the participants over time, so it's just a snapshot of a link, without any proof of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Causality"&gt;cause and effect&lt;/a&gt;. That said, the association is strong enough to warrant looking into further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers suggest that compounds found in plant-based foods are likely to be working in the body to reduce inflammation, and that red meat works in the opposite direction. While &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/most-of-the-uk-predicted-to-have-dental-disease-by-2050-study-finds"&gt;severe gum disease&lt;/a&gt; (or periodontitis) is largely driven by plaque build-up, the body's immune response is thought to be a significant factor too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We observed that there may be a connection between periodontal disease severity, diet, and inflammation," &lt;a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/news/mediterranean-diet-could-reduce-gum-disease"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Mainas. "These aspects should be holistically considered when assessing the treatment for periodontitis in patients."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our research offers an important starting point that can lead to more research to better understand the relationship between food intake and gum disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers aren't suggesting that you can just change your diet around and forget about &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/you-re-probably-brushing-your-teeth-wrong-here-are-4-expert-tips-for-better-dental-health"&gt;brushing your teeth&lt;/a&gt; to ward off &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/most-of-the-uk-predicted-to-have-dental-disease-by-2050-study-finds"&gt;gum disease&lt;/a&gt; – but the foods we're eating, and the bacteria they encourage, could be more important than previously thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add in all the other benefits of eating the Mediterranean way, particularly when it comes to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-say-this-one-particular-diet-may-slow-the-decline-of-the-brain"&gt;protecting brain function&lt;/a&gt;, and there's a long list of reasons to get these kinds of foods onto your plate more often than not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dieting changes aren't always easy of course, but they can be a relatively affordable, accessible, and effective way of improving oral health – something that we know is a problem &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/oral-health"&gt;for billions worldwide&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our research shows the potential effect that a nutrient-dense, plant-rich diet could play in improving the nation's gum health," &lt;a href="https://www.kcl.ac.uk/news/mediterranean-diet-could-reduce-gum-disease"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; periodontist Luigi Nibali, from King's College London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Nevertheless, more investigation is needed to develop personalized approaches to help people manage their gum health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/jper.70016"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Journal of Periodontology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 01:00:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOaG5OZDFRbDYxSUZ3NHJaLWVHU0M5SnEwQ185MWp3bmhDTnFCQ28zem85TEd5WVh4ejgyU3hyZVV2SzNMTTZ3dnlsN0xSMDhKdlZIaFRmSUJENjB4eUwyZHRBeUNxbC0tQ3JrZ09KMXNQYS1GdUdkUTJxY0ljSmNSV2g4NFFfM3NVTUdzYVNaNmtqcTA</guid></item><item><title>有目的地生活可以保护你的大脑免受痴呆症的侵害，显示出巨大的新研究-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/living-with-purpose-may-protect-your-brain-from-dementia-shows-huge-new-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_213984" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-213984" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-213984" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/Women-friends-biracial-seniors-success-by-Fellipe-Ditadi-for-Unsplash-RkpYFhi6Ro4.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/Women-friends-biracial-seniors-success-by-Fellipe-Ditadi-for-Unsplash-RkpYFhi6Ro4.jpg 1300w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/Women-friends-biracial-seniors-success-by-Fellipe-Ditadi-for-Unsplash-RkpYFhi6Ro4-326x175.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/Women-friends-biracial-seniors-success-by-Fellipe-Ditadi-for-Unsplash-RkpYFhi6Ro4-1024x551.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/Women-friends-biracial-seniors-success-by-Fellipe-Ditadi-for-Unsplash-RkpYFhi6Ro4-768x413.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/Women-friends-biracial-seniors-success-by-Fellipe-Ditadi-for-Unsplash-RkpYFhi6Ro4-696x374.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/Women-friends-biracial-seniors-success-by-Fellipe-Ditadi-for-Unsplash-RkpYFhi6Ro4-1068x574.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/Women-friends-biracial-seniors-success-by-Fellipe-Ditadi-for-Unsplash-RkpYFhi6Ro4-781x420.jpg 781w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/Women-friends-biracial-seniors-success-by-Fellipe-Ditadi-for-Unsplash-RkpYFhi6Ro4-530x285.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 1300px) 100vw, 1300px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-213984" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;By Fellipe Ditadi / Unsplash+&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;By Lisa Howard&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previous studies into regions of the world where people tend to live longer has shown that having a sense of purpose in life may help people live longer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, new research from the University of California in Davis shows that having a sense of purpose in life may have another benefit as people age: reducing the risk of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.ajgponline.org/article/S1064-7481(25)00354-9/abstract" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;new study, published in&lt;/a&gt; the American Journal of Geriatric Psychiatry, followed over 13,000 adults aged 45 and older for up to 15 years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers found that people who reported a higher sense of purpose in life were about 28% less likely to develop cognitive impairment—including mild cognitive impairment and dementia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protective effect of having a purpose was seen across racial and ethnic groups. It also remained significant even after accounting for education, depression, and the APOE4 gene, which is a known risk factor for Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Our findings show that having a sense of purpose helps the brain stay resilient with age,” &lt;a href="https://health.ucdavis.edu/news/headlines/having-a-sense-of-purpose-may-protect-against-dementia/2025/08" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said Aliza Wingo&lt;/a&gt;, senior author and professor in the UC Davis Department of Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences. “Even for people with a genetic risk for Alzheimer’s disease, sense of purpose was linked to a later onset and lower likelihood of developing dementia.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants were not specifically asked about the activities that gave their life purpose. However, previous studies on aging have found a wide rang of activities give older adults a sense of life purpose (sometimes referred to as “ikigai”).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Sense of Purpose Can Include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;• Relationships: Caring for family, spending time with grandchildren or supporting a spouse or friend.&lt;br&gt;
• Work or volunteering: Continuing professional work, mentoring or contributing to community causes.&lt;br&gt;
• Spirituality or faith: Religious beliefs, spiritual practices or involvement in faith-based communities.&lt;br&gt;
• Personal goals: Pursuing hobbies, learning new skills or setting and achieving personal milestones.&lt;br&gt;
• Helping others: Acts of kindness, philanthropy, caregiving or advocacy work.&lt;br&gt;
Purpose delays onset of cognitive decline&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers also found that people with higher purpose tended to experience cognitive decline later than those with lower purpose. On average, the delay in onset was very modest — about 1.4 months over an eight-year period, after considering the effects of age, education, depressive symptoms, and genetic risk. However, it is meaningful when compared to current treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“While medications like lecanemab and donanemab can modestly delay symptoms of cognitive impairment in Alzheimer’s disease, they come with risks and costs,” &lt;a href="https://health.ucdavis.edu/news/headlines/having-a-sense-of-purpose-may-protect-against-dementia/2025/08" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said Nicholas C. Howard&lt;/a&gt;, first author and public health researcher at UC Davis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Purpose in life is free, safe and accessible. It’s something people can build through relationships, goals and meaningful activities.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants in the study were part of the Health and Retirement Study, a nationally representative survey funded by the National Institute on Aging. All had normal cognitive health at the beginning of the study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers used a seven-item survey from the Ryff Measures of Psychological Well-being. Participants had six possible responses (from “strongly agree” to “strongly disagree”) for statements such as: “I am an active person in carrying out the plans I set for myself” and “I have a sense of direction and purpose in my life.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their answers were scored and averaged to obtain a well-being number between 1 and 6, with higher values indicating a strong sense of purpose in life. Their cognitive health was also tracked using a telephone-based test every two years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings support the idea that psychological well-being plays a key role in healthy aging, said Thomas Wingo, a co-author of the study and a professor and neurologist at UC Davis Health. Wingo hopes future studies will explore whether purpose-building interventions can help prevent dementia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What’s exciting about this study is that people may be able to ‘think’ themselves into better health. Purpose in life is something we can nurture,” he said. “It’s never too early — or too late — to start thinking about what gives your life meaning.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEND THIS HEALTH TIP to Friends and Family By Sharing on Social Media…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:22:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxPT0VmUkVHa0F0LUNyRWNOQW1jdHZmSGZaZzBUR25yV2NJc3dkcWF6VFpaRmlTQzVHZEJIdFJSbVExNjBNRlZqZHZYUDNISVBqUGNFb0U3a0o1clJYZmdSdG9OeDZpZDZlekwzdFFkdEYyaXdnMEhaTGJVenRvTW5KTG1qRzc2TnRlR3hBc0JYSzF2dEFXVkJQSEZISTAyLXhXa2h4dUROWlVQdHVSdjIw</guid></item><item><title>115个国家的HIV注射依赖于印度监管机构-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/india/hiv-jab-for-115-nations-rests-on-indian-regulators/articleshow/124199149.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;MUMBAI: There will be a dramatic shift in how the world prevents HIV and the timelines depend on how quickly Indian drug regulators act. A US-based pharma giant has granted royalty-free licences to four Indian generic manufacturers to produce lenacapavir, which prevents transmission by almost 100%, at $40 per person per year, roughly 0.1% of the original cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lenacapavir is an injectable drug whose protection from one jab lasts six months. The licensed manufacturers by Gilead Sciences include Dr Reddy's, Hetero, Emcureand Mylan. The first two have announced their pricing. The drugs are estimated to roll out in 2027. But, it could be much sooner or delayed, and what happens in India will impact local access as well as 115 low- and middle-income countries as these firms will be key exporters. Twenty-six additional such countries where people participated in crucial clinical trials are excluded from it as per licence terms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exports depend on registration and a certificate of pharmaceutical product from Indian FDA. Besides, there could be regulatory demand for local clinical trials despite strong phase-3 trial data from elsewhere. ""In that case, the delays could spill over in 2027,” said Leena Menghaney, a public health lawyer who has worked with advocacy groups such as Mumbai-based Sankalp Rehabilitation Trust, one of seven groups pressuring for global access to lenacapavir.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;” said Leena Menghaney, a public health lawyer who has worked with advocacy groups such as Mumbai-based Sankalp Rehabilitation Trust, one of seven groups pressuring for global access to lenacapavir.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Do you believe funding for HIV research should be prioritized over other health issues?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is another pathway to faster access. FDA could provide a waiver for local clinical trials on the grounds that HIV is an epidemic. India reports more than 60,000 new HIV infections annually. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is precedent for such a move. "Waivers have been given for HIV and TB drugs. These decisions are based on the results of phase-3 clinical trials in countries with very strong regulatory systems," Menghaney said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2015, the apex committee of the regulator Central Drugs Standard Control Organisation also granted a waiver of local trials for antiviral drugs against Hepatitis C. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if local production moves ahead quickly, access in India will be limited. National AIDS Control Organisation (Naco) has so far included only condoms as pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) in its HIV prevention programme. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been drugs similar to lenacapavir, although not on a par in terms of protection and cost, that were not included in the national programme. Naco officials had previously defended this position, saying condoms also help prevent the spread of other STDs and STIs, which increased in some countries when PrEP was introduced and condom use declined. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Dr Ishwar Gilada, an HIV specialist, said, "Bringing about behaviour change is difficult, but sex education and awareness are also part of Naco's responsibilities. For the first time in over 40 years, we have a way to control HIV's transmission by almost 100%. This will reduce the number of people requiring lifelong treatment." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ganesh Acharya, a city-based HIV-TB survivor, said, "Other such drugs so far have been needed to be taken monthly, are costly and offer relatively lower protection. Even condoms carry a risk of tearing. This drug could bring down new HIV numbers."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:47:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxQYmFFdi1fOUk3RndaSnhldVZZdHVGWEVHR19EaWNNSU84ZTA3eHhMWk92MUk4YjJSR3BhWVhua0FsOGdzcFRNd2N3aVMwdUJ4QkpBTjBYWGx1R09PMzJpTkVOZzZfR3IyOXdMNC0wUHNoNTExVUM1MXdhaU9JQkhYdGllaDBZeW1zM2FxN0xvYWNmUjdHbE5WWmRwWVhTai01UUtIcXpIaE43NmVzeUU4Mm5NZlhjTDF6bWc</guid></item><item><title>减肥注射如何使肥胖成为一个财富问题- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cre5xp83394o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;How weight-loss injections are turning obesity into a wealth issue&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-6 ioiEdf"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5b67/live/309c52d0-9867-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Nick Triggle profile image" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Nick Triggle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Health correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1ac1/live/450e0260-991e-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC A pound sign etched out with a tape measure " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;b id="three-years-ago,-a-fashion-editor-friend-returned-from-milan-fashion-week-bursting-with-a-story-to-tell." class="sc-d16436d-0 kPzeuB"&gt;Three years ago, a fashion editor friend returned from Milan Fashion Week bursting with a story to tell.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Most fashion editors stayed at the same hotel, she explained, and each bedroom had its own mini fridge. After checking out, en route to the airport, a stylist in her party cried out that he'd left "an important package" in his fridge and telephoned the hotel, pleading with them not to throw it away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Turns out he'd forgotten his Ozempic," my editor friend whispered. We were baffled. Ozempic?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Back then, Ozempic was not part of the common lexicon. But quietly, in certain circles, this injectable drug, which is licensed for the treatment of type 2 diabetes, was being prescribed privately and off-label for weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Flash forward to today and the picture is vastly different. "So many fashion people are on it," she tells me today. "And now they're very vocal." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Serena Williams, Elon Musk and Whoopi Goldberg have all spoken about using weight-loss injections. Some are now prescribed by the NHS, including Wegovy and Mounjaro, generating scores of headlines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Really, this should have made it a great leveller. In theory, anyone struggling with obesity can - without the expense of a private doctor - get help to manage their weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Only that's not the full picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3634/live/9b734b80-9ae8-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="AFP via Getty Images Models walk the runway wearing white and black
" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;AFP via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;'So many fashion people are on it and now they're very vocal,' says one London-based fashion editor (Milan Fashion Week is pictured)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Thousands of NHS patients are believed to be missing out. And with the NHS tightly restricting access, some working in the field warn a two-tier system around weight-loss drugs is developing - one that's benefitting the most well-off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Martin Fidock, who is UK managing director of Ovivia, which provides Wegovy and lifestyle support to NHS patients, claims that thanks to varying thresholds of eligibility in different regions, NHS prescriptions are a "postcode lottery".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;An estimated 1.5 million people in the UK use these drugs - but more than nine in 10 are believed to pay privately. Prices vary but it generally costs between £100 and £350 a month, depending on the dose and lifestyle support. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Then, last month, it was reported that pharmaceutical giant Eli Lilly was expected to &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cvg3ykg4jrro" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;increase the list price of Mounjaro&lt;/a&gt; by as much as 170%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;They have since done a deal for UK distributors, meaning rises are likely to be less, and the deal doesn't affect the cost to the NHS - but it has still caused concern in some quarters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's scary," says Brad, a tech company worker in his 40s. He has been taking Mounjaro for a year and worries he may not be able to afford to continue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I've lost 20kg and want to keep using it, but it's a lot of money. It's unfair."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f968/live/a8c3cda0-9ae8-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images (R) AFP via Getty Images (L) Two images of Elon Musk" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images (R) AFP via Getty Images (L)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Wegovy was called the 'Viagra' of weight-loss drugs - the huge interest around it is partly fuelled by social media buzz and celebrity users, including Elon Musk&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Nutritionists and GPs I spoke to have also expressed concerns about the broader system, and in particular whether existing health inequalities could worsen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We cannot allow good health to become a luxury for the wealthiest by limiting access to weight-loss drugs to those who can pay privately," argues Katharine Jenner, executive director of Obesity Health Alliance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;So could it really be that weight-loss injections - for all of their benefits - are turning obesity into a wealth issue?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;The NHS 'postcode lottery'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Weight-loss drugs have been available on the NHS for some time, but the landscape changed significantly with the introduction of some newer medications - among them, semaglutide, marketed under the brand name Wegovy, and tirzepatide, sold as Mounjaro.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Wegovy was first prescribed for obesity by the NHS in 2023, while Mounjaro followed earlier this year. They work in part as an appetite suppressant by mimicking a hormone, which makes people feel fuller. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Studies have suggested patients can lose as much as a fifth of their body weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;They are licensed for people with a BMI of 27 or more for those with a health condition or above 30 for those without (adjusted for certain ethnic groups). But tougher NHS criteria are being applied, and in England and Wales the drugs are mostly restricted to those with a BMI of over 35.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Plus there are more restrictions too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For Wegovy, local areas are making their own decisions on access.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Martin Fidock claims that in recent months a third of regional health boards have increased the BMI threshold, which he says has resulted in fewer people being able to get it. (The BBC has been unable to verify this data.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A spokesperson for Novo Nordisk, the pharmaceutical giant that makes Wegovy, told the BBC it is "concerned about the growing disparity" in access to NHS specialist weight management services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"This has led to a large proportion of people needing to pay out of pocket, an option which is out of reach in areas of depravation where obesity rates are significantly higher."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;NHS England has said the differences could be related to different levels of need and other providers being more active in certain regions, but confirmed it was up to local areas to decide how much to spend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0ac0/live/0750dec0-9af9-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Reuters Blue Ozempic injection pens lined up" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Reuters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;While Ozempic is intended for those with type 2 diabetes, Wegovy is prescribed specifically for weight loss&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;For Mounjaro, NHS England has started it for people with a BMI above 40 who also have certain health conditions. The NHS roll-out officially began in June, but a report published earlier this month suggests that not all general practices had started offering it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Just 18 out of 42 NHS boards across England confirmed that they'd begun prescribing it in line with the roll-out plan, according to data obtained by freedom of information requests published in the BMJ. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The NHS has previously said it is supporting the phased rollout for eligible patients and that "these represent brand-new services in primary care that are being established and scaled up over time".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But Mr Fidock believes we are seeing a "postcode lottery".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We have got an obesity epidemic and these drugs provide us with an opportunity to tackle it in a way we have never been able to do before. But your ability to benefit is dependent largely on whether you have the means to pay."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Adding to the challenge is the fact that more people from deprived areas struggle with obesity in the first place: more than a third of people in the most deprived areas are obese – twice that of more affluent neighbourhoods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Beyond the physical health risks - and there are many, including higher risks of cancer and heart disease, plus mental health problems - there may be social consequences too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;One US study found that obese men with a bachelor's degree earn 5% less than their thinner colleagues, while those with a graduate degree earn 14% less. For obese women it is worse still, earning 12% and 19% less respectively, based on data concerning 23,000 US workers, published in The Economist in 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;NHS GP Matthew Calcasola, who is also involved in a service Get a Drip, which offers weight-loss drugs privately, has his own concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We're concerned health inequality will build," he says. "GPs worry about this."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Private patients priced out&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Meanwhile, a booming private market has emerged. Sara de Souza, a business analyst from Nottingham, is among those delighted that it has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Following the birth of her son Vito in 2023, she put on 30kg. "I got to 96kg," she recalls. "Me and my husband both got into bad habits. We were so busy, we were eating junk food and having chocolates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I was always tired and struggled to pick up my baby. But I just couldn't lose the weight."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Sara tried dieting and went to see her GP who referred her to a lifestyle diet and activity programme. But still the pounds stuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At her heaviest her BMI was 37.5, but she wasn't eligible for NHS access and paid £200 a month for the drug through an app called Juniper, which also gave her diet and lifestyle advice. Within a year she had lost the full 30kg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Sara says the cost didn't impact her. 'Even if it had, I'd have carried on, because of the benefits'&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It completely changed my life. I felt like a new person, alive again. It's not just how I look, it's how I feel and being able to keep up with my son."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Sara says the cost didn't impact her. "Even if it had, I'd have carried on, because of the benefits."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Not everyone feels the same. Some 18% of overweight Britons would be willing to pay for weight-loss drugs - but if they were available on the NHS, 59% said they would be keen on using them, according to new polling by communications agency Strand Partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And some of those willing to pay privately fear they could find themselves being priced out following the proposed price spike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/db9c/live/e3617910-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A pen prepared for weight loss injection 
" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;'Some people can't move on to the higher doses because of cost,' says the UK head of an online pharmacy, speaking about weight-loss drugs in general&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If I'd had to pay £300 or even more, I would have really struggled to afford it," says Pete Beech, 57, from Southampton. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He weighed 18 stone and paid £160 a month for a prescription of Mounjaro to help him lose weight to qualify for an ultrasound treatment as part of his treatment for prostate cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The way the NHS is rationing these drugs has consequences beyond just obesity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;James O'Loan, head of online pharmacy Chemist 4 U, has already observed some people stretching themselves financially to get hold of weight-loss drugs - some have asked for payment plans, which they cannot offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Some people can't move on to the higher doses because of cost," he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5646/live/bad05750-991e-11f0-858a-a904eacbef23.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images for ESSENCE Serena Williams looking serious with her hands on her hips
" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images for ESSENCE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Serena Williams has spoken out about using weight-loss drugs - she says, to lift 'stigma' around them&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Then there are concerns about a weight-loss drug black market, or unscrupulous dispensing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Some services are desperate to dispense the stuff and don't care what happens," claims Professor Richard Donnelly, editor of medical journal Diabetes, Obesity and Metabolism. "People are just asked to fill in a quick questionnaire. There's no proper medical assessment or follow up."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He also stresses that they should not be seen as a quick fix. "They're not there to lose a bit of fat around the tummy."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Whilst generally well tolerated, there are risks of certain side effects — including nausea, constipation and diarrhoea. A study into potential serious side effects of weight loss jabs has also been launched after hundreds of people reported &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/c4ged0r1n3wo" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;problems with their pancreas. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The NHS advises people never take a medicine for weight management if it has not been prescribed for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'Not a magic bullet'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Some argue that the answer is, simply, to widen NHS access. The issue, of course, comes in part down to cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Michael Shah, senior analyst at Bloomberg Intelligence, believes that this could start to resolve itself in time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There are more than 160 weight-loss drugs in clinical development," he says. Once available, he predicts that the competition could push costs down across the board.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"NHS bargaining power should improve as additional players and treatments enter the space."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/3e25/live/d8db5b70-9ae8-11f0-b741-177e3e2c2fc7.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Kevin Mazur/WireImage via Getty Images Whoopi Goldberg attending the 90th Annual Academy Awards " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Kevin Mazur/WireImage via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Actress Whoopi Goldberg has said: 'I weighed almost 300 pounds... I was on all this stuff and one of the things that has helped me drop the weight is Mounjaro'&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Earlier this year the Tony Blair Institute suggested that the drugs should be offered to everyone with BMIs over 27, arguing that it costs even more to deal with the consequences of obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Obesity is estimated to cost the economy £98bn a year, according to research commissioned by the think tank, once you take into account lost productivity as well as the NHS treatment costs and the impact on the individual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The Institute suggests a means-tested system with those entitled to free prescriptions getting it free and others self-funding or encouraging employers to share the cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;NHS England has said it is looking at an option to "accelerate roll out to even more people in the future". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But it also pointed out that weight loss drugs should not be seen as a "magic bullet".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Are we medicalising a social issue?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;All of this begs a broader question - that is, in medicalising debates around tackling obesity, do we risk overlooking the wider social issue?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"By thinking we have a treatment for obesity we lose focus and stop thinking about the more difficult issues around the food industry and regulation, which are the root cause of this," warns Greg Fell, president of the Association of Directors of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I do have concerns about equity of access," he adds. "But I think the NHS has carefully thought about this and probably is, more or less, in the right place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cbce/live/857e5740-9af5-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Bin overflowing with junk food packaging" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Obesity was rare In post-war Britain due to food shortages - there wasn't the convenience food culture of today either&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In post-war Britain, obesity was rare due to food shortages and physically demanding lifestyles – lower-income groups were more likely to suffer from malnutrition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Only since the 1980s have obesity rates risen across all social classes, with a growing disparity between rich and poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It is driven by several interconnected factors. Katharine Jenner argues there needs to be more done to address one of them in particular: our "broken food system".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"People in poorer areas are surrounded by junk food advertising, more unhealthy takeaways, and face bigger barriers to buying healthy food," she says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Without investment in prevention, health will get worse, inequalities will widen, and the costs will fall on all of us."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;How to effectively achieve that is perhaps the biggest question of all. But whatever the answer - and regardless of whether the onus really should be on the state or as others argue, the individual - it runs far deeper than the cost of a weight-loss jab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We live in a society that prizes freedom of choice and expression, values material wealth and tolerates vast inequality," argues Chris Rojek, sociology professor at City St George's, University of London. "In such a system, casualties are inevitable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It would be naïve — or even pious — to claim we can simply solve this. The answer is complex and touches the very fabric of our society."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;i id="top-picture-credit:-onzeg/-getty-images" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;Top picture credit: Onzeg/ Getty Images&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/bbcindepth" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;&lt;i id="bbc-indepth" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;BBC InDepth&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="is-the-home-on-the-website-and-app-for-the-best-analysis,-with-fresh-perspectives-that-challenge-assumptions-and-deep-reporting-on-the-biggest-issues-of-the-day.-and-we-showcase-thought-provoking-content-from-across-bbc-sounds-and-iplayer-too.-you-can-send-us-your-feedback-on-the-indepth-section-by-clicking-on-the-button-below." class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt; is the home on the website and app for the best analysis, with fresh perspectives that challenge assumptions and deep reporting on the biggest issues of the day. And we showcase thought-provoking content from across BBC Sounds and iPlayer too. You can send us your feedback on the InDepth section by clicking on the button below.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 23:02:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBaeWZjd25EamxWeldhZFlSamd4R3o1Z0dHVHczVUMxRlpRQzIyMjdUODVHYmtremJpTEVDUWtXX0tKV29BcTRGZkVGYXdrbEwyRnNpRkFYb1ZpUdIBX0FVX3lxTFBxTk9NR0pwdFVnN29PeVdFd2xXSm40Y2VxWUZEeExRRGxPVXJNeFgzeEw4enhfY3p1YVlUc2ExdnhTZHpSTlJ0dXZ3dV93eGFFV2lvRXVpQjFzd1d4dTdz</guid></item><item><title>自1990年以来，印度的癌症病例增加了26 ％ ，死亡人数增加了21 ％ -印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/india/cancer-cases-in-india-up-by-26-deaths-21-since-1990/articleshow/124202330.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW DELHI: The incidence of cancer in India has gone up by 26%, from 84.8 per 1 lakh population in 1990 to 107.2 in 2023, according to a new study. Published in The Lancet, it shows deaths due to cancer increased by 21% during this period, despite advances in treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In comparison, both incidence and mortality have declined significantly in US and China over the 33-year period. The reason behind this is strong tobacco control, universal vaccination and organised screening in these two countries, Dr Abhishek Shankar, radiation-oncologist at AIIMS Delhi, said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;India, he added, continues to fare poorly on both counts because of persisting risk factors such as high use of tobacco, obesity and infections, coupled with limited access to early detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Early Detection Saves Lives: Watch for These Ovarian Cancer Symptoms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Study links 4.3m &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;cancer deaths&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt; in 2023 to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;modifiable risk factors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Evidence-based strategies like HPV and Hepatitis-B vaccination, mammography, lung cancer screening with low-dose CT, and colonoscopy screening, and timely treatment remain uneven or inadequate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For India to reverse its trajectory, we must urgently strengthen risk prevention strategies, expand evidence-based screening programmes and integrate cancer care into its universal health coverage agenda," Shankar said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study's lead author Dr Lisa Force from the Institute for Health Metrics and Evaluation (IHME), University of Washington, said, "Cancer remains an important contributor to disease burden globally and our study highlights how it is anticipated to grow substantially over the coming decades, with disproportionate growth in countries with limited resources." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;She added that despite the clear need for action, cancer control policies and implementation remain under-prioritised in global health, and there is insufficient funding to address this challenge in many settings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study shows cancer incidence has declined by 19% and 20% in China and the US, respectively, between 1990 and 2023, while their mortality rates attributable to cancer has also seen a robust decline - 43% decline in mortality due to cancer in China and 33% in the US. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study estimates that 42% (4.3 million) of the estimated 10.4 million cancer deaths in 2023 were attributable to 44 potentially modifiable risk factors - presenting an opportunity for action. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Behavioural risk factors contributed to the most cancer deaths across all country income levels in 2023, especially tobacco use which contributed to 21% of cancer deaths globally. Tobacco was the leading risk factor in all country income levels except low-income countries, where the leading risk factor was unsafe sex (linked to 12.5% of all cancer deaths)," the study said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A parliamentary committee report tabled in 2023 suggested raising taxes on tobacco products in India to make them less affordable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Committee recommends the ministry (health) to pursue with the department of revenue to expedite the decision on raising taxes on tobacco products," it said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;It also stressed upon the need to link the Population-Based Cancer Registry to Ayushman Bharat Digital Mission to get real time data on cancer patients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mission is a key health initiative by the govt which aims at providing digital health IDs for all Indian citizens to help hospitals, insurance firms, and citizens access health records electronically when required. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most cancer cases in India are detected in late stages leading to poor prognosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The parliamentary committee suggested that the issue of screening for cancer should be taken up at 'Jan Aandolan Pace', a mass movement to fight against cancer by timely screening. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A day in a month may be fixed for cancer screening on the lines of reproductive and child health," the parliamentary committee suggested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 22:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxPV2REUVNqUUpQdXRmLVVwN1pSLVk1cV92Qy1VTUJwajdUZVBZcXU5c2VVU1JzUXB2VTQtcEpIalo0aUV4NEtMTFVFWkp6SUxtTE5FbTRrWUF4M2FjZklRRkZER0FDWnFpZk5iZy13c3o3U2V0LWNmbnJDdEZPb2VEODg2d0pGMkhFSk1qMjIxZTYzVzhXckNrenZRX0s2LUhsQk1WbUxYaGp1VW0zeVFvWk5Bd19GWjFjeXBV</guid></item><item><title>如何避免今年冬天生病：提高免疫力的12种方法-泰晤士报</title><link>https://www.thetimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/article/how-not-to-get-sick-this-winter-2s93cs7jj</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Are you ready for winter? Braced for a dip in mood and a deluge of leaves on sodden streets that can make leaving the house for work, let alone that morning run, feel daunting? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The health secretary, Wes Streeting, recently said the NHS would hold “war game” exercises to prepare for the surge in seasonal illnesses, in the hope of avoiding yet another year of chaos in which staff at the beleaguered health service cannot cope with demand. “We’re doing everything we can to stop history repeating itself,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;While we might be wise not to hold our breath, there is plenty we can do ourselves to strengthen our immunity and protect ourselves from the health challenges winter presents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="paywall-EAB47CFD"&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;As the weather cools and daylight hours diminish, the lure of the couch grows stronger. But “exercise is definitely helpful to your immune system”, says Daniel Davis, professor of immunology at Imperial College London. Both cardiovascular and weight training increase the number of neutrophils, white blood cells important to help fight infection. These, Davis explains, send out “a web-like structure made of DNA and proteins that can capture bacteria and lead to their destruction”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;When we exercise to extremes, however, our sleep and stress levels are also often affected, which “could dampen immunity”, he says. “There’s some evidence, for example, that Olympic athletes might be more susceptible to certain types of respiratory infections after very strenuous exercise.” There’s no “threshold” as to how much activity will help to keep illness at bay, he adds, but balance appears key. The NHS suggests 150 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic activity a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/strength-training-midlife-weight-workout-exercises-zd6vmqx09" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to start weight training in midlife&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="4.4"&gt;&lt;div id="ed8f1bb0-886e-4211-88ee-b69ac93ad502"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__FullWidthImg-sc-4v1r4q-4 jGJovF"&gt;&lt;div class="responsive__FullWidthCaptionContainer-sc-1io40fc-3 hADFiz"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;Confronting the elements boosts physical and mental health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;GETTY IMAGES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;2. And don’t give up on outdoor exercise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Braving the elements “can improve mental and physical resilience”, says the personal trainer Kate Rowe-Ham, author of &lt;i&gt;Owning Your Menopause&lt;/i&gt;. “I love a rainy run.” She recommends joining a running club, which is not only safer than running alone but provides accountability, and adds: “Lots of clubs have a lit track to make running after dark easier.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;However, trainers with good tread are essential for muddy, wet terrain. Last year a systematic review into falling and older adults found that the winter months led to an increase in the incidence of falls. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“Trainers don’t have to be flashy or expensive but protecting your ankles is key,” says Rowe-Ham, who adds that now is a good time to start practising your balance ahead of January icy snaps. “Balance on one leg for 20 seconds every day. Repeat on the other leg. Adding in ankle circles, slowly rotating your elevated foot, improves mobility, which will help you withstand unstable ground.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/outdoor-workout-make-you-fitter-exercises-hcd95v0rm" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Green exercise: why an outdoor workout will make you fitter and slimmer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;3. Be careful about comfort eating&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;That packet of biscuits won’t eat itself but it doesn’t mean you have to. The desire to comfort ourselves with stodge, and a lower availability of fresh produce in the shops in autumn and winter, means that “we have a less diverse microbiome and that’s thought to make our immune system more vulnerable”, says the nutritionist Dr Megan Rossi, aka the Gut Health Doctor. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Adding excess weight can also weaken the immune system. A study in the journal Frontiers in Endocrinology this year found that overweight and obese people had more than a 10 per cent higher chance of developing chronic infectious diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Rossi suggests increasing your intake of fibre, which triggers the gut to produce the hormone GLP-1 to regulate appetite without weight loss jabs. She also suggests adding variety to your diet by using frozen food, such as berries and spinach, to keep our microbiome healthy or adding a can of legumes like chickpeas or butter beans to a soup for a lunch that “contain prebiotics that feed your gut microbes”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A sensible dinner choice would be oily fish such as mackerel that “supports our immune system”, Rossi says. Meanwhile, adding probiotics-rich kefir yoghurt to breakfasts and desserts will improve gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/life-style/health-fitness" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read more expert advice on healthy living, fitness and wellbeing&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;4. And go easy on the alcohol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;As the evenings draw in, the temptation for “wine o’clock” to start earlier might be strong but alcohol makes the gut lining more permeable, which causes inflammation that weakens the immune system. Rossi advises a maximum of one or two drinks, ideally dark beer or red wine. These contain polyphenols that feed the gut lining. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="4.20"&gt;&lt;div id="dca5b02a-91dd-4305-8c4a-b33f7ec09632"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__PrimaryImg-sc-4v1r4q-3 hpWIYt"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 responsive__InsetCaptionStyle-sc-1io40fc-2 fkMBIX"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;div class="tc-view__TcView-nuazoi-0 fPjBcr"&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;Hygiene is especially crucial in winter&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="tc-text__TcText-sc-15igzev-0 kwFxdN"&gt;GETTY IMAGES&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;5. Wash under your nails and disinfect light switches to lower your risk of norovirus&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;The NHS warned that there were 18 outbreaks of norovirus — the most common form of gastroenteritis — in one month alone last autumn. To minimise your risk of catching it this year, be scrupulous with hygiene. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“Alcohol hand gels don’t work very well against it. Soap and water are much more effective, so aim to wash your hands regularly,” says NHS GP Deepali Misra-Sharp. “Use warm water, and rub all parts of your hands — front, back, between the fingers and under the nails — for at least 20 seconds. Be extra vigilant about keeping kitchen and bathroom surfaces clean. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“Using a household disinfectant or diluted bleach solution is more effective than general surface sprays, as norovirus is quite resilient. Pay particular attention to frequently touched areas such as taps, door handles and light switches.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/how-to-get-fit-in-20-minutes-t9bptph8k" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to get fit in 20 minutes&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;6. Get your flu jab&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Spending more time indoors makes it easier for viruses to circulate, while “cold, dry air can make the lining of the nose and throat more vulnerable to infection”, Misra-Sharp explains. She adds that reduced sunlight exposure lowers vitamin D levels, “which can play a role in immune function”. Little wonder cases of flu rocket in winter. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Older adults, people with chronic health conditions, pregnant women and children can have the flu vaccine free on the NHS, yet government figures suggest the majority don’t. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“I strongly recommend vaccines where eligible,” Misra-Sharp says. Those who aren’t eligible can get the jab privately at pharmacies for about £20. “For many the cost is worthwhile, particularly if you live with or care for someone vulnerable, or if time off work would be difficult.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;On the NHS pregnant women and eligible children can have their vaccinations now; eligible adults can have theirs from October 1. Private vaccinations can also be booked now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Also worth considering is a vaccine for RSV (respiratory syncytial virus), a common virus that infects the lungs and breathing passages, which is usually mild but can cause pneumonia. Last September the NHS launched its RSV vaccination &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/vaccinations/rsv-vaccine/" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;programme&lt;/a&gt; for pregnant women and those aged 75 to 79, or who turned 80 after September 1, 2024. In some regions, including Essex and Suffolk, you can get vaccinated at pharmacies as well as your local GP surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/eat-yourself-fit-diet-exercise-health-body-2023-6vcznh9jc" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to eat yourself fit — the foods that boost muscles and stamina&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;7. That Covid booster is still important too&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Lockdowns might feel a lifetime away “but Covid is still circulating and can cause a nasty illness even if you’re generally healthy”, Misra-Sharp says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;You’re eligible for a booster on the NHS if you’re over 75, a resident in a care home for older adults or have a weakened immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Evidence suggests exercising before a vaccination may make it more efficient. “Antibody levels are affected by exercise beforehand,” says Davis, who is the author of &lt;i&gt;Self Defence: A Myth-busting Guide to Immune Health&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;In 2023 a systematic review in SAGE Open Medicine found higher levels of cells that produce antibodies were observed in patients who had a vaccination &lt;i&gt;and &lt;/i&gt;exercised, rather than simply had a vaccination, and that consistent “moderate-intensity physical activity”, whether directly before a jab or not, potentially improved the vaccination response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;“Try and have a good night’s sleep before you have a vaccine,” Davis adds. A 2023 meta-analysis in the journal Current Biology showed that a lack of sleep “substantially decreases the response to antiviral vaccination”, and that being well rested both before and after a jab can “enhance and prolong” the response. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/what-the-top-health-experts-do-each-day-and-you-should-too-nf92jtrxr" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;What the top health experts do each day (and you should too)&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;8. Don’t obsess about vitamin C — but do take vitamin D&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;There’s no persuasive evidence that taking a vitamin C supplement will prevent you getting a cold, and while a 2016 review in the American Journal of Lifestyle Medicine revealed that adults taking 1-2mg of vitamin C daily recovered from a cold 8 per cent quicker, this recovery might have been due to other measures: more rest and sleep, for example, according to Davis, who emphasises that there is, however, “good evidence” that vitamins D and A support immune health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Eggs and oily fish are good sources of vitamin D; orange vegetables such as carrots and leafy vegetables like spinach are rich in vitamin A. One recent Slovenian study found 63 per cent of participants were vitamin D deficient in winter compared with 6 per cent in summer, so consider a supplement — a major analysis in the BMJ discovered that vitamin D supplementation reduced the risk of acute respiratory infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;9. Brighten up&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Colder weather and fewer daylight hours “have a significant impact on how we think, feel and behave”, says Suzy Reading, chartered psychologist and author of &lt;i&gt;Self-Care for Winter: Seven Steps to Thriving in the Colder Months&lt;/i&gt;. A dip in mood can increase the likelihood of illness — research in the journal Frontiers in Psychology found that stress and depression impair the immune system. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Reading suggests deploying our senses for cheer. For example, wear a bright red coat that lifts your spirit, fill your house with lamps and candles, and make sure you have clean windows to maximise natural light.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;10. The two bacterial strains that limit cold and flu symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Seventy per cent of our immune system lives in the gut, Rossi says. Two bacterial strains beneficial for limiting cold and flu occurrence and reducing symptoms are LGG (&lt;i&gt;Lactobacillus rhamnosus&lt;/i&gt; &lt;i&gt;GG&lt;/i&gt;) and BB-12 (&lt;i&gt;Bifidobacterium animalis subsp Lactis&lt;/i&gt;). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A study in the British Journal of Nutrition revealed that college students who received a combination of both for 12 weeks experienced a 33 per cent reduction in the number of days with upper respiratory tract infection symptoms compared with those who received a placebo. Neither bacteria is commonly in food. Rossi’s company, Smart Strains, sells a supplement with both, as do Optibac (available from Boots) and Bio-Kult (from Holland &amp;amp; Barrett).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;11. Keep in touch with yourself (and others)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Reading says that a somatic hold — a gentle, self-applied touch — will release tension and stress. To do it, she says, “Rub your hands together to create heat, then cradle your face in your hands.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;Maintaining your social life may require more effort during darker evenings but it is important — studies have linked social isolation to an altered immune response. “Can you meet friends for brunch? Stay connected via voice notes?” Reading asks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;• &lt;a href="https://www.thetimes.com/article/the-26-best-ways-to-keep-fit-over-40-lf7hhrg7h" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The 26 best ways to keep fit over 40&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="responsive__Heading2-sc-4v1r4q-9 bQMpmd"&gt;12. Switch to a ‘winter’ duvet&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;During sleep, levels of the stress hormone cortisol, which dampens the immune system, are low, allowing it time to repair. Studies have shown that people with disrupted sleep, such as night shift workers, are more susceptible to infections. And in winter we have “a biological need” to kip more, says the sleep expert Dr Neil Stanley — until the introduction of the lightbulb, we had little choice but to. So if you’re tired at 9pm, go to bed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;A cool room is important for a good night’s sleep because your body temperature has to drop by about 1C to trigger drowsiness. Stanley recommends 16-18C. A cool bed, however, is not necessary — the body loses enough heat through the head and face, so “having a thicker, 15-tog duvet in the winter is perfectly sensible”, he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="last-paragraph" class="responsive__Paragraph-sc-1pktst5-0 gaEeqC"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Professor Daniel Davis and Dr Megan Rossi will be speaking at &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://live.newscientist.com/" class="link__RespLink-sc-1ocvixa-0 csWvlP"&gt;&lt;b&gt;New Scientist Live at Excel &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;London in October&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 22:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNTlJGZmN6cmoycDFDV1NwU3VwT25hSWYwYk5jNkhoM2pOSWNzWUZBN3Q0al9MTm1BY1NidzNCeUY0RHNvNWdQQWcySndiSzN0N1lhb1JrX28xa0lNVkFVNmtRZE9qMVFSdnJQMk1WcndWaGdGbWxsa2dSaTkwS3dFdXpwLUNXTE5yRE9kcU9LdW1NcmZYZGhpR2FQUHhTc25kb2c</guid></item><item><title>犹他州诊所的慢性疼痛治疗可能是一些创伤后应激障碍患者的答案- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51381412/utah-clinics-chronic-pain-treatment-could-be-the-answer-for-some-with-ptsd</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people lightheartedly joke about "having PTSD" (posttraumatic stress disorder) after unpleasant life experiences. But those who live with this debilitating condition know that it's anything but a joke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://psychiatry.org/patients-families/ptsd/what-is-ptsd" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;American Psychiatric Association&lt;/a&gt; states that PTSD "is a psychiatric disorder that may occur in people who have experienced or witnessed a traumatic event such as a natural disaster, a serious accident, a terrorist act, war/combat, or rape or who have been threatened with death, sexual violence or serious injury."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms can be debilitating and interfere with everyday life. They include feelings of shame, fear, self-destructive behavior, intrusive thoughts, aggressive behavior, distressing dreams, trouble sleeping and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're part of the 3.5% of the U.S. adult population that suffers from PTSD, perhaps you've tried a variety of treatments but these symptoms keep cropping up, lessening your quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, now a &lt;a href="https://sterlingpainandspine.com/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;new treatment&lt;/a&gt; is offering hope to many who thought relief was impossible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt; Photo: ibreakstock/Shutterstock.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding the brain's fight-or-flight response&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When your brain perceives that you're in danger, it activates the fight-or-flight response, which is also known as the acute stress response. &lt;a href="https://www.verywellmind.com/what-is-the-fight-or-flight-response-2795194" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Verywell Mind&lt;/a&gt; states that this danger might be something physical, such as a barking dog, or it may be psychological, like preparing to give a big presentation. Sometimes it can be triggered by something that isn't a true threat, but your brain thinks it is. (Phobias are a good example. Someone with claustrophobia — the fear of confined spaces — may feel their heart start to race while riding in an elevator, for instance.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this can serve as a good defense mechanism to protect yourself in harmful situations, some people — including those with PTSD — may suffer from an overactive fight-or-flight response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;WebMD&lt;/a&gt;, "PTSD causes your brain to get stuck in danger mode. Even after you're no longer in danger, it stays on high alert. Your body continues to send out stress signals, which lead to PTSD symptoms. Studies show that the part of the brain that handles fear and emotion (the amygdala) is more active in people with PTSD."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this has been your experience, it's time to finally break the cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How a Stellate Ganglion Block (SGB) can ease your troubled mind&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, doctors and researchers have been working to find a good solution for people who suffer from PTSD. But developing an effective treatment that's safe and fast-acting (with few side effects) has proven difficult. One study published on &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34255448/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;PubMed Central&lt;/a&gt; reports that "success rates of PTSD treatments are generally variable, with remission rates that range from 30% to 40%." But now a new treatment called Stellate Ganglion Block (SGB) is showing promising results and might just offer the relief people are looking for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SGB is a simple outpatient procedure involving an injection into the base of the neck, where the stellate ganglion — a collection of nerves — is located. Since this is connected to the amygdala (the part of the brain that handles fear), it can temporarily subdue the fight or flight response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rti.org/impact/stellate-ganglion-block-new-treatment-ptsd" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;RTI International&lt;/a&gt; launched a randomized, controlled trial of SGB in 2014 and concluded in 2019 that the treatment "is indeed effective" after monitoring patient health outcomes for eight weeks after injections. The study also showed improvement in depression, distress, anxiety, pain and physical and mental functioning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"SGB is a true breakthrough in PTSD treatment," states the nonprofit research institute. "It is a powerful new option for people suffering from PTSD—one that may be more readily accepted by military service members and veterans, for whom the stigma associated with mental healthcare is often a deterrent to seeking treatment. We hope that our study is the first step to healing for millions of veterans and others for whom PTSD symptoms have long been a barrier to a better life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A different &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/23707834/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;PubMed Central study&lt;/a&gt; concluded that SGB "is a minimally invasive procedure with an excellent safety profile that may provide sustained relief of PTSD symptoms. The procedure may also provide benefit for those who are resistant to psychotropic intervention."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, the outlook is positive that SGB can be a safe and effective alternative for PTSD and anxiety treatment. The best way to find out if it's right for you is to &lt;a href="https://sterlingpainandspine.com/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;consult a medical professional&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why it's important to seek treatment right away&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you or someone you know suffers from PTSD or severe anxiety, it's important to get medical help as early as possible. Apart from the toll this condition takes on a person's mental health, it can also cause serious physical harm to the brain. &lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/mental-health/post-traumatic-stress-disorder-ptsd#:~:text=PTSD%20causes%20your%20brain%20to,active%20in%20people%20with%20PTSD." target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;WebMD&lt;/a&gt; states that PTSD can cause the hippocampus (the area that controls your memory) to get smaller over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early treatment improves your quality of life in both the short and long term, so don't put off getting the help you need! Schedule an appointment with &lt;a href="https://sterlingpainandspine.com/" target="_blank" rel="sponsored"&gt;Sterling Orthopedic Pain &amp;amp; Spine&lt;/a&gt; and take back control of your life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The opinions and conclusions expressed in this article are the sponsor's own and do not reflect the views or opinions of KSL.com. This Site Does Not Provide Medical Advice. Any content on this Site, such as text, graphics, images, information obtained from, or contained on this Site are for informational purposes only. The content is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always seek the advice of your physician or other qualified health provider with any questions you may have regarding a medical condition. Never disregard professional medical advice or delay in seeking it because of something you have read on this site! The owner and operator of this site do not recommend or endorse any specific tests, physicians, products, procedures, opinions, or other information that may be mentioned on the site. Reliance on any information provided by the Operator, including their employees, contractors or others appearing on the Site at the invitation of the Operator, or other visitors to the Site is solely at your own risk. If you think you may have a medical emergency, call your doctor or 911 immediately.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 21:43:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOa0staEc5UXF3ZDBlMlRENWVucmpkdjRmRjV3STA2UURFOGFLUWdjSVViZFB3dE5pbl9VMTVZQnJmSXYzbHRJZ0NzOXRKZm5FY3cwb0NoNGUtU3l0X0hVaDA4QzkxUVVzYS1mbzM0cDU1ZVFGdnZCSVlhQjZDM21LSDVUdkt6ZVdtenlPU3NOb1JBdmdLdTFLLThMS19EWE9UQmlKRFR5TmkzcmFtdXZkXw</guid></item><item><title>“科学家只是武器化的食物中毒” ：工程沙门氏菌摧毁癌症肿瘤，而医生害怕活的药物革命-能源记者</title><link>https://www.energy-reporters.com/news/scientists-just-weaponized-food-poisoning-engineered-salmonella-bacteria-destroys-cancer-tumors-while-doctors-fear-the-living-drug-revolution/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Energy Reporters</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:46:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAJBVV95cUxNZEpkOFdmUzExMVZad0FrRm42emduRHZ1TVRFbGhja0JFWHhDT1ZaZFRIZ3Y0SGs3b2p0UE1jZF90dEpIdW9NbHI5YUtIZjJjd0Q5UUZJNnBRekRkMzliQmdSREdMLUY4V1dfMlhpWXk4cDh4b2NuaEN1bjZFcVI4R1VqZk94Uk9HQjZIUDY1eHpSZGptTjNKTWgzeEN2ZUptanktVDQ5WE9PeWh4dnNVMTR5ZmNraEVieGdzTUVCazZQUGsyeG1xT25lNTJoMEpXVTdfNU4wT0Ztd2N0Z1U5SktjY0J6UzVZak9Bcmg5WnBXYTJWb0NHMHdTVHBpWmRjbElNNkFiOFB5bjFV</guid></item><item><title>H3N2流感在印度北部德里迅速蔓延- DW</title><link>https://www.dw.com/en/h3n2-influenza-spreads-rapidly-in-delhi-northern-india/a-74154442</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-tracking-name="rich-text" data-tracking-skip="true" class="c17j8gzx rc0m0op r1ebneao s198y7xq rich-text l1evdo4u blt0baw s16w0xvi rcjjkz7 w128axg5 b1fzgn0z"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Northern India, in particular the Delhi metropolitan region, is experiencing a significant spike in infections with the H3N2 strain of &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/influenza/t-71362030"&gt;influenza&lt;/a&gt; this autumn. There are about 46 million people in the conurbation around the Indian capital, which extends across many neighboring towns and districts in the states of Haryana, Uttar Pradesh and Rajasthan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://www.localcircles.com/a/press/page/delhi-influenza" title="External link — to a survey"&gt;to a survey&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; by the community-based social media platform LocalCircles, 69% of households in the area currently have at least one person with flu-like symptoms. Doctors say H3N2 is currently the predominant influenza variant in the region.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"The increasing numbers make it clear that the virus is circulating extensively," Dr. Rituja Ugalmugle, a consultant at Wockhardt Hospitals in Mumbai Central, told the newspaper Indian Express. Reports of growing numbers of cases are also coming in from other states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c44391" data-lang-code="en" data-id="68339716" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Who's at risk&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;H3N2 infections often start with a sudden high fever, shivering, a sore throat and a runny nose. Other symptoms may include a dry or productive cough, bad headaches, aching arms and legs, muscle pains, and severe fatigue and weakness. Some patients, particularly children, may lose their appetite, feel nauseous, or have gastro-intestinal problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Children, the elderly, pregnant people, and people with chronic conditions such as asthma, diabetes and heart issues tend to be hit hardest. In most cases, disease progression is that of a typical but nasty flu, and patients usually recover within a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Infection can lead to serious complications such as bronchitis, pneumonia, or a worsening of existing heart or lung conditions. Hospitals report that many people exhibit symptoms for an extended period or become so sick that they have to be admitted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Unlike the common cold or regular flu, H3N2, which is &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/bird-flu-swine-flu-a-guide-to-h5n1-viruses-and-beyond/a-69367069"&gt;a subtype of Influenza A&lt;/a&gt;, is often more severe and tends to last longer," Dr. Mayanka Lodha Seth of Redcliffe Labs told the Indian Express.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The infection becomes dangerous if the patient starts to have difficulty breathing or develops chest pains, their lips or nails turn blue, they become confused, or they are very dehydrated. Anyone experiencing these symptoms should get treatment immediately. They should also seek urgent medical assistance if they have a high fever after being treated for several days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span data-slot-id="Article_InContent-1" class="rich-text-ad"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Necessary H3N2 precautions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with the &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/covid-19/t-62123668"&gt;coronavirus&lt;/a&gt;, doctors recommend frequent hand-washing, masking, avoiding crowds, maintaining a balanced diet and getting the latest annual &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/new-vaccines-show-promise-against-seasonal-h5n1-flu-strains/a-71111141"&gt;flu vaccine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is no specific therapy for H3N2. Doctors will usually treat the patient's symptoms with bed rest, plenty of fluids, and medicine to lower the fever. Serious cases and high-risk patients may be given anti-viral medication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"The current seasonal H3N2 emerged from the 1968 influenza pandemic. It developed by combining with an &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/bird-flu-us-livestock-human-risk-2025/a-70988147"&gt;avian H3 virus&lt;/a&gt;," said Dr. Martin Beer, vice president of the Friedrich Loeffler Institut (FLI), Germany's Federal Institute for Animal Health. "So the adaptation processes took place a long time ago, and the 'avian' components, like H3, are from that time."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since then, numerous variants of the H3N2 subtype have circulated globally. They return periodically as waves of seasonal flu, often with regional genetic mutations. "Annual circulation and immune pressure result in the adaptation of seasonal flu viruses, and we respond to them with new vaccines. So these days, with the seasonal H3N2 virus, it's no longer a case of adaptation from avian to human, but of continual optimization within the human host," Beer told DW.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="placeholder-image master_landscape big"&gt;&lt;img data-format="MASTER_LANDSCAPE" data-id="74120168" data-url="https://static.dw.com/image/74120168_${formatId}.jpg" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" alt="Five red-colorized blobs of virus against a dark-blue background "&gt;&lt;figcaption class="img-caption"&gt;The H3N2 subtype of the influenza A virus under the microscope&lt;small class="copyright"&gt;Image: NIH-NIAID/BSIP/picture alliance&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1931312824000076" title="External link — study published in February 2024"&gt;study published in February 2024&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; examined changes in the receptor specificity of H3N2 influenza viruses from 1990 through 2000. It found that the binding behavior of the human H3N2 influenza virus to human receptors had changed over the last few decades, leading to an extension of the receptor-binding site. This extension makes it easier for the virus to adapt to new hosts or tissue, and can increase transmissibility. It also makes it easier for the virus to evade both &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/immune-system/t-66950642"&gt;immune defenses&lt;/a&gt; and treatments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Fifty years of evolution leave visible and comprehensible traces of adaptation," Beer said. "The first, and most important, shift happened 50 years ago, and led to the pandemic at the time. Since then, H3N2 has returned in seasonal waves and at differing levels of intensity. In some years, in some regions, it's very dominant compared to other influenza variants, which can lead to a correspondingly high number of cases."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assessments by monitors and the World Health Organization (WHO) indicate that there is &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://cdn.who.int/media/docs/default-source/influenza/influenza-updates/2025/202536_who-respiratory-virus-update_544.pdf?sfvrsn=34883378_1&amp;amp;download=true" title="External link — currently a low risk of a pandemic"&gt;currently a low risk of a pandemic&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, provided there is no significant change in the structure of the virus and its transmission pathways. However, influenza viruses such as H3N2 are capable of mutating very quickly, so officials are remaining vigilant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should H3N2 mutate in such a way as to become more transmissible from human to human, or able to evade existing immunity, it could spread suddenly and quickly, which could lead to an epidemic or pandemic. Scientists therefore keep a very close eye on influenza viruses so they can react to worst-case scenarios.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article was originally written in German.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DW</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:30:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNZmZya0d4bzROZUpjSWJBZG5KeHRBSUUzZmtfYUJtYjA3azdfMzdraGpOMTRiMzVIU3dhUUtOT3hEd1gwZ1I1RUwxSUpTdWFqc0F1SHAyWTdfOU9fejNLWFJfUnhGc3V0NVRNZVZxQUpQaXJrcEY4ZHlRZkJvbzBYdFpoQUZMemZOUWFrakNmQ1HSAZABQVVfeXFMTUI5N2tFUGVCWGpYRUdVUnhVb3V6RUtJdW51UXA2Q1NFZkJNel9VVW5vdlRUenNMU2E2RktJV0RVbnNmWFVZV29fZlVFaUdpWFRIWDdQQU1iUVphajBLTUJDbzB3b2FCaFYxTkxGUzdxUmE2THNxZ3dSemRTNU9wMlZhdlZ0SUxfSFdYeXJ6MEE1</guid></item><item><title>医生测试了一种针对新冠肺炎的常用药物。结果令人惊叹- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/09/250928095616.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A widely available and affordable drug has been shown to be effective in treating seriously ill COVID-19 patients, according to a new international study led by researchers at the Australian National University (ANU) in collaboration with King's College London.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study analyzed data from almost 500 patients hospitalized with COVID-19 across six countries. Patients who inhaled heparin were half as likely to require ventilation and had a significantly lower risk of dying compared with those receiving standard care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Heparin, a drug traditionally injected to treat blood clots, was tested in this study in an inhaled form, targeting the lungs directly. As well as acting as an anticoagulant, heparin has anti-inflammatory and pan-antiviral properties. Earlier research results showed breathing and oxygen levels improved in COVID-19 patients after they inhaled a course of heparin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers believe the drug could also be useful in fighting other serious respiratory infections such as pneumonia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Clive Page, Emeritus Professor of Pharmacology at King's who co-led the international study with ANU's Professor van Haren, said: "Inhaled heparin is anti-viral, anti-inflammatory and anti-coagulant. There's no other drug that has that unique combination. We know it's only a matter of time until the next pandemic, and there are still COVID-19 patients who get very sick. This is a great weapon to have up our sleeve."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the findings highlight the potential of inhaled heparin, further development is required before the treatment can be routinely adopted. The researchers believe the drug could also be useful in fighting other serious respiratory infections such as pneumonia, which can be caused by a range of viruses and bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Professor van Haren, the drug would also be helpful for those with a compromised immune system, such as cancer patients, when they experience a respiratory infection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Frank van Haren, lead author, ANU and Director of the Intensive Care Unit at the St George Hospital in Sydney, said: "It doesn't matter what kind of respiratory infection the patient is dealing with, the drug -- when inhaled -- will stop it from infecting the patient and from damaging the lungs. We're aiming to conduct another trial in Europe to confirm its effectiveness in fighting other common respiratory infections such as influenza and RSV. And because it's inexpensive, it's much more accessible for those from low-income countries"&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers are now also developing an improved formulation of heparin, specifically designed to be given by inhalation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research is published in &lt;em&gt;eClinicalMedicine&lt;/em&gt; and simultaneously presented of at the European Respiratory Society (ERS) International Congress in Amsterdam on Sunday, September 28, the leading annual gathering for respiratory research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 20:08:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE83ZlJiSWxZQ2RiclRRcEl1Tzh5dUNaWFRMZUNXN3JjLWE0VW1EbkVqSWZaaVE3dW5la2d2ekw4dlVoTFpWY0k1dWlOU0EyZXdRRXBrNjFwWDJRREd4RU5TUmFfNHNSbUtaTG1YQXB4RQ</guid></item><item><title>每天食用这种果汁可以帮助减少动脉斑块，保护心脏-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/daily-consumption-of-this-juice-could-help-reduce-arterial-plaque-and-protect-the-heart/articleshow/124193656.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pomegranate juice, particularly consumed with seeds included, may reduce arterial plaque buildup by a significant amount, based on observations made by&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DPGd43aDwwW/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt; Ryan Fernando,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; a clinical nutrition counselor. A study cited by Ryan Fernando, showed that participants who consumed pomegranate extract or juice blended with seeds daily for a year had up to a 35 percent reduction in carotid intima-media thickness (CIMT).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/19766760/?utm_source=chatgpt.com" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;CIMT &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;is an innocuous, non-invasive marker used to ascertain the thickness of the inner layers of carotid arteries responsible for blood supply to the brain. Any rise in the thickness of this artery is generally associated with atherosclerosis, plaque buildup, and cardiovascular risk like heart attack or stroke. The diminution of CIMT as seen reflects reversal or retardation of the arterial plaque formation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Clear your arteries: 7 tips for preventing heart blockages naturally&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The role of whole pomegranate&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most significant part of the research was the employment of the seeds. Unlike most commercial pomegranate juices that don't contain the fibrous seed component, the research was conducted on juice or extract with whole fruit, including the seeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5977444/?utm_source=chatgpt.com#s6" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Pomegranate seeds &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;are richly polyphenol, containing punicalagins and ellagic acid, both of which have been studied intensively for their antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties. These compounds are most likely to play a key role in suppressing the oxidative stress in arterial walls, ensuring healthy endothelial function, and slowing the development of plaque formation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Arteries and plaque buildup&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arterial plaque consists of cholesterol, fatty deposits, calcium, and cellular waste. This becomes hardened as time progresses, narrowing the arteries and denying blood circulation. As the plaque accumulates, the intima-media layer of the walls of the arteries thickens and may be measured with ultrasound-based CIMT scans. Thickened intima-media is an established early indicator of cardiovascular disease risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reduction of CIMT by 35 percent is an impressive finding, and that dietary intake of certain whole-food nutrients may influence long-term cardiovascular disease outcomes seems to be the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A natural approach&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ryan Fernando described the effect of compounded pomegranate juice as being like "Drainex in the human body," referencing its potential role to assist the natural ability of the body to dissolve arterial deposits. Although not an exact simile, the term is a reference to the fruit's potential detoxifying effect on the circulatory system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daily drinking of pomegranate juice containing seeds can be an adjunct strategy for those concerned with high cholesterol, arterial plaque, or overall cardiovascular well-being. It should be noted here, though, that these types of dietary changes need to be one facet of a broader heart-healthy lifestyle that includes regular exercise, balanced nutritional intake, and medical oversight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Practical application&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To reap optimal health benefits, pomegranate juice should be prepared fresh at home from the entire seeds. Juicing the arils (the red, juicy flesh of the seeds) with a small amount of water or lemon juice helps maintain the fiber and phytonutrients of the seeds. Filtered, sweetened commercial juices might not provide similar health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healthy dieticians and practitioners can, as a preventive measure, recommend whole pomegranate juice blend to their clients at risk for cardiovascular disease, particularly patients with higher values of CIMT or family history of arterial plaque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:04:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxQeG11TXYwS0FVVHZFUEQ4eDlYNlFlbm1DRXJ5MlEyalBIYURpMi1WQmNrcTZjM3NyZkpjR2ZEUjRWM09YbVktWmZzd3l2OUxjaW9nbHlWZzFJYmJsbFJ0aDl0dGx4Vy1VVGhTUTV2M0RKMUM0Z20tb2lvYnBsYko1ZzNscmkyR29NOTRCaVB4Qkx3U24zMlotX29IMXFBTmZDT1ZPT3h5NFlPMmd2YlJHaXppZ0JYMXA4azVsSWJ1aGQ5WUVsRUhta1h2SWM4REstRllwOE5GUi1mVnpVTy1hNkU3MEhLcFRSbGV3ejZpSlYzc0hHeS1JWkdXSFdsQ2dSRHctTnF30gGLAkFVX3lxTE1ibmtscjBlT3lmUGhHN29FTDJobHBhY0RTMUxOM0QxRkljNExoRlRQZHpWT0QwTENpUlRSLVNFS1h5enFBY05ad0s2OXg0b2w3cjhPOTJqVlAweTNiLVU5UndVdnU5OUREVGZnTGJxbWQ0Qkc5b09FTjAxMS0yYXFDZHJDZU8yTmd5Zmc1S2pDanpQa0dxVU45VVJKYUxSdTdwQTRNLXB2bmlDeXBQYmI1aUNIVUhaVHUzZUUySHc3TndrbFdnMzdiOFJOckhVTXhydEUtcjhSVHJfWXdlVldubWJRcktrSFM5MjMwaUFGT1FOVkdTa0ZOR2lDUWpKOVF4bXRqUjBMeGVNcw</guid></item><item><title>心脏病专家说，一个日常习惯正在悄悄地增加您患心脏病的风险- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/one-daily-habit-cardiologists-quietly-145000672.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to heart disease, there’s a lot you can do to lower your risk. &lt;a href="https://world-heart-federation.org/what-we-do/prevention/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:According to the World Health Organization;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;According to the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, 80% of heart disease is preventable by having healthy diet and lifestyle habits in place. Following an eating plan like the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/962840/marysauer/mediterranean-diet-plan/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mediterranean;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Mediterranean&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://parade.com/976803/marysauer/what-is-dash-diet/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:DASH diet;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;DASH diet&lt;/a&gt;, consistently getting enough sleep and having good stress management habits in place are all powerful ways to lower your risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you likely know, getting regular exercise is also important for preventing heart disease. &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/fitness/fitness-basics/aha-recs-for-physical-activity-in-adults" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The American Heart Association recommends;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The American Heart Association recommends&lt;/a&gt; getting at least 150 minutes per week of moderate-intensity aerobic exercise or 75 minutes per week of vigorous aerobic exercise (ideally a combination of both).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While all of these habits are proactive ways to lower your risk of heart disease, there’s one common habit that cardiologists wish people would &lt;em&gt;stop&lt;/em&gt; doing and it’s something you’re likely doing right this very second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/stethoscope" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🩺;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;🩺&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/healthy-now" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/pill" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:💊;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;💊&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Habit That Increases the Risk of Heart Disease Without You Even Realizing It&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if you maintain a heart-healthy diet, if you spend the majority of the day being sedentary, you are increasing your risk of heart disease. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7092398/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:According to a scientific study published in the American Journal of Lifestyle Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;According to a scientific study published in the &lt;em&gt;American Journal of Lifestyle Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, sitting for more than 10.6 hours a day leads to a major jump in heart health-related risks: about 40% more risk of heart failure and 60% more risk for cardiovascular-related mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/cardiologist-morning-habit-for-heart-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:'I'm a Cardiologist—This Is the One Thing I Always Do as Soon as I Wake Up in the Morning';elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;'I'm a Cardiologist—This Is the One Thing I Always Do as Soon as I Wake Up in the Morning'&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What many don’t realize is that prolonged sitting isn’t just a lifestyle habit, it is a cardiovascular risk factor in its own right. To put it plainly, sitting for too long every day increases your risk of high blood pressure, coronary artery disease, stroke and cardiovascular death even if you feel fine right now. The damage builds slowly and quietly over the years,” says &lt;a href="https://doctors.bannerhealth.com/provider/ramy-doss/512285" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Ramy Doss, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Ramy Doss, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; a cardiologist with Banner Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://drmonashah.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Mona Shah, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Mona Shah, MD&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; who is board-certified in cardiology and holistic medicine, also says that spending the majority of the day sitting is detrimental to heart health. She explains that sitting for a prolonged period of time&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36267589/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:leads to a decrease in nitric oxide;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt; leads to a decrease in nitric oxide&lt;/a&gt;, a chemical that helps regulate arteries. This, Dr. Shah explains, causes more oxidation in the body, which causes more inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/day-of-heart-healthy-eating-according-to-a-cardiologist" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:'I'm a Cardiologist, and This Is What a Typical Day of Heart-Healthy Eating Looks Like for Me';elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;'I'm a Cardiologist, and This Is What a Typical Day of Heart-Healthy Eating Looks Like for Me'&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On top of that, Dr. Shah says that &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK565813/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:being sedentary can lead to weight gain;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;being sedentary can lead to weight gain&lt;/a&gt;, which can cause type 2 diabetes, a health condition directly correlated with heart attacks and heart disease. “When we spend hours on end sitting, our body’s metabolism slows, blood flow becomes sluggish and enzymes involved in breaking down fats are less active. Over time, this increases the risk for high blood pressure, high cholesterol and elevated blood sugar levels, all known culprits in the development of heart disease,” says Dr. Doss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Can an Intense Workout Make Up for Sitting All Day?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no debate that spending the majority of the day being sedentary is detrimental to heart health, but can you make up for it by doing an intense workout in the morning or evening? Both cardiologists say that this can help, but it can’t undo the damage entirely. “Working out or exercising once a day of course is going to help, however, it mitigates risk by only a little,” Dr. Shah says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Doss says to think of it this way: “If you were to smoke a cigarette in the morning, then eat healthy the rest of the day, would that completely cancel out the harm from the cigarette? Probably not. Similarly, if you exercise hard for an hour but then sit for 10 to 12 hours straight, the benefits of that workout are being partially undone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/how-many-minutes-should-you-walk-per-day-to-boost-heart-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Exactly How Many Minutes of Walking You Need To Do Per Day To Boost Heart Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Exactly How Many Minutes of Walking You Need To Do Per Day To Boost Heart Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Shah says that NEAT (non-exercise activity thermogenesis) plays a major role in heart health. She explains that running errands, housework, yard work and going for a walk are all forms of NEAT, which supports heart health by improving blood flow and lowering blood pressure, cortisol and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both cardiologists emphasize that exercise is great, but it’s not a complete antidote to sitting. “Research has shown that even individuals who meet or exceed the recommended 150 minutes of moderate-to-vigorous physical activity per week still have higher cardiovascular risk if they sit for long, uninterrupted periods throughout the day,” Dr. Doss says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ways To Work More Movement Into Your Day&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that you know why it’s important to consistently move your body throughout the day comes the big question: How can you make it happen? Both cardiologists say to think about ways to increase your NEAT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, Dr. Doss says that taking walking meetings and phone calls, parking farther away from entrances, doing squats when brushing your teeth and taking the stairs instead of the elevator are all ways to increase your NEAT. He also recommends setting a timer to take a two-minute movement break every 30 minutes or one hour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The key is consistency. Think of movement as something to sprinkle throughout your day, not just something you do in a single block of time. The heart thrives when the body is in motion,” Dr. Doss says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Doss emphasizes that movement is medicine. “Heart health isn't just about big actions. It’s about small, consistent ones,” he says. Focusing on finding more ways to move your body now means a healthier heart in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Up:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/best-packaged-foods-for-heart-health-according-to-cardiologist" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: 'I'm a Cardiologist, and These Are the 2 Packaged Snacks I Swear By for Heart Health';elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Related: 'I'm a Cardiologist, and These Are the 2 Packaged Snacks I Swear By for Heart Health'&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sources&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally reported by &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/daily-habit-quietly-raising-heart-disease-risk" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt; on Sep 28, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Health &amp;amp; Wellness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Health &amp;amp; Wellness&lt;/a&gt; section. Add Parade as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=parade.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 18:00:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPYzFaWnl0UHZYNGg0VFV1VGJrUzdQMTI2M1h0bnRXUnBadzJ4ck12UTBQVkZrVGxrRFZsdTdWQnQ5YWpGbWpCT1hjcWFGclg1RjVUMC0tSHFuakhXXzAzUS1VeEZuS1BhdTZqZGEwTGJhSDhXdTZJZDA0Y2dXVU9GMFBNdkVXc09Z</guid></item><item><title>针对合并两种常见药物发出紧急警告- Metro.co.uk</title><link>https://metro.co.uk/2025/09/28/two-commonly-taken-drugs-increase-risk-heart-conditions-25-taken-together-24283698/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-overlay__content"&gt;
							&lt;p class="newsletter-overlay__close"&gt;
								&lt;svg&gt;&lt;title&gt;Close Overlay&lt;/title&gt;&lt;use xlink:href="#common-close" href="#common-close"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
							&lt;/p&gt;
							&lt;h4&gt;News Updates&lt;/h4&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;Stay on top of the headlines with daily email updates.&lt;/p&gt;

							
						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Metro.co.uk</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 17:04:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxQVjhrelJua3U3OWRzWGE2Nm9GRWQ1Z011LThtczdHNVNYZmdORmdjNm5tQWRCVFlhNmNDMVNkdVZTTGg3Y0lHdHlqMkZtU0l3a3hCTVQyMU9PT2NBdnQ1Z2ViR1RfNkJZeGt3V0xPVTRoZjBESHJ5SnNsQmlWT1FETXhJYmc2dVFHdEkyaWlncEJCTGlrbW82WjRiTVJGaDdwWERMMW00NWNvaE0wWHRSeWliSzA</guid></item><item><title>您是否患有2型糖尿病？您也可能有可能出现导致器官衰竭的致命疾病的风险-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15115921/type-2-diabetes-deadly-sepsis-organ-failure.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The one in 10 Americans living with type 2 &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-787423d0-958d-11f0-8923-256e77754a14"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; may be at double the risk of deadly sepsis, especially if they're under 60, a study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers in Australia analyzed data from 157,000 adults to explore the connection between type 2 diabetes and sepsis, an &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13813249/rise-silent-killer-sepsis-cdc-data.html"&gt;extreme reaction to an infection&lt;/a&gt; that causes the immune system to attack healthy tissues and organs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Using patient medical records, the team found twice as many patients with type 2 diabetes were hospitalized for sepsis than people without type 2 diabetes when they were first enrolled in the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And over the course of 10 years, nearly 2.5 times the participants with type 2 diabetes developed sepsis compared to non-diabetics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The diabetics in their 40s were at a 14-fold increased risk of sepsis compared to non-diabetics in the same age range. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Previous research has suggested diabetics may be at an increased risk because they are more likely to develop wounds that don't heal and can become infected, as high blood sugar damages blood vessels and immune functions needed to close cuts and sores. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High blood sugar also weakens the immune system, making it harder to fight infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, the researchers behind the new study found diabetics were more likely to be older, smokers, insulin users and have heart failure, all of which weaken the immune system and vital organs, making the body a target for sepsis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers in Australia found type 2 diabetics were up to 14 times more likely than non-diabetics to suffer sepsis (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Professor Wendy Davis, lead study author and professor at the University of &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/western-australia/index.html" id="mol-787a8c70-958d-11f0-8923-256e77754a14"&gt;Western Australia&lt;/a&gt;, said: 'An association between type 2 diabetes and sepsis has been noted in some earlier studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Our study, in a large community-based sample of adults, confirms a strong relationship even after adjustment for a number of potential risk factors and the competing risk of death from unrelated causes, which may have occurred in people at high risk of sepsis before they developed sepsis, thus leading to overestimation of the incidence of sepsis if ignored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The best way to prevent sepsis is to quit smoking, normalize high blood sugar and prevent the onset of the micro- and macrovascular complications of diabetes. That's why this study is important.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sepsis&lt;a target="_self" href="/health/sepsis/index.html" id="mol-6dee3a50-e854-11ee-9371-b5d203091076" class=""&gt; &lt;/a&gt;is a medical emergency that is caused by the body's extreme reaction to an infection. It occurs when chemicals released in the bloodstream cause the immune system to go haywire. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead of sending infection-fighting white blood cells to attack a foreign invader, it targets healthy tissues and organs such as the limbs and the lungs and kidneys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Infections that lead to sepsis most commonly start in the skin, urinary tract, lungs, or gastrointestinal tract, but almost any infection can lead to sepsis - starting in wounds as innocuous as paper cuts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But according to non-profit Sepsis Alliance, half of all cases are from an unknown pathogen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sepsis kills 350,000 Americans adults every year and 75,000 children. That's done death every 90 seconds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The mortality rate ranges from 10 to 30 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The latest sepsis data from the CDC has shown a slight uptick in sepsis deaths in the last three months, which experts warn could be due to a lack of cohesive sepsis strategy in the US&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Sepsis symptoms can closely resemble the flu, so look out for a very high or low temperature, sweating, extreme pain, clammy skin, dizziness, nausea, high heart rate, slurred speech, and confusion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The new study, which is being presented this week at the Annual Meeting of the European Association for the Study of Diabetes (EASD), looked at the medical records of 157,000 adults between 2008 and 2011 from Australia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Of those, 1,430 had type 2 diabetes. They were matched with 5,720 individuals who were not diabetic based on age, sex and where they lived.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The average participant age was 66, and 52 percent were men. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers tracked their health status until they had a record of sepsis, died, or the study reached its end in 2021. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They found two percent of patients with type 2 diabetes were hospitalized for or with sepsis compared to 0.8 percent of their matched counterparts without diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And during the average 10-year follow-up time, 12 percent of participants with type 2 diabetes suffered sepsis compared to five percent of their matched counterparts, a 2.3-fold increased risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The most notable difference was in diabetics ages 41 to 50, who were at 14.5 times more likely to develop sepsis than non-diabetics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Janice Holloway, 65, from Arizona, suffered an infection from an unknown pathogen, which quickly turned to sepsis - the first signs of which were a rash on the back of her leg and a high fever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Sepsis can affect patients of any age, including three-year-old Beauden Baumkitchner, who had both legs amputated after he scraped his knee and contracted staph bacteria &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers said people with type 2 diabetes were more likely to be older, male, indigenous, smokers, use insulin, have high blood pressure or have heart failure, all of which are independently associated with a greater risk of sepsis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to Sepsis Alliance, slow wound healing seen in diabetics also raises the risk, as contaminants that can seep into the wounds and infect the bloodstream, causing sepsis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And as glucose builds up in the blood, it attacks blood vessels, leading to poor blood flow to tissues. This makes it more difficult for blood to deliver oxygen to vital organs that are needed to fight infection. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Professor Davis said: 'Our study identifies several modifiable risk factors, including smoking, high blood sugar, and complications of diabetes, underscoring that there are steps individuals can take to potentially lower their risk of sepsis.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the researchers cautioned the study is observational and cannot prove direct causation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:29:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPU2ZZdS1LUXhyMEpWSnM5Uk5HZ1V5Tmg1eVpobmptR2Z3VV9BT3NkQVY2SW5yLUt6QnJzYjU4SV8wNjJqT01pS09zbmJ6MFZlVVZ4dDlSV0wydnVPbmlXZV9MNnFkdEVNZm9RMXpHVXRnenp0R0UwTVdmVlJJd1Etamg2akZBSm9DRUo3YVVlY3A0OGoyWUJPVS1qU19MN2E1ZWfSAacBQVVfeXFMT0dVWnB4WHRtSEVSWUhGdWVBQ2N1UnlhOEEwTTBFZUNHdVNjVjVyWnVTZ3hHZGNuU2dpVmlqWDJiYmNLR0xiTmkyU3hYbm5tOUtqNFZPVmJwQkpkc1JPekYxQm96Ym1FLXQ1NGlvVk1RcERZMmJlbzNkVFZrc3pPZmtWdjFEWGxndEZocHNvMEdDWnhwcXgxZmpEREdPaVdOa1JLTEZXUms</guid></item><item><title>家庭将男性的心理健康状况下降与疫苗接种后的斗争联系起来-特立尼达快报</title><link>https://trinidadexpress.com/newsextra/family-links-man-s-mental-health-decline-to-post-vaccine-struggles/article_920e50ed-f8a5-4dd4-a33f-00837d40cd49.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;• Lifeline has a toll-free number: 800-5588. They can also be contacted at 231-2824 and 220-3636.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 27-year-old man who had reportedly been battling depression and health complications since receiving a COVID-19 vaccine in 2020 was found dead at his family home in Marabella on Saturday, in what police have described as a suspected suicide by hanging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deceased, N’kosi Stephanas Layne, was discovered by relatives around 7 a.m. on Saturday. Officers from the Marabella Police Station were called to the scene shortly after 10:25 a.m., where they met family members and were shown to a small 10x10 bedroom downstairs in the house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Layne’s body was found on the floor, with a brown curtain tied around his neck, which relatives had reportedly cut from the ceiling in an attempt to save his life. He was dressed in grey shorts and was bareback. Police noted ligature marks around the neck, discoloration of the lips, and no visible signs of violence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to family members, Layne had suffered a steady mental and physical decline over the past few years, which they believe began after he received a Sinopharm COVID-19 vaccine in late 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His grandparents, Evangeline and Andy Rahim, along with his mother, Joann Cooper, and aunt, Nicole Lamont, told police that following the vaccination, Layne experienced a range of health issues, including chronic insomnia, severe headaches, and a pre-existing heart condition. He also reportedly fell into a deep depression that the family struggled to manage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In search of relief, the family said they turned to alternative medicine and had been consulting with a herbal practitioner based in Tacarigua. However, Layne’s condition reportedly worsened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The grandparents told police that the last conversation they had with him was around 3a.m. on Thursday. Two days later, they found him hanging from the ceiling. Emergency medical personnel were called, but he was already deceased upon their arrival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scene was processed by Crime Scene Investigator WPC Nysus, along with Sgt Lee, Cpl Downes, PC Forbes, and PC Madho.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                &lt;p id="tncms-region-article_bottom_content" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Trinidad Express Newspapers</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:17:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6gFBVV95cUxOSkJiT2FoaV82X2ppTG9PZThEUEpvdTFiX2dyZzItdk5NM0d3RFRYZHBRVkhyRGZsYzZ0OWtCZWxITHZkSGJadWdnWndnak1zRDN2ZUFOUFp0Y2FXOTVFVV9sT2VGWWo1S29QQUlraVo2VVNFVk5NQjdsUVdQOUJMNkRON1hkMEhGdl9Vc3dscUpKM1hYSTlMZVJLbHFvWE1MMEc4WTdBaEtsdENHRVZlREtuYmlibl9sSG9wQllUSE9qV19fLTVEYl9vaExEX3R3RVctMUhZcERtY2YwY3lMWUxNUkFCREdCalHSAe8BQVVfeXFMUDFMajdXN19WOW45NzlNTkt5VjFNTHIzMlItTC1HTVlqdE1XMTlCSk9NSl90X2NnQURwN1JJa2hwdEs1Nmx0LUsyUUpITnpscXpMSUp0aS1IVTBxWDhJc0pmT1JjMGhjNlhycG9jNmxLVW9LSEwzaExzZGt0SUotb29xXy1jYXJWcFg1MzAtT05oRm9JUWpwcmp5dEk0dDBNT0QtaEtlRFdQNFhTVVJKOWdWdWRhU3p0ZHVtcDhrS1RpV1NGM056MWlIa1pyZTJHTlVORk13a2NCUnA3eEs3dmRScHNTQVVIMy1HS1BhQXc</guid></item><item><title>土耳其：糖尿病发病率为何飙升？ - DW</title><link>https://www.dw.com/en/turkey-why-are-rates-of-diabetes-soaring/a-74125306</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-tracking-name="rich-text" data-tracking-skip="true" class="c17j8gzx rc0m0op r1ebneao s198y7xq rich-text l1evdo4u blt0baw s16w0xvi rcjjkz7 w128axg5 b1fzgn0z"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past 20 years, there has been a 67% rise in &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/diabetes/t-64920900"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; cases in &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/turkey/t-65619354"&gt;Turkey&lt;/a&gt;, meaning that overall prevalence has almost doubled, to more than 16% of the population. The &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://diabetesatlas.org/data-by-location/country/trkiye/" title="External link — International Diabetes Federation"&gt;International Diabetes Federation&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt; now lists Turkey as the country with the highest diabetes prevalence in the European region. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to data from the &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/world-health-organization-who/t-38396203"&gt;World Health Organization's (WHO)&lt;/a&gt;Global Health Observatory, the age-standardized &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/global-diabetes-rate-has-doubled-in-last-30-years-study/a-70774403"&gt;prevalence of diabetes&lt;/a&gt; in Turkey in 2022 was 16.6% of the adult population (aged over 18): 16% of men and 17.1% of women. In comparison, the EU average is about 7–8%. Rates in Turkey are thus almost double the European median.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These statistics follow a consistent trend. WHO data shows that diabetes in Turkey has been steadily increasing for the past 20 years. In 2002, the age-standardized prevalence in people over 18 was 9.9%. In 2008, it was 11.4%, rising to 14.1% in 2015, 15.9% in 2020, and 16.6% in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Around one in six people are now affected. The risk is particularly apparent in people over the age of 30. In this group, the prevalence is 22.2% — more than one in five. Rates in the European Union in 2022 were far lower: 2.7% in France, 6.6% in Germany, and 7.2% in Italy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c43449" data-lang-code="en" data-id="74114117" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Criticism of Turkey's health policy&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experts in the field say the responsibility for this negative development lies primarily with politicians. "The biggest problem behind the rise is food policy," says Kayihan Pala, a parliamentarian with the opposition Republican People's Party (CHP) who is also a professor of public health. "The health ministry is not living up to its responsibilities."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Pala's view, the main reasons for the increase in cases of diabetes are not genetic factors, but lifestyle and diet: lack of exercise, as well as the consumption of large quantities of carbohydrates and various sugars.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to a 2014 &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/oecd-organization-for-economic-cooperation-and-development/t-17437710"&gt;OECD&lt;/a&gt; report, around 45% of those diagnosed as diabetic knew nothing about their illness. This indicates that millions more remain undiagnosed or are diagnosed late. A conspicuously high number of people in Turkey are admitted to hospital with what's called uncontrolled diabetes, when poor management of the condition leads to various complications. This ratio was 402.6 for every 100,000 inhabitants — eight-and-a-half times the OECD average of 47.3.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The latest OECD figures from 2023 show no improvement. While the number of people with diabetes in Turkey remains far higher than average, the reverse is true for the statistics of successful treatment. Kayihan Pala says this demonstrates the failure of the Turkish health system. Early diagnosis and systematic control of the disease are urgently needed, he says, as is the political will to encourage changes in lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c43449" data-lang-code="en" data-id="74113857" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Survey reveals inadequate treatment&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A study done by the Turkish health ministry confirms the OECD's findings: Many newly diagnosed patients have high levels of blood sugar. How well the disease is kept under control also varies. A patient's age, gender, and region of living may all make a difference. Women and men in low-income regions are especially disadvantaged. Diabetes is therefore not just a medical, but also a social and economic problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pala says the situation will not change without improved medical care and better provision of medication. "Some patients have difficulty accessing their medications," he says. "And post-diagnosis communication between patients and doctors is often poor."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-vendor-cmp-id="c44391" data-lang-code="en" data-id="66496852" class="embed dw-widget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Obesity and ineffective campaigns&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pala believes combating &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/overweight-and-obesity/t-64918529"&gt;obesity&lt;/a&gt; would prove decisive in reducing the prevalence of diabetes, but that Turkey's strategies for doing this are insufficient. Although obesity is one of the most important risk factors, the measures being implemented by the health ministry are not yet providing permanent solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="vjs-wrapper embed big"&gt;&lt;h2 aria-label="Embedded video — Blood sugar diet — Smart weight loss or just hype?" class="headline"&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;g fill-rule="evenodd"&gt;&lt;path d="M14.114 7.599H13.5l.002 4.706h.601l4.582 3.25-.005-11.11zM11.084 4.444l-9.007.002-1.336.797.002 9.514 1.334.793 9.007.006 1.509-.799-.004-9.516z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;Blood sugar diet — Smart weight loss or just hype?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;video id="video-73807835" controls playsinline="" preload="none" poster="data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAAAEAAAABCAQAAAC1HAwCAAAAC0lEQVR42mNkYAAAAAYAAjCB0C8AAAAASUVORK5CYII=" data-id="73807835" data-posterurl="https://static.dw.com/image/73735295_605.webp" data-duration="05:38"&gt;&lt;source src="https://hlsvod.dw.com/i/dwtv_video/flv/igs/igs20250905_diaetBlutzucker_,AVC_480x270,AVC_512x288,AVC_640x360,AVC_960x540,AVC_1280x720,AVC_1920x1080,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8" type="application/x-mpegURL"&gt;&lt;source src="https://tvdownloaddw-a.akamaihd.net/dwtv_video/flv/igs/igs20250905_diaetBlutzucker_AVC_1920x1080.mp4" type="video/mp4"&gt;&lt;track src="https://www.dw.com/media/subtitles/73915946" srclang="en" label="ENGLISH" default&gt;&lt;p class="vjs-no-js"&gt;To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that &lt;a href="https://videojs.com/html5-video-support/" target="_blank"&gt;supports HTML5 video&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/track&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/video&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ministry has now presented an action plan for the next three years. It aims to encourage healthy eating, regulate canteens in schools and offices, and increase physical activity. Some 7.7 million people were assessed as part of a campaign entitled "Discover your ideal weight, live healthily." However, the results were not published, nor were regional variations in the prevalence of obesity made known.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a rel="noopener follow" target="_blank" class="external-link" href="https://iris.who.int/server/api/core/bitstreams/e65ae612-3723-4df5-a0e3-639dcdaa9ef8/content" title="External link — WHO European Regional Obesity Report 2022"&gt;WHO European Regional Obesity Report 2022&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 20 20"&gt;&lt;path d="M11.5 3.5 11.5 4.233C14.342 4.233 15.167 4.245 15.167 4.258L8.984 10.467 10.033 11.516C14.826 6.725 16.228 5.333 16.242 5.333L16.267 9 17.733 9 17.733 2.767 11.5 2.767 11.5 3.5M2.267 11 2.267 17.233 16.733 17.233 16.733 12 15.267 12 15.25 15.75 9.5 15.75 3.75 15.75 3.75 6.25 9.5 6.233 9.5 4.767 2.267 4.767 2.267 11 "&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the percentage of people in Turkey who are overweight and obese is the &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/turkey-sees-sharp-rise-in-obesity/a-72701125"&gt;highest in Europe&lt;/a&gt;, with 66.8% of the population falling into this category.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span data-slot-id="Article_InContent-1" class="rich-text-ad"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Debate around starch-based sugars&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turkey's food standards are contributing to the problem. Statutory requirements for healthy nutrition are inadequate, and there are no restrictions on the advertising of unhealthy foods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Turkish food scientist Bulent Sik described the problem in an interview with DW: "The increase in the consumption of cheap, easily available snacks and sugary soft drinks is directly linked to the increase in obesity. As long as the production of these goods is not restricted, many measures are no more than symbolic policies," he said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Public health expert Kayihan Pala points to starch-based &lt;a class="internal-link" href="/en/sugars-hidden-dangers/a-68204548"&gt;sugars&lt;/a&gt; as another contributing factor. "It's scientifically proven that consuming large quantities of corn syrup, which is high in fructose, increases the prevalence of type 2 diabetes. People who aren't obese are also more likely to get sick if they consume these sugars," he warns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The issue of starch-based sugars has been under discussion in Turkey for years. The country's Sugar Law, passed in 2001, established production quotas of 10%. In 2008, the quota was raised to 15%, and in subsequent years it went up as high as 50%. In 2018, it was lowered again to 5%. Since then, following a decree from President Recep Tayyip Erdogan, it has dropped to 2.5%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="placeholder-image master_landscape big"&gt;&lt;img data-format="MASTER_LANDSCAPE" data-id="66793034" data-url="https://static.dw.com/image/66793034_${formatId}.jpg" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" alt="A child, seen partially from over her shoulder, wearing a white top and sitting at a small grey plastic desk with a yoghurt and a bottle of water on it"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="img-caption"&gt;Encouraging healthy eating in childhood is one of the most effective ways of combating obesity&lt;small class="copyright"&gt;Image: ANKA&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Children and school meals&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pala is calling for a fundamental policy shift in diabetes prevention in Turkey. "We need science-based, socially far-reaching programs for nutrition, prevention, and the fight against diabetes and obesity. Show projects alone won't get us anywhere."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The problem must be nipped in the bud, says Pala. Measures to combat diabetes have to focus on children, too. Healthy nutrition in childhood is a decisive factor. Pala is calling for free school meals for all children, describing it as one of the most effective measures in combating obesity and the risk of diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article was translated from German.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>DW</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:10:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBmbU1sV0NDdFVzT0t0MDFWR2FyWWhkcXBRNDg2bEF4b1BHTXA0bm5wVVFsZUg2MUtXN3BPelFmNjJ5VGh2YWNBSk1aLXNnd1N5T1BHN2RoM0R3Y0dVUnBhMnZtc3VQX2pOY1hKcmJ5SXJPeGxqQjhUQTFDSXFMQdIBfkFVX3lxTE5kaGFzdk03X1ZQRkJ0VGU3dHhZNjdrRFNNV1dSWEZTRWJUUmctWUE1OS0zVFFMS3dNNmZfd1VZdWlhSWNKNUh3aUpOaDJHdGVGNHFoN3BtMEc1SGItZzFVckkwbmlVUXcycWZIWWNpS0NRbmlkVVphN3hGSlgtUQ</guid></item><item><title>雅典的Guthrie诊所在车辆撞入建筑物后暂时关闭- WETM</title><link>https://www.mytwintiers.com/news-cat/local-news/guthrie-clinic-in-athens-temporarily-closed-after-vehicle-crashes-into-building/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content article-body rich-text "&gt;
		
		


&lt;p&gt;ATHENS, Pa. (&lt;a href="https://www.mytwintiers.com/"&gt;WETM&lt;/a&gt;) — The Guthrie Clinic in Athens will be closed for the time being after a vehicle crashed into it, causing damage to the building, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/TheGuthrieClinic/posts/pfbid02Z5GVQRyMrVcmW3Cg5u2iGqNj7EVJquU8y3uqGazk2TX6QUMU6W7vzLpPAtvFcrVil" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.facebook.com/TheGuthrieClinic/posts/pfbid02Z5GVQRyMrVcmW3Cg5u2iGqNj7EVJquU8y3uqGazk2TX6QUMU6W7vzLpPAtvFcrVil"&gt;post&lt;/a&gt; from the clinic’s Facebook page.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Due to the damage, appointments scheduled at Guthrie Athens location will be moved to the Family Medicine department at the Sayre clinic until further notice, Guthrie explained. The Sayre clinic is inside Guthrie Robert Packer Hospital, located at 1 Guthrie Square. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Although the location of appointments has changed, patients’ providers will remain the same, Guthrie emphasized. If you are someone with an appointment scheduled at the Athens location, Guthrie exclaimed that more information should come your way via phone call or text. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p hidden data-minutemedia-viewport="mobile" data-player-id="81wf8208" data-stn-player="" data-s2n-api="minuteMediaS2NApi"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Further, the damage to the building is being checked out, and a plan is being developed for needed repairs, Guthrie said. No further information about the incident has been provided at this time.&lt;/p&gt;

		&lt;p class="article-content-cta-group"&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;

	
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WETM</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:00:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxQOUx6OFFVdlNxWTFPU2F6Q05WYXpTeVVqa3RvT1drT0d5VE1iZ3JlX3dPUmVRX1Y3YjJQZHR0REJueWJUa3d2Mm96Q1Byb24ydmpVdVpmeW55a2s1NEs3QTctOWFVWXVIM2lqNzZxMWp5RkV1RVZsbC1vSFJyY1hkck5UVnl2SS03OVJwUUlFZllkRnQ3V0NQMlNhenpXdU5yVnJ3TzVFMWJCV2hiSjI4OVMydlBBYld5MTlLRFZoSnFQam1XSWxJ0gHMAUFVX3lxTE9JTDlrUXhJZU1fUGlhc05mczE5ZGhyVkltTjAyMGwwT01wdVJBS19yZ2k3TVJxLXFLd2p5WDB6dkI0dG5rUVRmM3FDNnF4VVIwTGJPU25TT0JHcFFHemRrZmlSN1VtQXV4cURpTWVEUkxhNVhuMU82bnplLTlrckplZmZtZ2ktaGg0ckE0R3FYUmRYbDZ5NmZyZ3VSdDh1aloxdy1XSnpQc2tCMU1Ec0NLYzR1Q0V6YXhmNjFabmlDWURVY3p3X214MkdzMw</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法，可以帮助降低血糖的令人惊讶的习惯- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/surprising-habit-help-lower-blood-sugar-11811190</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dietitians say drinking water is an easy habit that can help lower blood sugar. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It promotes satiety, reduces stress and keeps you energized, which may deter unhealthy snacking. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Try drinking H2O before morning coffee, carrying a water bottle and adding flavor boosters.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There are lots of solid tips for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/lifestyle-tweaks-healthy-blood-sugar-levels-11792895" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;better blood sugar management&lt;/a&gt;, like eating at regular intervals, consuming reasonable portions and exercising regularly, among others.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; But there’s one &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/small-daily-habits-diabetes-management-11792897" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;blood sugar–regulating habit&lt;/a&gt; you may be forgetting about that also makes a difference: Drinking water. This often-overlooked strategy is so effective that it’s recommended by both the American Heart Association and the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Drinking water benefits blood sugar management in several ways, including by avoiding the ill &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8072324/does-dehydration-cause-high-blood-sugar/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;effects of dehydration&lt;/a&gt;, helping you &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/2052969/5-sneaky-sources-of-added-sugars-that-are-probably-in-your-kitchen-right-now/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;steer clear of added sugars&lt;/a&gt; and more. Keep reading to learn why registered dietitians say it’s one small habit that might make a big difference in your blood sugar numbers.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-drinking-water-regularly-can-improve-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Drinking Water Regularly Can Improve Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Staying Hydrated Supports Satiety &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “If you’re dehydrated, it’s possible that you think you’re hungry—not thirsty,” says &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/jeanettegiacinto_rd/?hl=en" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Jeanette Giacinto, M.S., R.D.&lt;/a&gt; As a result, you may unnecessarily end up reaching for snacks, particularly those that contain refined carbohydrates and added sugar. That, in turn, can hurt blood sugar management, she explains. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you are experiencing &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8031222/reasons-why-you-wake-up-hungry/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;signs of hunger&lt;/a&gt;, such as stomach pangs, irritability or difficulty concentrating, then you absolutely should consider eating something.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; But if you just had a snack or meal and know that you ate an amount that typically satisfies you, Giacinto recommends having one or two glasses of water. Then check back in with yourself in 5 or 10 minutes. From there, if you still have that hungry feeling, go ahead and have a healthy snack.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dehydration May Affect Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When you are dehydrated, your blood becomes more concentrated. This can make &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/sneaky-signs-your-blood-sugar-is-too-high-11679557" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;blood sugar levels appear higher&lt;/a&gt; [on a reading], says &lt;a href="https://www.kristenlorenznutrition.com/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Kristen Lorenz, RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;. While the amount of sugar in your bloodstream hasn’t changed, the proportion of sugar to water has.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; So, if you were to measure your blood glucose level, it would be higher, and you might even see a spike.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; If you’re living with diabetes, the last thing you want are wonky blood sugar readings. Plus, with diabetes, you’re even more prone to the effects of dehydration. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; On the other hand, “drinking enough water helps dilute glucose in the bloodstream,” Lorenz says. “I wouldn’t recommend water as &lt;em&gt;the&lt;/em&gt; way to manage a person’s blood sugar, but I’d recommend adequate hydration for everyone.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Dehydration Can Contribute to Stress &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Research suggests that people who regularly don’t drink enough fluids—and therefore aren’t properly hydrated—are more reactive to stress.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; How so? “Chronic dehydration can increase the level of the stress hormone cortisol, and a more elevated cortisol level throughout the day can affect your ability to regulate your blood sugars well,” says Giacinto. That’s why it’s so important to know the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8060890/conditions-that-increase-risk-of-dehydration/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;initial signs of dehydration&lt;/a&gt; before it hits hard. These include having a dry mouth, feeling unusually thirsty, sweating or peeing less than normal or having dark-colored urine.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Drinking Water Can Help Keep Up Energy Levels &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Even slight dehydration has been shown to impact mood, energy and alertness.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This, too, can affect your food choices. “If a person is dragging, they often think that they need food versus maybe having some water,” says Lorenz. The result? You may be more likely to reach for glucose-spiking sources of quick sugar, like candy, cookies or a sweetened coffee drink. That’s not just problematic for blood sugar management. It can also impact how you feel. “As fast as these foods bring us up, blood sugar and energy levels can crash, making us feel terrible,” says Lorenz. “There’s this pendulous swing of high-to-low energy all day.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;
Next time you’re feeling low-energy, hydrate first. If you’re hungry, ask yourself if you need a snack or a meal, Lorenz suggests. When you choose to eat, make sure to consume a fiber-containing carbohydrate with protein, such as &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/261626/sprouted-grain-toast-with-peanut-butter-banana/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;nut butter on whole-grain toast&lt;/a&gt;, fruit with yogurt, or cucumber slices and hummus or tzatziki. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-strategies-to-make-drinking-water-part-of-your-routine"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Strategies to Make Drinking Water Part of Your Routine &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When you’re busy or on the go, it’s easy to forget to hydrate. “You’d be surprised at how many patients I have that simply don’t drink enough water,” says Lorenz. “It’s a constant issue—even with me and my dietitian friends.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Here’s how our experts recommend getting the water your body needs:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start the day strong: &lt;/strong&gt;Before coffee, chug some water. “I usually recommend 8 to 16 ounces of water first thing in the morning,” says Giacinto. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carry a water bottle: &lt;/strong&gt;Lorenz recommends having an “emotional support water bottle” with you at all times. Set a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8055032/drank-recommended-amount-water-daily-for-week/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;hydration goal&lt;/a&gt; to hit before you leave the house in the morning. As for how much to drink, a good target is 11.5 cups per day for women and 15.5 cups for men.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn how you “take” your water: &lt;/strong&gt;“Allow yourself to have a Goldilocks moment,” says Lorenz. Is ice water too cold, room temp too warm, but chilled without ice just right? Do you like to sip through a straw or out of a cup? Do you want it in a water bottle, and if so, do you prefer one that’s clear or opaque? Yes, these are a lot of questions just for water. But if you’re not a water lover, this can help you discover what tastes best to you and the mode of drinking that will motivate you to drink up throughout the day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitor seltzer water intake: &lt;/strong&gt;Carbonated waters are delicious, and they can make drinking water enjoyable. However, Lorenz worries that seltzer’s belly-filling carbonation might limit the ability to consume enough water. You don’t have to give up seltzer. Just make sure it’s not your main source of H2O and stick with a moderate amount.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-sc-block-adslot-inline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add some flavor: &lt;/strong&gt;“For someone who struggles with drinking water, making it fun makes it more likely you’ll hit your goal,” says Giacinto. That could be creating custom infusions like mint, lime and cucumber, fresh berries and basil, or mixed melon. If you need inspo, TikTok is never short of inventive ideas.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Staying hydrated by drinking water is a healthy habit to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290068/12-healthy-ways-to-lower-your-blood-sugar/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;support blood sugar management&lt;/a&gt;. Dietitians say dehydration can impact blood sugar in many ways, like causing you to reach for food when you’re actually thirsty, not hungry. It can also spur you to grab foods that are rich in refined carbs or added sugars for an energy pick-me-up. Additionally, dehydration can concentrate your blood and increase stress levels, both of which may make blood glucose readings higher. Expert-backed tips to stay hydrated include drinking water before having coffee in the morning, discovering how water tastes best to you, and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-best-ingredient-to-upgrade-your-water-fruit-11783370" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;creating flavored water infusions&lt;/a&gt; to make sipping throughout the day a bit more enticing and fun. So, what are you waiting for? Go ahead, grab a glass and drink up!&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPSE9lMnBCaTlJV2x3R1ZXbnVMUmItNEFfalVmdHotTWpkUW5GeEtHUFlBNnYwdXBWd1o3bTBnd1ZzSDRoaExPMFdxb2F0U3J0WGdPbzZoWWZyalVYRWVBWVZSOHBzcnVLcVp0bjFaTVlwQnBGRUhoMXNJbHRBV24zTQ</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，流行的减肥药物可能会增加视力丧失的风险- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/popular-weight-loss-drugs-glp-1may-increase-risk-of-vision-loss-studies-find/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two new studies examined whether GLP-1 popular weight-loss and diabetes drugs are linked to vision and eye problems in people with type 2 diabetes. One study reported a small uptick in optic nerve disorders among users of semaglutide or tirzepatide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The companion &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2837378" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;analysis&lt;/a&gt; tracked diabetic retinopathy patterns in patients prescribed GLP-1 medicines and assessed serious eye complications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This work included contributions from &lt;a href="https://case.edu/cancer/members/member-directory/rong-xu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Rong Xu, PhD&lt;/a&gt;, Case Western Reserve University School of Medicine (&lt;a href="https://case.edu/medicine/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;CWRU&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-glp-1-and-vision-loss"&gt;GLP-1 and vision loss&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers compared people starting semaglutide or tirzepatide with matched peers starting other diabetes medications and watched what happened over two years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They counted 35 cases of nonarteritic anterior ischemic optic neuropathy and 93 other optic &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/vagus-nerve-stimulation-offers-new-hope-for-severe-depression/"&gt;nerve&lt;/a&gt; disorders in the GLP-1 group, compared with 19 and 54 in the comparison group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The overall risk was low, but these findings highlight the need for close monitoring of these conditions,” wrote Xu. The authors emphasized scale and context. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The diabetic retinopathy analysis found a modest increase in new retinopathy cases among GLP-1 users, while fewer patients progressed to vision-threatening events such as vitreous hemorrhage or blindness. The authors urged routine monitoring for patients on these drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-medicines-and-eye-issues"&gt;Medicines and eye issues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Semaglutide and tirzepatide belong to the &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK551568/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;GLP-1 receptor agonist class&lt;/a&gt;, drugs that help lower blood sugar and support weight loss. They act on hormone pathways that affect insulin release and appetite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aao.org/eyenet/article/naion-diagnosis-and-management" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;NAION&lt;/a&gt; is an ischemic injury to the optic nerve that can cause sudden vision loss, usually in one eye. It is linked to reduced blood flow within the small vessels that feed the optic nerve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A comprehensive &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2411-5150/7/4/72" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; places NAION’s annual incidence in adults at roughly 2 to 12 per 100,000. Risk rises with age and with conditions like diabetes, hypertension, and sleep apnea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nei.nih.gov/learn-about-eye-health/eye-conditions-and-diseases/diabetic-retinopathy" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Diabetic retinopathy&lt;/a&gt; is different. It is a microvascular disease of the retina that develops over years of elevated blood sugar and can progress to macular edema, hemorrhage, and, in severe cases, vision loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-the-signal-matters"&gt;Why the signal matters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The optic nerve findings come from a very large electronic health record cohort, and the absolute numbers of events were small. Low risk does not mean no risk, so the pattern deserves attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These medicines also deliver important benefits beyond glucose control. In a large cardiovascular &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37952131/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;trial&lt;/a&gt; semaglutide cut major cardiovascular events by 20 percent in adults with overweight or obesity and established heart disease without diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-glp-1-drugs-might-harm-vision"&gt;How GLP-1 drugs might harm vision&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One possible piece of the puzzle is where these drug targets are found in the eye. Human retinal tissue shows low &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6099507/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;expression&lt;/a&gt; of the GLP-1 receptor in a small fraction of neurons in the ganglion cell layer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another piece is how quickly blood sugar falls. An earlier randomized &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/27633186/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;trial&lt;/a&gt; recorded more diabetic retinopathy complications in semaglutide users, an effect that clustered early and likely reflected rapid &lt;a href="https://diabetes.org/about-diabetes/a1c" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;A1C reduction&lt;/a&gt; in people with preexisting retinopathy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither of these points proves a direct causal mechanism for NAION or broader optic nerve problems. They do show biologic and clinical contexts that make careful follow up a sensible step.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-experts-are-weighing-the-risks"&gt;How experts are weighing the risks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specialists stress that associations seen in observational studies should not be mistaken for direct cause and effect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The observed increase in optic nerve disorders among GLP-1 users remains rare, at about one in 10,000, and most patients will never experience these events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eye doctors point out that many risk factors for optic &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/exercise-fuels-neuron-growth-through-muscle-signals/"&gt;nerve&lt;/a&gt; problems, including hypertension, obesity, and sleep apnea, are already common in people with diabetes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This overlap makes it difficult to separate the effects of the drugs from the effects of the underlying disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-patients-and-clinicians-can-do-now"&gt;What patients and clinicians can do now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start with a baseline &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/unexpected-find-inside-the-eye-of-a-tiny-wasp-megaphragma-viggianii/"&gt;eye&lt;/a&gt; exam when initiating a GLP-1 medicine if you have type 2 diabetes. Keep scheduled follow ups, especially in the first year, or sooner if symptoms arise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do not ignore new visual symptoms. Sudden vision loss, a shadow, or a major change in visual clarity calls for prompt ophthalmic evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Balance risks and benefits using your full medical picture. These drugs offer meaningful metabolic and cardiovascular gains that matter for long term health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The optic nerve signal linked to semaglutide or tirzepatide is real in these data, but it is rare. Regular screening and smart risk management help preserve the benefits of treatment while watching for uncommon problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2837377" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:19:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQVUtWb0hHUDlCa0g0eEpnc3c2d1BmcUhmZm9TRE9uU1VTenRkVzhZNUJRbTNCZ0E0NkVjTG1TOUlBRlZJQXhydm1ZQmE0RmE5Y1Z4LVppaVA2dFVTMUpPOEZIaU9PVlA4TnRvRlhleGh5cmgzLXRlTzEwakd3b3RDb1JuZDR2aU1jT3BqU0Y5Nm9EZVNYYXd4VEJyRzVKeWVBUGs5Yllybw</guid></item><item><title>碧姬·马克龙（ Brigitte Macron ）在70岁时进行平腹运动- valleyvanguardonline.com</title><link>https://www.valleyvanguardonline.com/brigitte-macrons-go-to-exercise-for-a-flat-stomach-at-70-ampversion/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>valleyvanguardonline.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 15:10:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPaFA5TGVkNmpzVEFTVzVVSVNWbTZPTWY3T3VoUG9LSUQ1dFpPOUNJRl82bHNRazNrbm13YmxTQmRHUGdaWXNjOThlWFdVRGpHNXF0dUItT1ZLVlg5aDd3VXgtVHFVQWI0SElaMW1RVWZBNU1yQzNxemJiMi02M0xIX0JoaWNabUtqN05UOTItMXdvOVFmczM1Y1pKVDhkZ0FjM2ZpdnNLX3M</guid></item><item><title>一位顶级胃肠病学家警告说，这种常见的马桶错误会导致便秘-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/this-common-toilet-mistake-is-causing-constipation-a-top-gastroenterologist-warns/articleshow/124196032.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Constipation is a common digestive problem. Feeling blocked up is not normal; however, millions of people are suffering from it. Several factors, including poor diet, lack of exercise, certain medications, and diseases, contribute to constipation. Dr. Saurabh Sethi, a California-based gastroenterologist trained at Harvard and Stanford, has warned that a common bathroom habit could be the culprit behind your bowel issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;One bathroom mistake that’s causing constipation &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, bathroom habits have a huge impact on how you empty your bowels. According to Dr. Sethi, a common toilet habit is causing &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/7-natural-remedies-for-constipation-relief-how-to-improve-digestion-naturally-at-home/articleshow/122415063.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;constipation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in most people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;6 Foods that help you poop better and relieve constipation in the morning&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gastroenterologist with over 25 years of clinical experience recalled a patient who came to his office complaining of chronic constipation. “I had someone come to my office complaining about constant constipation and straining. She was eating fiber, drinking water, doing everything right.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, what’s the cause behind constipation? That’s when Dr. Sethi asked the patient about her “to describe how she sits on the toilet.” He soon found the culprit behind the constipation. It was her seating position on the toilet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Seating position in the toilet matters&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what was wrong with the patient’s seating position? “She was sitting normally on a Western toilet,” the doctor shared in a newsletter. Wondering what’s wrong in that, because everyone does it? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, the ‘normal’ seating position on the Western toilet itself is the problem. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When you sit with your feet flat on the floor, your body isn't in the right position to empty your bowels easily. Your rectum has a bend that makes it harder for stool to pass through,” the gastroenterologist explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to fix it? &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fix is indeed simple. Dr. Sethi recommends to follow these steps:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Put a small stool under your feet while on the toilet&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raise your knees above your hips&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This straightens out the bend and makes everything flow easier&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Eastern toilets naturally put you in a squatting position, which is why people in those countries have less constipation. You're basically mimicking that position,” he adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are struggling with &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/constipation-morning-habits-that-help-with-constipation-and-bloating/articleshow/124023247.cms" rel="noopener" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;constipation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, even after having a balanced diet rich in fiber and an active lifestyle, think about your seating position. “Try this tonight. Most people see results immediately. No more straining. No more sitting there for 20 minutes,” Dr. Sethi assures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt; This article is for informational purposes only and is not a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult a qualified healthcare provider regarding any questions or concerns about your health, medical conditions, or constipation. Individual results may vary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 14:43:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgJBVV95cUxONi1lSVAxaEloMFBCUGc2UzFsQ3JzcHhWSnNrR2dRRnVCV3JjNEFrWVh2el9HajVoeVhHS28zV2hiQ3VWMEdXZjZiVGZzUmJWYXM4RlNaS1UxVGhPU3ZHZkx3MFZ3QkxoSEdpVHpPeERqYUpIUW9LMjBiZ0xTOHBEYnlpN2VWTjc2TmFQcHdGTkYtekNEeU9Bbnhla1E5akszU2xqZDZLOE9jNk1yNUdqVGJ2c1VJQ0RRWTBWU2kzSUxROEJvTm9QSFV0bHhXZ0huTzdzM214ekdSRHQ2REdMc1J0QUlIYzlJSkNNTmJpRWtjX3VDWGRNMFVvVFFXM2oyWDg4WDQ3WjNRQWlfTHc</guid></item></channel></rss>