<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>关于长期冠状病毒病因的新线索可以解锁治疗方法-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/15/long-covid-chronic-inflammation-treatment/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QX38T0PUWX1UD971BV0UV5PDK0" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Why some people experience long-lasting physical and mental effects from covid-19 could be linked to chronic inflammation, according to new research that experts say could help develop new treatments for the confounding condition that continues to afflict millions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:01:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQdGVuSHpwQ0lYVm84RWY3N0hKcjVwcnpySVN2MDhWYU5mYkh6OS1mWFF2NkVSMkFGTzhEdVN2dE5sWndHUWFZMWlyVXRzUjYxeUpHNGEtSTVOS1I1U0hfSk04ci1rUGlIQm1tTndlb1ZXR0VMMEh2eXZ0LVM4STNvY3VSMVg4NHhwbmk5SnlxMUIzdjlSbHc</guid></item><item><title>成千上万的美国农民患有帕金森氏症。他们归咎于致命的杀虫剂。- MLive.com</title><link>https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/12/thousands-of-us-farmers-have-parkinsons-they-blame-a-deadly-pesticide.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content impact-article  "&gt;&lt;p class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z2M3ANX3OVHE7AJEJ2RHC4MRFM"&gt;Paul Friday remembers when his hand started flopping in the cold weather – the first sign nerve cells in his brain were dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="W2ZE2LIMJFE3ZJCXFF2QQIPBB4"&gt;He was eventually diagnosed with Parkinson’s, a brain disease that gets worse over time. His limbs got stiffer. He struggled to walk. He couldn’t keep living on his family farm. Shortly afterward, Friday came to believe that decades of spraying a pesticide called paraquat at his peach orchard in southwestern Michigan may be the culprit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="P2JCXDFYURB55A2RQKEMJTSQZA"&gt;“It explained to me why I have Parkinson’s disease,” said Friday, who is now 83, and makes that claim in a pending lawsuit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VRUL3AZYOJBDFJBELVLBCNTMRQ"&gt;The pesticide, a weed killer, is extremely toxic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7YB674MWOVDNZKFFDB45BXCDII"&gt;With evidence of its harms stacking up, it’s already been banned in dozens of countries all over the world, including the United Kingdom and China, where it’s made. Yet last year, its manufacturer Syngenta, a subsidiary of a company owned by the Chinese government, continued selling paraquat in the United States and other nations that haven’t banned it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="F7Y5O3TXPBBWDJKRETXF7URHF4"&gt;Health statistics are limited. Critics point to research linking paraquat exposure to Parkinson’s, while the manufacturer pushes back, saying none of it is peer-reviewed. But the lawsuits are mounting across the United States, as farmers confront Parkinson’s after a lifetime of use, and much of the globe is turning away from paraquat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JEDZRWYMBJAN3EAKC47BL4PVHA"&gt;It has many critics wrestling with the question: What will it take to ban paraquat in the United States? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6T4XUVSTU5CNLCWQ4TQKRM4MFE"&gt;“What we’ve seen over the course of decades is a systemic failure to protect farmworkers and the agricultural community from pesticides,” said Jonathan Kalmuss-Katz, a senior attorney at Earthjustice, an environmental law organization that advocates against paraquat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Paul Friday was a lifelong peach farmer in Coloma, Michigan until he developed Parkinson's Disease in 2017.&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Photo provided by Luiba Friday&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Thousands of lawsuits pile up&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XOCKWDYSSVCTROU6MSMOVHZL64"&gt;It was hard for Ruth Anne Krause to watch her husband of 58 years struggle to move his hands. He was an avid woodcarver, shaving intricate details into his creations, before it became too difficult for him to hold the tools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3EDD5UF5SVEJRGCIHVLFIFFEGQ"&gt;Jim Krause was diagnosed with Parkinson’s disease in 2019, after he spent decades operating a 20-acre stone fruit farm in central California. His wife says he often donned a mask and yellow rubber boots to spray paraquat on the fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SHSPPGDLPFEG7CEL22ZN7D6MAA"&gt;Krause, who had no family history of neurological disease as is typical, died in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FZWEWOJ6LRGYZACOHVIQMH2NOU"&gt;“I want people to know what happened,” said Ruth Anne Krause, who is worried that paraquat is still being sold to American farmers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MWTSGRKFLBDYLCFSFHAUBOLL24"&gt;Krause is one of thousands of people who have sued Syngenta, a manufacturer, and Chevron USA, a seller, over paraquat exposure. They’re alleging the chemical companies failed to warn of the dangers of paraquat despite knowing it could damage human nerve cells and studies showing it’s linked to Parkinson’s disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Between 11 million and 17 million pounds of paraquat are sprayed annually on American farms, according to the latest data from the U.S. Geological Survey. The pesticide is used as a burn down, meaning farmers spray it to quickly clear a field or kill weeds. It's effective, but highly toxic. (Julie Bennett | preps@al.com)&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Julie Bennett | preps@al.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7LCTCRPUUZF3XMWDQXJCABO7VI"&gt;Chevron, which never manufactured paraquat and hasn’t sold it since 1986, has “long maintained that it should not be liable in any paraquat litigation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KQ3NHW4GPFHJRL5CYDRXRWYCFU"&gt;“And despite hundreds of studies conducted over the past 60 years, the scientific consensus is that paraquat has not been shown to be a cause of Parkinson’s disease,” the company said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ENAL7CTX7VF7VJUKDONTSAMYVY"&gt;Syngenta has emphasized there is no evidence that paraquat causes Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E7H3YVLGPNAOHMJCUPBLSMO4YU"&gt;“We have great sympathy for those suffering from the debilitating effects of Parkinson’s disease,” a Syngenta spokesperson said in a statement. “However, it is important to note that the scientific evidence simply does not support a causal link between paraquat and Parkinson’s disease, and that paraquat is safe when used as directed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TFX57IT5BVAVPKYVOOUUMDVZTM"&gt;More than 6,400 lawsuits against Syngenta and Chevron that allege a link between paraquat and Parkinson’s are pending in the U.S. District Court of Southern Illinois. Another 1,300 cases have been brought in Pennsylvania, 450 in California and more are scattered throughout state courts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="T7FPVRRWXJDJ5AMXR6WPCVVYHM"&gt;“I do think it’s important to be clear that number is probably not even close to representative of how many people have been impacted by this,” said Christian Simmons, a legal expert for Drugwatch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FC6EJZHEKJDCHFCSMIPDAH6DWU"&gt;Syngenta &lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/2025-03/Financial%20Report%202024.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;told its shareholders in March&lt;/a&gt; that an additional 1,600 cases have been voluntarily dismissed or resolved. In 2021, the company settled an unspecified number in California and Illinois for $187.5 million, &lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/bond-investor-information/financial-results/Syngenta-AG-2021-Financial-Report.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to a company financial report&lt;/a&gt;. Some others have been dismissed for missing court deadlines. None have gone to trial yet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3HL2637WKBHRPF6RVYGXZFOYSA"&gt;Behind these thousands of lawsuits, a list growing nearly every day, is a person suffering from Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UXSM5JW5TBEVRAPVMR5KKNMJGQ"&gt;In Ohio, there’s Dave Jilbert a winemaker who sprayed the pesticide on his vineyard south of Cleveland. He was diagnosed with Parkinson’s in 2020 and now he is suing and working to get paraquat banned. Terri McGrath believes &lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/12/michigan-family-has-7-parkinsons-cases-did-weed-killer-play-a-role.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/12/michigan-family-has-7-parkinsons-cases-did-weed-killer-play-a-role.html"&gt;years of exposure to paraquat&lt;/a&gt; at her family farm in rural Southwest Michigan likely contributed to her Parkinson’s. Six other family members also have the disease. And in south Alabama, Mac Barlow is suing after receiving a similar diagnosis following years of relying on paraquat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PAMUDHHLPND7JDOWIOZQDS4X3A"&gt;“For about 40 years off and on, I’ve been using that stuff,” Barlow said. “I’ll be honest with you, if I knew it was going to be that bad, I would have tried to figure out something else.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-28" data-gaid="inarticle-28"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;In Alabama, farmer Mac Barlow was diagnosed with Parkinson's after years of spraying paraquat. Teri McGrath believes years of exposure to paraquat at her family farm in rural Southwest Michigan  contributed to her Parkinson’s. In Ohio, there’s Dave Jilbert a winemaker who sprayed the pesticide on his vineyard. He was diagnosed with Parkinson’s in 2020. Like Barlow, Jilbert is now suing.&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Photos by Julie Bennett, Isaac Ritchey and David Petkiewicz&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-29" data-gaid="inarticle-29"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Paraquat in the United States&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-30" data-gaid="inarticle-30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SRZCGOWUZBFTLC4F47BZAIXRWY"&gt;Since hitting the market in the 1960s, paraquat has been used in farming to quickly “burn” weeds before planting crops. The pesticide, originally developed by Syngenta and sold by Chevron, rips tissue apart, destroying plants on a molecular level within hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-31" data-gaid="inarticle-31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TXJFF3ZCVBF6ZJZUZAF4QAEORU"&gt;“It’s used because it’s effective at what it does. It’s highly toxic. It’s very good at killing things,” said Geoff Horsfield, policy director at the Environmental Working Group. “And unfortunately, when a pesticide like this is so effective that also means there’s usually human health impacts as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-32" data-gaid="inarticle-32"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D3K2QBNFGRHMDK3UD4KKJJ7XEY"&gt;By the 1970s, it became a tool in the war on drugs, sprayed to kill Mexican marijuana plants. In 1998, that history landed it in Hollywood when the Dude in “The Big Lebowski” calls someone a “human paraquat,” a buzzkill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-33" data-gaid="inarticle-33"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SIRLSB4UNZDGVERNIAOURN63CA"&gt;Today, between 11 million and 17 million pounds of paraquat are sprayed annually to help grow cotton, soybean and corn fields, among other crops, throughout the country, the U.S. Geological Survey, USGS, reports. And despite the alleged known risks, its use is increasing, according to the most current federal data, more than doubling from 2012 to 2018. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-34" data-gaid="inarticle-34"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CMG6JIUF7JBANGFWO4AH3BQSBA"&gt;The USGS says on its website new pesticide use data will be released in 2025. It hasn’t been published yet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-35" data-gaid="inarticle-35"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:PLAQXGROCRGU5HYMZQEHQBLSSQ" data-fusion-component="PLAQXGROCRGU5HYMZQEHQBLSSQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rawhtml"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:PLAQXGROCRGU5HYMZQEHQBLSSQ" data-fusion-component="PLAQXGROCRGU5HYMZQEHQBLSSQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-36" data-gaid="inarticle-36"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Y7QVSR7FRZBGHP5236Q63IKFIQ"&gt;Because paraquat kills any growth it touches, it’s typically used to clear a field before any crops are planted. &lt;a href="https://npic.orst.edu/factsheets/paraquat.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Low levels of paraquat residue&lt;/a&gt; can linger on food crops, but the foremost threat is direct exposure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-37" data-gaid="inarticle-37"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MWQFYNAYI5HFBOUMIHN37OWRHM"&gt;Pesticides are among the most common means of suicide worldwide, &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/preventing-suicide-by-phasing-out-highly-hazardous-pesticides" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, and paraquat is frequently &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3243009/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;used because of its lethality.&lt;/a&gt; After some nations, like South Korea and Sri Lanka, banned it, they saw a significant drop in suicides, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/ije/article-abstract/45/2/470/2572538?redirectedFrom=fulltext" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;research shows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-38" data-gaid="inarticle-38"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="X6TDAXHM3FEGJPMUFVJLWTAJAY"&gt;The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency already restricts paraquat, labeling it as “registered use,” with a skull and crossbones, meaning it can only be used by people who have a license. Because of its toxicity, the federal government requires it to have blue dye, a sharp smell and a vomiting agent, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chemical-emergencies/chemical-fact-sheets/paraquat.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;U.S. Centers for Disease Control, CDC&lt;/a&gt;. Sprayers are also told to wear protective gear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-39" data-gaid="inarticle-39"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GRTLJOHETZHIDJAZMYX63EXFD4"&gt;Despite those safety measures, U.S. poison centers have gotten hundreds of paraquat-related calls in the past decade, their annual reports show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-40" data-gaid="inarticle-40"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z6S3OILK2FATJETFWTXM5CLP7A"&gt;Swallowing is the most likely way to be poisoned by paraquat, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chemical-emergencies/chemical-fact-sheets/paraquat.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;, but skin exposure can also be deadly. In fact, if it spills on someone, health officials say they should wash it off immediately and quickly cut off their clothes. That way they don’t risk spreading more deadly pesticide on their body as they pull their shirt over their head. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-41" data-gaid="inarticle-41"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PW3QJZ22SVDLRHGVV4Q4RLAFIE"&gt;In one 2023 case &lt;a href="https://poisoncenters.org/annual-reports" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;documented by America’s Poison Centers&lt;/a&gt;, a 50-year-old man accidentally sipped blue liquid from a Gatorade bottle that turned out to be paraquat. After trying to throw it up, he went to the emergency room, struggling to breathe, nauseous and vomiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-42" data-gaid="inarticle-42"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZPHWCT4EU5ASNIAZ3EBZ6ZNQ5E"&gt;Doctors rushed to treat the man, but he turned blue from a lack of oxygen and his organs failed. He died within three days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-43" data-gaid="inarticle-43"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TUH5ANIKXVE3HDZE2RKBJLS4VI"&gt;In another poison center report, a 65-year-old man spilled paraquat on his clothes and kept working. Ten days later, he went to the emergency room with second-degree burns on his stomach. Dizzy and nauseous, he was admitted for two days before going home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-44" data-gaid="inarticle-44"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DMG33SK3YFGAJFDHZUKXAM6MQA"&gt;A week later, he went back to the ICU as his kidney, lungs and heart stopped working. He died 34 days after the spill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-45" data-gaid="inarticle-45"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="553FPIV5UFHALN35UJGQ4T7RS4"&gt;These annual poison center case summaries provide insight into paraquat’s toxicity, but it’s unclear exactly how many people in the U.S. have been injured or killed by the weed killer, because there’s only a patchwork of data creating an uneven and incomplete picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-46" data-gaid="inarticle-46"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7I53DH2WIJFSXARIBIBJV3OM6A"&gt;The latest annual National Poison Data System report logged 114 reports and one death caused by paraquat in 2023. Over a decade, from 2014 to 2023, this system documented 1,151 paraquat calls. And a separate database shows the EPA has investigated 82 human exposure cases since 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-47" data-gaid="inarticle-47"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6YFPNYW56ZCSXHITEXMXVDB6JU"&gt;Even secondary exposure can be dangerous. &lt;a href="http://www.rimed.org/rimedicaljournal/2023/06/2023-06-40-images-castaneda-guarderas.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;One case published in the Rhode Island Medical Journal&lt;/a&gt; described an instance where a 50-year-old man accidentally ingested paraquat, and the nurse treating him was burned by his urine that splashed onto her forearms. Within a day, her skin blistered and sloughed off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-48" data-gaid="inarticle-48"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JNFIC26RQNAHFBJDRTZTGIYDOU"&gt;And a former &lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/public-interest/2025/08/former-grad-student-sues-msu-for-100m-alleging-herbicide-pesticide-exposure-caused-cancer.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Michigan State horticulture student&lt;/a&gt; is suing the university for $100 million, claiming that she developed thyroid cancer from her exposure to pesticides including paraquat, glyphosate and oxyfluorfen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-49" data-gaid="inarticle-49"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BMRB6CTK2VHSXB3BI2HCFQUGSE"&gt;Meanwhile, a much more widespread threat looms large in the background: long-term, low-level exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-50" data-gaid="inarticle-50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Parkinson’s on the rise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-51" data-gaid="inarticle-51"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7EMZTEMDJNAIBD4LL7PZPKBSDI"&gt;Parkinson’s disease is the fastest growing neurological disorder in the world, with cases projected to double by 2050, partly due to an aging population, according to a study published in &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/388/bmj-2024-080952" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;The BMJ, a peer-reviewed medical journal&lt;/a&gt;. It occurs when the brain cells that make dopamine, a chemical that controls movement, stop working or die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-52" data-gaid="inarticle-52"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZRNHS4T6OJBXHCNIIHTGOU55FM"&gt;The exact cause is unknown, likely a mix of genetic and, largely, environmental factors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-53" data-gaid="inarticle-53"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RNKG4Z2HTVE53M7KHCND3C6TMQ"&gt;A Parkinson’s Foundation study found that 87% of those with the disease do not have any genetic risk factors. That means, “for the vast majority of Americans, the cause of Parkinson’s disease lies not within us, but outside of us, in our environment,” said neurologist and researcher Ray Dorsey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-54" data-gaid="inarticle-54"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6XQZAEE335C5DNGKKFVSFMV54I"&gt;That’s why Dorsey, who literally wrote the book on Parkinson’s, calls the disease “largely preventable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-55" data-gaid="inarticle-55"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZZWS6GBDZ5CIVIV4UBZLLNLEJU"&gt;There’s a long list of environmental factors linked to Parkinson’s, but pesticides are one of the biggest threats, according to Dorsey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-56" data-gaid="inarticle-56"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PSPBPSNYPRB2LO24K2TTB2IH3Y"&gt;“If we clean up our environment, we get rid of Parkinson’s disease,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-57" data-gaid="inarticle-57"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Paul Friday dedicated his life to growing peaches on his 50-acre farm in Coloma, Michigan. After buying 50 acres of land in 1962, he started experimenting with crossbreeding to develop the perfect peach. He is now one of thousands of farmers who have filed lawsuits claiming a toxic pesticide called paraquat is to blame for their Parkinson's, a neurological disease.&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Photo courtesy of Paul Friday&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-58" data-gaid="inarticle-58"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QHJOILGAHNAYRBWIVAGPMIQDZ4"&gt;Research, dating back decades, has explored this link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-59" data-gaid="inarticle-59"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QCM45H3C3VBIZKSD5FU65PAIAY"&gt;An &lt;a href="https://www.neurology.org/doi/10.1212/WNL.37.4.728" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;early 1987 case report published in Neurology&lt;/a&gt; discusses the case of a 32-year-old citrus farmer who started experiencing tremors, stiffness and clumsiness after 15 years of spraying paraquat. But “a cause-and-effect relationship is difficult to establish,” a doctor wrote at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-60" data-gaid="inarticle-60"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MCO3VRLBCNHR3EA23RYALKHR74"&gt;A decade later, an animal study from Parkinson’s researcher Deborah Cory-Slechta found that paraquat absorbed by mice destroys the specific type of dopamine neuron that dies in Parkinson’s disease. More recently, her research has found paraquat that’s inhaled can also bypass the blood-brain barrier, threatening neurons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-61" data-gaid="inarticle-61"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UN7EPONBYJAGNNCXVHWGIYYTEU"&gt;“It’s quite clear that it gets into the brain from inhalation models,” Cory-Slechta said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-62" data-gaid="inarticle-62"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="J7AEPYTUYNCVZMWREVY3EUKOEQ"&gt;Critics point to other epidemiological studies being more definitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-63" data-gaid="inarticle-63"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KDKSTFSLCRCAFEIXAQ6XYTMHHA"&gt;In 2011, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3114824/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;researchers studied&lt;/a&gt; farmworkers exposed to two pesticides, rotenone and paraquat, and determined those exposures increased the risk of developing Parkinson’s by 150%. &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38309714/#full-view-affiliation-1" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Another study, published last year&lt;/a&gt;, looked at 829 Parkinson’s patients in central California. It found people who live or work near farmland where paraquat is used have a higher risk of developing the disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-64" data-gaid="inarticle-64"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SR7NPPRFHJFLHI23MT3OJ6GQB4"&gt;“It’s kind of like secondhand smoke,” Dorsey said. “You can just live or work near where it’s sprayed and be at risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-65" data-gaid="inarticle-65"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6ND4QCSEP5AO3JKKXAH3EA7KRQ"&gt;This is a growing concern in American suburbs where new houses press up against well-maintained golf courses.&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2833716" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; A study published in JAMA&lt;/a&gt; this year found that living within a mile of a golf course increased the risk of Parkinson’s disease by 126%. It didn’t name specific chemicals but did point to pesticides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-66" data-gaid="inarticle-66"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="643PN2Q5N5EXNMDO2X4K53KGUE"&gt;The EPA in 2021 banned paraquat from golf courses “to prevent severe injury and/or death” from ingestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-67" data-gaid="inarticle-67"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TO4QJDL7VJGJREMAICTDLA5LV4"&gt;Despite all that, it’s difficult to prove whether paraquat directly causes Parkinson’s because it develops years after exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-68" data-gaid="inarticle-68"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RTP572Y3GZF2FG6PU5463CLEUA"&gt;“The disease unfolds over decades, and the seeds of Parkinson’s disease are planted early,” Dorsey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-69" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-69"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Where do the lawsuits stand?&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-70" data-gaid="inarticle-70"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QWX7WOH3RFBNJLGLUM3YJYWJDI"&gt;The legal case over paraquat inched toward a settlement earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-71" data-gaid="inarticle-71"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UBL2KQE3INCTXEX35SEELYS4JM"&gt;Most of the lawsuits have been brought in Illinois under what’s known as multi-district litigation. Unlike a class-action lawsuit, this puts individual cases in front of one federal judge. A few bellwether cases are then chosen to represent the masses and streamline the legal process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-72" data-gaid="inarticle-72"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VGIRUA4XVFDOBFGCM63IITDUOY"&gt;Syngenta, Chevron and the plaintiffs agreed to settle in April, which would wrap up thousands of cases, but an agreement is still being hammered out, court records show. If details can’t be finalized, it will go to trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-73" data-gaid="inarticle-73"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="quote-container"&gt;&lt;div class="impact-quote blockquote"&gt;&lt;div class="quote-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s kind of like secondhand smoke. You can just live or work near where it’s sprayed and be at risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="source-attribution"&gt;Ray Dorsey, a Parkinson's disease research&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-74" data-gaid="inarticle-74"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GILTO3IACNA4TM2U7COHKZXJKM"&gt;Syngenta has adamantly denied the lawsuits’ allegations, saying it backs paraquat as “&lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/2024-11/PQ-Booklet1600212.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;safe and effective&lt;/a&gt;” when it’s used correctly and emphasizing there has been no peer-reviewed scientific analysis that shows paraquat causes Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-75" data-gaid="inarticle-75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="X5LTLXF35NHJDBIVDOJRZOYQOQ"&gt;“Syngenta believes there is no merit to the claims, but litigation can be distracting and costly,” a spokesperson said. “Entering in the agreement in no way implies that paraquat causes Parkinson’s disease or that Syngenta has done anything wrong. We stand by the safety of paraquat.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-76" data-gaid="inarticle-76"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M4QGZGICNZCT5M7ESKM3H3NIEE"&gt;Chevron has also denied the claims saying the “scientific consensus is that paraquat has not been shown to be a cause of Parkinson’s disease.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-77" data-gaid="inarticle-77"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;What company files show&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-78" data-gaid="inarticle-78"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4XOEMU7DM5FVNOWYGLSHIRJX7U"&gt;A trove of internal documents released during litigation, &lt;a href="https://www.thenewlede.org/paraquat-papers-media-library/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;as reported by The Guardian and the New Lede&lt;/a&gt;, appeared to show that the manufacturers were aware of evidence that paraquat could collect in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-79" data-gaid="inarticle-79"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z6QBJSAR2ZFL7PF4NROAAZ5MSA"&gt;But the New Lede acknowledged the documents do not show company scientists believed that paraquat causes Parkinson’s, Syngenta officials pointed out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-80" data-gaid="inarticle-80"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L4AHTOFWLVHU7G6O5PL5LGNDS4"&gt;The trail of bread crumbs started as early as 1958 when a company scientist wrote about a study of 2.2 dipyridyl, a chemical in paraquat, saying it appears to have moderate toxicity “mainly by affecting the central nervous system, and it can be absorbed through the skin,” the internal documents said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-81" data-gaid="inarticle-81"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TLTBEWEQ45HPZGFAYBHTDUTZ7Y"&gt;Imperial Chemical Industries, which later became Syngenta, started selling paraquat under the brand name Gramoxone in 1962, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6689968/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to research&lt;/a&gt;. Gramoxone contains nearly 44% paraquat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-82" data-gaid="inarticle-82"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Syngenta sells paraquat under the brand name Gramaxone, as a resgistered-use pesticide. It's labeled with a skull and cross bones and the warning "one sip can kill." The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency also puts the regulations and rules for use on the label. It's dyed blue and has a strong odor as safety mechanisms. (Photo by Rose White | MLive)&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Rose White | rwhite@MLive.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-83" data-gaid="inarticle-83"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RILEQBRW75AUZDNHEPN32M4EIM"&gt;The internal documents show by 1974, the company updated safety precautions, recommending that anyone spraying the pesticide wear a mask, as there were the first reports of human poisoning and concerns about the effects of paraquat started to grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-84" data-gaid="inarticle-84"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FYY6PR67EFB67G4X233QAJC33U"&gt;A year later, Ken Fletcher from Imperial Chemical wrote a letter to Chevron scientist Dr. Richard Cavelli, saying the chemical company knew of “sporadic reports of CNS (central nervous system) effects in paraquat poisoning” that he believed to be coincidental.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-85" data-gaid="inarticle-85"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OWYNMMWELVAWPGOA5BFRTN2VPM"&gt;Within months, Fletcher also indicated “possible chronic effects” of paraquat exposure, calling it “quite a terrible problem” that should be studied more, the documents say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-86" data-gaid="inarticle-86"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KUTYEHBGV5C5JPLU5JQ65JE2YA"&gt;“Due possibly to good publicity on our part, very few people here believe that paraquat causes any sort of problem in the field,” he wrote in the mid 1970s. “Consequently, any allegation of illness due to spraying never reaches serious proportions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-87" data-gaid="inarticle-87"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JSRARDDIT5A23JTRBSLU6PB2PQ"&gt;By the 1980s, outside research started to pick at the question of paraquat and Parkinson’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-88" data-gaid="inarticle-88"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GYVUGY3OOZBS5DA4XCZ6JAPDK4"&gt;“As more researchers dug into it, it’s only been more firmly established,” said Horsfield with the Environmental Working Group. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-89" data-gaid="inarticle-89"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FHCGRTN6BZDEDEFYIQIYKXQ6SU"&gt;Syngenta pushes back on this, though, saying two recent reports cast doubt on these claims. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-90" data-gaid="inarticle-90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YS4C3IEPWZGJ7FBG2VWYEFVVEE"&gt;A&lt;a href="https://www.cdpr.ca.gov/2024/12/30/department-of-pesticide-regulation-releases-preliminary-findings-from-review-of-environmental-and-human-health-studies-related-to-the-use-of-the-pesticide-paraquat/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; 2024 scientific report&lt;/a&gt; from California pesticide regulators found recent evidence was “insufficient to demonstrate a direct causal association with exposure to paraquat and the increased risk of developing Parkinson’s disease.” And a September analysis from Douglas Weed, an epidemiologist and independent consultant, reached a similar conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-91" data-gaid="inarticle-91"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BO3ZK642V5GTHFLHGDE6SSMSXY"&gt;Syngenta also claims on its website to be a target of a “mass tort machine” that hovers behind multi-district litigation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-92" data-gaid="inarticle-92"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Why hasn’t the EPA banned it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-93" data-gaid="inarticle-93"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="75CKAB5XJJENNN3MLHZD2ZKDRQ"&gt;In 1981, Norway became the first country to outlaw paraquat due to the risk of poisoning. One by one, more countries followed suit. In 2007, the European Union &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/business/environment/eu-court-reimposes-ban-on-paraquat-weedkiller-idUSL11666800/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;approved a blanket ban&lt;/a&gt; for all 27 member countries, according to media reports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-94" data-gaid="inarticle-94"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DF5YBLFXR5H7PGK2G4RJXJV4KQ"&gt;Yet Syngenta is still allowed to manufacture paraquat in countries that have banned its use. It’s been prohibited in the United Kingdom for 18 years and China banned paraquat to “safeguard people’s life, safety and health,” in 2012, &lt;a href="http://www.chinapesticide.org.cn/eng/detail/21956" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to a government announcement&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-95" data-gaid="inarticle-95"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M25A354WVBEUNBJSEQMHSDZRSU"&gt;Yet about two-thirds of the paraquat imported to the U.S. between 2022 and 2024 came from companies owned by the Chinese government, SinoChem and Red Sun Group, &lt;a href="https://pesticidestorymap.com/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to a joint report&lt;/a&gt; published by three advocacy organizations in October.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-96" data-gaid="inarticle-96"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2Q7WICJXVVGWDDGDYDYKQIJWGQ"&gt;It found most of the 40 million and 156 million pounds imported annually over the past eight years comes from Chinese manufacturing facilities, in either China or Syngenta’s big factory in northern England. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-97" data-gaid="inarticle-97"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NKJXSBUUGFAQBKWV4CYXKMVPC4"&gt;Although hundreds of companies sell paraquat, Syngenta says &lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/docs/the-global-market-in-paraquat.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;it accounts for a quarter of global sales.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-98" data-gaid="inarticle-98"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XPJQ5UVY55DMHOZEDA2OGQD7MU"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/business/chemchina-sinochem-merge-agricultural-assets-syngenta-idUSKBN1Z40HA/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;According to previous media reports&lt;/a&gt;, SinoChem, a Chinese state-owned conglomerate, acquired Syngenta in a 2020 merger. SinoChem posted &lt;a href="https://fortune.com/company/sinochem-holdings/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;$3.4 billion&lt;/a&gt; in profits last year, but it’s unclear how much came from paraquat sales because the company doesn’t make earnings reports public. &lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/2025-03/Financial%20Report%202024.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Syngenta reported&lt;/a&gt; $803 million in sales of its “non-selective herbicides,” the class that includes paraquat-containing Gramoxone, according to its 2024 financial report. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-99" data-gaid="inarticle-99"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HHGMRJMUP5GU3JY3G6FGHXB7DQ"&gt;While Chinese companies supply paraquat to American farmers, the report points out China is also a big purchaser of crops, like soybeans, that are grown with help from the pesticide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-100" data-gaid="inarticle-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RSBBWQ5DLJDOXLNWJQ2SRW3PVE"&gt;“In these two ways, China economically benefits from the application of paraquat in the U.S., where it outsources many of its associated health hazards,” the report said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-101" data-gaid="inarticle-101"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="764KX4XJJ5GRDMKSZTE6QVPBVU"&gt;Paraquat, now prohibited in more than 70 countries, &lt;a href="https://www.ewg.org/areas-focus/toxic-chemicals/paraquat" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to the Environmental Working Group&lt;/a&gt;, was reauthorized by the EPA in 2021 when it passed a regularly scheduled 15-year review — a move challenged by critics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-102" data-gaid="inarticle-102"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2Q3265P3B5G75MRS6LQ7VPOELU"&gt;“EPA has the same information that those countries have,” said Kalmuss-Katz, the attorney with EarthJustice. “EPA has just reached a fundamentally different, and what we believe is a legally and scientifically unsupported position, which is: massive amounts of paraquat can continue to be sprayed without unreasonable risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-103" data-gaid="inarticle-103"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="43QS4VGRE5EHPODA5PWMI53J2Y"&gt;The federal agency determined paraquat remains “an effective, inexpensive, versatile, and widely used method of weed control,” and any risks to workers are “outweighed by the benefits” of farms using the weed killer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-104" data-gaid="inarticle-104"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HJPUMSSU5NBHPDMFC4D5BIEY5M"&gt;“It is one of the mostly highly regulated pesticides available in the United States,” the agency said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-105" data-gaid="inarticle-105"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="34QDSAGPFFGZLJAGBAEU6DG5JA"&gt;This decision allowed it to be used with “new stronger safety measures to reduce exposure,” like requiring buffer zones where pesticides can’t be sprayed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-106" data-gaid="inarticle-106"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VGLT7MCGHFD2ZEWWSWWRBROO6A"&gt;For plants like cotton, alfalfa, soybeans and peanuts, the EPA wrote in its decision “growers may need to switch to alternative (weed-killers), which could have financial impacts.” Unlike other pesticides, paraquat works well in low temperatures and early in the season, according to the agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-107" data-gaid="inarticle-107"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="quote-container"&gt;&lt;div class="impact-quote pullquote"&gt;&lt;div class="quote-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we’ve seen over the course of decades is a systemic failure to protect farmworkers and the agricultural community from pesticides.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="source-attribution"&gt;Jonathan Kalmuss-Katz from EarthJustice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-108" data-gaid="inarticle-108"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2JUORFJJCJGV3FHSBIL4RL2PPM"&gt;More than 200,000 public comments have been submitted to the EPA’s docket on paraquat over the years. Industry groups, farmers, advocacy organizations and others have all chimed in, arguing for or against the weed killer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-109" data-gaid="inarticle-109"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KDQMEVORGFAS3N7SVIWSJFJAPE"&gt;One submitted by a North Dakota farmer, Trey Fischbach, urged the EPA to continue allowing paraquat to fight resistant weeds like kochia, writing it’s the “last tool in the toolbox.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-110" data-gaid="inarticle-110"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HOO2H3BTHNGCHNY34WIRMNU4OA"&gt;The EPA also noted there weren’t many other options. “The chemical characteristics of paraquat are also beneficial as a resistance management tool, where few alternatives are available.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-111" data-gaid="inarticle-111"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ANVFXM4LIZBUVDBEXGLE75CAMI"&gt;But farmers can get trapped on what critics call the “&lt;a href="https://www.panna.org/resources/the-pesticide-treadmill/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;pesticide treadmill&lt;/a&gt;,” in which broad pesticide use leads to “superweeds” that require stronger and stronger pesticides to be knocked down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-112" data-gaid="inarticle-112"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WMHATQ6VW5D5VJ6WZL7D5XIMD4"&gt;A comment submitted by Kay O’Laughlin, from Massachusetts, urged instead: “Do your job and ban paraquat because it is killing people. I speak as someone who lost a brother to Parkinson’s. People should not be disposable so that big agro can make ever greater profits!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-113" data-gaid="inarticle-113"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ST7LZTJNG5D7BLMJN7BLZDWUX4"&gt;The EPA’s 2021 decision was challenged within two months by environmental and farmworker groups who sued the EPA. Kalmuss-Katz said the groups challenged the EPA over reapproving paraquat without “truly grappling” with the connection to Parkinson’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-114" data-gaid="inarticle-114"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7TQ6CZ24SNDTPET5JMIE2CBIDE"&gt;“The EPA here failed to adequately protect farmworkers,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-115" data-gaid="inarticle-115"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:IMCYKIZT4BF5NH2OK56RJ6JHUI" data-fusion-component="IMCYKIZT4BF5NH2OK56RJ6JHUI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:IMCYKIZT4BF5NH2OK56RJ6JHUI" data-fusion-component="IMCYKIZT4BF5NH2OK56RJ6JHUI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-116" data-gaid="inarticle-116"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N5FTKEU5GBHW7C6IJW3HWAHAHA"&gt;After that, the environmental agency shifted under President Joe Biden. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-117" data-gaid="inarticle-117"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GAYRCOE5WNFINGLHJSQRJOLB5Q"&gt;The EPA decided to consider the issues raised in the lawsuits and started seeking additional information last year. In early 2025, it asked the courts for more time to assess the human health risks of paraquat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-118" data-gaid="inarticle-118"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EVK5BC2DOVH6ND2ZIXAQ3AVMNQ"&gt;But the EPA wasn’t focused on Parkinson’s, saying in its decision the “weight of evidence was insufficient” to link paraquat exposure to the neurological disease. Rather, the federal question was over how the weed killer turns into a vapor that could harm people when inhaled or touched. “Parkinson’s Disease is not an expected health outcome of pesticidal use of paraquat,” the EPA said in its review. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-119" data-gaid="inarticle-119"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NE5I2W6LO5BYNNLYCBLZBHK2LY"&gt;The study could take up to four years, according to the EPA, saying it’s “complex, large scale and is conducted under real world conditions,” while paraquat remains on the market. The &lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/document/EPA-HQ-OPP-2011-0855-0554" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;agency in October&lt;/a&gt; updated the review, saying it’s now seeking additional information from Syngenta. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-120" data-gaid="inarticle-120"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5AT4THVERJGOLMIZJSEAS63CNQ"&gt;Meanwhile, the EPA has shifted again. The Trump administration this year &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/21/climate/from-industry-to-epa-lobbyist-now-oversees-pesticide-rules.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;put four former industry lobbyists&lt;/a&gt; or executives, from the agricultural, chemical and cleaning industries, in charge of regulating pesticides at the EPA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-121" data-gaid="inarticle-121"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2BCAIDNAJRDIVHNCVNYDD3ZT3E"&gt;And while it’s not clear where the agency stands on paraquat, there has been an early sign of backing away from opposition to controversial pesticides. Shortly after Kyle Kunkler, a recent American Soybean Association lobbyist, was tapped to lead pesticide policy, the EPA moved to reapprove the use of &lt;a href="https://cen.acs.org/environment/pesticides/EPA-allow-new-dicamba-herbicides/103/web/2025/07" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;a different, controversial weed killer&lt;/a&gt; that had previously been banned by federal courts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-122" data-gaid="inarticle-122"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Growing pressure to ban it&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-123" data-gaid="inarticle-123"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KIE4VEVGPFAYFEAXHJ7PT74PPM"&gt;But grassroots pressure to ban paraquat continues to mount.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-124" data-gaid="inarticle-124"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YRPVDBB45FHV3JDLWBID2RHIGY"&gt;“This is a pivotal time for whether paraquat is going to remain active in the United States,” said Simmons, a legal expert for Drugwatch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-125" data-gaid="inarticle-125"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YZHJ4EKKUJAJ5LD6DMQD3O7FIY"&gt;Last year, more than 50 Democratic lawmakers, expressing “grave concern” in letters, urged the EPA to ban paraquat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-126" data-gaid="inarticle-126"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NIAR7O7LD5AUBDL3NLGQWZCG2Y"&gt;“Due to their heightened exposure to paraquat, farmworkers and rural residents are hardest hit by the harmful health effects of paraquat like Parkinson’s,” said &lt;a href="https://casar.house.gov/sites/evo-subsites/casar.house.gov/files/evo-media-document/casar-paraquat-epa-letter.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;an Oct. 7, 2024&lt;/a&gt;, letter signed by U.S. representatives. A &lt;a href="https://www.booker.senate.gov/imo/media/doc/letter_to_epa_re_banning_paraquat.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;separate letter&lt;/a&gt; was signed by a small group of senators. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-127" data-gaid="inarticle-127"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7ZZ2MWHCWFFGXC7VP3P64QAUSI"&gt;California, a heavy user of paraquat as the top agricultural state, became the first to move toward banning paraquat last year. But the bill ended up getting pared back with Gov. Gavin Newsom signing a law to fast-track reevaluating paraquat’s safety, &lt;a href="https://subscriber.politicopro.com/article/2024/09/newsom-signs-bill-to-speed-up-review-of-widely-banned-herbicide-00181530" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;reporting shows&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-128" data-gaid="inarticle-128"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BA2FTDNV3VD6PP3MABVAC6NYQE"&gt;Pennsylvania lawmakers are also considering banning it under &lt;a href="https://www.pahousegop.com/News/35878/Latest-News/Bill-Package-to-Increase-Food-Safety-Sought-by-Mihalek-and-Bipartisan-Coalition-" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;state bills introduced this year&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-129" data-gaid="inarticle-129"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JG64LT3J4FACBHIM7UKCU6VKNQ"&gt;“There are better, healthier alternatives,” said state Rep. Natalie Mihalek, a Republican who introduced the Pennsylvania legislation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-130" data-gaid="inarticle-130"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RX6OMI5PI5DNRFV4KLXCYUCARE"&gt;On a federal level, outside the EPA, pesticides appear to be in the crosshairs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-131" data-gaid="inarticle-131"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7F2SQ5LXVVGQHHHLDDQRAQV6EU"&gt;Health and Human Services secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., has criticized chemicals being used in farming. But a new Make America Healthy Again report shows Kennedy has backed away from restricting pesticides after agricultural groups pushed back on the “inaccurate story about American agriculture and our food system.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-132" data-gaid="inarticle-132"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IVLWSRV27FFT3ENFIZSJFAT7OM"&gt;At the same time, there’s been &lt;a href="https://civileats.com/2024/03/27/inside-bayers-state-by-state-efforts-to-stop-pesticide-lawsuits/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;a reported industry effort&lt;/a&gt; to pass state laws that would protect pesticide manufacturers from liability. Two states, North Dakota and Georgia, already passed these laws, according to &lt;a href="https://nationalaglawcenter.org/update-on-state-pesticide-liability-limitation-bills/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;the National Agricultural Law Firm&lt;/a&gt;. But&lt;a href="https://www.booker.senate.gov/news/press/booker-introduces-pesticide-injury-accountability-act" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; a federal bill introduced&lt;/a&gt; this year would ensure the manufacturers can’t be held responsible for harming farmers in any state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-133" data-gaid="inarticle-133"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="quote-container"&gt;&lt;div class="impact-quote blockquote"&gt;&lt;div class="quote-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a pivotal time for whether paraquat is going to remain active in the United States.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="source-attribution"&gt;Christian Simmons, legal expert for DrugWatch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-134" data-gaid="inarticle-134"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K4UYKBRXFBE77HL7ER7CUG4GPA"&gt;As this tug of war continues, paraquat continues to be sprayed on agricultural fields throughout the United States. The EPA is still assessing its risks. And nearly 90,000 Americans are getting diagnosed with Parkinson’s disease every year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-135" data-gaid="inarticle-135"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z4A3S22DAFFZPDMJC5BVKAINKI"&gt;Meanwhile for critics, the evidence seems clear: it’s too dangerous. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-136" data-gaid="inarticle-136"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="V37TDYW2SZBDBHSWV6FJYV44NI"&gt;“The easiest thing to do is we should ban paraquat,” Dorsey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-137" data-gaid="inarticle-137"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5LUSMJY2LVC3NBJ3TYQFOXQY3U"&gt;&lt;i&gt;AL.com reporter Margaret Kates contributed to this story. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-138" data-gaid="inarticle-138"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MLive.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxQbVpxRG9waEFXOWcwQzdyd1ljYy1UUGdXV1Y2c1YxQ1ZzVjI2ODBBR0hCRFVIYVVUVVdSV2dOend6UGpsWDdFU0FSbUVYOUhMbjlMX1RIT1VtM1Qwb1hObTNZTXFiWVBwdlFNWkRlWFpBX2FadTFPRzNSdkF0b05vWHM5ZFRnMTVkSHg4UzhFc3VkdWJKUEFpQllPRXFHQjdzOW9JTlNIUnl0MEV6c0E</guid></item><item><title>列|我是一名医生。以下是我推荐的对抗炎症的11种食物。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/15/foods-that-fight-inflammation/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="G22IUVOO5VHUVJJ4PKFJ73BJ4M" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are anti-inflammatory diets backed by science? Can some foods really cause inflammation in my body?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TQ7BEQUMEFBJ3HPAE22CQ2HHLA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When my patients ask me about anti-inflammatory diets, they’re usually expecting me to talk about &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/06/25/turmeric-supplements-may-harm-liver-some-people/" target="_blank"&gt;turmeric&lt;/a&gt; or the latest &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/01/29/green-smoothies-juices-shortcomings-benefits/" target="_blank"&gt;viral green drink&lt;/a&gt;. Lists of “toxic” foods are popular on social media — followed by advice to start the day with things like celery juice to help you “detox.” And while I’d love to say that a cup of blueberries a day will “turn off” inflammation, that’s not what the evidence shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 10:41:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOdExSOFpvWXZ1NDJJRmQxOVo2U2FYVzFRVDZkVnIxY3BrVnVsNHFKSUgxdUpScnlqOHcwSlhwLXV0UFN5dHZGTkd3Q2NocnQ4ZXI2a2hrOHlGY1FYVTFKanNJQjNrZE5ITDZZRXhuX1RzMmcyZWRkdkhWX3NGU0p5MDJLNmM4cVpN</guid></item><item><title>想在2026年拥有更健康的大脑吗？报名参加Well的5天挑战赛。-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/15/well/mind/brain-health-challenge-sign-up.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 10:00:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQYjhTYUNwajg5Yk41SDlKVDhEZlpySFREamVUcXVzQlREVm1kMmI4TGJGNVY0QnJrS2I4TDNEQ1pMay1VSjQtczY4RzZ4YXlxNGlQa1NmdUlsb3htZVBXZzk2cF9ybTEtMjlva2t4THU3ajVzME8xWGtKYk1DbVFQZ1liejlsdFU</guid></item><item><title>合成染料亚甲基蓝的健康宣称背后是什么？ - NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/15/nx-s1-5634680/methylene-blue-supplement-safety</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-102203" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Getty Images/Illustration Andrea D'Aquino for NPR
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Wellness enthusiasts seeking to hack their way to health and longevity have a new favorite remedy — one that &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@sarahlawuk/video/7140354795554213125?_r=1&amp;amp;_t=ZP-92AJZMNpvag" target="_blank"&gt;stains their tongues blue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Methylene blue has been around since the 1870s when it was used as a textile dye. Since then it's been prescribed as an antimalarial treatment and an antidote for cyanide poisoning. Today it's&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;medication approved by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration as treatment for methemoglobinemia, a rare blood disorder.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But online influencers are promoting it for what they claim are its wellness properties. It's taking off among biohackers, who seek to optimize their health via lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/pifmGCPjluM" target="_blank"&gt;Commentators speculated&lt;/a&gt; that Robert F. Kennedy Jr. takes methylene blue after a video of the nation's top health official circulated early this year. He can be seen using an eyedropper to mix a cobalt blue liquid into a cup of water. Kennedy never confirmed what he was taking, though the vibrant color and applicator resembles the methylene blue products that are sold by online retailers. And Kennedy's known for &lt;a href="https://subscriber.politicopro.com/article/2025/07/rfk-jr-takes-his-vitamins-but-this-vitamin-industry-ceo-isnt-sure-hes-an-ally-00476806" target="_blank"&gt;taking supplements&lt;/a&gt;, and has a track record of embracing debunked or unproven scientific claims.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Claim:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Methylene blue improves the function of mitochondria — components of our cells which convert nutrients into energy — and that results in a host of benefits, such as slowed aging, better mood and sharper cognition. Some even claim it alleviates jetlag.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Evidence:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Lab studies and animal trials have found that methylene blue can help cells make energy more efficiently by giving mitochondria an easier way to move electrons when their normal pathways are damaged or stressed, says Lorne Hofseth, who studies dyes' effect on cancer and inflammation at the University of South Carolina College of Pharmacy.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;He also cites studies done in rodents and worms to show that methylene blue improves brain energy use, reduces inflammation, and protects against neurological damage.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When it comes to research in humans, there have been several smaller trials in select populations that have shown antidepressant or cognitive benefits from pure methylene blue. But Hofseth says these findings remain preliminary — which is why he strongly discourages people from taking it as a supplement, as right now, the risks outweigh the benefits.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"You're wasting your money," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That doesn't mean methylene blue is a total scientific dead end. Hofseth points to promising work being done in the UK on a modified form of the dye to treat Alzheimer's disease. But this methylene blue is different from the dye people are purchasing as an over the counter supplement.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So why might online influencers feel convinced that methylene blue makes them feel better and think faster?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Cognition is subjective," says Nicole Brandt, a professor at the University of Maryland School of Pharmacy who studies geriatric pharmacotherapy. "We have good and bad days if we sleep well, if we eat well."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Risks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In addition to wasting money, Hofseth and Brandt both warn of adverse side effects from methylene blue. That includes serotonin toxicity, which is a serious drug reaction, which can cause elevated blood pressure, diarrhea, seizures, and even death: People who take certain antidepressants, including Zoloft and Lexapro, are especially at risk.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Methylene blue &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4091817/" target="_blank"&gt;could also be dangerous for&lt;/a&gt; people who have a &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/genetics/condition/glucose-6-phosphate-dehydrogenase-deficiency/" target="_blank"&gt;genetic disorder&lt;/a&gt; affecting red blood cells called glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase deficiency.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Another concern is people may not know what they're getting when they buy methylene blue over the counter.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We really don't have good oversight, or any oversight to nutritional supplements and what's in them," Brandt says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Unlike drugs, supplements are not approved by the FDA for safety and efficacy before they go on the market. But they do have to follow certain rules around labeling. Manufacturers are also subject to inspection, and the FDA monitors safety concerns once products are on the market.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;However, federal regulators have finite resources and are unable to catch every bad actor, says Dr. Joshua Sharfstein, a professor at Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health and a former principal deputy commissioner at the FDA. That's why he says it's buyer beware with methylene blue, and similar products&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"The internet is a big place," he told NPR. "There are a lot of products for sale that are not safe."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It's also not clear whether methylene blue meets the regulatory definition of a supplement. It's listed in an FDA database as a generic drug that requires a prescription.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And most methylene blue products are not in a federal registry of dietary supplement labels, according to Jeff Ventura, vice president for communications at the Council for Responsible Nutrition. Many of the products seen online are not explicitly identified as supplements.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The FDA did not respond to a request for comment about how it's possible for online retailers to sell methylene blue without a prescription.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bottom Line:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Those who still want to try methylene blue should first talk to a clinician to ensure they're not at risk for adverse side effects. And if someone's taking methylene blue for a specific health concern, like brain fog or fatigue, a primary care provider can also help address those issues, says Sharfstein.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If you do decide to try the product, be warned: It could turn your teeth, tongue and urine bright blue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQV3dYT2lFem9PLURsdjFWQmlVZm03WWVDeE9raVJtY1VQU2d3bWZXcmFPbkZ0SmppLWFFMjhaUGVJQnRmeEg2dTlSYWh6SDZzeHRrdE1JOEo4X0hpMU1jbmRWMGxoOU92YjNFUFlUX1daLTVVQ1NscGlJTDhwOWR5bUhVRQ</guid></item><item><title>肠道不健康的迹象和恢复肠道的4种方法- CNET</title><link>https://www.cnet.com/health/medical/signs-unhealthy-gut-how-fix-it-microbiome-expert/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="c-ShortcodeContent c-ShortcodeContent-theme:default sm:u-col-2 md:u-col-6 lg:u-col-12"&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p1"&gt;An unhealthy gut can look like more than just a casual &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/upset-stomach-these-6-natural-remedies-may-help/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;stomachache&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. After all, Gail Cresci, a microbiome expert at the Cleveland Clinic, describes the microorganisms inside your gut as "little pets living inside your intestinal tract," and like real-life pets, they can exhibit multiple symptoms that reveal they aren't at their best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p2"&gt;As your gut's microorganisms help you digest food, produce vitamins and hormones, support your &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/best-zinc-supplements/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;immune system&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and regulate inflammation, they have a significant impact on your overall health. That's why it's crucial you pay attention to signs your gut may be unhealthy, and do what you can to get things back on track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr data-ng-block="{" id&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Don't miss any of our unbiased tech content and lab-based reviews. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a target="_self" data-id="6481f688-630b-45e1-a512-ff6f56bd8201" href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=cnet.com"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Add CNET&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; as a preferred Google source.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr data-ng-block="{" id&gt;&lt;h2 id="76c0aa22-bb3e-48f3-a1f7-30d06e799aa4" data-ng-block="{"&gt;7 signs of an unhealthy gut&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you're bloated or you have lots of gas, you may have a disrupted composition and function of the gut microbiome," Cresci said, adding that the only way to know for sure is to have it measured with a microbiome test like a stool sample.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six &lt;a target="_self" data-id="af31c9b8-8e82-425e-9831-648529de341e" href="https://www.healthline.com/health/gut-health#improving-gut-health"&gt;other signs&lt;/a&gt; of an unhealthy gut may include: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-ng-block="{" id&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fatigue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Food intolerance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Skin irritation or problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trouble sleeping&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vomiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Upset stomach&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research has &lt;a data-id="6be54eaa-9115-468a-be0c-92ab77c90ac0" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6048199/" target="_self"&gt;linked skin issues like acne and psoriasis&lt;/a&gt; to the gut. Studies are also looking into how the gut biome &lt;a data-id="6be54eaa-9115-468a-be0c-92ab77c90ac0" href="https://academic.oup.com/hropen/article/2022/2/hoac015/6553029" target="_self"&gt;affects reproductive health&lt;/a&gt; and hormone levels.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-all-top spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-small c-shortcodeImage-pullRight"&gt;&lt;a rel href="https://www.cnet.com/health-tips/" target="_blank" class="c-shortcodeImage_imageContainer"&gt;   &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="94708dfd-99a0-4fe2-b095-7e92f882caaa" data-ng-block="{"&gt;How to keep your gut healthy &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to see a doctor to determine the root cause of your health concern and rule out other conditions. Making changes to your diet or routine that may improve your gut and overall health is a good first step.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cresci also said that there's no exact standard for the perfectly healthy gut microbiome because everyone's composition is so different. Bearing that in mind, here are four things you can do to help keep it on the right track.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone's gut microbiome is different, so there's no model for what a perfectly healthy one looks like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Carol Yepes/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="01fc1652-fb16-4b9a-a088-ffe23a8edab5" data-ng-block="{"&gt; 1. Eat gut-friendly foods &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gut microbiome prefers foods we can't digest. This includes &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/is-fibermaxxing-new-protein-goals-asked-nutrition-experts/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;foods with a lot of fiber&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, such as fresh fruits, vegetables, whole grains, legumes, seeds and nuts; foods we already know we should eat for their nutritional properties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Cresci, foods high in sugar and fat and low in fiber should be removed from your gut or eaten in lower amounts. "These are all associated with the consumption of a Western diet, which is also associated with a disrupted microbiome," she said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond a gut-healthy diet, which not-so-coincidentally coincides with a &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;span&gt;heart-healthy diet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, eating fermented foods can help replace the good microbes and their metabolites. Cresci lists yogurt, kombucha and kefir as examples.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="5ac7a098-85ca-486b-b30b-0c2980f6f670" data-ng-block="{"&gt; 2. Make note of the medications you're taking &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a well-known fact that taking antibiotics &lt;a target="_self" data-id="dce02fc7-a605-4e78-86af-53300e39ae08" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7732679/"&gt;disrupts, at least temporarily, the family of "good" bacteria&lt;/a&gt; thriving in your body. Some &lt;a target="_self" data-id="dce02fc7-a605-4e78-86af-53300e39ae08" href="https://www.cdc.gov/antibiotic-use/community/pdfs/aaw/au_arent_always_the_answer_fs_508.pdf"&gt;common side effects&lt;/a&gt; of taking antibiotics include nausea, diarrhea and developing yeast infections. If you're prescribed an antibiotic or have recurring infections that have you taking antibiotics often, ask your doctor about what you can do to help minimize the disruption to your microbiome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other medications that can disrupt our microbiomes, Cresci says, include those that alter the pH of the stomach and take away acid. Examples include proton pump inhibitors, aka PPIs, and histamine H2-receptor antagonists or H2 blockers, which are used to reduce acid reflux symptoms and might be available over the counter.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By keeping track of the medications you're taking, you can help pinpoint the cause of your symptoms and (with sign-off from your doctor) take the appropriate steps or substitutions if gut health is an issue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="c876917b-a21c-44df-9743-beeb169eaa5b" data-ng-block="{"&gt; 3. Find the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; probiotics or supplements  &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to incorporating more yogurt or fermented foods into their diet, some people may &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;span&gt;seek a probiotic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in hopes of balancing their gut, as they're designed to &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/how-do-probiotics-improve-your-gut-health/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mimic an intact microbiota&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. If you're considering taking a supplement, including probiotics, Cresci told CNET it's important to know that probiotics are strain-specific, and "each strain has its own method of action."  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, some probiotics are designed to help people with antibiotic-induced diarrhea, but that won't work for a person taking them for bowel regularity.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You want to take the one that has been studied for whatever your problem is," she said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, keep in mind that probiotics will not completely override what you eat.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you have a bad diet, and you want to keep eating a bad diet but want to improve your microbiome, a probiotic isn't gonna help you," Cresci said. "You have to do the other part too."  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whole grains, fruits and vegetables are great food choices if you want to start healing your gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;piotr_malczyk/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="90970c8c-7c40-4c77-9db1-2c50c03fa448" data-ng-block="{"&gt; 4. Move your body every day and prioritize sleep  &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Get better sleep" or "exercise more" might sound like tired advice, but improving your sleep hygiene and &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;span&gt;squeezing in more physical activity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are tried and true ways to improve your health, including your gut health.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exercise may &lt;a data-id="74795062-398a-4c91-a327-5038c8b42238" href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/gut-health-workout" target="_self"&gt;help your gut in different ways&lt;/a&gt;, including by improving your circulation, helping your metabolism and aiding your digestive muscles, according to the Cleveland Clinic. If you dread running or don't have time to go to the gym, don't worry: There are small ways you can get your body in the habit of moving every day or at least more frequently.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting good sleep is another general piece of wellness advice tied directly to the health of our guts. According to Cresci, our microbiome adheres to the &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/sleep/internal-clock-out-of-whack-heres-how-to-reset-and-get-better-sleep/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;circadian rhythm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, too. So, if we eat when our gut microbiome isn't ready, we won't be set up to process the nutrients of our food properly.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lack of sleep also triggers an increase in stress and cortisol, which have &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;span&gt;negative mental&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and physical impacts.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's a lot going on with the gut-brain interaction, so that signals back to the microbiome, and vice versa," Cresci said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps most fundamental is the fact that when we're exhausted, we don't have the energy to check off many of the things that keep us healthy, including exercising or finding a nutritious meal -- both of which affect our gut health.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When you're sleepy, tired, exhausted, you tend not to do the things we know are good for microbiomes," Cresci said. "So it kind of perpetuates itself." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNET</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 09:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNVDg5NlJkY3RId2RsdVJDOFA2VlNVdmVadjJPalZjdVNuc3hNenNjQ0gxaUlJa0J5bkRCVkJqZ2NWUHpzTi1nR1Q0a09OZ2RPT3hITlRuMkJYaHotYXNWdHR0emlQNUh4WUdsdFRBbTIzMW1tLW5fSkZaVTVvV2FhczZmTzRmaTNnbVlHX3Vn</guid></item><item><title>AIIMS研究发现，心脏病是45: 5以下人群猝死的主要原因您应该注意的“不寻常”警告信号-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/aiims-study-finds-heart-disease-as-the-leading-cause-of-sudden-death-in-people-under-45-5-unusual-warning-signs-you-should-pay-attention-to/photostory/125969976.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turns out, you are never too young to fall prey to heart disease nowadays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new AIIMS study has brought in a major health alert for India and the world: Heart disease has become the leading cause of sudden death among people in the age group of 18 to 45. Once considered an older person's disease, cardiovascular causes are striking younger adults who often appear healthy just moments before collapsing suddenly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a one-year autopsy-based study from AIIMS, it was found that more than half of all sudden deaths in this age group were due to heart-related problems, the major killers being CAD along with other cardiovascular conditions. Sudden loss of consciousness was the most common symptom before death, often leaving families in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The particular report carries much significance, as it advocates for a better level of awareness regarding heart disease, especially in seemingly healthy persons. The early recognition of subtle and atypical warning signs can save lives. Whereas the classic symptoms of a heart attack, like sharp chest pain, are well-known to all, in many young adults, these atypical warning signs do not appear serious on the face of it. Early detection and timely intervention make all the difference — it saves lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 03:47:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2gJBVV95cUxNS1RRTkdEYkpyQTZNNTJSUmZlc2E4WjhNNjlRQlBBdzNydkdHcDhBZElBT2xMcko5V01TenJDcEZUTk1PbG01Z2RYRzNfY1B4WHB4U0ROOFNlcHUzdWdINExfcEpraVF3d2dMaVdXU1ZSTUw1Yjh2eGN3RVNwblZaNFZYRDZ4NTRqRFBDWUxPTWNiVjFjZG9iMTFYUGZOM1hwRXlqdkptSkpzcllyR2w5cjVtTnItN0pOOVNVYXphazcxc3RWMmVBMC1lT0pqRjVIQjJ5MkhTR1JKcnBzV0JMZUl5TDg3eW92LS00VDFQT1dDOEZ2TFRMaXhDYldURHFNYWRrVV9EWUo5dVBsRHBLNlFobGNiNUs1TGk2Q0FVQ1JkLWxURWJMVlFqclpOQW56dS1zNktRSEhESldnSWpDdzY2a01fajBaSG83cEUzLVNQQ24zd05IR3VB0gHiAkFVX3lxTE0zSFFQVWx3TlptMUdWdDdvazh0dHc0N2lxM0JXTXI3V3gxUGJIaENYeFNEZWh4NnE4WmlOd0NfWk14UzVxSG4xODBfaUYycVY4WE5tYkpQdFdNejJJZXN1QnFEek5KM1FpTm5XYWFkOGhhS2VZd0RmbG5ZTTNkRkFmOTh6RzVfei1iMVI4VE1UeURsYXppMnhwN1F5Si0wZzA0WjFHcDM3SEEycGFJU0VCSlQtZ3VfbUVYZFFWcUVHT1BkN1BnbEpXTzE3SXBQeFlmamxOR3F5aFFBNGd2UXREWXBfaVVGM25kQVAyX3RjbmNYcHY0RzE3dHJaNGtoWGtWWG95U1psTDN5SlVQMEkyaXpFUnRNbjlwb0VVbmZFMm8yLVpGWVB1b0FGQ2w0eGpvTlE2RXFGQXdjUHNFYnpXUHpYcFEydk5mQk1GMEpjRmZpWndUakNqdmRRdENIRldDdw</guid></item><item><title>专家解释如何为英国“超级流感”浪潮做好准备- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/expert-explains-how-to-prepare-for-wave-of-uk-super-flu</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The NHS is facing severe pressure this winter as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt; cases surge earlier than usual, with some calling it "super flu".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's what you need to know about this year's flu season and how to protect yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is 'super flu'?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professor Meghana Pandit, NHS national medical director, &lt;a href="https://www.england.nhs.uk/2025/12/nhs-facing-worst-case-scenario-december-amid-super-flu-surge/"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;: "With record demand for A&amp;amp;E and ambulances and an impending resident doctors strike, this unprecedented wave of super flu is leaving the NHS facing a worst-case scenario for this time of year."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/worlds-first-death-from-h5n5-bird-flu-strain-reported-in-us"&gt;World's First Death From H5N5 Bird Flu Strain Reported in US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although this term has now been repeated frequently in the media, it was not intended as a new scientific designation. Although the flu season began early, both the spread of the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; and the severity of illness remain within what experts consider normal for a flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Influenza&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt; are constantly evolving to evade our immune system, which is why the flu vaccine must be updated regularly. Some years the virus mutates more than others, and it typically undergoes a major change every &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/15218094/"&gt;four to five years&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The "subtype" of flu that is dominant this year, called influenza A/H3N2, has been around since &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7144439/"&gt;1968&lt;/a&gt;, and there have been over a dozen such changes in that time. By this definition, we see "super flu" every few years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is the situation in the UK really as bad as some headlines suggest?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The situation isn't unprecedented – it falls within the range of what scientists would expect in a bad flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_185494" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185494" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/person_with_flu_642.jpg" alt="person with the flu on a couch " class="wp-image-185494 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/person_with_flu_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/person_with_flu_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-185494" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The winter flu season in the UK might be bad, but it's not unprecedented. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADerLg27AE/"&gt;tommaso79/Getty Images Pro/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the season started early, it is misleading to directly compare the number of cases and hospitalisations to the same week in previous years. In fact, the situation is comparable to previous years after taking the early season start into account, as a &lt;a href="https://zenodo.org/records/17704679"&gt;recent analysis&lt;/a&gt; my colleagues and I conducted shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Which areas of the UK are worst affected?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most important consideration from a public health perspective is the burden on healthcare systems in different regions, which is determined by what the virus is doing and what resources are available in those regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The available data only provides general infection trends at regional levels. England's influenza season started &lt;a href="https://scotland.shinyapps.io/phs-respiratory-covid-19/"&gt;earlier than in Scotland&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://phw.nhs.wales/topics/immunisation-and-vaccines/fluvaccine/weekly-influenza-and-acute-respiratory-infection-report/"&gt;Wales&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.publichealth.hscni.net/services-and-teams/public-health-services/health-protection/surveillance-data/respiratory-0"&gt;Northern Ireland&lt;/a&gt;, so we might expect the situation to turn earlier in England than elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on the &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/national-flu-and-covid-19-surveillance-reports-2025-to-2026-season"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; for England from the UK Health Security Agency, the north and the Midlands are possibly experiencing higher flu rates – but not significantly so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why are we seeing more flu cases in younger people?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children and teens are more likely to get infected due to their high contact rates in schools, where a lot of spread happens, and also because their immune systems are less experienced at dealing with flu viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adults are less likely to become infected overall, as they typically have lower contact rates and their immune systems have &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.3002864"&gt;more experience with influenza&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, people over 64 are more likely to have existing health conditions that put them at higher risk of severe illness if they do become infected, and their immune systems have started to weaken in a process called &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8023351/"&gt;immunosenescence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Babies are also at greater risk of severe illness &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26702035/"&gt;as their immune systems are still undeveloped&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People of a similar age tend to have been infected with &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/article?id=10.1371/journal.ppat.1010317"&gt;similar flu viruses&lt;/a&gt;, which might explain why certain age groups are more affected by flu than others in some seasons. It might be that the virus this year happens to have found an immunity gap in children that isn't present in other age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Vaccine effectiveness is lower for older people, so should they still get the jab?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest data shows that the flu vaccine reduces the risk of being hospitalised with flu by about &lt;a href="https://www.eurosurveillance.org/content/10.2807/1560-7917.ES.2025.30.46.2500854#html_fulltext"&gt;30 to 40%&lt;/a&gt; in older people. That's lower than vaccines against some other viruses, but similar to previous years for flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_185492" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185492" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/feeling_syringe_vaccine_642.jpg" alt="person with blue gloves filling a hypodermic syringe from a vial" class="wp-image-185492 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/feeling_syringe_vaccine_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/feeling_syringe_vaccine_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-185492" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Flu vaccines reduce the risk of being hospitalised with flu by around 40% in older people. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGjcLdyAm0/"&gt;lovelyday12/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recommendations this year are therefore unchanged: vaccination is still the best thing you can do to protect yourself and help reduce the burden on the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does the vaccine have different effectiveness in different age groups?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This season's vaccines are offering &lt;a href="https://ukhsa.blog.gov.uk/2025/11/11/how-well-will-i-be-protected-from-flu-this-year-with-the-current-uk-influenza-vaccines/#:%7E:text=The%20UK%20Health%20Security%20Agency%20(UKHSA)%20monitors,flu%20*%20Epidemiological%20studies%20of%20vaccine%20effectiveness"&gt;effective protection&lt;/a&gt; against severe flu. Children are around 70 to 75% less likely to attend or be admitted to hospital with flu if vaccinated, and, as mentioned above, adults are around 30 to 40% less likely to attend or be admitted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children are offered a nasal spray, whereas adults are given an injection. Studies have shown that the nasal spray vaccine works better in children and less well in adults, which is why the recommendations are different. So one reason for the difference is that we are comparing estimates from different vaccines as well as different age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another reason is differences in existing immunity. Adults have already been exposed to many flu viruses over their lives, so the incremental gain of one extra vaccine is probably smaller – but still beneficial – than for a child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What should I do if I think I've caught it: call 111, stay home, or go to A&amp;amp;E?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay home if you are sick, rest, and take sensible precautions to avoid spreading the virus to others. Getting influenza is very unpleasant, but everyone will get it roughly &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.3002864"&gt;once every five years&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the vast majority of cases, people get better on their own. But you should still follow the &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/flu/"&gt;NHS guidelines&lt;/a&gt; regarding seeking treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Are there test kits (lateral flow) I can buy at the pharmacy, as there were for COVID?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, very similar tests exist for the flu, and you can buy these at pharmacies and online. Although it's interesting to know if it's influenza or some other virus that is making you sick, if you have flu symptoms, the advice is the same regardless of which virus caused it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is it too late to get the vaccine – given that it takes two weeks for the vaccine to properly kick in?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;No, it's not too late, and the sooner the better! Even after the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pandemic" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73047" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;epidemic&lt;/a&gt; has peaked, it will take a few months before cases reach low levels again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is still a risk of infection in that time, so any extra protection from the vaccine is still helpful.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/271959/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/james-hay-2545553"&gt;James Hay&lt;/a&gt;, Research Fellow, Infectious Diseases Modelling, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-oxford-1260"&gt;University of Oxford&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/what-is-super-flu-and-other-questions-answered-271959"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 01:11:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPTklUMUxuanBWZzgtUDlXUGs4SHdiSzZQQlFIZVROX3FERlBzcGFlZmUyQ1ZlQWFTMFZZSzB2dHd5VlNaMl96eVBpVzJGZVItaEZwV2ZtTE42N0Z5YlJNWVV1RW9CY0VHMjBRV0o4UXcwYkJXNlpDMEFqUkhHeUhaVDg2bVEtdS1UcEhtVQ</guid></item><item><title>我们的大脑仍然可以使用一个巧妙的技巧来超越人工智能- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/our-brains-can-still-outsmart-ai-using-one-clever-trick</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Despite the rapid advances in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence"&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt; in recent years, the humble human brain still has the edge over computers in its ability to transfer skills and learn across tasks. A new study reveals how we likely do this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Led by a team from Princeton University, the researchers behind the new study didn't actually run tests on humans, but instead used animals that are very close to us in terms of biology and brain function: rhesus macaques &lt;span&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rhesus_macaque"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Macaca mulatta&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These monkeys were asked to identify shapes and colors on a screen, and to look in particular directions to give their answers. While this was happening, brain scans were used to check for overlapping patterns and shared areas of activity in the animals' brains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/computers-made-from-human-brain-tissue-are-coming-are-we-prepared"&gt;Computers Made From Human Brain Tissue Are Coming. Are We Prepared?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those scans showed the monkey brains using different blocks of neurons – 'cognitive Legos', in the words of the researchers – across tasks. Existing blocks can be repurposed and recombined across new tasks, showing a neural flexibility that even the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/does-using-artificial-intelligence-ruin-your-actual-intelligence-scientists-investigated"&gt;best AI models&lt;/a&gt; can't compete with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"State-of-the-art AI models can reach human, or even super-human, performance on individual tasks," &lt;a href="https://pni.princeton.edu/news/2025/cognitive-legos"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Tim Buschman, from Princeton University. "But they struggle to learn and perform many different tasks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We found that the brain is flexible because it can reuse components of cognition in many different tasks. By snapping together these 'cognitive Legos', the brain is able to build new tasks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you can see in the video below, the animals had to discriminate between shapes and colors in three separate but related tasks that required the animals to continually learn and apply what they knew from one task to the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cognitive Lego blocks the researchers identified were concentrated in the brain's &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prefrontal_cortex"&gt;prefrontal cortex&lt;/a&gt;. The region is linked to higher cognition – solving problems, planning, making decisions – and seems to play an important role in cognitive flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that when certain cognitive blocks weren't needed, activity in them was reduced, suggesting the brain can file away the neural Legos that it doesn't immediately need to better focus on the task at hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think about a cognitive block like a function in a computer program," &lt;a href="https://pni.princeton.edu/news/2025/cognitive-legos"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Buschman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One set of neurons might discriminate color, and its output can be mapped onto another function that drives an action. That organization allows the brain to perform a task by sequentially performing each component of that task."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It explains how monkeys and possibly humans can &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-brain-has-a-hidden-rhythm-and-it-may-reveal-how-smart-you-are"&gt;adapt to challenges&lt;/a&gt; and tasks they haven't seen before, and use &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-critical-boom-in-technology-traced-back-more-than-half-a-million-years"&gt;existing knowledge&lt;/a&gt; to tackle them – something that  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73092" data-postid="185062" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt; in its current form struggles with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further down the line, the researchers suggest their findings could help train AIs to be more adaptable to new tasks. Their work could also be useful in developing treatments for neurological and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/several-psychiatric-disorders-share-the-same-root-cause-study-reveals"&gt;psychiatric disorders&lt;/a&gt; where people struggle to apply skills to new settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, these cognitive Legos show, on a fundamental level, how our brains are more flexible and adaptable than AI models, which exhibit so-called &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.1611835114"&gt;catastrophic forgetting&lt;/a&gt;: a weakness that means neural networks can't learn consecutive tasks without forgetting how to perform the last one they trained on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/heres-why-multitasking-gets-trickier-and-even-dangerous-as-we-age"&gt;task-switching&lt;/a&gt; isn't exactly great &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-multitasking-drains-your-energy-reserves-and-what-you-can-do-about-it"&gt;for our brains,&lt;/a&gt; applying what we know from one task to another can be a useful shortcut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If, as suggested by our results, the brain can reuse representations and computations across tasks, then this could allow one to rapidly adapt to changes in the environment, either by learning the appropriate task representation through reward feedback or by recalling it from long-term memory," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09805-2"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09805-2"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:02:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPWFNBLWJ3VzNKaW9oY0xGS3Bpc1Vrc0prY1ZINWgzM3p6T3BOR0kxVUg1bGhWNnhBNUJ6SWF0VGMwRzFHQ055bnNTQTRWQjRqSnNyNHBDa2JsRFEtM3UtU3djNTNweEJNWGhrQ1FLZjZFRVdDajlocDRtOWx2dHd0WXB6OVRfRDlaQmRsZw</guid></item><item><title>这位RFK Jr.的疫苗顾问对他的批评者有一些选择-Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/14/vaccine-adviser-retsef-levi-acip-rfk-kennedy-00688979</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOMGJYVDBwc01LUWwxMjk0REcxZXlQRUFpanZrRHZnRHdEbnR3M19rTTBsY1lLLVhRLW5jbnRMaFpwZlk5WEdGUVZMMWtHQXNFLWdZR3k3ZWpTT3VETWFORVh0V0VVQWpFZ2laOW1CQ0ZTbWk4SEVsMHFwV243UEdCa3phZUdVWVJ2YUhfNXNvQWlfWWQxdk42Tm93</guid></item><item><title>首次使用3D打印的人类角膜移植，实验室培养的组织在数百万盲人的“游戏规则改变者”中恢复视力-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/first-human-cornea-transplant-using-3d-printed-lab-grown-tissue-restores-sight-in-a-game-changer-for-millions-who-are-blind/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_226802" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-226802" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-226802" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash.jpg 1400w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-326x182.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-1024x571.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-768x428.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-696x388.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-1068x595.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-754x420.jpg 754w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-530x295.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-226802" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;File photo – credit: Maria Maximova&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first successful human implant of a 3D-printed cornea made from human eye cells cultured in a laboratory has restored a patient’s sight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Carolina-based company that developed the cornea described the procedure as a ‘world first’—and a major milestone toward its goal of alleviating the lack of available donor tissue and long wait-times for people seeking transplants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Precise Bio, its robotic bio-fabrication approach could potentially turn a single donated cornea into hundreds of lab-grown grafts, at a time when there’s currently only one available for an estimated 70 patients who need one to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This achievement marks a turning point for regenerative ophthalmology—a moment of real hope for millions living with corneal blindness,” Aryeh Batt, Precise Bio’s co-founder and CEO, &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/medtech/precise-bio-completes-first-human-cornea-transplant-using-3d-printed-lab-grown-tissue" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said in a statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For the first time, a corneal implant manufactured entirely in the lab from cultured human corneal cells, rather than direct donor tissue, has been successfully implanted in a patient.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company said the transplant was performed Oct. 29 in one eye of a patient who was considered legally blind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is a game changer. We’ve witnessed a cornea created in the lab, from living human cells, bring sight back to a human being,” said Dr. Michael Mimouni, director of the cornea unit at Rambam Medical Center in Israel, who performed the procedure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JUST WOW&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Tooth Is Implanted in 34-year-old’s Eye to Restore His Vision After Two Decades" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/tooth-is-implanted-in-34-year-olds-eye-to-restore-his-vision-after-two-decades/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Tooth Is Implanted in 34-year-old’s Eye to Restore His Vision After Two Decades&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was an unforgettable moment—a glimpse into a future where no one will have to live in darkness because of a shortage of donor tissue.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubbed PB-001, the implant is designed to match the optical clarity, transparency and bio-mechanical properties of a native cornea. Previously tested in animal models, the company said its graft is capable of integrating with a patient’s own tissue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outer layer of the eye—covering the iris and pupil—can end up clouding a person’s vision following injuries, infections, scarring and other conditions. PB-001 is currently being tested in a single-arm phase 1 trial in Israel, which aims to enroll between 10 and 15 participants with excess fluid buildups in the cornea due to dysfunction within its inner cell layers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Precise Bio said it plans to announce top-line results from the study in the second half of 2026, tracking six-month efficacy outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGHT RESTORED WITH STEM CELLS&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Sight Restored to People Blinded in Eye Accidents Using New Stem Cell Treatment" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/sight-restored-to-people-blinded-in-eye-accidents-using-new-stem-cell-treatment/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Sight Restored to People Blinded in Eye Accidents Using New Stem Cell Treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The corneas are designed to be compatible with current surgery hardware and workflows. Shipped under long-term cryopreservation, it is delivered preloaded on standard delivery devices and unrolls during implantation to form a natural corneal shape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“PB-001 has the potential to offer a new, standardized solution to one of ophthalmology’s most urgent needs—reliable, safe, and effective corneal replacement,” said Anthony Atala, M.D., co-founder of Precise Bio and director of the Wake Forest Institute for Regenerative Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;STAR POWER&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Kate Winslet Makes Dreams Come True for Girl Losing Her Sight–Bringing Her to the Theater and Funding a Safari" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/kate-winslet-makes-dreams-come-true-for-girl-losing-her-sight-bringing-her-to-the-theater/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Kate Winslet Makes Dreams Come True for Girl Losing Her Sight–Bringing Her to the Theater and Funding a Safari&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The ability to produce patient-ready tissue on demand could lead the way towards reshaping transplant medicine as we know it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Edited from &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/medtech/precise-bio-completes-first-human-cornea-transplant-using-3d-printed-lab-grown-tissue" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt; by Conor Hale)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 18:00:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7AFBVV95cUxNSUg3Qld5d0RRRklLV1kxWmd3M2MzYnVUZG9ValpNQ3BNQWp5Sm1IeVUzdGJpWWpIdWhIY2JwMVhYTHVjaTFDN3lqME9fNFZxNVVWQnNZcDVaNTQ0TDl0eTNnNnFvZDBTUEZLYlkyMnBaRk94SHNhRDlVR2NrZVRlamR4VFNSYmlZRjBWcGc1ZklfZXVtMlBrRmladFhPS0JQSVhrVlZzQTVjQmdmOTRGVXdMYTZuTlRUWkxZMFh6Zk1tQ0pxUUtSOXpvaENFRXlvYnBqVFBvbHNPcG9jbEprMkFCQm1Db2pVT2h2dQ</guid></item><item><title>我丈夫在未经我允许的情况下向我释放了他的幻想。我不知道我们的婚姻能否幸存下来。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/sex-husband-bed-advice-bathroom-fight.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4iu6hd005pyum21bx5p45j@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhbih001v3b786hv4re0b@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do it,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="103" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3y001y3b78pxeqfuzt@published"&gt;My husband recently surprised me with something unexpected when we were in bed. We had just finished having sex when he stood up and gave me a golden shower. I was shocked and disgusted and fled the room. After I had washed off, I angrily demanded to know why the hell he would do such a thing. He said he had been fantasizing about it for more than a year and needed to “get it out of his system.” I’m not sure if I can trust him again and we haven’t had sex or slept in the same room since. Is it worth trying to save my marriage?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3z001z3b78t4ttc906@published"&gt;—Pissed Off&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3z00203b78t4uw0fs2@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Pissed Off,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="111" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3z00213b78tumkn8xt@published"&gt;It’s worth doing what you’re doing now—refusing sex and sleeping in separate rooms—while you sort out your feelings. Sometimes, it’s unfair to judge people based on their worst behavior; at other times, the worst behavior is so scarring that it ends up defining the relationship for us, like it or not. Now is the time to take stock. Is the relationship otherwise loving, with open communication and a strong sense of equality/both partners’ needs being met? Or was this a leak from a torrent of domineering behavior that disregards your ability to consent in favor of his comfort/pleasure? That is, is this plausibly a one-time thing, or part of a pattern?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="237" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs4100223b78wvgjqh7i@published"&gt;His peeing on you without discussing it with you first was not OK. Though there are plenty of piss enthusiasts out there, many people are disgusted by the notion for good reasons: Most of us are taught from an early age that such waste is dirty and should be avoided at all costs. As with any kink or fetish, though, regardless of the cultural associations around it, it should have been discussed ahead of time and you should have been given the opportunity to voice your disinterest. You had no reason to expect that your husband would do this, especially because you were still in bed. Those who are into piss tend to arrange for such play to be carried out in a manner that is easy to clean after—they may love it, but they typically don’t want to live in the smell of it. This may involve doing it in the shower/bathtub or putting special sheets on the bed that contain the liquid without absorbing it. There was an overall lack of consideration on your husband’s part by not discussing his interest with you ahead of time and by then &lt;em&gt;pissing in the bed you sleep in&lt;/em&gt;. It’s “out of his system,” fine—just make sure that’s true and make clear that these kinds of surprises are not welcome. If you have a hard time moving forward, you may want to enlist the help of a counselor.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jhx7s00243b78jryngibu@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmj4ji4e900263b78l6izgfzo@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jibbn00293b78wxw6ghli@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jierp002b3b783453xkof@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="145" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs8002e3b78c5wh6h76@published"&gt;I am pretty happy in my marriage of over 30 years. My question is how to deal with the fact that my husband loves to have sex early in the morning and before we go to sleep. I wouldn’t mind but, our sex is hindered by the fact that it’s hard for my husband to maintain an erection. If he takes a pill, it will get hard but he says it gives him headaches. I hate to say this, but without the pill, his penis is either half hard or gives out in the middle of us making love—so I am very seldom satisfied. Afterward, he just goes to sleep. He thinks it’s great. I don’t want to hurt his feelings. It’s funny because I used to be the one with a low sex drive, but now I want more sex! How can I make this better?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002f3b78q8sgo572@published"&gt;—Somebody Tell Me What to Say&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002g3b78si2t2fgk@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Somebody Tell Me What to Say,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="114" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002h3b78fd08yj98@published"&gt;Definitely prioritize not hurting your husband’s feelings. This does not mean letting him off the hook for not being a thoroughly considerate partner, but you want to communicate so that he can hear you. I think first, you must determine what it is that you want. You are “dealing” with your husband’s penchant for early morning and late night sex. What would be better for you? Figure it out and ask for it. You’ve been doing it his way as a matter of default—that has bought you leverage. “I think it would be really hot if we …” is a positive way to frame this as a potentially pleasurable experience for both of you.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="127" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002i3b787n3ychj7@published"&gt;Other people’s erections are, uh, hard to manage. He’s talked about getting a headache from pills before, so maybe that’s your way in. I don’t know how extensively he’s sampled the different PDE5 inhibitors on the market, but sometimes people tolerate them differently. So if sildenafil (Viagra) gave him a headache, he may want to try tadalafil (Cialis) and/or vardenafil (Levitra) to see if he has better results. He could also try a cock ring. This is a delicate topic and you should handle it as sensitively as possible. It is fair for you to want a more reliable dick, but in attempting to achieve that, don’t insult him. You might ask him if he’s satisfied with his erection quality. If he’s not, there’s an in, too.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivsa002j3b78yvb1qf7z@published"&gt;Say he has no designs to do anything about the erections that underwhelm you. Are there other means of getting off that would suit you? If so, request them: oral, manual, toys, etc. You have every right to ask him to help you orgasm before he turns over and falls asleep. You can say something like, “I’m happy that you find our sex so satisfying—can you help me get off, too?” And then tell him how you want him to do that. Be specific.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jizb4002l3b78t0u6t4yc@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmj4jj5le002n3b7874c91s3q@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Us Your Questions About the Workplace!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="36" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jjgqg002q3b78r8o3cucc@published"&gt;The columnists behind our advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jjkks002t3b782uirr9pd@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jjobl002w3b78qu4voslp@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="43" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g300303b78bcyxmonb@published"&gt;I am a newly married gay man, and I thought my husband and I were going to be spending Christmas with my sister and her family. Except, she just added a condition that has me wondering whether to speak to her ever again.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g300313b78foq8tbk1@published"&gt;She and her husband have a son who just turned 3, and she said that she wants my husband and me to sleep in separate bedrooms while we stay over. Her claim is that he’s “too young to understand” why we would be sharing a room. My brother and his wife have stayed over at their place before, and when I asked him, he said they have never been faced with this sort of request (luckily he’s on my side). I have a suspicion that my sister’s husband is behind this, as he’s very Catholic.  This feels like a slap in the face to put it mildly. Is it worth reconsidering our relationship?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400323b785fpqtwnf@published"&gt;—I Thought I Had a Supportive Sister&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="8" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400333b78nh9uv866@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear I Thought I Had a Supportive Sister,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="222" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400343b78svsjulg9@published"&gt;Your sister’s condition is rude and discriminatory. I think it is also based on a fallacy. Her son is not too young to understand why you’d be sleeping in the same room. If he notices at all, which is unlikely as he is 3 and still exists mostly in his own head, all his parents would have to say to him is that his uncle is staying in the same room as another man because they are married. Unless a huge deal is made about something like this, kids tend to roll with the punches. Some uncles marry women, others marry men, still others marry people who don’t fit neatly into either category. Some never get married. Easy. If for some reason, this isn’t easy, there are several picture books made for kids that explain LGBTQ+ identities—&lt;a href="https://www.readbrightly.com/30-great-lgbtq-books-kids/"&gt;here’s a big list of them&lt;/a&gt;. Gay people are a part of the world this kid lives in, and shielding it from him is an exercise in futility. In fact, your presence in his life and household gives his parents the opportunity to explain that some people are gay, which may be different than what he is used to, but makes you no less worthy of familial bonds and love. That your sister and her husband seem to want to bury this truth is very disappointing.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400353b78f90gejd5@published"&gt;I don’t know if this is worth completely burning a bridge, though. There’s a middle ground to explore where you refuse discriminatory boarding terms but keep your sister in your life. It seems like this is the first time you’ve come up against something so overtly steeped in homophobia from this family member—you haven’t yet pushed back nor seen her reaction to the pushback. I don’t think you should tolerate sustained bigotry, but I also know that sisters are hard to come by and it’s worth finding a solution to keep family members in your life. It’s not always possible, but you should at least try.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="103" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400363b78q3b4h2eq@published"&gt;I would tell her that you and your husband will not be sleeping in separate rooms, nor should you have to change your way of life for the sake of a 3-year-old. (Incidentally, I have no time for people who talk about how queerness risks confusing children. To be a child is to be in a state of perpetual confusion, and as detailed above, this one’s particularly easy to clear up.) But you could get a hotel/Airbnb nearby so that you can spend time with your family during the holidays. This way you don’t have to compromise your marriage &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; your holiday plans.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk8g400393b78xm7r1qlp@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmj4j7mih001n3b786vzo892s@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4j7ukn001r3b78q1f4mlo8@published"&gt;Growing up, I was really into kink. When I met my late husband, it was a big part of my life, and he and I were heavily involved in our local BDSM scene. When he died in 2019, I felt like that part of my life died with me. I’ve gotten back into sex and dating, and I’ve mostly been having vanilla sex. It’s … not satisfying. I find myself missing kink, but it’s also caught up in missing my husband. My friends think I’m just mourning and confused, but I’m not so sure. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/12/new-sex-interests-friends-grief-advice.html"&gt;Is there a way to get back into kink after what I’ve been through?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmj4iu6hd005syum2ar5pu42m@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQbnJJUm9lRHhwZ3FCQ1JqSjZxZ3pnbFJJckZidmhCSTg0UDRlVDhTYkI1QTZLbWFMWkJZVi1ZUlZtVkt0ZjI4Q2t1UTlMeXIwUDVjSUpFS3hxcGdINWo3OFp6UzJwcVRwNndkeDNwVFNkcUV0Y1BVTmp2NDd2S1B0MQ</guid></item><item><title>哈佛肠道发现可能会改变我们治疗肥胖和糖尿病的方式- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251214100926.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;A research project supported by FAPESP and carried out at Harvard University in the United States has identified a set of metabolites that move from the intestine to the liver and then on to the heart, which distributes them throughout the body. These circulating compounds appear to influence how metabolic pathways function within the liver and how sensitive the body is to insulin. The findings point to potential new strategies for treating obesity and type 2 diabetes. The study was published in &lt;em&gt;Cell Metabolism&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The hepatic portal vein drains much of the blood from the intestine to the liver. Therefore, it's the first place to receive products from the gut microbiome. In the liver, they can be conjugated, transformed, or eliminated, and then enter the systemic circulation," explains Vitor Rosetto Muñoz, first author of the study and postdoctoral researcher at the Ribeirão Preto School of Physical Education and Sports at the University of São Paulo (EEFERP-USP) in Brazil.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"By analyzing the blood leaving the intestine and the peripheral blood circulating throughout the body, we were able to more accurately observe the enrichment of these metabolites derived from the gut microbiome in each location and, consequently, how they can modify hepatic metabolism and metabolic health," adds Muñoz. He completed this work during an internship at the Joslin Diabetes Center at Harvard Medical School in the United States with support from a FAPESP scholarship under the guidance of researcher Carl Ronald Kahn.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gut Microbiome Diversity and Metabolic Disease Risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over the past several years, scientists have increasingly recognized that the gut microbiome acts as a key link between genetics, environmental factors, and the development of metabolic disorders. Studies have shown that people and animals with obesity, type 2 diabetes, glucose intolerance, or insulin resistance often have distinct gut microbial compositions compared to those without these conditions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even so, researchers still struggle to determine which specific bacteria or microbial products drive these differences or how they interact with intestinal tissues. To explore this question, the recently published study examined metabolites in the blood of mice that varied in their susceptibility to obesity and diabetes. Samples were taken from the hepatic portal vein, which carries blood from the intestine to the liver, and from peripheral blood, which travels from the liver to the heart before circulating through the body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Normally, studies tend to look at metabolites present in fecal material or peripheral blood, but they don't accurately reflect what's first reaching the tissue of the liver, which is an important metabolic organ linked to different diseases," says the researcher.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Environmental and Genetic Effects on Metabolite Profiles&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In healthy mice, the team detected 111 metabolites enriched in the hepatic portal vein and 74 in peripheral blood. When mice genetically predisposed to obesity and type 2 diabetes were fed a hyperlipidemic diet (rich in fat), the number of metabolites enriched in the hepatic portal vein dropped from 111 to 48. This finding indicates that environmental factors, such as diet, can strongly influence the distribution of these compounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The metabolite profiles in these susceptible mice also differed from those observed in a strain of mice naturally resistant to metabolic syndrome. This contrast suggests that genetic background plays a central role in shaping which metabolites appear in the hepatic portal vein.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This shows that both the environment and the host's genetics can interact in complex ways with the gut microbiome. As a result of these interactions, different combinations of metabolites may be sent to the liver and subsequently to the peripheral circulation. These metabolites likely play an important role in mediating the conditions that lead to obesity, diabetes, and metabolic syndrome," says Muñoz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing Microbiome Disruption and Metabolite Effects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To identify which bacteria and microbial byproducts contribute to these metabolite patterns, the researchers treated obesity and diabetes susceptible mice with an antibiotic designed to target specific intestinal microorganisms. As expected, the treatment altered the microbiome and changed the balance of metabolites in both peripheral blood and the hepatic portal vein.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One outcome was an increase in metabolites such as mesaconate, which participates in the Krebs cycle, a fundamental energy-producing pathway in cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using this insight, the scientists exposed hepatocytes (liver cells) to mesaconate and its isomers, which are chemical compounds with the same molecular formula but different structures. The treatments improved insulin signaling and regulated genes involved in hepatic fat accumulation (lipogenesis) and fatty acid oxidation, both of which are crucial processes for maintaining metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The metabolites found in the blood of these two sites, therefore, play important roles in mediating the effects of the microbiome on liver metabolism and the pathogenesis of type 2 diabetes insulin resistance, which is related to eating a high-fat diet," says Muñoz.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Next Steps in Mapping Gut Driven Metabolic Pathways&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scientists now aim to characterize each metabolite in greater detail and determine how they are produced. This deeper understanding of microbial influences on metabolism may eventually lead to the identification of molecules that could serve as new therapeutic options for metabolic diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:24:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE1iRllkR2I3OE8yX1daRkFMV3J2ajcwZDktc3ZGekVKMEVBSnlKYV85TWVYbzBQY1lzZUlQWXBFX2dwYlNzOExPN2dsMUxJZllHVm5kdGE1bE5Zek43ZnU0RG5UcTNXMzhQWEozY0hsbw</guid></item><item><title>心脏外科医生分享了您应该“绝对避免”的四种食物，这些食物会“积极毒害”您的身体- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/lifestyle/food-and-drink/food-drink-to-avoid-christmas-997708-20251209</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:15:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQclRiZnJwSDVLVDdoQTZkLUJzR0dmOExUZ2JudDNvU05qVy10Y3dQclNmeWZIQUZBdEliOTJSOHlac1Y1UV8tSWVMRExad1FzeDZFMWFPVHFaak90aXdiWVp3UVlPZkdQT1ROLU9JVzZVV1UxUmdWY0hfVXh0SnJ4VEU0VnBGX2J5R3hXZ25EOVFVa1RQWmlpRjF0Yw</guid></item><item><title>简单的饮食，是一种天然的Ozempic ，并诱使您感到饱腹感-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15257157/Nutrition-Twins-natural-ozempic-weight-loss-GLP-1.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Forget needles and prescriptions, one of the hottest trends in health right now is using nutrition and lifestyle to hack your body into making more of its own natural 'Ozempic.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The key behind Ozempic and similar name-brand medications is their mimicking of a hormone produced naturally in the body called glucagon-like peptide-1, or GLP-1. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Your body already produces GLP-1, which is responsible for appetite, feeling full and supporting metabolism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The more GLP-1 you have, the easier it is to control cravings and &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-8c6cea70-b991-11f0-b9f6-9f861087316c" class="class"&gt;lose weight&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, &lt;a target="_self" class="class" href="/wellness-us/nutrition/article-13265507/best-hacks-lose-weight-fast-easy.html"&gt;weight-loss drugs&lt;/a&gt; can cost more than $1,000 a month and require injecting yourself weekly with a needle. Many users also report undesirable side effects like diarrhea, vomiting and even suicidal thoughts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About one in eight adults (12 percent) report ever having taken a GLP-1 inhibitor. T&lt;span&gt;his includes the six percent of adults who say they are currently taking one of these drugs, according to a KFF poll.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But more and more people are exploring ways to naturally increase the hormone and harness its weight-loss abilities by eating the&lt;span&gt; right foods and following gut-supporting habits that can significantly boost how much and how often the hormone is released.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As registered dietitian nutritionists and personal trainers with more than 15 years of experience, we reveal the top foods to eat for boosting your natural GLP-1 without using the drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The Nutrition Twins (pictured) reveal the top foods to eat for boosting weight loss, along with some of their favorite products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Fiber is the foundation of natural GLP-1 support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Fiber slows digestion, stabilizes blood sugar and naturally encourages GLP-1 release, all of which support fullness and weight management. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatRHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-6a168fb0-d5d1-11f0-9789-efd82214dd7b" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15257157/Nutrition-Twins-natural-ozempic-weight-loss-GLP-1.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;Fiber options for turning on your body’s natural 'Ozempic'&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;ul class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Garlic&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Onions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Leeks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Green Bananas&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Jerusalem artichokes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Oats&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Cooked and cooled grains and potatoes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Lentils&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Chickpeas&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Beans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Apples&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Asparagus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Root vegetables&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="class"&gt;Prunes &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High-fiber foods also add volume to meals, keeping you satisfied while managing calories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prebiotic fibers are non-digestible carbs that feed beneficial gut bacteria. These bacteria ferment prebiotics into short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs), which signal your gut to release GLP-1 and peptide YY, another hormone that helps you feel full and regulate appetite. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Garlic and onions are two examples of prebiotic-rich foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Resistant starch is a special type of prebiotic fiber that resists digestion in the small intestine and reaches the large intestine intact, where it then feeds gut bacteria to produce SCFAs. This stimulates GLP-1 and PYY release, promoting fullness and helping with calorie control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Good sources of resistant starch include lentils and cooked-and-cooled potatoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another type of fiber known as fermentable fibers are found in beans, oats, apples, root vegetables and prunes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These fibers also encourage SCFA production, reduce inflammation, and enhance GLP-1 signaling, contributing to appetite regulation and supporting weight management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Protein: Satiety hormones in action&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Protein-rich foods naturally stimulate hormones that help you feel full, including GLP-1 and PYY, which signals to your brain that you have eaten enough. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pairing protein with fiber slows digestion, prolongs satiety and helps curb cravings, supporting weight management and steadier energy levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research shows that protein-rich meals - often containing around 20 to 30g or more, raise GLP-1 and PYY - though responses can vary depending on the rest of the meal and individual biology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Our top protein options to boost natural GLP-1 include eggs, fish, poultry, beans, lentils and yogurt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Prunes are a good source of fiber, which slows digestion, stabilizes blood sugar and naturally encourages GLP-1 release, all of which support fullness and weight management (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Healthy Fats: Sustained fullness and GLP-1 support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Healthy fats slow digestion and help support GLP-1 release, keeping you fuller longer and helping curb cravings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pairing these fats with fiber and protein maximizes satiety and steadies blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Even small amounts - ideal for calorie control, like a drizzle of olive oil, a few nuts or a slice of avocado - can make a meaningful difference in meal satisfaction while supporting your body’s natural GLP-1 response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Our top choices include olive oil, avocados, nuts, seeds and fatty fish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Polyphenols &amp;amp; Antioxidants: Nourish your gut and GLP-1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Polyphenols are plant compounds that feed beneficial gut bacteria and help support GLP-1 release. Foods rich in polyphenols also act as antioxidants, reducing inflammation that can interfere with hormone signaling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Top polyphenol- and antioxidant-rich choices include blueberries, raspberries, strawberries, pomegranate, dark chocolate with 70 percent cocoa or higher, green tea, grapes and apples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Healthy fats, which include those found in nuts, slow digestion and help support GLP-1 release, keeping you fuller longer and helping curb cravings (stock image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-medium health-ccox mol-style-bold"&gt;Live Probiotics: live support for your gut and GLP-1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Live fermented foods provide beneficial bacteria that support GLP-1 and PYY signaling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Key strains include Bifidobacterium, Lactobacillus and Akkermansia muciniphila, and they’re linked to increased GLP-1 production.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Akkermansia thrives when paired with polyphenol-rich foods, prebiotic fibers and omega-3s. Preclinical studies show it produces a protein called P9 that signals gut cells to make more GLP-1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some of our favorite probiotic and gut-supporting foods include yogurt with live cultures, kefir, sauerkraut, kimchi, tempeh and miso, among others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox health" data-version="2" id="mol-bbb0a5d0-d5d2-11f0-9789-efd82214dd7b" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15257157/Nutrition-Twins-natural-ozempic-weight-loss-GLP-1.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;How to easily add more GLP-1-boosting foods to your meals &lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt; &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Breakfast&lt;/span&gt;:  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Top oatmeal or whole-grain cereal with berries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sprinkle with nuts or seeds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Enjoy Greek yogurt with fruit and a pinch of chia or flaxseeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Add a few slices of avocado or a light drizzle of olive oil to scrambled eggs or savory toast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Try a smoothie with kefir, spinach, frozen berries and a scoop of protein powder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Lunch&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Toss beans, lentils or chickpeas into salads or grain bowls with a teaspoon of olive oil–based dressing for healthy fats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Include lean protein such as grilled chicken, turkey or tofu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Dinner&lt;/span&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Roast a mix of colorful vegetables and drizzle lightly with olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Include fiber-rich sides like quinoa, barley or lentils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Choose fatty fish like salmon or anchovies and rotate with lean proteins like chicken, turkey or plant-based options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Add miso soup or fermented vegetables like kimchi or sauerkraut for gut support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-bold"&gt;Snacks and drinks&lt;/span&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Include small portions of fruit, nuts, seeds and fermented foods daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sip green or black tea.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 16:08:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNa3dGNWNuTHpZYmE1MGdrSnpsNlpJNlhyVWxfTGFDN1ZQT3JGcnNfcWZ4Vjlqc0wxWktQemQ1QkIyb2ZfY09rR1hsUkpMcW9CRUdMMmdTYUpvazhVejV6Y2pEdFFORjZCVF9iMEwwQkJJSHNtQWVGUnVlNHFyYlVVWDJkb0w4a1prR1FRS2ZEWWpzdmtJZHY4MDNfa3FOZEExS0ZUX21aVmVKZw</guid></item><item><title>一个研究生的疯狂想法引发了一个重大的老龄化突破- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251213032625.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;One potential strategy for treating a wide range of illnesses involves targeting senescent cells. These cells -- also known as "zombie cells" -- stop multiplying but fail to clear themselves from the body as healthy cells normally do. They appear in many conditions, including cancer, Alzheimer's disease, and throughout the aging process. Although scientists are working on ways to eliminate or repair these cells, a major challenge has been detecting them within living tissue without disturbing nearby healthy cells.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Mayo Clinic, writing in the journal &lt;em&gt;Aging Cell&lt;/em&gt;, describe a new method for labeling senescent cells. Their approach uses "aptamers" -- short pieces of synthetic DNA that fold into three-dimensional structures. These structures can attach to proteins found on the outer surfaces of cells. In experiments with mouse cells, the team identified several rare aptamers, selected from more than 100 trillion random DNA sequences, that were able to recognize specific surface proteins and mark senescent cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This approach established the principle that aptamers are a technology that can be used to distinguish senescent cells from healthy ones," says biochemist and molecular biologist Jim Maher, III, Ph.D., a principal investigator of the study. "Though this study is a first step, the results suggest the approach could eventually apply to human cells."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How a Chance Conversation Sparked a Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The idea that led to this project began when a Mayo Clinic graduate student shared an offbeat thought during a casual discussion with a classmate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keenan Pearson, Ph.D. -- who recently received his degree from Mayo Clinic Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences -- had been working with Dr. Maher on how aptamers might be used for neurodegenerative diseases or brain cancer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, several floors above, fellow graduate student Sarah Jachim, Ph.D., was studying senescent cells and aging in the lab of researcher Nathan LeBrasseur, Ph.D.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their paths crossed at a scientific gathering, where they exchanged ideas about their thesis projects. Dr. Pearson wondered if aptamers could be adapted to detect senescent cells. "I thought the idea was a good one, but I didn't know about the process of preparing senescent cells to test them, and that was Sarah's expertise," says Dr. Pearson, who became lead author of the publication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mentors Back a Bold Student Idea&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The students brought their concept to their advisors and to researcher Darren Baker, Ph.D., whose work centers on senescent cell therapies. Dr. Maher recalls that the idea initially struck him as "crazy" but worth exploring. All three mentors supported the proposal. "We frankly loved that it was the students' idea and a real synergy of two research areas," says Dr. Maher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As early experiments produced promising results, the pair enlisted more students from their labs. Then-graduate students Brandon Wilbanks, Ph.D., Luis Prieto, Ph.D., and M.D.-Ph.D. student Caroline Doherty added new techniques, including advanced microscopy and additional tissue types. "It became encouraging to expend more effort," Dr. Jachim says, "because we could tell it was a project that was going to succeed."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revealing New Clues About Senescent Cells&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Beyond providing a tagging method, the research offered insight into the biology of senescent cells. "To date, there aren't universal markers that characterize senescent cells," says Dr. Maher. "Our study was set up to be open-ended about the target surface molecules on senescent cells. The beauty of this approach is that we let the aptamers choose the molecules to bind to."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team found that several aptamers attached to a variant of a protein called fibronectin on the surface of mouse cells. Scientists do not yet know how this fibronectin variant relates to senescence. However, its discovery suggests that aptamers may help identify features unique to senescent cells.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Potential Applications for Human Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More work will be needed to find aptamers that can reliably detect senescent cells in human tissue. If aptamers can be adapted for this purpose, they could eventually be used to deliver treatments directly to these cells. Dr. Pearson notes that aptamers are less costly and more flexible than traditional antibodies, which are commonly used to distinguish one cell type from another.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"This project demonstrated a novel concept," says Dr. Maher. "Future studies may extend the approach to applications related to senescent cells in human disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:35:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9tYzI4Y2Zzd3BRZFNJY0t3eGlzWVR1SmpqMjJFTkx5SkV5bzlTUzZfRllIdGFPUFVEUGFmUmRvUTBPWDJnLS1rR1VvMlZOVEgtMkt2TlAyU1dvY2xZYlFOeTFYMk9VMjBWSU0wWjFfdw</guid></item><item><title>我尝试了“每天超过10,000步”的步行方法–这就是为什么我是一个粉丝-独立报</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/japanese-walking-workout-iwt-10000-steps-weight-loss-b2884233.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iBibVd"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 jVZWGn"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 eZqxmv"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 tawua"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 gZmYS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 cglitp"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 keLMOw sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 dIsmaL"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;alking is an accessible form of movement with impressive health-boosting credentials; I think there is enough research available to safely make that statement. Treating &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/10k-steps-a-day-walking-b2735565.html"&gt;10,000 steps per day&lt;/a&gt; as the gold standard for a healthy lifestyle is far more contentious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number stems from a 1960s Japanese marketing campaign for a pedometer called the Manpo-Kei, or “10,000 steps metre”. It’s a nice round number, but it’s not one identified by science as the holy grail for health – a 2023 study by the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.ugr.es/en/about/news/how-many-steps-take-each-day-reduce-risk-premature-death8000"&gt;University of Granada&lt;/a&gt; suggests that, while more is better, 8,000 is sufficient “to significantly reduce the risk of premature death”​​. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="/topic/walking"&gt;Walking&lt;/a&gt; 10,000 steps also takes a fair old while. Even at a decent nick, this task is likely to take you upwards of 90 minutes each day, making it a struggle for busy folks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-31azim-0 eBMXOi nextSwipeIgnore sentry-block"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU sc-wlmftc-0 ccDPKb"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-hKDTPf hmBpZX"&gt;&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/K7Ehvq-bm6I"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, an alternative walking protocol – colloquially termed “Japanese walking” due to its country of origin – has stepped into the spotlight online. It takes just 30 minutes per day, with fitness coach and content creator &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/coacheugeneteo/?hl=en"&gt;Eugene Teo&lt;/a&gt; claiming it offers “10 times the benefits” of walking 10,000 steps per day in his viral video above. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a fitness writer, I’ve covered walking extensively, finding it’s one of the best ways to help people of all fitness levels introduce more movement into their regular routine. So, intrigued, I endeavoured to try “Japanese walking” and find out if the impressive health claims around it held water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to try the ‘Japanese walking’ method&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complete the sequence below five times without any breaks:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-kk992l-0 sc-1k7glnk-1 dDVXDN irZnNR"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Three minutes of walking at a low intensity (40 per cent peak aerobic capacity, or a relaxed pace) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Three minutes of walking at a high intensity (70 per cent peak aerobic capacity, or a brisk pace) &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of Japanese walking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The “Japanese walking” protocol comes from a study published in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17605959/"&gt;Mayo Clinic Proceedings&lt;/a&gt; journal in 2007. It was designed to test whether high-intensity interval walking training (IWT) can offer greater benefits than moderate-intensity continuous walking training, in terms of improving thigh muscle strength, peak aerobic capacity (the maximum amount of oxygen you can take in and use during exercise) and blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over five months, 60 men and 186 women with an average age of 63 were divided into three groups; no walking training, IWT and CWT (continuous walking training). The CWT group was instructed to walk at 50 per cent of their peak aerobic capacity (a fairly slow pace) and take 8,000 or more steps per day at least four times per week. The IWT group was told to complete the protocol above, four or more times per week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among participants who met these conditions, those in the IWT group saw a 13 per cent increase in isometric knee flexion, a 17 per cent increase in isometric knee flexion, and an eight per cent increase in peak aerobic capacity for walking. This was “significantly greater than the increases observed in the moderate-intensity continuous walking training group”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research also found a greater reduction in resting systolic blood pressure in the IWT group, despite the fact they didn’t spend as much time walking each week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The conclusion states: “high-intensity interval walking may protect against age-associated increases in blood pressure and decreases in thigh muscle strength and peak aerobic capacity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/life-style/japanese-walking-trend-weight-loss-b2759539.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The latest walking trend that could help burn more calories and lower blood pressure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 htsIMX"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/36/Walking-is-one-of-the-most-accessible-forms-of-movement-offering-impressive-health-benefits.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/36/Walking-is-one-of-the-most-accessible-forms-of-movement-offering-impressive-health-benefits.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/36/Walking-is-one-of-the-most-accessible-forms-of-movement-offering-impressive-health-benefits.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Walking is one of the most accessible forms of movement, offering impressive health benefits" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-263151"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Walking is one of the most accessible forms of movement, offering impressive health benefits&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (David Lovelady)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What happened when I tried Japanese walking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t have a full science lab set up at home; what I do have is two legs, a &lt;a href="/extras/indybest/outdoor-activity/sports-equipment-accessories/best-garmin-watch-b1903982.html"&gt;Garmin watch&lt;/a&gt; and a lot of walking experience, so I decided to put these to good use. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During my Monday lunch break, I took my dog for a 30-minute walk as normal. Then, at 1pm the following day, I tried the “Japanese walking” method on the same looped route, setting my Garmin Vivoactive to record both sessions and taking note of any subjective changes I felt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My usual 30-minute walk saw me accrue nearly 3,000 steps, covering 2.12km at an average speed of 14min 10sec per kilometre. My heart rate averaged 85bpm, remaining fairly constant throughout, and I burned an estimated 157 calories. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As anyone who has owned a dog might expect, there was a good deal of stopping and starting to inspect particularly interesting trees and bollards, and I defaulted to a fairly casual pace amid a busy work day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Japanese walking protocol, my numbers looked a bit different, with my fast pace falling just below 120 steps per minute and my slow pace a few shy of 100 steps per minute. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I travelled significantly further, covering 2.94km and 3,500 steps at an average speed of 10min 12sec per kilometre. My average heart rate came out very similar (86bpm) but there were noticeable peaks (104bpm) and troughs in line with the high- and low-speed intervals. My estimated calorie burn was also significantly higher: 211. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/life-style/health-and-families/how-many-steps-a-day-cancer-risk-b2756669.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How many steps to take each day to slash your risk of cancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of the Japanese walking method&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea that walking faster, or sprinkling more intensity into your exercise, holds greater benefits is nothing new. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specialist in walking for health, &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://education.ua.edu/about/directory/faculty-directory/elroy-aguiar/"&gt;Dr Elroy Aguiar&lt;/a&gt;, is an assistant professor at the University of Alabama’s department of kinesiology. He was the lead author on a 2024 paper published in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/sms.14762"&gt;Scandinavian Journal of Medicine and Science in Sports&lt;/a&gt;, which correlated as little as one minute of high-intensity activity with improved health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One of the really interesting findings from our paper was that, if you look at people’s highest one minute of activity across each day, averaged across the monitoring period, that was a very strong signal for whether they had one or more metabolic syndrome risk factors [elevated waist circumference, high triglycerides, low HDL (or “good” cholesterol), high blood pressure and high blood sugar] present,” he tells me. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another series of studies he worked on, featured in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/29858465/"&gt;British Journal of Sports Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, pointed to the fact that “if you walk at a cadence of about 100 steps per minute, that’s equivalent to what’s called ‘moderate-intensity’, and all of the research in this area suggests that most of the benefits [of walking] accumulate at a moderate or higher intensity”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond this, completing the Japanese walking method four times per week leaves you half-an-hour away from the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/physical-activity"&gt;World Health Organisation’s&lt;/a&gt; “global recommendations of at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity physical activity per week”. Add a couple of short full-body &lt;a href="/topic/strength-training"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt; sessions into the mix and you have a decent &lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/short-workouts-plan-fitness-dan-john-b2737277.html"&gt;minimalist workout plan&lt;/a&gt; for beginners. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/life-style/step-count-walking-benefits-10000-day-b2739534.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How your step count became the ultimate modern humblebrag&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 cztisH"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/09/13/09/Untitled-design-%2889%29.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/09/13/09/Untitled-design-%2889%29.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2024/09/13/09/Untitled-design-%2889%29.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Completing the ‘Japanese walking’ method a few times each week sets you well on your way to hitting the World Health Organisation’s weekly physical activity guidelines" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-263152"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Completing the ‘Japanese walking’ method a few times each week sets you well on your way to hitting the World Health Organisation’s weekly physical activity guidelines&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Harry Bullmore/The Independent)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Potential drawbacks of the Japanese Walking method&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of the information above paints the Japanese walking method in a favourable light – as it should, with the protocol delivering impressive results in a non-intimidating time-span. However, if we are questioning the claim that it is “better” than walking 10,000 steps a day, there are a few further areas to consider. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Firstly, Dr Aguiar’s 2024 paper supported the idea that the “best” walking method for reducing metabolic risk factors involves a combination of high volume (number of steps) and high intensity (walking speed). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Accumulating a high volume of walking throughout the day [8,000-plus steps], then focussing on at least 30 minutes of faster walking or jogging, would be a way to move the metrics in a positive direction and lower your metrics for each of the [metabolic syndrome] risk factors,” he says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I racked up a little over 3,500 steps when trying the Japanese Walking method – less than half of the 8,000 daily steps research has repeatedly linked to many favourable health outcomes, and short of the 5,000 mark often viewed as the threshold for a sedentary lifestyle. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using this method as part, rather than all, of your daily steps could be a better approach for achieving your health goals. However, if you only have 30 minutes per day free, it still offers dramatically more benefits than not moving at all, and improved return on investment over a regular 30-minute walk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another area where the Japanese walking method loses out to walking 10,000 steps per day is movement regularity. While the former involves a concentrated 30-minute dose of activity, the latter can be spread throughout the day, encouraging you to abandon your office chair and sofa more often. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 10-year study of 8,000 people, published in the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30551177/"&gt;American Journal of Epidemiology&lt;/a&gt;, found that those replaced 30 minutes of daily sitting with light activity had a 17 per cent lower risk of dying in that period. This even applied if they accrued these 30 minutes across short intervals throughout the day – hence why your smartwatch is constantly sending you reminders to stand up and move. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular movement can also help maintain mobility and reduce stiffness in our joints and muscles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we’re dealing with an adaptation from stillness, movement is the answer, so any movement is better than just being still,” movement mechanics expert and &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.thetrainingstimulus.com/"&gt;The Training Stimulus&lt;/a&gt; founder Ash Grossmann summarises. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final factor to consider is enjoyment. By adding a rigid framework, Japanese walking ensures intensity. However, it also meant I was unable to stop and chat to people in the park or appreciate my surroundings to the same extent. For me, this lowered the stress-busting potential of my walk, sacrificing some of the usual mental health benefits of walking for physical ones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/news/health/fart-walk-benefits-type-2-diabetes-cancer-b2744886.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the heck is a fart walk? Why this practice is being hailed as the secret to healthy aging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 cztisH"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/50/I-found-the-Japanese-walking-method-was-more-effective-at-raising-my-heart-rate-potentially-offering.jpeg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/50/I-found-the-Japanese-walking-method-was-more-effective-at-raising-my-heart-rate-potentially-offering.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/06/04/8/50/I-found-the-Japanese-walking-method-was-more-effective-at-raising-my-heart-rate-potentially-offering.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="I found the 'Japanese walking' method was more effective at raising my heart rate, potentially offering greater physical benefits, but I preferred the calming effects of a standard walk" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-263153"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;I found the 'Japanese walking' method was more effective at raising my heart rate, potentially offering greater physical benefits, but I preferred the calming effects of a standard walk&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Harry Bullmore/The Independent)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Japanese walking method: the verdict&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my time writing about health and fitness, the net positive effect of regular movement has been one of the most striking common denominators. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those looking for a minimum effective dose: any movement will do you a lot of good, particularly if your starting point is a sedentary lifestyle. But if you can fit one or two quick full-body strength training sessions, regular aerobic activity (like walking) and an occasional dash of more intense exercise into each week, it will stand you in very good stead. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Walking is among the most accessible forms of exercise there is, lowering the barrier to entry for exercise for billions of people, which is why I’m always keen to promote it. However, in the modern world, even finding time for a quick walk can be tricky for particularly busy individuals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese walking method provides a time-savvy way to enjoy many of the benefits of a greater volume of daily walking. Sure, you could enjoy higher-intensity exercise in any number of other forms, from cycling to a HIIT workout, but walking remains the most efficient – you don’t even need a change of clothes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So should you try it? Yes, especially if you’re short on time and looking for a way to squeeze health-boosting movement into your day. And should you stick with it? This depends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you enjoy this framework, or find it’s something you can stick to with a good degree of regularity, that’s the ticket to a sustainable movement habit and the many health benefits that come from it. If not, look for an alternative form of moderate- to high-intensity exercise that you find fun, and commit to this instead – consistency is the key to long-term results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/walking-10000-steps-a-day-calories-fitness-b2650416.html"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Walking 10,000 steps day might not matter if you don’t do this one thing, according to an expert&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxOc0RPQ042dmZvckQ4eDdDMVNvZWk5YmtKcHJBQWhRbEU0c1UxaVk1OUw5dTRSdy1KeV92Qi1rNnZSQWM2aHFjQy1nT1F3eldId25VUWVlTGc0WUZ6X2tVWDh4VzBQZzRFakkycHpmSVg2Q3NETW9CMjBKdFdqWkVfNFRoMzV4ZlRpdkROa3pHZ3VkazFITGVFSXpwQUw4ZXNnWVdYWXFfdVZGbXhiT1RhRnQ1cTdZUQ</guid></item><item><title>阿托伐他汀召回可能会影响数十万患者–并反映出FDA在检查海外生产的药物时遇到的麻烦-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/atorvastatin-recall-may-affect-hundreds-152027420.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you take cholesterol-lowering drugs called statins, you may have noticed a flurry of &lt;a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/money/2025/10/23/generic-statin-atorvastatin-calcium-recall/86861216007/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:news coverage;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;news coverage&lt;/a&gt; since &lt;a href="https://www.aarp.org/health/conditions-treatments/atorvastatin-recall-october-2025/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:late October 2025;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;late October 2025&lt;/a&gt; about an extensive recall of thousands of bottles of atorvastatin, the generic version of Lipitor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Both generic atorvastatin and brand-name Lipitor contain the same active ingredient, atorvastatin calcium, and are considered bioequivalent by the Food and Drug Administration. This medication is the &lt;a href="https://clincalc.com/DrugStats/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:No. 1-selling drug;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;No. 1-selling drug&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S., with over 115 million prescriptions going to more than 29 million Americans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;I am a &lt;a href="https://pharmacy.uconn.edu/person/c-michael-white/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:clinical pharmacologist and pharmacist;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;clinical pharmacologist and pharmacist&lt;/a&gt; who has assessed the manufacturing quality of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280251343626" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:prescription;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;prescription&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280241233255" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:over-the-counter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;over-the-counter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/87551225251326811" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:illicit drugs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;illicit drugs&lt;/a&gt;, as well as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028019900504" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dietary supplements;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dietary supplements&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This atorvastatin recall is large, potentially affecting hundreds of thousands of patients. But it’s only the latest in a &lt;a href="https://www.propublica.org/article/fda-drug-loophole-sun-pharma" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:series of concerning manufacturing issues;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;series of concerning manufacturing issues&lt;/a&gt; that have come to light since 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;What pills are being recalled, and why?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ascend Laboratories, based in New Jersey, originally issued the recall for &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/scripts/ires/?Event=97639" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:about 142,000 bottles;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;about 142,000 bottles&lt;/a&gt; of its generic atorvastatin on Sept. 19. Each bottle contained 90, 500 or 1,000 tablets, enough to fill prescriptions for three, 17 or 33 patients, respectively, for one month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;About three weeks later, on Oct. 10, the FDA quantified the risk of using these poor-quality tablets and gave the recall a &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/scripts/ires/?Event=97639" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Class II status;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Class II status&lt;/a&gt;, which means that the medication could cause “&lt;a href="https://pharmacyfreak.com/drug-recalls-in-the-usa-what-happens-when-the-fda-recalls-a-drug-understanding-class-i-ii-and-iii-recalls/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:temporary or medically reversible;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;temporary or medically reversible&lt;/a&gt; adverse health consequences.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Manufacturers &lt;a href="https://pharmaeducation.net/quality-control-tests-of-tablets-or-evaluation-of-tablets/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:must conduct quality tests;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;must conduct quality tests&lt;/a&gt; on random samples of tablets from every batch they make. These tests make sure the pills contain the correct dosage of the active ingredient, are made to the proper physical specifications and are not contaminated with heavy metals or microbes. If the samples test &lt;a href="https://www.gmpsop.com/what-are-the-elements-of-quality-control-process-in-pharmaceuticals/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:“out of specification”;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;“out of specification”&lt;/a&gt; for any feature, the company must conduct further testing and destroy defective batches, losing the cost of manufacturing them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In this case, sample pills &lt;a href="https://www.usp.org/sites/default/files/usp/document/harmonization/gen-method/stage_6_monograph_25_feb_2011.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:failed to dissolve properly;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;failed to dissolve properly&lt;/a&gt; when they were tested. Batches manufactured from November 2024 through September 2025 all had this defect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As with other drugs, when you swallow atorvastatin, it must &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK557405/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dissolve before the active ingredient can be absorbed;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;dissolve before the active ingredient can be absorbed&lt;/a&gt; by the body. It then goes to the liver, where it reduces the blood concentrations of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028017722009" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:low-density lipoproteins;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;low-density lipoproteins&lt;/a&gt; – also called LDL, or “bad cholesterol.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If the drug doesn’t dissolve properly, the amount absorbed by the body is substantially reduced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJMoa050461" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lowering LDL with atorvastatin;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Lowering LDL with atorvastatin&lt;/a&gt; has been shown to reduce cardiovascular events like heart attacks and strokes after a few years by 22%. When almost 30,000 people in a 2021 study stopped taking their &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2021.13186" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:atorvastatin or other statin for six months;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;atorvastatin or other statin for six months&lt;/a&gt;, the risk of cardiovascular events, deaths and emergency room visits increased between 12% to 15%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So, while patients wouldn’t immediately feel a difference if their atorvastatin tablets didn’t dissolve properly, their risk of cardiovascular events would significantly rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;What should patients on generic atorvastatin do?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;First, don’t stop taking the medication without talking with your pharmacist or prescriber. Even if you have the recalled pills, taking them is still better than not taking the medicine at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You can determine whether your medication came from Ascend Laboratories by looking at your prescription label.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Search for the abbreviations &lt;a href="https://www.printablelabeltemplates.com/wp-content/uploads/2017/12/prescription-label-template-microsoft-word-prescription-label-template-best-business-template-within-prescription-label-template-RfKgMc.jpg" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:MFG or MFR;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;MFG or MFR&lt;/a&gt;, which stand for “manufacturing” or “manufacturer.” If it says “MFG Ascend” or “MFR Ascend,” that means that Ascend Laboratories supplied the medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The first five letters of a National Drug Code, abbreviated as NDC on the prescription label, also reveal the manufacturer or distributor. &lt;a href="https://ndclist.com/ndc/67877-513/package/67877-513-10" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ascend products have the number 67877;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Ascend products have the number 67877&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If Ascend Laboratories is the distributor, a pharmacist can cross-reference your prescription number to obtain the lot number and compare it with the &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/scripts/ires/?Event=97639" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:posted lot numbers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;posted lot numbers&lt;/a&gt; on the FDA website for recalled atorvastatin. If your product has been recalled, your pharmacy may have other generic versions of atorvastatin in stock that are not part of this recall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;You should be able to tell from the prescription label whether your atorvastatin comes from the manufacturer that announced the recall. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gettyimages.com/detail/photo/elderly-woman-examining-a-medicine-bottle-in-a-royalty-free-image/2194995487" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:benixs/Moment via Getty Images;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;benixs/Moment via Getty Images&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Alternatively, the pharmacist can get a new prescription from your health care provider for another &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/009127000204200902" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:generic statin drug, such as rosuvastatin;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;generic statin drug, such as rosuvastatin&lt;/a&gt;, which &lt;a href="https://www.pharmacypracticenews.com/Clinical/Article/06-22/Using-National-Guidelines-to-Determine-Hyperlipidemia-Treatment/67209" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:works similarly;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;works similarly&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;A pattern of lapses for overseas manufacturers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While the defective atorvastatin is distributed by a U.S. company, it is actually manufactured by &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/scripts/ires/?Event=97639" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Alkem Laboratories in India;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Alkem Laboratories in India&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In fact, many aspects of pharmaceutical drug manufacturing are now occurring overseas, primarily in China and India. This has limited the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028019881692" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:FDA’s ability to provide the oversight;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;FDA’s ability to provide the oversight&lt;/a&gt; required for drugs sold in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the 1990s and early 2000s, the FDA &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028019881692" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:performed routine surveillance inspections;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;performed routine surveillance inspections&lt;/a&gt; of U.S. manufacturing plants every three years, but seldom conducted them overseas. In the wake of several high-profile manufacturing quality lapses, including at &lt;a href="https://oig.hhs.gov/fraud/enforcement/generic-drug-manufacturer-ranbaxy-pleads-guilty-and-agrees-to-pay-500-million-to-resolve-false-claims-allegations-cgmp-violations-and-false-statements-to-the-fda/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:the Indian generic drug giant Ranbaxy Laboratories;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;the Indian generic drug giant Ranbaxy Laboratories&lt;/a&gt;, Congress &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/about-fda/fda-track-agency-wide-program-performance/fda-track-generic-drug-user-fee-amendments-gdufa-performance-reports" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:established a funding mechanism;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;established a funding mechanism&lt;/a&gt; and the FDA established a universal standard for inspecting both U.S. and overseas manufacturers every five years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, the U.S. fell behind with international inspections after COVID-19 shut down international travel, and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280251343626" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:it has yet to catch up;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;it has yet to catch up&lt;/a&gt;. Additionally, overseas manufacturers generally get warning of an upcoming inspection, making the process potentially less rigorous than in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A lack of inspections for eye drop manufacturers, especially in India, led to massive recalls in 2023 after a wave of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280241233255" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:rare eye infections;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;rare eye infections&lt;/a&gt; caused some people to lose their eyesight. The problem was traced to widespread unsanitary manufacturing conditions and improper testing for sterility at overseas facilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2024, &lt;a href="https://www.medpagetoday.com/publichealthpolicy/fdageneral/114762" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:eight deaths and multiple hospitalizations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;eight deaths and multiple hospitalizations&lt;/a&gt; led an Indian manufacturer, Glenmark Pharmaceuticals, to recall 47 million potassium chloride extended-release capsules that did not dissolve properly. In February 2025, inspectors found that the company had falsified quality results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The FDA recently started &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280251343626" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:laboratory spot testing;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;laboratory spot testing&lt;/a&gt; of prescription and over-the-counter drugs arriving in the U.S. to compensate for these limitations. Outside laboratories such as &lt;a href="https://www.valisure.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Valisure;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Valisure&lt;/a&gt; also do independent testing. Independent testing has caught several dangerous products, but due to limited resources, only a few products can be tested each year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2023, Alkem Laboratories, which manufactured the currently recalled atorvastatin, had to recall 58,000 bottles of the blood pressure drug &lt;a href="https://www.hmpgloballearningnetwork.com/site/pln/news/beta-blocker-recalled-1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:metoprolol XL;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;metoprolol XL&lt;/a&gt; because the pills also did not properly dissolve. Spot testing also led to widespread recalls after FDA and Valisure laboratories found cancer-causing chemicals called nitrosamines in some &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/1060028019892222" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:blood pressure, diabetes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;blood pressure, diabetes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jama.2021.10043" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:indigestion drugs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;indigestion drugs&lt;/a&gt; tested between 2019 and 2020, as well as benzene in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10600280251343626" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:numerous sunscreen and antibacterial gel products;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;numerous sunscreen and antibacterial gel products&lt;/a&gt; tested between 2020 and early 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Raising consumer vigilance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With these growing gaps in oversight, it’s reasonable to be mindful of changes in how a particular medication affects you. If your prescription drug suddenly stops working, it might be because that particular batch of the medication was not manufactured properly. Alerting the FDA &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/safety/medical-product-safety-information/medwatch-forms-fda-safety-reporting" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:about sudden loss of drug effectiveness;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;about sudden loss of drug effectiveness&lt;/a&gt; could help the agency more quickly identify manufacturing issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2024, the FDA started &lt;a href="https://www.ema.europa.eu/en/partners-networks/international-activities/bilateral-interactions-non-eu-regulators/united-states" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sharing the inspection burden;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;sharing the inspection burden&lt;/a&gt; with other regulatory agencies like the European Medicines Agency for the European Union. Such coordinated efforts could lead to less duplication and a bump in inspections of overseas manufacturers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the meantime, however, consumers are largely at the mercy of spotty inspections and testing, and rarely hear about problems unless poorly manufactured drugs cause widespread adverse events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="http://theconversation.com/us?utm_source=Yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=related-link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related-link-0&amp;amp;utm_content=article-268364" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The Conversation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt;, a nonprofit, independent news organization bringing you facts and trustworthy analysis to help you make sense of our complex world. It was written by: &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/c-michael-white-382205?utm_source=Yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=related-link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=byline-link&amp;amp;utm_content=article-268364" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:C. Michael White;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;C. Michael White&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-connecticut-1342?utm_source=Yahoo&amp;amp;utm_medium=related-link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=byline-link&amp;amp;utm_content=article-268364" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:University of Connecticut;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;University of Connecticut&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;C. Michael White does not work for, consult, own shares in or receive funding from any company or organization that would benefit from this article, and has disclosed no relevant affiliations beyond their academic appointment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:20:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQQUVyNU1zdVBRblhLN1I0M3ZjdWF0Q1l0ZUwyaURTenpGeGdxUW9zTHR1Zk5LWWJfMkRqSkZBTEZsUXdVOTF3VkVqVmJuNTViNW1MUWVBdjRIM2tFT2wzSm9OVUVFQzZleTdWNmJYU3VpaGxQVVh0U0NOZ1JfQU9PbFRaRmNiS2k5TjB5LVYydWJFeVFW</guid></item><item><title>25岁的认证营养和健康教练的首选早餐： “它让我成功，它让我感觉良好” - CNBC</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2025/12/14/certified-nutrition-and-health-coachs-go-to-breakfast.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-articleBody--AEqcE" id="MakeItRegularArticle-ArticleBody-5" data-module="ArticleBody" data-test="articleBody-1" data-analytics="MakeItRegularArticle-articleBody-5-1"&gt;&lt;span class="HighlightShare-styles-makeit-hidden--MFwCR"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;From how much &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/04/16/4-energy-boosting-foods-according-to-nutritionists.html"&gt;energy you have first thing in the morning&lt;/a&gt;, to how &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/23/a-nutritionist-shares-the-best-grocery-foods-to-boost-mood-brain-energy-happiness.html"&gt;your mood&lt;/a&gt; ebbs and flows throughout the day, the foods you eat have a significant impact on how you feel. It's why doctors and nutritionists alike consider the first meal of the day to be most important. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://healthwithhunter.shop/pages/about-me" target="_blank"&gt;Hunter Stoler&lt;/a&gt;, a NYC-based certified nutrition and health coach, has a go-to breakfast that he eats just about every day to feel his best. Known as "&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/healthwithhunter/" target="_blank"&gt;Health with Hunter&lt;/a&gt;" on social media, the 25-year-old also recommends this breakfast to his more than 400,000 followers on Instagram and 300,000+ followers on TikTok. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll say six out of every seven days a week, I have a yogurt bowl just because I know it's balanced," Stoler tells CNBC Make It.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His yogurt bowl recipe is high in fiber and protein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="withOneTrustPlaceholder-placeholderDimensions OneTrustLoadingPlaceholder-container"&gt;&lt;span class="DynamicLoadingIndicator-spinnerParent" data-test="DynamicLoadingIndicator" data-testid="DynamicLoadingIndicator"&gt;&lt;span class="DynamicLoadingIndicator-spinner"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It sets me up for success, it makes me feel good and I'm full for a few hours after that," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The breakfast allows him to up his fiber intake, which, research shows, many people often lack in their diets. Less than 10% of U.S. adults get the recommended daily intake of fiber, according to a study which was presented at &lt;a href="https://nutrition.org/n24/" target="_blank"&gt;Nutrition 2021 Live Online&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are the key ingredients in Stoler's daily yogurt bowl. Plus, some of his other healthy breakfast options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Health with Hunter's go-to high-fiber, high-protein breakfast&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just about every morning, Stoler mixes together these five ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Non-fat Greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Half a serving of protein powder&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Frozen organic wild blueberries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Healthy cereal or granola&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spices (cinnamon, pumpkin spice or a pinch of salt)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's flexibility in that, but the structure of the meal is the same," Stoler says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That combination of protein from the protein powder and Greek yogurt, fiber from the blueberries, and potentially a little bit from the cereal or granola, is what's going to keep me really full and just satisfied."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research shows that the antioxidants found in blueberries can help &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2024/01/14/holy-grail-of-longevity-foods-that-this-doctor-eats-every-day.html"&gt;reduce inflammation, improve your brain health&lt;/a&gt; and lead to more positive health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-container--Gwv2j" data-test="Pullquote"&gt;&lt;div class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-pullquote--yciaK Pullquote-styles-makeit-pullquoteBase--I6tb3"&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-quotemark--wOJVx"&gt;&lt;span class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-quotemark1--_xuDE"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-quotemark2--Fbxk0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-wrapper--J7kni"&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-quote--PKfrc"&gt;The opportunities are endless, but remember, it's about the structure with flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-sourceWrapper--_Vvz3"&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-sourceAccentWrapper--Ubl5i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-source--S2oO1"&gt;Hunter Stoler&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Pullquote-styles-makeit-info--K2Jz_"&gt;Nutrition and health coach&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of Stoler's other go-to morning meals that's high in fiber and protein is overnight oatmeal. He mixes together almond milk or whole milk with a cup of glyphosate-free oats and a scoop of protein powder. He stores it in his fridge until the following day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Then the next morning, you have delicious oats that you could top with fruit, a nut butter, which is really great, cinnamon and maybe a little bit of Greek yogurt for more protein," Stoler says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If he's craving a warm, healthy breakfast, he toasts high-fiber bread and tops it with savory foods like scrambled eggs and avocado, or yogurt for a sweet option. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The opportunities are endless, but remember, it's about the structure with flexibility," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to give your kids the ultimate advantage?&lt;/strong&gt; Sign up for CNBC's new online course, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://smarter.cnbcmakeit.com/p/how-to-raise-financially-smart-kids?utm_source=cnbc&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=makeitarticle&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=bottom" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Raise Financially Smart Kids&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Learn how to build healthy financial habits today to set your children up for greater success in the future. Use coupon code EARLYBIRD for 30% off. Offer valid from Dec. 8 to Dec. 22, 2025. Terms apply.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-relatedContent--nvEkA" id="MakeItRegularArticle-RelatedContent-1"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-container--UeiCK"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-nonCollapsibleContent--jmjdo"&gt;&lt;h2 class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-header--DqhoP"&gt;Take control of your money with CNBC Select &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CNBC Select is editorially independent and may earn a commission from affiliate partners on links.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="ArticleBody-MobileAdhesion" class="MobileAdhesion-container" data-module="mps-slot"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 15:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOWnZWVjlqSlZoOUNOZWVmR3R1WGx1Tzh5QTdIR3BGbHhWR09BQzRERDVjXzQ5WDd0VGhGdWpzQVNvSDc0akJJcHdZc1RUbERGSnBlekx5LUE4Z0duZVVjQ1pDNndjNTNQNElsMEJtRVY0cFM2ZzRKWm1nUVdIR2VtRkktd0dYak85R3hyNjRoR0d3TEVC0gGaAUFVX3lxTE1mVGNIeXN3cGFpU0trTU5xNHRrMjV5MTNackRuMXZ4dzNiMHRVendEa2w4Wl9UUXRDSFotZ2RnXzNCdHVVaVNsTXdSY3N0aFVVa3JFU2RkVG9oVHIxUnYzSExqXzEyb25GeWdFS1UzUFVHYnZ6RnVTemg3cjRKS2xfNnBHT1F1cENZTDF6Sld6emdpczRWbDhkVXc</guid></item><item><title>如何在圣诞节前接种流感疫苗-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/cold-flu/how-get-a-flu-vaccine-before-christmas-jab/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;Her message was echoed by Nick Thayer, the head of policy for the Company Chemists Association. He said there is “no national shortage of flu vaccines, but the bulk of them are administered in October and November”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means that “by the time you get to December, some places are running low, and some will have none left from their original allocation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may therefore need to shop around for your flu vaccine. “Look on the websites for pharmacies, look on the NHS website, if you are eligible for a free jab or talk to your local pharmacy and ask,” Thayer advises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are unable to get the vaccine before Christmas, stick to the basics to reduce your risk of catching the flu. These include handwashing, avoiding crowded indoor gatherings, staying home when unwell, and self-isolating within families where possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flu jab remains a valuable layer of protection, according to Dr Clarke. It is safe and generally thought to achieve maximum protection for an individual after 10 to 14 days. Whilst there is still a chance you might get the flu after having the jab, it is likely to be milder and not last as long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protection from the flu vaccine goes down over the year and the types of virus it protects against are updated annually, which is why it is important to stay up to date with your inoculations, according to the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whilst this year’s dominant strain is thought to be a mutated version of the influenza A virus, data shows that the flu vaccine still provides good protection against it. The UK Health Security Agency found it has been &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/flu-vaccine-providing-important-protection-despite-new-subclade"&gt;70 to 75 per cent effective at preventing hospital attendance in children aged 2 to 17, and 30 to 40 per cent effective in adults&lt;/a&gt;. This is broadly in line with effectiveness in previous flu seasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost 17 million vaccines have been delivered this autumn, which is 350,000 more compared to this time last year, although Dr Clarke wishes more of us would choose to be inoculated. The latest National Flu and Covid-19 Surveillance Report shows that only 70.9 per cent of over-65s have received their flu jab this season. Rates amongst eligible under-65s are far lower, hovering around 35 per cent. “It really would make a difference,” says Dr Clarke.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:44:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPNWQ1LWRLd0ExNlM4ZXh6NFhzd01aZUI3S2d3d0gwNXNraC1nNWdUSm9SaHhzeWZMS3pveFNtNzVKUEVTUHk4WHhOTzZYZHdKM1ZNTFdQdGdyOGRlZUszMkRBX21JbTBwZjJEM25XNjd2Ui1QLUZSSFlManRLUmFGWnRYbHJvZjdCcXFWTWd1T0hjZXlqaHdvMlFidXRXWWFDdlpBS0cya3Rwdw</guid></item><item><title>Ozempic可降低糖尿病患者的癫痫风险，新研究发现- NDTV</title><link>https://www.ndtv.com/health/ozempic-may-lower-risk-of-epilepsy-in-diabetes-patients-new-study-finds-9808380</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="Art-exp_wr" id="ignorediv"&gt;
                                        
                                        
                                        &lt;p&gt;A recent study points to a potential link between GLP-1 drugs and its ability to reduce risk of epilepsy in people with type 2 diabetes. GLP-1 drugs (semaglutide) are those which mimic the function of glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) hormone. &lt;a class="sp_lnk2" href="https://www.ndtv.com/health/who-should-avoid-ozempic-doctor-explains-why-the-drug-is-not-for-everyone-9803567"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt; is the brand name for semaglutide, which is a once-weekly injectable formulation that is approved for adults in India with uncontrolled type 2 diabetes, along with diet and exercise. GLP-1 receptor agonists helps in regulating blood sugar levels, appetite and digestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;em&gt;Neurology&lt;/em&gt;, the medical journal of the American Academy of Neurology. It offers early evidence of neurological benefits from these medications. While the findings reveal only a link, larger, randomised controlled trials are needed to verify if &lt;a class="sp_lnk2" href="https://www.ndtv.com/health/weight-loss-drug-ozempic-launched-in-india-priced-at-rs-8-800-a-month-9797458"&gt;GLP-1 drugs &lt;/a&gt;truly protect against epilepsy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Study Uncovers Epilepsy Risk Reduction&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edy Kornelius, MD, PhD, of Chung Shan Medical University in Taichung, Taiwan, and study author said, "Additional randomized, controlled trials that follow people over time are needed to confirm these findings, but these results are promising, since people with &lt;a class="sp_lnk2" href="https://www.ndtv.com/health/can-chewing-curry-leaves-on-an-empty-stomach-help-in-managing-diabetes-9800482"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; are at increased risk for developing epilepsy later in life. Epilepsy can have many physical, psychological and social consequences, and many people do not respond to the current medications, so finding ways to reduce this risk is critical."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the study, researchers tapped into a U.S. health database, analysing adults newly diagnosed with type 2 diabetes who started either GLP-1 receptor agonists (GLP-1 RAs) or dipeptidyl peptidase-4 inhibitors (DPP-4 inhibitors, or gliptins). None of the participants had a prior diagnosis of &lt;a class="sp_lnk2" href="https://www.ndtv.com/health/early-diagnosis-saves-lives-why-recognizing-seizures-early-can-change-the-course-of-epilepsy-9635287"&gt;epilepsy&lt;/a&gt; or seizure. The GLP-1 medications included dulaglutide, liraglutide and semaglutide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="v-ndtv"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Key Findings and Methodology&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers followed 452,766 individuals, averaging 61 years old. Half of them (226,383) received GLP-1 drugs like dulaglutide, liraglutide, or semaglutide. The other half got DPP-4 inhibitors. These individuals were followed for at least five years, tracking new epilepsy diagnoses. Data showed 1,670 epilepsy cases (2.35%) among GLP-1 users versus 1,886 (2.41%) in the DPP-4 group-a small but notable gap. Adjusted results show a modest reduction in epilepsy risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers adjusted for confounders like age, &lt;a class="sp_lnk2" href="https://www.ndtv.com/health/high-blood-pressure-symptoms-5-signs-of-hypertension-during-pregnancy-9807707"&gt;hypertension&lt;/a&gt;, cardiovascular disease, and other comorbidities. The refined results indicated GLP-1 users had a 16% lower risk of developing epilepsy compared to DPP-4 users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breaking it down by drug, semaglutide stood out with the strongest protective signal. Dulaglutide and liraglutide also trended positively, though less pronounced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Expert Insights and Limitations&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;"More research is needed, but these findings support the theory that GLP-1 drugs may have neurological benefits beyond controlling blood sugar," Kornelius said. "It should be noted that these findings do not imply that DPP-4 inhibitors are harmful in any way or that GLP-1 drugs are definitely beneficial for brain health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GLP-1 drugs mimic the gut hormone glucagon-like peptide-1, boosting insulin release, slowing digestion, and curbing appetite. Their rising popularity, fueled by weight-loss brands like Ozempic (semaglutide) and Wegovy, has sparked interest in other benefits, including potential neuroprotective roles seen in animal models for conditions like Parkinson's and &lt;a class="sp_lnk2" href="https://www.ndtv.com/health/hearing-loss-an-early-warning-sign-for-alzheimers-study-warns-dont-ignore-these-other-red-flags-9689285"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study has its limitations. Its retrospective, observational nature can't rule out unmeasured biases. Newer drugs like tirzepatide (a GLP-1/GIP dual agonist, marketed as Mounjaro or Zepbound) weren't included, as they launched post-study period and the results don't apply to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other factors like missing data on epilepsy risk factors; family history, genetics, alcohol consumption, or sleep disorders, further impacts interpretation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these hurdles, the large sample and rigorous adjustments shows credibility. Epilepsy affects over 50 million worldwide, with diabetes as a known risk amplifier via shared pathways like inflammation and vascular damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Disclaimer: This content including advice provides generic information only. It is in no way a substitute for a qualified medical opinion. Always consult a specialist or your own doctor for more information. NDTV does not claim responsibility for this information.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                                                        
                                                                                                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                                                        

                                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NDTV</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 14:34:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQY3QwNUttSU9pSGpES0VwY2FiYkY2Q1preEZJTDZPNFAycUpJbHlLcGUzc0c1LWQzQmYwYkdUUnNNUGtVMlBaZ1RhOE9lSmxsX254aHRkMVplMkQ0WlFfbTdiMHhUZTJGNFZlV2JmZ1NXWUVOdW85STBybmQ4VlZ0RUZTUllpU2hUS2FGMjgwamRIbloxTjhfRHlweHZDT2MtMDc5TVQyVVJyTk0</guid></item><item><title>大量研究发现医用大麻患者非常令人担忧的结果-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/huge-study-medical-marijuana</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="article-featured-image-figure"&gt;
			
			
	&lt;p class="article-featured-image-caption-container"&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="article-featured-image-caption"&gt;
			Illustration by Tag Hartman-Simkins / Futurism. Source: Getty Images
 		&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	
	
	
	
	&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;In a blow to the medical cannabis establishment, a team of psychiatrists performed a detailed analysis on 15 years of cannabis research — and found not only that medical marijuana doesn’t seem to help people with acute pain or insomnia, which proponents often tout, but that almost of third of medical weed users are abusing the drug.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The findings, published in the medical journal &lt;em&gt;JAMA&lt;/em&gt;, will likely further fuel an ongoing debate on &lt;a href="https://www.theatlantic.com/ideas/archive/2025/01/marijuana-legalization-drawbacks/681519/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;whether the states went too far with legalization&lt;/a&gt;. And it comes at a wild moment: just as &lt;a href="https://www.axios.com/2025/12/12/marijuana-thc-cannabis-laws-state-federal-trump" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;president Donald Trump signaled&lt;/a&gt; this week he’ll loosen federal restrictions on weed.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“While many people turn to cannabis seeking relief, our review highlights significant gaps between public perception and scientific evidence regarding its effectiveness for most medical conditions,” said Michael Hsu, lead author and addiction psychiatrist at the University of California, Los Angeles, in a &lt;a href="https://www.uclahealth.org/news/release/evidence-lacking-medical-cannabis-most-conditions" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; about the study.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Clear guidance from clinicians is essential to support safe, evidence-based decision-making when discussing medical cannabis with their patients,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The team looked over more than 2,500 clinical trials that studied the efficacy of medical marijuana products and also certain cannabinoids, which are isolated cannabis compounds, approved by the Food and Drug Administration for use in “HIV/AIDS-related anorexia, chemotherapy-induced nausea and vomiting, and certain pediatric seizure disorders.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;On the question of pain management, the team found very little sign that cannabis help&lt;strong&gt;s&lt;/strong&gt; with acute pain. They found the same for insomnia, and sleep trials that studied whether cannabis helped with getting a restful night of slumber came up with very little evidence of its effectiveness as well.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Researchers also found that 29 percent of medical marijuana users showed evidence of “cannabis use disorder,” a catch-all term for people who show a problematic usage pattern with the drug.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;But the team did find&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;that FDA-approved cannabinoids had a “small but significant reduction in nausea and vomiting” for people going through chemotherapy for cancer and other situations where people have difficulty keeping food down. They also helped people with AIDS/HIV retain or increase body weight when up against a placebo.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“There are some legitimate purposes for these compounds,” Kevin Hill, one of the study authors and an addiction psychiatrist at Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center in Boston, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/12/health/medical-cannabis-benefits.html?partner=slack&amp;amp;smid=sl-share" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;The New York Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. “And there’s a whole other group of people who are saying they’re using it medically, but they’re really not. They’re just rationalizing their recreational use.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Related to that point, the team found that high-potency cannabis was associated with increased risk for developing signs of psychosis compared to the low-potency stuff, while smoking weed daily increased the risk for heart complications, such as coronary heart disease, myocardial infarction, and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;It’s clear that there are people who abuse medical marijuana, judging from the evidence — but something tells us that this study will not stop the growing clout of the cannabis industry, a $32 billion sector and growing.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on cannabis:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/the-byte/scientists-weed-cognitive-decline"&gt;If You Blazed Massive Amounts of Weed as a Youth, Scientists Have Interesting News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE9DZHFUQ3JBSEFNQ29TOG5nVlhESlJkamJaMkdqRDhwSjhONnVfRG5IX3RoTTZvXzh5NnpEQlF3bUhXcGpkR3V5SE5Vc2NVM1c5X2NoZ2RxdjFFZGdDY1FZR0tRNHlaX1hlODhGNnB1UEMtc1E</guid></item></channel></rss>