<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>讣告： Michael Avelar ， 1983-2025 -失落的海岸哨所</title><link>https://lostcoastoutpost.com/2025/dec/15/obituary-michael-avelar-1983-2025/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-text" class="article-text"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Michael
Avelar, of McKinleyville, passed away on November 29, 2025 at the age
of 42 after living for many years with Machado Joseph’s Disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
He
was born on March 15, 1983, in Arcata to Henry and Maria Avelar. His
arrival marked the beginning of a life defined by curiosity,
creativity, and deep connection. Michael grew up surrounded by a
warm, close-knit family who often gathered with relatives and
friends—always with plenty of food, laughter, and love.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
As a boy, he loved playing Magic cards,
exploring computers, and reading fantasy books late into the
night—long past when he was supposed to be asleep. In his early
teens, he enjoyed playing golf. Michael joined a model rocket club,
building rockets with friends and his close cousin, Jason Lowe, and
delighted in launching them thousands of feet into the sky. His
fascination with the cosmos led to countless nights of telescope
viewing and astrophotography. Michael always wanted to understand how
everything worked and why, a lifelong curiosity that shaped much of
who he became.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
At
McKinleyville High School, Michael excelled academically. He was
intellectual, scientific, and absorbed knowledge like a sponge. He
thrived on challenging projects—often working extra hours simply
because he loved learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
His passion for computers led him to pursue a
career in programming. After attending Humboldt State University,
working in the photo department at Longs Drugs, and living in Arcata,
Michael moved to Seattle, Washington. There, he spent most of his
adult career as a valued computer programmer at Moodlerooms, working
alongside his close childhood friend, Mark Nielsen, before returning
to his hometown of McKinleyville in 2012.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Michael enjoyed camping, fishing with his dad,
mushroom hunting &amp;amp; traveling—visiting Japan and Europe with
Mark, spending a summer in the Azores with family, cruising to the
Bahamas and Alaska, and taking many road trips, including two RV
journeys across the United States &amp;amp; Canada to see national parks
and monuments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
In later years, Michael turned inward toward
spirituality. He found joy in spending time with family, taking
scenic drives, and experimenting in the kitchen — making jams, cider,
preserves, and baked treats, all “in the name of science.” Michael’s love of nature remained constant throughout his life. He
also continued to enjoy his evenings playing video games.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
Michael
was preceded in death by his mother, Maria, and his brother, Nelson.
He is survived by his father, Henry; his sister, Melissa; his aunt
Elizabeth, her husband Geoff Wright; his cousins Grace, Gavin and
Garrett.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
The
family extends profound gratitude to all of Michael’s health care
providers, and especially to Jeremy, who lived with Michael as his
primary caregiver and friend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
In
honor of Michael, donations may be made to the National Ataxia
Foundation to help find a cure and ease for others. A celebration of
his life will be held at a later date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ataxia.org"&gt;https://www.ataxia.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The obituary above was submitted on behalf of Michael Avelar’s &lt;/i&gt;&lt;i&gt;loved ones. The &lt;/i&gt;Lost Coast Outpost &lt;i&gt;runs obituaries of Humboldt County residents at no charge. See guidelines &lt;a href="https://lostcoastoutpost.com/faq/#obituaries"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Lost Coast Outpost</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 14:59:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOWU9MelBLa21hVWh6M1gtbUdrOFdRWXAyTkpLU3JzRVA2RXlFRXh3MmNrTGpBVnl3dnlVZ2dqQk9Vd1ZZay1Rcmo4cXVHUjdQQ1puZ0dRU0lTOGUyVkdlQ1RnLTMzLUx4OVp5bjRGRWJIY2ZkZGFYWG9oOWprYjRFTw</guid></item><item><title>关于长期冠状病毒病因的新线索可以解锁治疗方法-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/15/long-covid-chronic-inflammation-treatment/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QX38T0PUWX1UD971BV0UV5PDK0" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Why some people experience long-lasting physical and mental effects from covid-19 could be linked to chronic inflammation, according to new research that experts say could help develop new treatments for the confounding condition that continues to afflict millions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:01:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQdGVuSHpwQ0lYVm84RWY3N0hKcjVwcnpySVN2MDhWYU5mYkh6OS1mWFF2NkVSMkFGTzhEdVN2dE5sWndHUWFZMWlyVXRzUjYxeUpHNGEtSTVOS1I1U0hfSk04ci1rUGlIQm1tTndlb1ZXR0VMMEh2eXZ0LVM4STNvY3VSMVg4NHhwbmk5SnlxMUIzdjlSbHc</guid></item><item><title>他们是医务人员、社会工作者、邻居和911。认识做这一切的医护人员。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/15/rural-healthcare-workers-north-carolina/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ALKKQOSDQZD7JL5RC4HJYNIZAU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;BURNSVILLE, N.C.&lt;b&gt; — &lt;/b&gt;In this remote corner of western North Carolina, some of the people whom paramedics Evan Carroll and Nicole McKinney serve don’t have cellphone service, and bridges that once took the two to isolated homes deep in the mountains were washed away by Hurricane Helene. And instead of simply responding to emergencies, Carroll and McKinney make old-fashioned medical house calls for nonurgent care. They help elderly patients monitor their high blood pressure and other chronic conditions. They advise people on what they should be eating, even dropping off meals and produce. They set up transportation and help make sure people are following doctors’ orders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:01:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOaDk0ZlFPS3JFSEpKdFNueTV1b3haM25FQ3BKaC1JQ3AwWUFnaTFIZkxobTFRX2pmazhBY0VvMXEyZ2tQenF1QWtFNTlCU0c3U2dIc3h5RW5GYUJDVlRYQ3JwYnhCQ0FiWV9HUnh0NWl6ZkZmTmpCQmtGTXI4SURoV25YUU5lWlZQeGpuQlUwZFhtenM</guid></item><item><title>您的焦虑可能是饮食问题- Vox</title><link>https://www.vox.com/life/472211/anxiety-treatment-supplement-diet-magnesium-choline</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="zephr-anchor" class="_1agbrix10"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;By May 2024, Ebony Dupas knew she had a problem. She had started to feel a mild anxiety about her sense of direction and purpose in life earlier that year, but within a couple months, that had spiraled into a paranoia that she could neither shake nor explain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Referred by her doctor, Dupas began consulting with different psychiatrists, all of whom considered diagnosing her with generalized anxiety disorder, bipolar disorder, or schizophrenia. Most wanted to put her on medication right away. But one psychiatrist first ordered bloodwork to see if something else might be going on. “I was mostly depleted of magnesium,” Dupas says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Most people being treated for mental health conditions such as anxiety or depression typically use a mix of just two strategies: medication (usually an SSRI) and psychotherapy. But there’s increasing interest in the connection between food and the brain, and especially how nutrition could affect psychiatric conditions. Researchers have not only found a connection between the &lt;a href="/2014/11/26/7289495/microbiome-gut-bacteria-health"&gt;gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt; and mental health, but also connections between deficiencies in certain micronutrients, including &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0028390811003054"&gt;magnesium&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41380-025-03206-7#Sec28"&gt;choline&lt;/a&gt;, and conditions like anxiety and depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;What’s less clear is how supplementation could alleviate certain symptoms. We don’t have robust clinical trial data showing how micronutrients affect people’s mental health, and the role of supplements in mental health is understudied, particularly because the research can be so challenging. Most supplements also don’t require approval by the Food and Drug Administration (FDA) to go to market, meaning there’s an abundance of different options, most of which have different formulas that aren’t robustly studied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;While researchers have long understood that nutrition is important for brain health, people don’t typically look to their diets as a way to improve their mental health, and doctors don’t always think to connect mental health with diet. The link between food and the brain “is overlooked by most people,” says &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneral.org/doctors/18123/uma-naidoo"&gt;Uma Naidoo&lt;/a&gt;, director of nutritional and lifestyle psychiatry at Massachusetts General Hospital and author of the 2023 book&lt;em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hachettebookgroup.com/titles/uma-naidoo-md/calm-your-mind-with-food/9780316502092/"&gt;Calm Your Mind With Food&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;. Future research to clarify the link between micronutrients — through either food or supplements — and mental health outcomes could help us stop underestimating that link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p id="how-diet-is-linked-to-mental-health" class="_7ka5u1 _7ka5u0 duet--article--standard-heading xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How diet is linked to mental health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The connection between diet and the brain seems counterintuitive, but it’s actually linked to basic biology. “The same environment where food is being digested is also the environment where neurotransmitters are produced,” Naidoo says. The gut produces most of the body’s serotonin, as well as a good portion of the neurotransmitter GABA. Drugs used to alter levels of serotonin are frequently used to treat depression and anxiety. The most common group are known as selective serotonin reuptake inhibitors (SSRIs).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;One of the best understood links between nutrition and mental health involves how food affects the gut microbiome. Researchers have known for years now that &lt;a href="https://nyaspubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/nyas.13712"&gt;gut inflammation&lt;/a&gt; and changes in the gut microbiome are linked to mental conditions like &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/trends/neurosciences/abstract/S0166-2236(13)00008-8?kuid=79939ea6-6dfb-43bc-b620-d9ab0df56eaf&amp;amp;kref=https%3A%2F%2Fkemperwellness.com%2Fblog%2Flets-get-real-about-anxiety-and-mental-health%2F"&gt;anxiety and depression&lt;/a&gt;, and possibly other &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s12888-023-05003-4"&gt;psychiatric disorders&lt;/a&gt;. But there’s also a growing and ongoing interest in how specific vitamins and minerals affect the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--block-placement _80slsf2 _80slsf0 duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-pullquote _1iohv3z0"&gt;&lt;p class="_1iohv3z1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup _1iohv3z2 xkp0cg9"&gt;“The brain and mental health are no longer just ‘above the neck’ problems.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;cite class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup _1iohv3z3"&gt;— Uma Naidoo, director of nutritional and lifestyle psychiatry at Mass General&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Deficiencies in several different micronutrients, including magnesium, &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/11/9/2232"&gt;B vitamins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s40263-019-00640-4"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2702216"&gt;omega-3s&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41380-025-03206-7#Sec28"&gt;choline&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/16930802/"&gt;L-theanine&lt;/a&gt; have been shown to affect mental health conditions. Researchers can &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0028390811003054"&gt;induce anxiety in mice&lt;/a&gt;, for example, by manipulating and lowering their magnesium levels. The extent to which supplementation affects mental health in humans is less well-established.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;The research so far is a little sparse and mixed. A&lt;a href="https://assets.cureus.com/uploads/review_article/pdf/237565/20240430-16558-smymmw.pdf?"&gt; 2024 review&lt;/a&gt; found that “supplemental magnesium is likely useful in the treatment of mild anxiety and insomnia,” especially in people with already low magnesium. But across studies, results showing how much magnesium supplements can help people with mental health conditions like anxiety or depression are often inconsistent, likely because there are so many different forms these supplements can take.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Magnesium, for example, can be taken as a supplement in the forms of magnesium citrate, magnesium malate, magnesium glycinate, magnesium oxide, magnesium chloride, and more. How well the body can make use of magnesium in these different forms, and how good these different forms are at delivering magnesium to the brain still needs to be better studied, says Alexander Rawji, a psychiatrist in Long Island, New York, and the lead author of the paper. Similar challenges exist for other micronutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;As you may have learned in high school biology, eating varied foods rich in certain vitamins and minerals is crucial because your body cannot make its own supply and yet relies on them to perform critical functions. And research suggests that most Americans don’t get nearly enough of many micronutrients. Previous &lt;a href="https://lpi.oregonstate.edu/mic/micronutrient-inadequacies/overview#toc-micronutrient-deficiencies-and-inadequacies-"&gt;national survey data&lt;/a&gt; said that as much as 94 percent of the US population does not get adequate daily vitamin D, 52 percent don’t get enough magnesium, and 92 percent don’t get enough choline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Few people would argue that diet is completely unimportant for brain health. But while a connection between nutrition and brain health is clear, the persistent gaps in scientific knowledge make it difficult to really say what role supplements should play in the treatment of mental illness. Ideally, future research would get us to a place where we better understand how micronutrients in the diet distinctly affect the workings of the brain, as well as which supplements are best absorbed by the body and brain. On top of that, we don’t even fully &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/the-neuroscientist-who-lost-her-mind/201804/we-scientists-know-so-little-about-mental-illness"&gt;understand the mechanisms that cause most mental health disorders&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p id="what-role-should-nutrition-play-in-mental-health-care" class="_7ka5u1 _7ka5u0 duet--article--standard-heading xkp0cg1"&gt;&lt;h2 class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What role should nutrition play in mental health care?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Once her blood test results came back, Dupas’ psychiatrist put her on a regimen of supplements — magnesium, L-theanine, B-complex vitamins, and omega-3s — in addition to a small dose of an SSRI. But Dupas didn’t stay on the medication for long. After a couple weeks, “I felt really clear again,” she says. “I could focus again and not feel paranoid that people are coming after me.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Dupas could be an outlier. Research suggests the vast majority of people with a mental health condition won’t see dramatic improvement of their symptoms from supplementation alone. Nevertheless, she’s grateful that she stumbled across a doctor who actually ordered bloodwork to see if there may be any hidden culprits exacerbating symptoms and hopes more patients get similar treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Providers should be ordering bloodwork for patients, especially if they have multiple health conditions and medications that could be affecting their health, Rawji says. And if they have a deficiency, that’s certainly something to address. A complicating factor, however, is the fact that blood panels can’t always give you a perfect picture of what’s going on — tests to detect magnesium levels in blood serum often come back normal even if their body stores of magnesium are low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Regardless, Rawji uses supplements as “part of a multipronged approach” in his treatment of patients, he says. How much the supplements will help will vary person to person, and they definitely shouldn’t replace other treatments, including medications like SSRIs or benzodiazepines. “If you expect magnesium to be a benzo for anxiety then you’re going to be very disappointed,” he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Not all psychiatrists are trained to ask questions related to diet when assessing patients or to look for nutrition deficiencies, according to Naidoo, the doctor from Mass General. This could lead to ignoring relatively easy interventions that can make real differences. Furthermore, overemphasizing supplements comes with its own risks. If you eat a healthy, well-balanced whole foods diet, you’ll probably get more than enough of the vitamins and minerals you need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;There’s “almost always” an opportunity to use nutrition to improve mental health, since no one really has a perfect diet, says Naidoo. If you’re particularly concerned with including more of certain micronutrients into your diet, she suggests eating more green leafy vegetables, nuts, and legumes for magnesium. Milk, eggs, and whole grains are good sources of B vitamins; eggs, beans and cruciferous vegetables are good for choline; fatty fish and eggs are good for vitamin D; and you can get L-theanine from green tea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="duet--article--article-body-component"&gt;&lt;p class="duet--article--dangerously-set-cms-markup duet--article--standard-paragraph _1agbrixi lg8ac51 lg8ac50 xkp0cg1"&gt;Nutrition is a huge, consequential tool for how we maintain our bodies. And we understand, now more than ever, that the importance of food for the body includes benefits for the brain. “The brain and mental health are no longer just ‘above the neck’ problems,” Naidoo says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Vox</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNUU9FNW10X2pncmdlazJ4b1hKVGx1WXJBMUhhUmMwRnRPWFhsS3FsLXo0aXBvQnpBaW8xMXdpcng2ZnQwc3Z1ck5mUFFua1E1R0pPbDFYbjc1R2F2cFBlUmVBU2hTUklKYTYySWtyQ0pHckh2V3BXNWxVeG5rMWNCTmJkaXNjUXBjdDRn</guid></item><item><title>新冠肺炎还是流感？以下是如何区分的方法- Yahoo Life UK</title><link>https://uk.style.yahoo.com/flu-covid-cold-symptoms-signs-health-winter-092559143.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As winter settles in, it’s not just the colder mornings and darker evenings making people feel a bit off – it’s the sudden surge in seasonal illnesses too. Many of us are battling &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:1;pos:1" href="https://uk.style.yahoo.com/foods-drinks-help-soothe-a-sore-throat-winter-sick-140549076.html" data-ylk="slk:scratchy throats;cpos:1;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;scratchy throats&lt;/a&gt;, blocked noses and that &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:2;pos:1" href="https://uk.style.yahoo.com/does-vitamin-c-help-with-colds-150005313.html" data-ylk="slk:run-down feeling;cpos:2;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;run-down feeling&lt;/a&gt; that always seems to arrive ahead of Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But this year, flu season has escalated far more quickly than expected. Last week, it was reported that the number of flu patients in hospitals in England had hit a record high for this time of year, with an average of 2,660 patients in hospital each day – &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:3;pos:1" href="https://uk.news.yahoo.com/flu-cases-nhs-hospitals-jump-100228297.html" data-ylk="slk:a 55% jump in just seven days;cpos:3;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;a 55% jump in just seven days&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Cases are also reported to be more &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:4;pos:1" href="https://uk.style.yahoo.com/flu-cases-uk-vaccine-cold-cough-symptoms-christmas-103222620.html" data-ylk="slk:than 50% higher;cpos:4;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;than 50% higher&lt;/a&gt; than they were last winter, putting extra strain on NHS services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, the usual &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:5;pos:1" href="https://uk.style.yahoo.com/norovirus-myths-debunk-cases-spread-winter-illness-133716378.html" data-ylk="slk:winter bugs;cpos:5;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;winter bugs&lt;/a&gt; and respiratory infections are circulating widely and COVID continues to persist &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:6;pos:1" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/national-flu-and-covid-19-surveillance-reports-2025-to-2026-season/national-flu-and-covid-19-surveillance-report-11-december-2025-week-50" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:in the background;cpos:6;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;in the background&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So, if you’re feeling unwell and unsure what’s causing it, here’s a simple guide to help you make sense of your symptoms – and what steps to take next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="differences-between-flu-and-covid-symptoms"&gt;Differences between flu and COVID symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;While flu often gets better by itself, some can become seriously ill. (Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="what-is-flu-and-what-are-the-symptoms"&gt;What is flu and what are the symptoms?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The flu is a contagious respiratory infection caused by influenza viruses. Similarly to COVID, it is spread by droplets from an infected person coughing, sneezing or talking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Flu symptoms, according to the NHS, include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;a sudden high temperature&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;feeling tired or exhausted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;feeling sick and being sick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While flu will often get better on its own, some can get seriously ill, which is why it's important to protect yourself with the NHS vaccine if you're advised to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Symptoms present similarly in children, though they can get pain in their ear and seem less active too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="what-is-covid-and-what-are-the-symptoms"&gt;What is COVID and what are the symptoms?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A headache and runny nose are some of the main symptoms of COVID. (Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;COVID is also a contagious respiratory illness, but is caused by the SARS-CoV-2 virus, a form of coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As per the NHS, symptoms include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;a high temperature or shivering (chills)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;a loss or change to your sense of smell or taste&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;feeling tired or exhausted&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;feeling sick or being sick&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;These are thought to be similar between adults and children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When the UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) first reported the Nimbus variant in England, it outlined that there wasn't enough evidence to suggest any new symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, some doctors associated the Stratus variant with hoarseness – a scratchy or raspy voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don't delay in getting free COVID-19 or flu jabs this winter if advised or invited. (Getty Images)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="what-to-do-if-you-have-flu-or-covid-19"&gt;What to do if you have flu or COVID-19&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you have flu, rest and sleep, keep warm, take recommended doses of paracetamol or ibuprofen and drink plenty of fluids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="ask-for-an-urgent-gp-appointment-or-call-nhs-111-if-any-of-the-following-apply"&gt;Ask for an urgent GP appointment or call NHS 111 if any of the following apply:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;you or your child have symptoms of flu and you're worried about your baby's or child's symptoms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;you're 65 or over, you're pregnant, you have a long-term medical condition&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;you have a weakened immune system&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;your symptoms don't improve after seven days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="if-you-have-covid-19-symptoms-call-nhs-111-if"&gt;If you have COVID-19 symptoms, call NHS 111 if:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;you're feeling worried or unsure what to do&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;you're worried about a baby or child under five&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For either, try to stay at home and avoid contact with other people if you have a high temperature or do not feel well enough to do your normal activities (taking extra care to avoid those at high risk).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold" data-jump-link-target="" id="call-999-or-go-to-ae-if"&gt;Call 999 or go to A&amp;amp;E if:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;you get sudden chest pain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;you have difficulty breathing&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;you start coughing up a lot of blood&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;your child seems very unwell, is getting worse or you think there's something seriously wrong&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo Life UK</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:50:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOSUpSNUxpc0tHWDJoLXBFemMwdzRoNWdIWDhiYzRmY3B2ZFgzVDJXTDdrN3o2UWR4Y1pQRFhCSGVKMnZZVkhWUjJFdVgybU9KLWVwUU9CUFk5ZUhHQVFzYkhaSFV0S3ZVNGVQMF9mQTVxZWRBRTRxMDJNUHY2d3cxWGFXN2F0aWJ6QVNleWJB</guid></item><item><title>如何在圣诞节前接种流感疫苗-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/cold-flu/how-get-flu-vaccine-before-christmas-jab/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;Her message was echoed by Nick Thayer, the head of policy for the Company Chemists Association. He said there is “no national shortage of flu vaccines, but the bulk of them are administered in October and November”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means that “by the time you get to December, some places are running low, and some will have none left from their original allocation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You may therefore need to shop around for your flu vaccine. “Look on the websites for pharmacies, look on the NHS website, if you are eligible for a free jab or talk to your local pharmacy and ask,” Thayer advises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are unable to get the vaccine before Christmas, stick to the basics to reduce your risk of catching the flu. These include handwashing, avoiding crowded indoor gatherings, staying home when unwell, and self-isolating within families where possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flu jab remains a valuable layer of protection, according to Dr Clarke. It is safe and generally thought to achieve maximum protection for an individual after 10 to 14 days. Whilst there is still a chance you might get the flu after having the jab, it is likely to be milder and not last as long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Protection from the flu vaccine goes down over the year and the types of virus it protects against are updated annually, which is why it is important to stay up to date with your inoculations, according to the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whilst this year’s dominant strain is thought to be a mutated version of the influenza A virus, data shows that the flu vaccine still provides good protection against it. The UK Health Security Agency found it has been &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.gov.uk/government/news/flu-vaccine-providing-important-protection-despite-new-subclade"&gt;70 to 75 per cent effective at preventing hospital attendance in children aged 2 to 17, and 30 to 40 per cent effective in adults&lt;/a&gt;. This is broadly in line with effectiveness in previous flu seasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost 17 million vaccines have been delivered this autumn, which is 350,000 more compared to this time last year, although Dr Clarke wishes more of us would choose to be inoculated. The latest National Flu and Covid-19 Surveillance Report shows that only 70.9 per cent of over-65s have received their flu jab this season. Rates amongst eligible under-65s are far lower, hovering around 35 per cent. “It really would make a difference,” says Dr Clarke.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQR2haMzhTWWNTblc3M3VPNTZ1T25McjBlbzNRWXJraUxKMjM2blB1bDhtVmhZWXcxWU5odGdnVzBMTXJTc3piSGJETkl2NmtWSkRnRkVXeUI1OGtrb1h3YUVoMlZfREN3eExFa3B0QnBEU2h3RGhTNGlZeVRNdmR5cHYtSmJlVTU0Wk5wUnViUjNWX294UVIxWU5RaWFUb1FhLTc1YUZwRQ</guid></item><item><title>DNA研究揭示了世界上已知最早瘟疫的携带者- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/dna-study-reveals-carrier-of-worlds-earliest-known-plague</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;A plague that swept through Eurasia for 2,000 years – millennia before the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ancient-dna-evidence-reveals-where-the-black-death-most-likely-originated"&gt;Black Death&lt;/a&gt; of the Middle Ages – has only ever been detected in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-have-discovered-the-earliest-evidence-of-plague-in-a-neolithic-graveyard"&gt;human remains&lt;/a&gt;, until now. For decades, it has been unclear how the Bronze Age plague spread so widely, but now we know which animal was a likely carrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team of archaeologists sifted through scraps of DNA in the bones and teeth of Bronze Age cattle, goats, and sheep, as part of a large, ongoing study to track how these animals migrated, alongside humans, from the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-dust-may-have-determined-the-spread-of-ancient-human-civilisations"&gt;Fertile Crescent&lt;/a&gt; in the Middle East across Eurasia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such ancient samples of animal DNA are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1098/rstb.2019.0569"&gt;never fully intact&lt;/a&gt;, usually quite fragmented, and very contaminated with the leftovers of organisms that inhabited the animal's body in life, and long after death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/black-deaths-carnage-traced-to-a-volcanic-eruption-half-a-world-away"&gt;Black Death's Carnage Traced to a Volcanic Eruption Half a World Away&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When we test livestock DNA in ancient samples, we get a complex genetic soup of contamination," University of Arkansas archaeologist Taylor Hermes &lt;a href="https://news.uark.edu/articles/80485/how-did-bronze-age-plague-spread-a-sheep-might-solve-the-mystery"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a large barrier to getting a strong signal for the animal, but it also gives us an opportunity to look for pathogens that infected herds and their handlers."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One pathogen Hermes and his colleagues encountered in the remains of a 4,000-year-old domesticated sheep unearthed at &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arkaim"&gt;Arkaim&lt;/a&gt;, an archaeological site &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arkaim"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;in the Southern Ural Mountains of Russia, stopped them in their tracks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On one tooth was the DNA of the plague bacteria, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yersinia_pestis"&gt;Yersinia pestis&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/em&gt; an ancient strain that was unable to infect fleas, as it did later during the Middle Ages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis &lt;/em&gt;had yet to figure out how to use fleas as a vector during the Bronze Age, archaeologists have often wondered how the plague spread so widely among humans. We know many humans died from infection, their bodies still containing genetic traces of an identical strain of plague, uncovered at sites thousands of kilometers apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the first evidence of the Late Neolithic Bronze Age lineage of the bacteria found in a non-human animal, a discovery which the researchers shared &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ancestor-of-black-death-has-been-discovered-in-bronze-age-sheep"&gt;in a preprint&lt;/a&gt; earlier this year. The research has now been peer reviewed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_185507" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185507" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/MapOfBronzeAgePlagueFoundInHumansAndSheep-642x268.jpg" alt="Map of Eurasia showing sites where human remains containing plague bacteria DNA have been found, and one sheep. " class="wp-image-185507 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/MapOfBronzeAgePlagueFoundInHumansAndSheep-642x268.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/MapOfBronzeAgePlagueFoundInHumansAndSheep-768x321.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/MapOfBronzeAgePlagueFoundInHumansAndSheep-600x251.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/MapOfBronzeAgePlagueFoundInHumansAndSheep.jpg 866w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-185507" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;DNA of &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis&lt;/em&gt; has been found in the remains of a domesticated sheep, to add to detections in ancient humans across Eurasia, at Late Neolithic Bronze Age (LNBA) sites. (Light-Maka et al., &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's easy to imagine how domestic sheep, roaming across the vast grasslands of the Eurasian Steppe, may have encountered a wild animal carrying the bacteria, but not made sick by it, and then spread it between herds and shepherds. However, the team notes they can't rule out human-to-sheep transmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It had to be more than people moving. Our plague sheep gave us a breakthrough," Hermes &lt;a href="https://news.uark.edu/articles/80485/how-did-bronze-age-plague-spread-a-sheep-might-solve-the-mystery"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We now see it as a dynamic between people, livestock and some still unidentified 'natural reservoir' for it, which could be rodents on the grasslands of the Eurasian steppe or migratory birds."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_185219" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185219" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/conceptual-scenario-for-LNBA-lineage-transmission-642x639.jpg" alt="" class="size-medium wp-image-185219" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/conceptual-scenario-for-LNBA-lineage-transmission-642x639.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/conceptual-scenario-for-LNBA-lineage-transmission-678x675.jpg 678w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/conceptual-scenario-for-LNBA-lineage-transmission-768x764.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/conceptual-scenario-for-LNBA-lineage-transmission-600x597.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/conceptual-scenario-for-LNBA-lineage-transmission.jpg 1039w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-185219" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Conceptual scenario of the LNBA lineage transmission concluded from sheep- and human-derived &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis&lt;/em&gt; genomes. (Light-Maka et al., &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tracking down the DNA of ancient pathogens is tricky. People don't bury animals with the same care as they do other humans, so their remains are not usually so well-preserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many specimens of domestic animals that archaeologists find are actually the leftovers of human meals, which means they tend to have been cooked (a sure-fire way to break down the DNA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-black-death-shaped-human-evolution-and-were-still-in-its-shadow"&gt;The Black Death Shaped Human Evolution, And We're Still in Its Shadow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Moreover, people tend to avoid consuming visibly sick animals, and therefore faunal assemblages are likely biased toward healthy animals," biologist Ian Light-Maka, of the Max Planck Institute for Infection Biology, Hermes, and their colleagues write in their &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2025.07.029"&gt;published paper&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Even when infected animals are consumed, a single animal may infect many people, and the probability of that specific animal being found and later studied may be low."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is only the third time that some strain of &lt;em&gt;Y. pestis&lt;/em&gt; has ever been found in ancient animals. The first two were a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1098/rstb.2019.0569"&gt;medieval rat&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s42003-024-06676-7"&gt;Neolithic dog&lt;/a&gt;; however, those DNA samples were too fragmented to produce reliable results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest find is particularly exciting, Hermes &lt;a href="https://news.uark.edu/articles/80485/how-did-bronze-age-plague-spread-a-sheep-might-solve-the-mystery"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;, because the site where this sheep was found, Arkaim, is a human settlement linked to the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sintashta_culture"&gt;Sintashta culture&lt;/a&gt;, known for creating impressive bronze weapons, riding horses, and spreading their genes into Central Asia. These people have also been found with traces of the Late Neolithic Bronze Age (LNBA) plague strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When this infected sheep lived, the Sintashta were just beginning to expand their livestock herds, since their horse-riding abilities allowed them to cover greater territory quickly, potentially increasing exposure to wild species harboring the plague.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Nevertheless, it is not possible with a single genome to reconstruct a complete understanding of the ecology of the LNBA lineage across the diverse set of cultures and geographies afflicted by this prehistoric plague lineage, and our results suggest its reservoir remains at large," the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2025.07.029"&gt;conclude.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research is published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2025.07.029"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:01:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOWDZ3eWRNY041RWVCNWtlbng1MG5jUzcxYnNNQ0YxRGJGNjRkX0VDMFplaHR0NnJqS2dJY2ZPRVJ2ZTZDNHRleURHcmVFNkdTaUNBbEF4aWMzNXNtY0tua1owOE9YQ0xiMVcxTXprUXd1WWhyajlsOGxpVVZsRmVPdXRVUFZ0RFFia3NwTFlxWQ</guid></item><item><title>成千上万的美国农民患有帕金森氏症。他们归咎于致命的杀虫剂。- MLive.com</title><link>https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/12/thousands-of-us-farmers-have-parkinsons-they-blame-a-deadly-pesticide.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content impact-article  "&gt;&lt;p class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z2M3ANX3OVHE7AJEJ2RHC4MRFM"&gt;Paul Friday remembers when his hand started flopping in the cold weather – the first sign nerve cells in his brain were dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="W2ZE2LIMJFE3ZJCXFF2QQIPBB4"&gt;He was eventually diagnosed with Parkinson’s, a brain disease that gets worse over time. His limbs got stiffer. He struggled to walk. He couldn’t keep living on his family farm. Shortly afterward, Friday came to believe that decades of spraying a pesticide called paraquat at his peach orchard in southwestern Michigan may be the culprit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="P2JCXDFYURB55A2RQKEMJTSQZA"&gt;“It explained to me why I have Parkinson’s disease,” said Friday, who is now 83, and makes that claim in a pending lawsuit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VRUL3AZYOJBDFJBELVLBCNTMRQ"&gt;The pesticide, a weed killer, is extremely toxic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7YB674MWOVDNZKFFDB45BXCDII"&gt;With evidence of its harms stacking up, it’s already been banned in dozens of countries all over the world, including the United Kingdom and China, where it’s made. Yet last year, its manufacturer Syngenta, a subsidiary of a company owned by the Chinese government, continued selling paraquat in the United States and other nations that haven’t banned it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="F7Y5O3TXPBBWDJKRETXF7URHF4"&gt;Health statistics are limited. Critics point to research linking paraquat exposure to Parkinson’s, while the manufacturer pushes back, saying none of it is peer-reviewed. But the lawsuits are mounting across the United States, as farmers confront Parkinson’s after a lifetime of use, and much of the globe is turning away from paraquat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JEDZRWYMBJAN3EAKC47BL4PVHA"&gt;It has many critics wrestling with the question: What will it take to ban paraquat in the United States? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6T4XUVSTU5CNLCWQ4TQKRM4MFE"&gt;“What we’ve seen over the course of decades is a systemic failure to protect farmworkers and the agricultural community from pesticides,” said Jonathan Kalmuss-Katz, a senior attorney at Earthjustice, an environmental law organization that advocates against paraquat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Paul Friday was a lifelong peach farmer in Coloma, Michigan until he developed Parkinson's Disease in 2017.&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Photo provided by Luiba Friday&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Thousands of lawsuits pile up&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XOCKWDYSSVCTROU6MSMOVHZL64"&gt;It was hard for Ruth Anne Krause to watch her husband of 58 years struggle to move his hands. He was an avid woodcarver, shaving intricate details into his creations, before it became too difficult for him to hold the tools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3EDD5UF5SVEJRGCIHVLFIFFEGQ"&gt;Jim Krause was diagnosed with Parkinson’s disease in 2019, after he spent decades operating a 20-acre stone fruit farm in central California. His wife says he often donned a mask and yellow rubber boots to spray paraquat on the fields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SHSPPGDLPFEG7CEL22ZN7D6MAA"&gt;Krause, who had no family history of neurological disease as is typical, died in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FZWEWOJ6LRGYZACOHVIQMH2NOU"&gt;“I want people to know what happened,” said Ruth Anne Krause, who is worried that paraquat is still being sold to American farmers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MWTSGRKFLBDYLCFSFHAUBOLL24"&gt;Krause is one of thousands of people who have sued Syngenta, a manufacturer, and Chevron USA, a seller, over paraquat exposure. They’re alleging the chemical companies failed to warn of the dangers of paraquat despite knowing it could damage human nerve cells and studies showing it’s linked to Parkinson’s disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Between 11 million and 17 million pounds of paraquat are sprayed annually on American farms, according to the latest data from the U.S. Geological Survey. The pesticide is used as a burn down, meaning farmers spray it to quickly clear a field or kill weeds. It's effective, but highly toxic. (Julie Bennett | preps@al.com)&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Julie Bennett | preps@al.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7LCTCRPUUZF3XMWDQXJCABO7VI"&gt;Chevron, which never manufactured paraquat and hasn’t sold it since 1986, has “long maintained that it should not be liable in any paraquat litigation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KQ3NHW4GPFHJRL5CYDRXRWYCFU"&gt;“And despite hundreds of studies conducted over the past 60 years, the scientific consensus is that paraquat has not been shown to be a cause of Parkinson’s disease,” the company said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ENAL7CTX7VF7VJUKDONTSAMYVY"&gt;Syngenta has emphasized there is no evidence that paraquat causes Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="E7H3YVLGPNAOHMJCUPBLSMO4YU"&gt;“We have great sympathy for those suffering from the debilitating effects of Parkinson’s disease,” a Syngenta spokesperson said in a statement. “However, it is important to note that the scientific evidence simply does not support a causal link between paraquat and Parkinson’s disease, and that paraquat is safe when used as directed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TFX57IT5BVAVPKYVOOUUMDVZTM"&gt;More than 6,400 lawsuits against Syngenta and Chevron that allege a link between paraquat and Parkinson’s are pending in the U.S. District Court of Southern Illinois. Another 1,300 cases have been brought in Pennsylvania, 450 in California and more are scattered throughout state courts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="T7FPVRRWXJDJ5AMXR6WPCVVYHM"&gt;“I do think it’s important to be clear that number is probably not even close to representative of how many people have been impacted by this,” said Christian Simmons, a legal expert for Drugwatch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FC6EJZHEKJDCHFCSMIPDAH6DWU"&gt;Syngenta &lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/2025-03/Financial%20Report%202024.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;told its shareholders in March&lt;/a&gt; that an additional 1,600 cases have been voluntarily dismissed or resolved. In 2021, the company settled an unspecified number in California and Illinois for $187.5 million, &lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/bond-investor-information/financial-results/Syngenta-AG-2021-Financial-Report.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to a company financial report&lt;/a&gt;. Some others have been dismissed for missing court deadlines. None have gone to trial yet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3HL2637WKBHRPF6RVYGXZFOYSA"&gt;Behind these thousands of lawsuits, a list growing nearly every day, is a person suffering from Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UXSM5JW5TBEVRAPVMR5KKNMJGQ"&gt;In Ohio, there’s Dave Jilbert a winemaker who sprayed the pesticide on his vineyard south of Cleveland. He was diagnosed with Parkinson’s in 2020 and now he is suing and working to get paraquat banned. Terri McGrath believes &lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/12/michigan-family-has-7-parkinsons-cases-did-weed-killer-play-a-role.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.mlive.com/news/2025/12/michigan-family-has-7-parkinsons-cases-did-weed-killer-play-a-role.html"&gt;years of exposure to paraquat&lt;/a&gt; at her family farm in rural Southwest Michigan likely contributed to her Parkinson’s. Six other family members also have the disease. And in south Alabama, Mac Barlow is suing after receiving a similar diagnosis following years of relying on paraquat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PAMUDHHLPND7JDOWIOZQDS4X3A"&gt;“For about 40 years off and on, I’ve been using that stuff,” Barlow said. “I’ll be honest with you, if I knew it was going to be that bad, I would have tried to figure out something else.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-28" data-gaid="inarticle-28"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;In Alabama, farmer Mac Barlow was diagnosed with Parkinson's after years of spraying paraquat. Teri McGrath believes years of exposure to paraquat at her family farm in rural Southwest Michigan  contributed to her Parkinson’s. In Ohio, there’s Dave Jilbert a winemaker who sprayed the pesticide on his vineyard. He was diagnosed with Parkinson’s in 2020. Like Barlow, Jilbert is now suing.&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Photos by Julie Bennett, Isaac Ritchey and David Petkiewicz&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-29" data-gaid="inarticle-29"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Paraquat in the United States&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-30" data-gaid="inarticle-30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SRZCGOWUZBFTLC4F47BZAIXRWY"&gt;Since hitting the market in the 1960s, paraquat has been used in farming to quickly “burn” weeds before planting crops. The pesticide, originally developed by Syngenta and sold by Chevron, rips tissue apart, destroying plants on a molecular level within hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-31" data-gaid="inarticle-31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TXJFF3ZCVBF6ZJZUZAF4QAEORU"&gt;“It’s used because it’s effective at what it does. It’s highly toxic. It’s very good at killing things,” said Geoff Horsfield, policy director at the Environmental Working Group. “And unfortunately, when a pesticide like this is so effective that also means there’s usually human health impacts as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-32" data-gaid="inarticle-32"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D3K2QBNFGRHMDK3UD4KKJJ7XEY"&gt;By the 1970s, it became a tool in the war on drugs, sprayed to kill Mexican marijuana plants. In 1998, that history landed it in Hollywood when the Dude in “The Big Lebowski” calls someone a “human paraquat,” a buzzkill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-33" data-gaid="inarticle-33"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SIRLSB4UNZDGVERNIAOURN63CA"&gt;Today, between 11 million and 17 million pounds of paraquat are sprayed annually to help grow cotton, soybean and corn fields, among other crops, throughout the country, the U.S. Geological Survey, USGS, reports. And despite the alleged known risks, its use is increasing, according to the most current federal data, more than doubling from 2012 to 2018. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-34" data-gaid="inarticle-34"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CMG6JIUF7JBANGFWO4AH3BQSBA"&gt;The USGS says on its website new pesticide use data will be released in 2025. It hasn’t been published yet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-35" data-gaid="inarticle-35"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:PLAQXGROCRGU5HYMZQEHQBLSSQ" data-fusion-component="PLAQXGROCRGU5HYMZQEHQBLSSQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rawhtml"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:PLAQXGROCRGU5HYMZQEHQBLSSQ" data-fusion-component="PLAQXGROCRGU5HYMZQEHQBLSSQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-36" data-gaid="inarticle-36"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Y7QVSR7FRZBGHP5236Q63IKFIQ"&gt;Because paraquat kills any growth it touches, it’s typically used to clear a field before any crops are planted. &lt;a href="https://npic.orst.edu/factsheets/paraquat.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Low levels of paraquat residue&lt;/a&gt; can linger on food crops, but the foremost threat is direct exposure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-37" data-gaid="inarticle-37"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MWQFYNAYI5HFBOUMIHN37OWRHM"&gt;Pesticides are among the most common means of suicide worldwide, &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/preventing-suicide-by-phasing-out-highly-hazardous-pesticides" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to the World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, and paraquat is frequently &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3243009/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;used because of its lethality.&lt;/a&gt; After some nations, like South Korea and Sri Lanka, banned it, they saw a significant drop in suicides, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/ije/article-abstract/45/2/470/2572538?redirectedFrom=fulltext" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;research shows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-38" data-gaid="inarticle-38"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="X6TDAXHM3FEGJPMUFVJLWTAJAY"&gt;The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency already restricts paraquat, labeling it as “registered use,” with a skull and crossbones, meaning it can only be used by people who have a license. Because of its toxicity, the federal government requires it to have blue dye, a sharp smell and a vomiting agent, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chemical-emergencies/chemical-fact-sheets/paraquat.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;U.S. Centers for Disease Control, CDC&lt;/a&gt;. Sprayers are also told to wear protective gear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-39" data-gaid="inarticle-39"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GRTLJOHETZHIDJAZMYX63EXFD4"&gt;Despite those safety measures, U.S. poison centers have gotten hundreds of paraquat-related calls in the past decade, their annual reports show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-40" data-gaid="inarticle-40"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z6S3OILK2FATJETFWTXM5CLP7A"&gt;Swallowing is the most likely way to be poisoned by paraquat, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chemical-emergencies/chemical-fact-sheets/paraquat.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;, but skin exposure can also be deadly. In fact, if it spills on someone, health officials say they should wash it off immediately and quickly cut off their clothes. That way they don’t risk spreading more deadly pesticide on their body as they pull their shirt over their head. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-41" data-gaid="inarticle-41"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PW3QJZ22SVDLRHGVV4Q4RLAFIE"&gt;In one 2023 case &lt;a href="https://poisoncenters.org/annual-reports" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;documented by America’s Poison Centers&lt;/a&gt;, a 50-year-old man accidentally sipped blue liquid from a Gatorade bottle that turned out to be paraquat. After trying to throw it up, he went to the emergency room, struggling to breathe, nauseous and vomiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-42" data-gaid="inarticle-42"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZPHWCT4EU5ASNIAZ3EBZ6ZNQ5E"&gt;Doctors rushed to treat the man, but he turned blue from a lack of oxygen and his organs failed. He died within three days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-43" data-gaid="inarticle-43"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TUH5ANIKXVE3HDZE2RKBJLS4VI"&gt;In another poison center report, a 65-year-old man spilled paraquat on his clothes and kept working. Ten days later, he went to the emergency room with second-degree burns on his stomach. Dizzy and nauseous, he was admitted for two days before going home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-44" data-gaid="inarticle-44"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DMG33SK3YFGAJFDHZUKXAM6MQA"&gt;A week later, he went back to the ICU as his kidney, lungs and heart stopped working. He died 34 days after the spill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-45" data-gaid="inarticle-45"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="553FPIV5UFHALN35UJGQ4T7RS4"&gt;These annual poison center case summaries provide insight into paraquat’s toxicity, but it’s unclear exactly how many people in the U.S. have been injured or killed by the weed killer, because there’s only a patchwork of data creating an uneven and incomplete picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-46" data-gaid="inarticle-46"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7I53DH2WIJFSXARIBIBJV3OM6A"&gt;The latest annual National Poison Data System report logged 114 reports and one death caused by paraquat in 2023. Over a decade, from 2014 to 2023, this system documented 1,151 paraquat calls. And a separate database shows the EPA has investigated 82 human exposure cases since 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-47" data-gaid="inarticle-47"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6YFPNYW56ZCSXHITEXMXVDB6JU"&gt;Even secondary exposure can be dangerous. &lt;a href="http://www.rimed.org/rimedicaljournal/2023/06/2023-06-40-images-castaneda-guarderas.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;One case published in the Rhode Island Medical Journal&lt;/a&gt; described an instance where a 50-year-old man accidentally ingested paraquat, and the nurse treating him was burned by his urine that splashed onto her forearms. Within a day, her skin blistered and sloughed off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-48" data-gaid="inarticle-48"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JNFIC26RQNAHFBJDRTZTGIYDOU"&gt;And a former &lt;a href="https://www.mlive.com/public-interest/2025/08/former-grad-student-sues-msu-for-100m-alleging-herbicide-pesticide-exposure-caused-cancer.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Michigan State horticulture student&lt;/a&gt; is suing the university for $100 million, claiming that she developed thyroid cancer from her exposure to pesticides including paraquat, glyphosate and oxyfluorfen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-49" data-gaid="inarticle-49"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BMRB6CTK2VHSXB3BI2HCFQUGSE"&gt;Meanwhile, a much more widespread threat looms large in the background: long-term, low-level exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-50" data-gaid="inarticle-50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Parkinson’s on the rise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-51" data-gaid="inarticle-51"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7EMZTEMDJNAIBD4LL7PZPKBSDI"&gt;Parkinson’s disease is the fastest growing neurological disorder in the world, with cases projected to double by 2050, partly due to an aging population, according to a study published in &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/388/bmj-2024-080952" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;The BMJ, a peer-reviewed medical journal&lt;/a&gt;. It occurs when the brain cells that make dopamine, a chemical that controls movement, stop working or die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-52" data-gaid="inarticle-52"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZRNHS4T6OJBXHCNIIHTGOU55FM"&gt;The exact cause is unknown, likely a mix of genetic and, largely, environmental factors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-53" data-gaid="inarticle-53"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RNKG4Z2HTVE53M7KHCND3C6TMQ"&gt;A Parkinson’s Foundation study found that 87% of those with the disease do not have any genetic risk factors. That means, “for the vast majority of Americans, the cause of Parkinson’s disease lies not within us, but outside of us, in our environment,” said neurologist and researcher Ray Dorsey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-54" data-gaid="inarticle-54"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6XQZAEE335C5DNGKKFVSFMV54I"&gt;That’s why Dorsey, who literally wrote the book on Parkinson’s, calls the disease “largely preventable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-55" data-gaid="inarticle-55"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZZWS6GBDZ5CIVIV4UBZLLNLEJU"&gt;There’s a long list of environmental factors linked to Parkinson’s, but pesticides are one of the biggest threats, according to Dorsey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-56" data-gaid="inarticle-56"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PSPBPSNYPRB2LO24K2TTB2IH3Y"&gt;“If we clean up our environment, we get rid of Parkinson’s disease,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-57" data-gaid="inarticle-57"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Paul Friday dedicated his life to growing peaches on his 50-acre farm in Coloma, Michigan. After buying 50 acres of land in 1962, he started experimenting with crossbreeding to develop the perfect peach. He is now one of thousands of farmers who have filed lawsuits claiming a toxic pesticide called paraquat is to blame for their Parkinson's, a neurological disease.&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Photo courtesy of Paul Friday&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-58" data-gaid="inarticle-58"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QHJOILGAHNAYRBWIVAGPMIQDZ4"&gt;Research, dating back decades, has explored this link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-59" data-gaid="inarticle-59"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QCM45H3C3VBIZKSD5FU65PAIAY"&gt;An &lt;a href="https://www.neurology.org/doi/10.1212/WNL.37.4.728" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;early 1987 case report published in Neurology&lt;/a&gt; discusses the case of a 32-year-old citrus farmer who started experiencing tremors, stiffness and clumsiness after 15 years of spraying paraquat. But “a cause-and-effect relationship is difficult to establish,” a doctor wrote at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-60" data-gaid="inarticle-60"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MCO3VRLBCNHR3EA23RYALKHR74"&gt;A decade later, an animal study from Parkinson’s researcher Deborah Cory-Slechta found that paraquat absorbed by mice destroys the specific type of dopamine neuron that dies in Parkinson’s disease. More recently, her research has found paraquat that’s inhaled can also bypass the blood-brain barrier, threatening neurons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-61" data-gaid="inarticle-61"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UN7EPONBYJAGNNCXVHWGIYYTEU"&gt;“It’s quite clear that it gets into the brain from inhalation models,” Cory-Slechta said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-62" data-gaid="inarticle-62"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="J7AEPYTUYNCVZMWREVY3EUKOEQ"&gt;Critics point to other epidemiological studies being more definitive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-63" data-gaid="inarticle-63"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KDKSTFSLCRCAFEIXAQ6XYTMHHA"&gt;In 2011, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3114824/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;researchers studied&lt;/a&gt; farmworkers exposed to two pesticides, rotenone and paraquat, and determined those exposures increased the risk of developing Parkinson’s by 150%. &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/38309714/#full-view-affiliation-1" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Another study, published last year&lt;/a&gt;, looked at 829 Parkinson’s patients in central California. It found people who live or work near farmland where paraquat is used have a higher risk of developing the disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-64" data-gaid="inarticle-64"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SR7NPPRFHJFLHI23MT3OJ6GQB4"&gt;“It’s kind of like secondhand smoke,” Dorsey said. “You can just live or work near where it’s sprayed and be at risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-65" data-gaid="inarticle-65"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6ND4QCSEP5AO3JKKXAH3EA7KRQ"&gt;This is a growing concern in American suburbs where new houses press up against well-maintained golf courses.&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2833716" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; A study published in JAMA&lt;/a&gt; this year found that living within a mile of a golf course increased the risk of Parkinson’s disease by 126%. It didn’t name specific chemicals but did point to pesticides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-66" data-gaid="inarticle-66"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="643PN2Q5N5EXNMDO2X4K53KGUE"&gt;The EPA in 2021 banned paraquat from golf courses “to prevent severe injury and/or death” from ingestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-67" data-gaid="inarticle-67"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TO4QJDL7VJGJREMAICTDLA5LV4"&gt;Despite all that, it’s difficult to prove whether paraquat directly causes Parkinson’s because it develops years after exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-68" data-gaid="inarticle-68"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RTP572Y3GZF2FG6PU5463CLEUA"&gt;“The disease unfolds over decades, and the seeds of Parkinson’s disease are planted early,” Dorsey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-69" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-69"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Where do the lawsuits stand?&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-70" data-gaid="inarticle-70"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QWX7WOH3RFBNJLGLUM3YJYWJDI"&gt;The legal case over paraquat inched toward a settlement earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-71" data-gaid="inarticle-71"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UBL2KQE3INCTXEX35SEELYS4JM"&gt;Most of the lawsuits have been brought in Illinois under what’s known as multi-district litigation. Unlike a class-action lawsuit, this puts individual cases in front of one federal judge. A few bellwether cases are then chosen to represent the masses and streamline the legal process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-72" data-gaid="inarticle-72"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VGIRUA4XVFDOBFGCM63IITDUOY"&gt;Syngenta, Chevron and the plaintiffs agreed to settle in April, which would wrap up thousands of cases, but an agreement is still being hammered out, court records show. If details can’t be finalized, it will go to trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-73" data-gaid="inarticle-73"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="quote-container"&gt;&lt;div class="impact-quote blockquote"&gt;&lt;div class="quote-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s kind of like secondhand smoke. You can just live or work near where it’s sprayed and be at risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="source-attribution"&gt;Ray Dorsey, a Parkinson's disease research&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-74" data-gaid="inarticle-74"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GILTO3IACNA4TM2U7COHKZXJKM"&gt;Syngenta has adamantly denied the lawsuits’ allegations, saying it backs paraquat as “&lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/2024-11/PQ-Booklet1600212.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;safe and effective&lt;/a&gt;” when it’s used correctly and emphasizing there has been no peer-reviewed scientific analysis that shows paraquat causes Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-75" data-gaid="inarticle-75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="X5LTLXF35NHJDBIVDOJRZOYQOQ"&gt;“Syngenta believes there is no merit to the claims, but litigation can be distracting and costly,” a spokesperson said. “Entering in the agreement in no way implies that paraquat causes Parkinson’s disease or that Syngenta has done anything wrong. We stand by the safety of paraquat.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-76" data-gaid="inarticle-76"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M4QGZGICNZCT5M7ESKM3H3NIEE"&gt;Chevron has also denied the claims saying the “scientific consensus is that paraquat has not been shown to be a cause of Parkinson’s disease.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-77" data-gaid="inarticle-77"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;What company files show&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-78" data-gaid="inarticle-78"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4XOEMU7DM5FVNOWYGLSHIRJX7U"&gt;A trove of internal documents released during litigation, &lt;a href="https://www.thenewlede.org/paraquat-papers-media-library/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;as reported by The Guardian and the New Lede&lt;/a&gt;, appeared to show that the manufacturers were aware of evidence that paraquat could collect in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-79" data-gaid="inarticle-79"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z6QBJSAR2ZFL7PF4NROAAZ5MSA"&gt;But the New Lede acknowledged the documents do not show company scientists believed that paraquat causes Parkinson’s, Syngenta officials pointed out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-80" data-gaid="inarticle-80"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L4AHTOFWLVHU7G6O5PL5LGNDS4"&gt;The trail of bread crumbs started as early as 1958 when a company scientist wrote about a study of 2.2 dipyridyl, a chemical in paraquat, saying it appears to have moderate toxicity “mainly by affecting the central nervous system, and it can be absorbed through the skin,” the internal documents said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-81" data-gaid="inarticle-81"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TLTBEWEQ45HPZGFAYBHTDUTZ7Y"&gt;Imperial Chemical Industries, which later became Syngenta, started selling paraquat under the brand name Gramoxone in 1962, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6689968/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to research&lt;/a&gt;. Gramoxone contains nearly 44% paraquat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-82" data-gaid="inarticle-82"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="customEmbed_01"&gt;&lt;div class="article__custom-image"&gt;&lt;p class="caption"&gt;Syngenta sells paraquat under the brand name Gramaxone, as a resgistered-use pesticide. It's labeled with a skull and cross bones and the warning "one sip can kill." The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency also puts the regulations and rules for use on the label. It's dyed blue and has a strong odor as safety mechanisms. (Photo by Rose White | MLive)&lt;span class="credits"&gt; Rose White | rwhite@MLive.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-83" data-gaid="inarticle-83"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RILEQBRW75AUZDNHEPN32M4EIM"&gt;The internal documents show by 1974, the company updated safety precautions, recommending that anyone spraying the pesticide wear a mask, as there were the first reports of human poisoning and concerns about the effects of paraquat started to grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-84" data-gaid="inarticle-84"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FYY6PR67EFB67G4X233QAJC33U"&gt;A year later, Ken Fletcher from Imperial Chemical wrote a letter to Chevron scientist Dr. Richard Cavelli, saying the chemical company knew of “sporadic reports of CNS (central nervous system) effects in paraquat poisoning” that he believed to be coincidental.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-85" data-gaid="inarticle-85"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OWYNMMWELVAWPGOA5BFRTN2VPM"&gt;Within months, Fletcher also indicated “possible chronic effects” of paraquat exposure, calling it “quite a terrible problem” that should be studied more, the documents say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-86" data-gaid="inarticle-86"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KUTYEHBGV5C5JPLU5JQ65JE2YA"&gt;“Due possibly to good publicity on our part, very few people here believe that paraquat causes any sort of problem in the field,” he wrote in the mid 1970s. “Consequently, any allegation of illness due to spraying never reaches serious proportions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-87" data-gaid="inarticle-87"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JSRARDDIT5A23JTRBSLU6PB2PQ"&gt;By the 1980s, outside research started to pick at the question of paraquat and Parkinson’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-88" data-gaid="inarticle-88"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GYVUGY3OOZBS5DA4XCZ6JAPDK4"&gt;“As more researchers dug into it, it’s only been more firmly established,” said Horsfield with the Environmental Working Group. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-89" data-gaid="inarticle-89"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FHCGRTN6BZDEDEFYIQIYKXQ6SU"&gt;Syngenta pushes back on this, though, saying two recent reports cast doubt on these claims. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-90" data-gaid="inarticle-90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YS4C3IEPWZGJ7FBG2VWYEFVVEE"&gt;A&lt;a href="https://www.cdpr.ca.gov/2024/12/30/department-of-pesticide-regulation-releases-preliminary-findings-from-review-of-environmental-and-human-health-studies-related-to-the-use-of-the-pesticide-paraquat/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; 2024 scientific report&lt;/a&gt; from California pesticide regulators found recent evidence was “insufficient to demonstrate a direct causal association with exposure to paraquat and the increased risk of developing Parkinson’s disease.” And a September analysis from Douglas Weed, an epidemiologist and independent consultant, reached a similar conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-91" data-gaid="inarticle-91"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BO3ZK642V5GTHFLHGDE6SSMSXY"&gt;Syngenta also claims on its website to be a target of a “mass tort machine” that hovers behind multi-district litigation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-92" data-gaid="inarticle-92"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Why hasn’t the EPA banned it?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-93" data-gaid="inarticle-93"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="75CKAB5XJJENNN3MLHZD2ZKDRQ"&gt;In 1981, Norway became the first country to outlaw paraquat due to the risk of poisoning. One by one, more countries followed suit. In 2007, the European Union &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/business/environment/eu-court-reimposes-ban-on-paraquat-weedkiller-idUSL11666800/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;approved a blanket ban&lt;/a&gt; for all 27 member countries, according to media reports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-94" data-gaid="inarticle-94"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DF5YBLFXR5H7PGK2G4RJXJV4KQ"&gt;Yet Syngenta is still allowed to manufacture paraquat in countries that have banned its use. It’s been prohibited in the United Kingdom for 18 years and China banned paraquat to “safeguard people’s life, safety and health,” in 2012, &lt;a href="http://www.chinapesticide.org.cn/eng/detail/21956" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to a government announcement&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-95" data-gaid="inarticle-95"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M25A354WVBEUNBJSEQMHSDZRSU"&gt;Yet about two-thirds of the paraquat imported to the U.S. between 2022 and 2024 came from companies owned by the Chinese government, SinoChem and Red Sun Group, &lt;a href="https://pesticidestorymap.com/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to a joint report&lt;/a&gt; published by three advocacy organizations in October.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-96" data-gaid="inarticle-96"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2Q7WICJXVVGWDDGDYDYKQIJWGQ"&gt;It found most of the 40 million and 156 million pounds imported annually over the past eight years comes from Chinese manufacturing facilities, in either China or Syngenta’s big factory in northern England. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-97" data-gaid="inarticle-97"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NKJXSBUUGFAQBKWV4CYXKMVPC4"&gt;Although hundreds of companies sell paraquat, Syngenta says &lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/docs/the-global-market-in-paraquat.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;it accounts for a quarter of global sales.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-98" data-gaid="inarticle-98"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XPJQ5UVY55DMHOZEDA2OGQD7MU"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/article/business/chemchina-sinochem-merge-agricultural-assets-syngenta-idUSKBN1Z40HA/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;According to previous media reports&lt;/a&gt;, SinoChem, a Chinese state-owned conglomerate, acquired Syngenta in a 2020 merger. SinoChem posted &lt;a href="https://fortune.com/company/sinochem-holdings/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;$3.4 billion&lt;/a&gt; in profits last year, but it’s unclear how much came from paraquat sales because the company doesn’t make earnings reports public. &lt;a href="https://www.syngenta.com/sites/default/files/2025-03/Financial%20Report%202024.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Syngenta reported&lt;/a&gt; $803 million in sales of its “non-selective herbicides,” the class that includes paraquat-containing Gramoxone, according to its 2024 financial report. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-99" data-gaid="inarticle-99"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HHGMRJMUP5GU3JY3G6FGHXB7DQ"&gt;While Chinese companies supply paraquat to American farmers, the report points out China is also a big purchaser of crops, like soybeans, that are grown with help from the pesticide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-100" data-gaid="inarticle-100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RSBBWQ5DLJDOXLNWJQ2SRW3PVE"&gt;“In these two ways, China economically benefits from the application of paraquat in the U.S., where it outsources many of its associated health hazards,” the report said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-101" data-gaid="inarticle-101"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="764KX4XJJ5GRDMKSZTE6QVPBVU"&gt;Paraquat, now prohibited in more than 70 countries, &lt;a href="https://www.ewg.org/areas-focus/toxic-chemicals/paraquat" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;according to the Environmental Working Group&lt;/a&gt;, was reauthorized by the EPA in 2021 when it passed a regularly scheduled 15-year review — a move challenged by critics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-102" data-gaid="inarticle-102"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2Q3265P3B5G75MRS6LQ7VPOELU"&gt;“EPA has the same information that those countries have,” said Kalmuss-Katz, the attorney with EarthJustice. “EPA has just reached a fundamentally different, and what we believe is a legally and scientifically unsupported position, which is: massive amounts of paraquat can continue to be sprayed without unreasonable risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-103" data-gaid="inarticle-103"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="43QS4VGRE5EHPODA5PWMI53J2Y"&gt;The federal agency determined paraquat remains “an effective, inexpensive, versatile, and widely used method of weed control,” and any risks to workers are “outweighed by the benefits” of farms using the weed killer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-104" data-gaid="inarticle-104"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HJPUMSSU5NBHPDMFC4D5BIEY5M"&gt;“It is one of the mostly highly regulated pesticides available in the United States,” the agency said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-105" data-gaid="inarticle-105"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="34QDSAGPFFGZLJAGBAEU6DG5JA"&gt;This decision allowed it to be used with “new stronger safety measures to reduce exposure,” like requiring buffer zones where pesticides can’t be sprayed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-106" data-gaid="inarticle-106"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VGLT7MCGHFD2ZEWWSWWRBROO6A"&gt;For plants like cotton, alfalfa, soybeans and peanuts, the EPA wrote in its decision “growers may need to switch to alternative (weed-killers), which could have financial impacts.” Unlike other pesticides, paraquat works well in low temperatures and early in the season, according to the agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-107" data-gaid="inarticle-107"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="quote-container"&gt;&lt;div class="impact-quote pullquote"&gt;&lt;div class="quote-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we’ve seen over the course of decades is a systemic failure to protect farmworkers and the agricultural community from pesticides.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="source-attribution"&gt;Jonathan Kalmuss-Katz from EarthJustice&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-108" data-gaid="inarticle-108"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2JUORFJJCJGV3FHSBIL4RL2PPM"&gt;More than 200,000 public comments have been submitted to the EPA’s docket on paraquat over the years. Industry groups, farmers, advocacy organizations and others have all chimed in, arguing for or against the weed killer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-109" data-gaid="inarticle-109"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KDQMEVORGFAS3N7SVIWSJFJAPE"&gt;One submitted by a North Dakota farmer, Trey Fischbach, urged the EPA to continue allowing paraquat to fight resistant weeds like kochia, writing it’s the “last tool in the toolbox.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-110" data-gaid="inarticle-110"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HOO2H3BTHNGCHNY34WIRMNU4OA"&gt;The EPA also noted there weren’t many other options. “The chemical characteristics of paraquat are also beneficial as a resistance management tool, where few alternatives are available.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-111" data-gaid="inarticle-111"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ANVFXM4LIZBUVDBEXGLE75CAMI"&gt;But farmers can get trapped on what critics call the “&lt;a href="https://www.panna.org/resources/the-pesticide-treadmill/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;pesticide treadmill&lt;/a&gt;,” in which broad pesticide use leads to “superweeds” that require stronger and stronger pesticides to be knocked down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-112" data-gaid="inarticle-112"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WMHATQ6VW5D5VJ6WZL7D5XIMD4"&gt;A comment submitted by Kay O’Laughlin, from Massachusetts, urged instead: “Do your job and ban paraquat because it is killing people. I speak as someone who lost a brother to Parkinson’s. People should not be disposable so that big agro can make ever greater profits!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-113" data-gaid="inarticle-113"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ST7LZTJNG5D7BLMJN7BLZDWUX4"&gt;The EPA’s 2021 decision was challenged within two months by environmental and farmworker groups who sued the EPA. Kalmuss-Katz said the groups challenged the EPA over reapproving paraquat without “truly grappling” with the connection to Parkinson’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-114" data-gaid="inarticle-114"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7TQ6CZ24SNDTPET5JMIE2CBIDE"&gt;“The EPA here failed to adequately protect farmworkers,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-115" data-gaid="inarticle-115"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:IMCYKIZT4BF5NH2OK56RJ6JHUI" data-fusion-component="IMCYKIZT4BF5NH2OK56RJ6JHUI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:IMCYKIZT4BF5NH2OK56RJ6JHUI" data-fusion-component="IMCYKIZT4BF5NH2OK56RJ6JHUI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-116" data-gaid="inarticle-116"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N5FTKEU5GBHW7C6IJW3HWAHAHA"&gt;After that, the environmental agency shifted under President Joe Biden. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-117" data-gaid="inarticle-117"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GAYRCOE5WNFINGLHJSQRJOLB5Q"&gt;The EPA decided to consider the issues raised in the lawsuits and started seeking additional information last year. In early 2025, it asked the courts for more time to assess the human health risks of paraquat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-118" data-gaid="inarticle-118"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EVK5BC2DOVH6ND2ZIXAQ3AVMNQ"&gt;But the EPA wasn’t focused on Parkinson’s, saying in its decision the “weight of evidence was insufficient” to link paraquat exposure to the neurological disease. Rather, the federal question was over how the weed killer turns into a vapor that could harm people when inhaled or touched. “Parkinson’s Disease is not an expected health outcome of pesticidal use of paraquat,” the EPA said in its review. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-119" data-gaid="inarticle-119"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NE5I2W6LO5BYNNLYCBLZBHK2LY"&gt;The study could take up to four years, according to the EPA, saying it’s “complex, large scale and is conducted under real world conditions,” while paraquat remains on the market. The &lt;a href="https://www.regulations.gov/document/EPA-HQ-OPP-2011-0855-0554" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;agency in October&lt;/a&gt; updated the review, saying it’s now seeking additional information from Syngenta. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-120" data-gaid="inarticle-120"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5AT4THVERJGOLMIZJSEAS63CNQ"&gt;Meanwhile, the EPA has shifted again. The Trump administration this year &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/21/climate/from-industry-to-epa-lobbyist-now-oversees-pesticide-rules.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;put four former industry lobbyists&lt;/a&gt; or executives, from the agricultural, chemical and cleaning industries, in charge of regulating pesticides at the EPA. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-121" data-gaid="inarticle-121"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2BCAIDNAJRDIVHNCVNYDD3ZT3E"&gt;And while it’s not clear where the agency stands on paraquat, there has been an early sign of backing away from opposition to controversial pesticides. Shortly after Kyle Kunkler, a recent American Soybean Association lobbyist, was tapped to lead pesticide policy, the EPA moved to reapprove the use of &lt;a href="https://cen.acs.org/environment/pesticides/EPA-allow-new-dicamba-herbicides/103/web/2025/07" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;a different, controversial weed killer&lt;/a&gt; that had previously been banned by federal courts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-122" data-gaid="inarticle-122"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-heading"&gt;Growing pressure to ban it&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-123" data-gaid="inarticle-123"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KIE4VEVGPFAYFEAXHJ7PT74PPM"&gt;But grassroots pressure to ban paraquat continues to mount.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-124" data-gaid="inarticle-124"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YRPVDBB45FHV3JDLWBID2RHIGY"&gt;“This is a pivotal time for whether paraquat is going to remain active in the United States,” said Simmons, a legal expert for Drugwatch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-125" data-gaid="inarticle-125"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YZHJ4EKKUJAJ5LD6DMQD3O7FIY"&gt;Last year, more than 50 Democratic lawmakers, expressing “grave concern” in letters, urged the EPA to ban paraquat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-126" data-gaid="inarticle-126"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NIAR7O7LD5AUBDL3NLGQWZCG2Y"&gt;“Due to their heightened exposure to paraquat, farmworkers and rural residents are hardest hit by the harmful health effects of paraquat like Parkinson’s,” said &lt;a href="https://casar.house.gov/sites/evo-subsites/casar.house.gov/files/evo-media-document/casar-paraquat-epa-letter.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;an Oct. 7, 2024&lt;/a&gt;, letter signed by U.S. representatives. A &lt;a href="https://www.booker.senate.gov/imo/media/doc/letter_to_epa_re_banning_paraquat.pdf" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;separate letter&lt;/a&gt; was signed by a small group of senators. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-127" data-gaid="inarticle-127"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7ZZ2MWHCWFFGXC7VP3P64QAUSI"&gt;California, a heavy user of paraquat as the top agricultural state, became the first to move toward banning paraquat last year. But the bill ended up getting pared back with Gov. Gavin Newsom signing a law to fast-track reevaluating paraquat’s safety, &lt;a href="https://subscriber.politicopro.com/article/2024/09/newsom-signs-bill-to-speed-up-review-of-widely-banned-herbicide-00181530" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;reporting shows&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-128" data-gaid="inarticle-128"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BA2FTDNV3VD6PP3MABVAC6NYQE"&gt;Pennsylvania lawmakers are also considering banning it under &lt;a href="https://www.pahousegop.com/News/35878/Latest-News/Bill-Package-to-Increase-Food-Safety-Sought-by-Mihalek-and-Bipartisan-Coalition-" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;state bills introduced this year&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-129" data-gaid="inarticle-129"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JG64LT3J4FACBHIM7UKCU6VKNQ"&gt;“There are better, healthier alternatives,” said state Rep. Natalie Mihalek, a Republican who introduced the Pennsylvania legislation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-130" data-gaid="inarticle-130"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RX6OMI5PI5DNRFV4KLXCYUCARE"&gt;On a federal level, outside the EPA, pesticides appear to be in the crosshairs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-131" data-gaid="inarticle-131"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7F2SQ5LXVVGQHHHLDDQRAQV6EU"&gt;Health and Human Services secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., has criticized chemicals being used in farming. But a new Make America Healthy Again report shows Kennedy has backed away from restricting pesticides after agricultural groups pushed back on the “inaccurate story about American agriculture and our food system.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-132" data-gaid="inarticle-132"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IVLWSRV27FFT3ENFIZSJFAT7OM"&gt;At the same time, there’s been &lt;a href="https://civileats.com/2024/03/27/inside-bayers-state-by-state-efforts-to-stop-pesticide-lawsuits/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;a reported industry effort&lt;/a&gt; to pass state laws that would protect pesticide manufacturers from liability. Two states, North Dakota and Georgia, already passed these laws, according to &lt;a href="https://nationalaglawcenter.org/update-on-state-pesticide-liability-limitation-bills/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;the National Agricultural Law Firm&lt;/a&gt;. But&lt;a href="https://www.booker.senate.gov/news/press/booker-introduces-pesticide-injury-accountability-act" target="_blank" rel=""&gt; a federal bill introduced&lt;/a&gt; this year would ensure the manufacturers can’t be held responsible for harming farmers in any state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-133" data-gaid="inarticle-133"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="quote-container"&gt;&lt;div class="impact-quote blockquote"&gt;&lt;div class="quote-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is a pivotal time for whether paraquat is going to remain active in the United States.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="source-attribution"&gt;Christian Simmons, legal expert for DrugWatch&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-134" data-gaid="inarticle-134"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K4UYKBRXFBE77HL7ER7CUG4GPA"&gt;As this tug of war continues, paraquat continues to be sprayed on agricultural fields throughout the United States. The EPA is still assessing its risks. And nearly 90,000 Americans are getting diagnosed with Parkinson’s disease every year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-135" data-gaid="inarticle-135"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z4A3S22DAFFZPDMJC5BVKAINKI"&gt;Meanwhile for critics, the evidence seems clear: it’s too dangerous. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-136" data-gaid="inarticle-136"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="V37TDYW2SZBDBHSWV6FJYV44NI"&gt;“The easiest thing to do is we should ban paraquat,” Dorsey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-137" data-gaid="inarticle-137"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5LUSMJY2LVC3NBJ3TYQFOXQY3U"&gt;&lt;i&gt;AL.com reporter Margaret Kates contributed to this story. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-138" data-gaid="inarticle-138"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MLive.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxQbVpxRG9waEFXOWcwQzdyd1ljYy1UUGdXV1Y2c1YxQ1ZzVjI2ODBBR0hCRFVIYVVUVVdSV2dOend6UGpsWDdFU0FSbUVYOUhMbjlMX1RIT1VtM1Qwb1hObTNZTXFiWVBwdlFNWkRlWFpBX2FadTFPRzNSdkF0b05vWHM5ZFRnMTVkSHg4UzhFc3VkdWJKUEFpQllPRXFHQjdzOW9JTlNIUnl0MEV6c0E</guid></item><item><title>这到底是怎么回事……香蕉水？ -《洛杉矶时报》</title><link>https://www.latimes.com/lifestyle/story/2025-12-15/banana-water-explained</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-element="story-body" class="ct-rich-text-children font-cms-font-brand-text font-normal text-lg leading-7.75 [&amp;amp;_&amp;gt;p]:text-cms-story-body-color-text clearfix max-w-170 mt-7.5 mb-10 mx-auto" data-subscriber-content&gt; &lt;p&gt;If a can of coconut water and a banana smoothie had a baby, it might be banana water. The latest plant-based hydration beverage on the market is being touted as “the peel good beverage” that offers “a bunch of nutrients.” And it’s drumming up attention on social media. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Boyfriend says it has aromatics of slightly overripe banana,” one Reddit user, &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.reddit.com/user/leemoongrass/" target="_blank"&gt;leemoongrass&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Volumeeating/comments/1asn7px/my_boyfriend_just_came_home_with_this_lmao/?rdt=52704" target="_blank"&gt;commented&lt;/a&gt;, adding, “It honestly isn’t that bad.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It smells like baby food,” &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DQXGmLvD9x_/" target="_blank"&gt;lsp2c&lt;/a&gt; said on Instagram. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not to be confused with banana water for plants, a DIY fertilizer made by soaking banana peels in water to extract nutrients, such as potassium and vitamin C, for your flora. Or homemade banana drinks, such as hot water &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.allrecipes.com/recipe/270779/hot-banana-water/" target="_blank"&gt;steeped with banana peels&lt;/a&gt; and strained, or blended banana smoothies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new drink, sold in supermarkets, is being marketed as an alternative to sports drinks, a sort of coconut water 2.0.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But some have taken to social media with questions: “How do you think you juice a banana?!” &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@tybottofficial/video/7504810072766188830" target="_blank"&gt;tybottofficial&lt;/a&gt; asked on TikTok, while unpacking a box of organic banana water from Woodstock. “I wonder if they’re just in a factory, like, you know, really milking these bananas, I guess?” (He gave the drink a 7.5 out of 10.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.woodstock-foods.com/the-goods/product.organic-banana-water-042563018771.html" target="_blank"&gt;Woodstock&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="link" href="https://banagua.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Banagua&lt;/a&gt;, leading manufacturers of banana water, make their banana water in Thailand from organic “Thai golden” and “Thai cultivated” bananas, which are shorter and stubbier-looking than the standard yellow bananas sold in most American supermarkets and which have a slight pinkish tint. The fruit gets pinker in the processing and the drink has a pinkish hue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re a label ogler, the ingredient list will put you at ease. Banana water contains just one ingredient: bananas. There’s no significant water added to it. A banana is 80% water, Banagua co-founder Rob Smithson says, and the processing of the drink (an “enzymatic process”) separates the water from the pulp — the drink is slightly viscous but not pulpy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woodstock’s bananas are steamed and mashed with “proprietary enzymes” to release nutrients. “Think of it as liquefied bananas,” says Bruce Bruemmer,  vice president of brand management at UNFI Brands+, Woodstock’s parent company. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The upshot? Both companies say their banana water is especially healthy, brimming with electrolytes like potassium, B6 and magnesium, as well as minerals and antioxidants such as vitamin A and C. The drink has no added sugar, and zero fat, sodium and cholesterol, though a 330ml can does have about 13 grams of carbohydrates, slightly less than Naked coconut water’s 14 grams in a container of the same size. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So how healthy &lt;i&gt;is&lt;/i&gt; banana water, what does it taste like, and is it worth the hype? Here’s the deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Manufacturer’s claims:&lt;/b&gt; “Our banana water has 205 mg of magnesium — 50% of the daily value,” Smithson says of Banagua’s Original Banana, which went on the market in July 2025. “And it’s especially hydrating — probably 2-3 bananas per can, which you can bring anywhere and you don’t have to worry about moldy bananas. And just 50 calories — Naked’s coconut water has 60.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woodstock’s 500ml can of banana water, which went on the market in March 2024, has just 80 calories. “Our Woodstock Organic Banana Water stands out for its great taste and natural hydration,” Bruemmer says, “delivering 765mg of electrolytes — similar to many sports drinks — without any artificial colors, flavors or preservatives.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Nutritionists’ take:&lt;/b&gt; “It’s probably a sequel to coconut water,” says &lt;a class="link" href="https://gufaculty360.georgetown.edu/s/contact/00336000014Re56AAC/thomas-g-sherman" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Thomas Sherman&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of pharmacology and physiology at Georgetown University Medical Center. “It would appeal to people who are worried about animal wellness and saturated fat in their milk drinks or who are worried about too high sugar — so this fits the bill. But I question its effectiveness — these types of beverages offer such trivial amounts of electrolytes compared to what’s already in our food. And it’s expensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sherman says that, in the end, it comes down to the consumer’s intentions for choosing banana water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you’re buying it because of the taste, and you want to support a plant-based beverage, and [because] it’s fairly low sugar, then fine,” he says. “But if you’re buying it because you’re interested in getting more potassium and magnesium and calcium with low sodium, then it’s silly because just &lt;i&gt;eat plants&lt;/i&gt;, &lt;i&gt;eat food&lt;/i&gt;, that’s going to supply hundreds of times more potassium and calcium and magnesium.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Categorizing banana water as a sports drink is problematic, adds &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.eatrightpro.org/about-us/for-media/meet-our-spokespeople/vanessa-king" target="_blank"&gt;Vanessa King&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian nutritionist specializing in supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sports drinks replace electrolytes,” King says. “The problem with banana water is that while bananas are very high in potassium, the electrolyte that you predominantly lose when you exercise is sodium — and it doesn’t provide sodium. I would not choose it over a sports drink.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;King points out that “banana juice,” as she calls it, suffers from the same concerns as other juices: “It’s more concentrated sugar without the fiber you’d get from the fruit version.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But any amount of potassium, magnesium, vitamin A and C — all key nutrients in banana water — is helpful, King says. “They’re  all nutrients that are generally under-consumed by Americans. But bananas also have those nutrients!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The taste: &lt;/b&gt;We found it sweet and tropical-tasting, slightly viscous but surprisingly refreshing. However, we didn’t go bananas for it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cost: &lt;/b&gt;Banagua’s Original Banana (330ml): $3.49; Woodstock’s Organic Banana Water (500ml): $2.99.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Los Angeles Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE9JdEkxdUZseDNoN0dEcEVPNTFyV1h3bnFZRWdrUWU1bV9TejFqdWRlSE0zcXNlOThuQ05JQ3BsSDN3Y0hEdzRXZE14Y2xUV1JtRlplUTNybHRtZFRNU0NhWGdVZzJjdTRnR2xERkwyVmx4YzM0eEprMEpiTEM2dw</guid></item><item><title>列|我是一名医生。以下是我推荐的对抗炎症的11种食物。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/15/foods-that-fight-inflammation/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="G22IUVOO5VHUVJJ4PKFJ73BJ4M" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Are anti-inflammatory diets backed by science? Can some foods really cause inflammation in my body?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TQ7BEQUMEFBJ3HPAE22CQ2HHLA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When my patients ask me about anti-inflammatory diets, they’re usually expecting me to talk about &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/06/25/turmeric-supplements-may-harm-liver-some-people/" target="_blank"&gt;turmeric&lt;/a&gt; or the latest &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/01/29/green-smoothies-juices-shortcomings-benefits/" target="_blank"&gt;viral green drink&lt;/a&gt;. Lists of “toxic” foods are popular on social media — followed by advice to start the day with things like celery juice to help you “detox.” And while I’d love to say that a cup of blueberries a day will “turn off” inflammation, that’s not what the evidence shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 10:41:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOdExSOFpvWXZ1NDJJRmQxOVo2U2FYVzFRVDZkVnIxY3BrVnVsNHFKSUgxdUpScnlqOHcwSlhwLXV0UFN5dHZGTkd3Q2NocnQ4ZXI2a2hrOHlGY1FYVTFKanNJQjNrZE5ITDZZRXhuX1RzMmcyZWRkdkhWX3NGU0p5MDJLNmM4cVpN</guid></item><item><title>什么是痛风，为什么痛风呈上升趋势？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/15/well/live/gout-pain-treatment-recovery.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 10:00:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNQmR0VlBsMlFVR2lSVWk5RmM2T0UwaENKTFFaTUxVTV9HNUpaUm0zVWtDRkxVME15VElCZzFiTEZLWk0weHJGZVY1UDlKaWlFREFOeWcwcXpVdGVhbERwT08wa2dZVmh3UU56UnhJZW5OOXNDc01ydWtCNFNuOHhYTi01NVM</guid></item><item><title>想在2026年拥有更健康的大脑吗？报名参加Well的5天挑战赛。-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/15/well/mind/brain-health-challenge-sign-up.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 10:00:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQYjhTYUNwajg5Yk41SDlKVDhEZlpySFREamVUcXVzQlREVm1kMmI4TGJGNVY0QnJrS2I4TDNEQ1pMay1VSjQtczY4RzZ4YXlxNGlQa1NmdUlsb3htZVBXZzk2cF9ybTEtMjlva2t4THU3ajVzME8xWGtKYk1DbVFQZ1liejlsdFU</guid></item><item><title>合成染料亚甲基蓝的健康宣称背后是什么？ - NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/15/nx-s1-5634680/methylene-blue-supplement-safety</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-102203" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Getty Images/Illustration Andrea D'Aquino for NPR
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Wellness enthusiasts seeking to hack their way to health and longevity have a new favorite remedy — one that &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@sarahlawuk/video/7140354795554213125?_r=1&amp;amp;_t=ZP-92AJZMNpvag" target="_blank"&gt;stains their tongues blue&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Methylene blue has been around since the 1870s when it was used as a textile dye. Since then it's been prescribed as an antimalarial treatment and an antidote for cyanide poisoning. Today it's&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;medication approved by the U.S. Food and Drug Administration as treatment for methemoglobinemia, a rare blood disorder.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But online influencers are promoting it for what they claim are its wellness properties. It's taking off among biohackers, who seek to optimize their health via lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;   
   
   

   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/pifmGCPjluM" target="_blank"&gt;Commentators speculated&lt;/a&gt; that Robert F. Kennedy Jr. takes methylene blue after a video of the nation's top health official circulated early this year. He can be seen using an eyedropper to mix a cobalt blue liquid into a cup of water. Kennedy never confirmed what he was taking, though the vibrant color and applicator resembles the methylene blue products that are sold by online retailers. And Kennedy's known for &lt;a href="https://subscriber.politicopro.com/article/2025/07/rfk-jr-takes-his-vitamins-but-this-vitamin-industry-ceo-isnt-sure-hes-an-ally-00476806" target="_blank"&gt;taking supplements&lt;/a&gt;, and has a track record of embracing debunked or unproven scientific claims.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Claim:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Methylene blue improves the function of mitochondria — components of our cells which convert nutrients into energy — and that results in a host of benefits, such as slowed aging, better mood and sharper cognition. Some even claim it alleviates jetlag.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Evidence:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Lab studies and animal trials have found that methylene blue can help cells make energy more efficiently by giving mitochondria an easier way to move electrons when their normal pathways are damaged or stressed, says Lorne Hofseth, who studies dyes' effect on cancer and inflammation at the University of South Carolina College of Pharmacy.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;He also cites studies done in rodents and worms to show that methylene blue improves brain energy use, reduces inflammation, and protects against neurological damage.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When it comes to research in humans, there have been several smaller trials in select populations that have shown antidepressant or cognitive benefits from pure methylene blue. But Hofseth says these findings remain preliminary — which is why he strongly discourages people from taking it as a supplement, as right now, the risks outweigh the benefits.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"You're wasting your money," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That doesn't mean methylene blue is a total scientific dead end. Hofseth points to promising work being done in the UK on a modified form of the dye to treat Alzheimer's disease. But this methylene blue is different from the dye people are purchasing as an over the counter supplement.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So why might online influencers feel convinced that methylene blue makes them feel better and think faster?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Cognition is subjective," says Nicole Brandt, a professor at the University of Maryland School of Pharmacy who studies geriatric pharmacotherapy. "We have good and bad days if we sleep well, if we eat well."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Risks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In addition to wasting money, Hofseth and Brandt both warn of adverse side effects from methylene blue. That includes serotonin toxicity, which is a serious drug reaction, which can cause elevated blood pressure, diarrhea, seizures, and even death: People who take certain antidepressants, including Zoloft and Lexapro, are especially at risk.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Methylene blue &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4091817/" target="_blank"&gt;could also be dangerous for&lt;/a&gt; people who have a &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/genetics/condition/glucose-6-phosphate-dehydrogenase-deficiency/" target="_blank"&gt;genetic disorder&lt;/a&gt; affecting red blood cells called glucose-6-phosphate dehydrogenase deficiency.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Another concern is people may not know what they're getting when they buy methylene blue over the counter.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We really don't have good oversight, or any oversight to nutritional supplements and what's in them," Brandt says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Unlike drugs, supplements are not approved by the FDA for safety and efficacy before they go on the market. But they do have to follow certain rules around labeling. Manufacturers are also subject to inspection, and the FDA monitors safety concerns once products are on the market.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;However, federal regulators have finite resources and are unable to catch every bad actor, says Dr. Joshua Sharfstein, a professor at Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health and a former principal deputy commissioner at the FDA. That's why he says it's buyer beware with methylene blue, and similar products&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"The internet is a big place," he told NPR. "There are a lot of products for sale that are not safe."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;It's also not clear whether methylene blue meets the regulatory definition of a supplement. It's listed in an FDA database as a generic drug that requires a prescription.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And most methylene blue products are not in a federal registry of dietary supplement labels, according to Jeff Ventura, vice president for communications at the Council for Responsible Nutrition. Many of the products seen online are not explicitly identified as supplements.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The FDA did not respond to a request for comment about how it's possible for online retailers to sell methylene blue without a prescription.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bottom Line:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Those who still want to try methylene blue should first talk to a clinician to ensure they're not at risk for adverse side effects. And if someone's taking methylene blue for a specific health concern, like brain fog or fatigue, a primary care provider can also help address those issues, says Sharfstein.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If you do decide to try the product, be warned: It could turn your teeth, tongue and urine bright blue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQV3dYT2lFem9PLURsdjFWQmlVZm03WWVDeE9raVJtY1VQU2d3bWZXcmFPbkZ0SmppLWFFMjhaUGVJQnRmeEg2dTlSYWh6SDZzeHRrdE1JOEo4X0hpMU1jbmRWMGxoOU92YjNFUFlUX1daLTVVQ1NscGlJTDhwOWR5bUhVRQ</guid></item><item><title>儿童猝死令基因治疗研究领域充满希望- statnews.com</title><link>https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/15/gene-therapy-capsida-biotherapeutics-clinical-trial-death-ramifications/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gene therapy researchers were converging on a holy grail. A few years ago, researchers at labs and companies reported they had engineered viruses that could ferry corrective genes deep into the brain, giving potential entry to a new world of treatments for Alzheimer’s, Parkinson’s, and a slew of rare genetic diseases.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This summer, after years of careful study, the first person underwent gene therapy using one of the new viruses. The patient, a young child, died two and a half days later.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The death has sent concern and uncertainty rippling through labs and companies developing gene therapies for the brain, along with rare disease groups who hoped these tools could deliver long-sought cures. They worry that Capsida Biotherapeutics unearthed a broader risk for other viruses designed to travel like a messenger pigeon to our brains, one that could derail years of progress. &lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker article" aria-labelledby="restricted-story-heading" aria-describedby="restricted-story-description" checked&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-bar"&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-text"&gt;STAT+ Exclusive Story&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-login"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;img class="restricted-content-breaker-bg" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-breaker-bg.png" alt="STAT+"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper"&gt;
				&lt;span class="stat-paywall-archive"&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/"&gt;
						&lt;img class="stat-plus-logo" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-logo-white.svg" alt="STAT+"&gt;
					&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/span&gt;
				&lt;h2 id="restricted-story-heading"&gt;This article is exclusive to STAT+ subscribers&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;h3 id="restricted-story-description"&gt;Unlock this article — plus daily coverage and analysis of the biotech sector — by subscribing to STAT+.&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper-cta mobile"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta mobile"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-cards"&gt;
					&lt;div class="slider-container" aria-label="Subscription plan toggle"&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="individual" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Individual plans&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;p class="switch" role="switch" tabindex="0" aria-checked="false"&gt;
							&lt;button class="slider"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="group" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Group plans&lt;/button&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
							

		
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button view-all" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker view all plans" aria-label="View All Plans"&gt;View All Plans&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="restricted-message-breaker"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-wrapper"&gt;
								
								&lt;div class="restricted-content-message"&gt;
					&lt;p class="restricted-content-text"&gt;
						To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.					&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button restricted-button" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker subscribe cta 1"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
								
							&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 09:32:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPZkp6MDdZUGJkUU5FeTEtNlRCRk5BMk9TZzRaRmVkQ1dycmluU3NXOE16ejNySTRiaUdYQ003N3FpT1lKMlZTMWVRanhGc0EzVEdRVktmYVpkZk8zdXdLQ0w3UEhORWVESHVQZEo4OXNpRWVvd1N3QTl6THFLSnYyazY2dnI0R3F1c0NpNHplZTRpZWVkbGRnSnI3dVc4LWd3MDJCRUdiUGtrNGFF</guid></item><item><title>肠道不健康的迹象和恢复肠道的4种方法- CNET</title><link>https://www.cnet.com/health/medical/signs-unhealthy-gut-how-fix-it-microbiome-expert/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="c-ShortcodeContent c-ShortcodeContent-theme:default sm:u-col-2 md:u-col-6 lg:u-col-12"&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p1"&gt;An unhealthy gut can look like more than just a casual &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/upset-stomach-these-6-natural-remedies-may-help/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;stomachache&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. After all, Gail Cresci, a microbiome expert at the Cleveland Clinic, describes the microorganisms inside your gut as "little pets living inside your intestinal tract," and like real-life pets, they can exhibit multiple symptoms that reveal they aren't at their best.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p2"&gt;As your gut's microorganisms help you digest food, produce vitamins and hormones, support your &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/best-zinc-supplements/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;immune system&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and regulate inflammation, they have a significant impact on your overall health. That's why it's crucial you pay attention to signs your gut may be unhealthy, and do what you can to get things back on track.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr data-ng-block="{" id&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Don't miss any of our unbiased tech content and lab-based reviews. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a target="_self" data-id="6481f688-630b-45e1-a512-ff6f56bd8201" href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=cnet.com"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Add CNET&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; as a preferred Google source.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr data-ng-block="{" id&gt;&lt;h2 id="76c0aa22-bb3e-48f3-a1f7-30d06e799aa4" data-ng-block="{"&gt;7 signs of an unhealthy gut&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you're bloated or you have lots of gas, you may have a disrupted composition and function of the gut microbiome," Cresci said, adding that the only way to know for sure is to have it measured with a microbiome test like a stool sample.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Six &lt;a target="_self" data-id="af31c9b8-8e82-425e-9831-648529de341e" href="https://www.healthline.com/health/gut-health#improving-gut-health"&gt;other signs&lt;/a&gt; of an unhealthy gut may include: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-ng-block="{" id&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fatigue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Food intolerance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Skin irritation or problems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trouble sleeping&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vomiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Upset stomach&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research has &lt;a data-id="6be54eaa-9115-468a-be0c-92ab77c90ac0" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6048199/" target="_self"&gt;linked skin issues like acne and psoriasis&lt;/a&gt; to the gut. Studies are also looking into how the gut biome &lt;a data-id="6be54eaa-9115-468a-be0c-92ab77c90ac0" href="https://academic.oup.com/hropen/article/2022/2/hoac015/6553029" target="_self"&gt;affects reproductive health&lt;/a&gt; and hormone levels.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-all-top spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-small c-shortcodeImage-pullRight"&gt;&lt;a rel href="https://www.cnet.com/health-tips/" target="_blank" class="c-shortcodeImage_imageContainer"&gt;   &lt;/a&gt; &lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="94708dfd-99a0-4fe2-b095-7e92f882caaa" data-ng-block="{"&gt;How to keep your gut healthy &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to see a doctor to determine the root cause of your health concern and rule out other conditions. Making changes to your diet or routine that may improve your gut and overall health is a good first step.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cresci also said that there's no exact standard for the perfectly healthy gut microbiome because everyone's composition is so different. Bearing that in mind, here are four things you can do to help keep it on the right track.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone's gut microbiome is different, so there's no model for what a perfectly healthy one looks like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;Carol Yepes/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="01fc1652-fb16-4b9a-a088-ffe23a8edab5" data-ng-block="{"&gt; 1. Eat gut-friendly foods &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gut microbiome prefers foods we can't digest. This includes &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/is-fibermaxxing-new-protein-goals-asked-nutrition-experts/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;foods with a lot of fiber&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, such as fresh fruits, vegetables, whole grains, legumes, seeds and nuts; foods we already know we should eat for their nutritional properties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Cresci, foods high in sugar and fat and low in fiber should be removed from your gut or eaten in lower amounts. "These are all associated with the consumption of a Western diet, which is also associated with a disrupted microbiome," she said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond a gut-healthy diet, which not-so-coincidentally coincides with a &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;span&gt;heart-healthy diet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, eating fermented foods can help replace the good microbes and their metabolites. Cresci lists yogurt, kombucha and kefir as examples.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="5ac7a098-85ca-486b-b30b-0c2980f6f670" data-ng-block="{"&gt; 2. Make note of the medications you're taking &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's a well-known fact that taking antibiotics &lt;a target="_self" data-id="dce02fc7-a605-4e78-86af-53300e39ae08" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7732679/"&gt;disrupts, at least temporarily, the family of "good" bacteria&lt;/a&gt; thriving in your body. Some &lt;a target="_self" data-id="dce02fc7-a605-4e78-86af-53300e39ae08" href="https://www.cdc.gov/antibiotic-use/community/pdfs/aaw/au_arent_always_the_answer_fs_508.pdf"&gt;common side effects&lt;/a&gt; of taking antibiotics include nausea, diarrhea and developing yeast infections. If you're prescribed an antibiotic or have recurring infections that have you taking antibiotics often, ask your doctor about what you can do to help minimize the disruption to your microbiome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other medications that can disrupt our microbiomes, Cresci says, include those that alter the pH of the stomach and take away acid. Examples include proton pump inhibitors, aka PPIs, and histamine H2-receptor antagonists or H2 blockers, which are used to reduce acid reflux symptoms and might be available over the counter.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By keeping track of the medications you're taking, you can help pinpoint the cause of your symptoms and (with sign-off from your doctor) take the appropriate steps or substitutions if gut health is an issue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="c876917b-a21c-44df-9743-beeb169eaa5b" data-ng-block="{"&gt; 3. Find the &lt;em&gt;right&lt;/em&gt; probiotics or supplements  &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to incorporating more yogurt or fermented foods into their diet, some people may &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;span&gt;seek a probiotic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in hopes of balancing their gut, as they're designed to &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/nutrition/how-do-probiotics-improve-your-gut-health/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mimic an intact microbiota&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. If you're considering taking a supplement, including probiotics, Cresci told CNET it's important to know that probiotics are strain-specific, and "each strain has its own method of action."  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, some probiotics are designed to help people with antibiotic-induced diarrhea, but that won't work for a person taking them for bowel regularity.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You want to take the one that has been studied for whatever your problem is," she said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, keep in mind that probiotics will not completely override what you eat.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you have a bad diet, and you want to keep eating a bad diet but want to improve your microbiome, a probiotic isn't gonna help you," Cresci said. "You have to do the other part too."  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="c-shortcodeImage u-clearfix c-shortcodeImage-large c-shortcodeImage-hasCaption"&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_caption g-inner-spacing-right-small g-text-xxsmall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whole grains, fruits and vegetables are great food choices if you want to start healing your gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="c-shortcodeImage_credit g-inner-spacing-right-small g-outer-spacing-top-xsmall g-color-text-meta g-text-xxxsmall"&gt;piotr_malczyk/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="90970c8c-7c40-4c77-9db1-2c50c03fa448" data-ng-block="{"&gt; 4. Move your body every day and prioritize sleep  &lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Get better sleep" or "exercise more" might sound like tired advice, but improving your sleep hygiene and &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;span&gt;squeezing in more physical activity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are tried and true ways to improve your health, including your gut health.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exercise may &lt;a data-id="74795062-398a-4c91-a327-5038c8b42238" href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/gut-health-workout" target="_self"&gt;help your gut in different ways&lt;/a&gt;, including by improving your circulation, helping your metabolism and aiding your digestive muscles, according to the Cleveland Clinic. If you dread running or don't have time to go to the gym, don't worry: There are small ways you can get your body in the habit of moving every day or at least more frequently.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement" class="c-adDisplay_container c-pageArticle_ad c-pageArticle_ad-90 g-outer-spacing-bottom-medium c-adDisplay_container_incontent-ad-plus-billboard-middle spaced blank"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting good sleep is another general piece of wellness advice tied directly to the health of our guts. According to Cresci, our microbiome adheres to the &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/health/sleep/internal-clock-out-of-whack-heres-how-to-reset-and-get-better-sleep/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink c-shortcodeLink-active"&gt;&lt;span&gt;circadian rhythm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, too. So, if we eat when our gut microbiome isn't ready, we won't be set up to process the nutrients of our food properly.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lack of sleep also triggers an increase in stress and cortisol, which have &lt;span section="shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;a href="/" rel class="c-shortcodeLink"&gt;&lt;span&gt;negative mental&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and physical impacts.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There's a lot going on with the gut-brain interaction, so that signals back to the microbiome, and vice versa," Cresci said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps most fundamental is the fact that when we're exhausted, we don't have the energy to check off many of the things that keep us healthy, including exercising or finding a nutritious meal -- both of which affect our gut health.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When you're sleepy, tired, exhausted, you tend not to do the things we know are good for microbiomes," Cresci said. "So it kind of perpetuates itself." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNET</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 09:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNVDg5NlJkY3RId2RsdVJDOFA2VlNVdmVadjJPalZjdVNuc3hNenNjQ0gxaUlJa0J5bkRCVkJqZ2NWUHpzTi1nR1Q0a09OZ2RPT3hITlRuMkJYaHotYXNWdHR0emlQNUh4WUdsdFRBbTIzMW1tLW5fSkZaVTVvV2FhczZmTzRmaTNnbVlHX3Vn</guid></item><item><title>英国外科医生说晨吐与健康妊娠结局有关，解释了为什么会发生；分享管理技巧|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/uk-surgeon-says-morning-sickness-is-linked-to-healthy-pregnancy-outcomes-explains-why-it-happens-shares-tips-to-manage-101765779403920.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/uk-surgeon-says-morning-sickness-is-linked-to-healthy-pregnancy-outcomes-explains-why-it-happens-shares-tips-to-manage-101765779403920.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For many expectant mothers, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/dietitian-shares-5-red-flags-of-food-intolerance-affecting-your-gut-bloating-cramping-nausea-and-more-101758258032942.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="nausea"&gt;nausea &lt;/a&gt;and vomiting are an all-too-familiar part of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/pregnancy" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="pregnancy"&gt;pregnancy &lt;/a&gt;- and despite its name, “&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/physician-reveals-fathers-pre-conception-fitness-affects-pregnancy-outcomes-like-morning-sickness-and-preeclampsia-101764591697716.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="morning sickness"&gt;morning sickness&lt;/a&gt;” rarely confines itself to the early hours of the day. The symptoms can strike at any time, often disrupting daily life and taking a physical and emotional toll. However, emerging research suggests that this uncomfortable phase may also be a reassuring sign, with nausea and vomiting linked to healthier pregnancies, improved foetal outcomes and a lower risk of &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fertility-expert-explains-what-ivf-can-do-for-couples-struggling-with-recurrent-pregnancy-loss-or-miscarriage-101759985443795.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="pregnancy loss"&gt;pregnancy loss&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/15/550x309/morning_sickness_1765779826032_1765779826183.jpg" alt="Morning sickness during pregnancy can strike at any time of the day!(Pixabay)" title="Morning sickness during pregnancy can strike at any time of the day!(Pixabay)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/15/550x309/morning_sickness_1765779826032_1765779826183.jpg" alt="Morning sickness during pregnancy can strike at any time of the day!(Pixabay)" title="Morning sickness during pregnancy can strike at any time of the day!(Pixabay)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Morning sickness during pregnancy can strike at any time of the day!(Pixabay)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/anushka-sharma-s-nutritionist-reveals-how-her-pregnancy-diet-differed-from-most-indian-women-s-eating-habits-101765701206354.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Anushka Sharma’s nutritionist reveals how her ‘pregnancy diet’ differed from most Indian women’s eating habits"&gt;Anushka Sharma’s nutritionist reveals how her ‘pregnancy diet’ differed from most Indian women’s eating habits&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr Karan Rajan, a UK-based surgeon and popular health content creator, has explained why morning sickness happens - and why it is not just a morning phenomenon.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;In an Instagram video posted on December 15, the surgeon highlights that morning sickness can be an indicator of a healthy pregnancy and offers tips to help manage nausea and vomiting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Morning sickness during pregnancy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Rajan points out that there is nothing strictly “morning” about morning sickness, as symptoms can occur at any time of day during pregnancy. He notes, “Whoever invented the term morning sickness is a filthy liar. There's nothing mourning about it. It's more like 24/7 life sickness. The worst subscription service you never signed up for.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;However, the surgeon adds that, somewhat ironically, morning sickness has been linked to better pregnancy outcomes. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;He explains that preliminary research suggests nausea and vomiting are associated with a lower risk of pregnancy loss and improved foetal outcomes, although the evidence has limitations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Rajan explains, “This may be because morning sickness correlates with a higher level of hCG, Human Chorionic Gonadotropin, as well as oestrogen and progesterone. All these hormones are associated with a well-developing placenta. And all of these hormones are associated with nausea pathways in the brain and/or gut.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Nausea hacks that might help&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Rajan shares some strategies that helped his pregnant wife manage morning sickness, which she experienced predominantly during her first trimester. He suggests, “Bland food like toast or crackers first thing in the morning actually helps since nausea is worsened by an empty stomach. Similarly, nibbling something edible periodically and grazing with smaller, more frequent meals was more helpful than three larger meals.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;He also highlights ginger as an effective way to manage morning sickness, along with certain anti-nausea supplements. The surgeon recommends, “Ginger in tea form, candy chews, or even raw help, because the gingerol chemicals have a GI effect. My wife didn't use these, but &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/rujuta-diwekar-suggests-4-must-have-foods-during-navratri-fasting-bananas-for-vitamin-b6-to-cashews-for-magnesium-101758605494186.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vitamin B6"&gt;vitamin B6&lt;/a&gt; supplements and doxylamine are safe to take in pregnancy and are useful anti-nausea aids.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 06:51:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgJBVV95cUxQNDRROHJmbkhqTG4ycVAwckowckRaeDk5V3dtTGpGX1pld08xQUZ6WS1qS3JhZUxFNEZtRVNHZ1A2Q2N2M2t4V204eC1UR215bmc5V0JYVzV2UGlNY3c4STJwQ2RIUmdLd3FDT2k3TTdJQzQ1bllrYzB1dG95QnBnTnp3SFgzV0p5aFdkZmJyLXh5d1NSc1RzVlp1V3JVOVhQbGRDMGhLeU15VFhfTTJFcnRtdHpWSThSd0dnZlRtZV9oUkIyOGtlWTFhOFdkUVc3OEtodEprcjkwel94MF9KNF9BTW1RdmFfNy11N2JzZ0tJeU9zb0hDTWlPR3NpZU5rVURlR0RTQWxRYjVnMlZpMmJzajlad9IBmwJBVV95cUxPOXFabW5jVFY2RXU5ZDlqM2JGRmlEckRROHI2eVJMd2l1VXphS0pFSXpzV0RXNWdVOVdJQ1drZ3dQRXp6ZlFmZkxkVGVOYmdTajU2c3NZbGk5MXItZ0k2cEhNM3dRM0ZkSjVRNHpXOERsaExXWDl0RnVnVGQycG41Qm9QeVBRQXZ3LTJpVGRRdDhVU2lZWkxaUGlwUnRrVmNVLUpMUXdqcjJnLVlZSWlCaXVsMWRPUzJRVVo0bHJyVkdFZmRDMllXaDlQaExmLVd5SFlSb25LdkhORkhvQ0dPV0hZX2NlYzk2cFpRSlp1LVZPNGJGNm5WcWxwQTdqWkdUZ1dfSmxkc0NSc01yYkJLNldMZ1dMY29vdDI0</guid></item><item><title>新研究显示，这种蛋白质可能掌握长寿的秘密- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/this-protein-may-hold-the-secret-to-longevity-new-research-reveals/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 04:11:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPRlZoM3B2U1o4ZGpqMUhTai1hTTdqYWlUeVNCNkw2SkFlZHhXdHBtVDdrM045SlpMb2g5UElMNG9LMlhLcElhWDFFZ05IbEZIei1sNkF2c290ZzdGc3RZXzFDSXNkUG9fbkRTQlY4U0NFUlpFNWNRWTJ1RDZMTFM5NG1LaklidFVPYmlQX09rcjhCRW9Oa0pj</guid></item><item><title>AIIMS研究发现，心脏病是45: 5以下人群猝死的主要原因您应该注意的“不寻常”警告信号-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/aiims-study-finds-heart-disease-as-the-leading-cause-of-sudden-death-in-people-under-45-5-unusual-warning-signs-you-should-pay-attention-to/photostory/125969976.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turns out, you are never too young to fall prey to heart disease nowadays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new AIIMS study has brought in a major health alert for India and the world: Heart disease has become the leading cause of sudden death among people in the age group of 18 to 45. Once considered an older person's disease, cardiovascular causes are striking younger adults who often appear healthy just moments before collapsing suddenly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a one-year autopsy-based study from AIIMS, it was found that more than half of all sudden deaths in this age group were due to heart-related problems, the major killers being CAD along with other cardiovascular conditions. Sudden loss of consciousness was the most common symptom before death, often leaving families in shock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The particular report carries much significance, as it advocates for a better level of awareness regarding heart disease, especially in seemingly healthy persons. The early recognition of subtle and atypical warning signs can save lives. Whereas the classic symptoms of a heart attack, like sharp chest pain, are well-known to all, in many young adults, these atypical warning signs do not appear serious on the face of it. Early detection and timely intervention make all the difference — it saves lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 03:47:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2gJBVV95cUxNS1RRTkdEYkpyQTZNNTJSUmZlc2E4WjhNNjlRQlBBdzNydkdHcDhBZElBT2xMcko5V01TenJDcEZUTk1PbG01Z2RYRzNfY1B4WHB4U0ROOFNlcHUzdWdINExfcEpraVF3d2dMaVdXU1ZSTUw1Yjh2eGN3RVNwblZaNFZYRDZ4NTRqRFBDWUxPTWNiVjFjZG9iMTFYUGZOM1hwRXlqdkptSkpzcllyR2w5cjVtTnItN0pOOVNVYXphazcxc3RWMmVBMC1lT0pqRjVIQjJ5MkhTR1JKcnBzV0JMZUl5TDg3eW92LS00VDFQT1dDOEZ2TFRMaXhDYldURHFNYWRrVV9EWUo5dVBsRHBLNlFobGNiNUs1TGk2Q0FVQ1JkLWxURWJMVlFqclpOQW56dS1zNktRSEhESldnSWpDdzY2a01fajBaSG83cEUzLVNQQ24zd05IR3VB0gHiAkFVX3lxTE0zSFFQVWx3TlptMUdWdDdvazh0dHc0N2lxM0JXTXI3V3gxUGJIaENYeFNEZWh4NnE4WmlOd0NfWk14UzVxSG4xODBfaUYycVY4WE5tYkpQdFdNejJJZXN1QnFEek5KM1FpTm5XYWFkOGhhS2VZd0RmbG5ZTTNkRkFmOTh6RzVfei1iMVI4VE1UeURsYXppMnhwN1F5Si0wZzA0WjFHcDM3SEEycGFJU0VCSlQtZ3VfbUVYZFFWcUVHT1BkN1BnbEpXTzE3SXBQeFlmamxOR3F5aFFBNGd2UXREWXBfaVVGM25kQVAyX3RjbmNYcHY0RzE3dHJaNGtoWGtWWG95U1psTDN5SlVQMEkyaXpFUnRNbjlwb0VVbmZFMm8yLVpGWVB1b0FGQ2w0eGpvTlE2RXFGQXdjUHNFYnpXUHpYcFEydk5mQk1GMEpjRmZpWndUakNqdmRRdENIRldDdw</guid></item><item><title>“36小时脂肪燃烧”和冲刺背后的真相-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/the-truth-behind-36-hours-of-fat-burning-and-sprinting/articleshow/125968818.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;High-intensity sprints can increase your metabolism and fat burn for many hours. At one glance, it seems like another one of those overstated fitness promises. However, unlike other viral videos, this one does have some valid backing from science. It is not a question of whether it is true, but of what it is conveying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;No fat is melted by sprinting for a day and a half. What actually happens is much more useful as well as interesting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why is sprinting different than regular cardio&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sprinting is an intensive activity that tests the body to its limits. Within a few seconds, heart rate accelerates, ventilation increases, and major muscle group activation occurs. Such intensive exercises compel the body to work with energy that is metabolized quickly but inefficiently by the body, causing stress that the body tries to correct afterward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;5 morning drinks that melt belly fat and shrink the waist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While jogging or walking is a process of aerobics, sprinting is more anaerobic. Anaerobic systems produce energy quickly. This is what creates a higher energy debt that must be repaid by burning calories after the session is over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding the 36 hour effect&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;After such strenuous physical activity, it does not return to its normal state easily. Instead, it remains engaged in efforts to restore oxygen levels, repair muscle tissues, remove metabolic wastes, as well as rebalance hormone levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This phase is called Excess Post Exercise Oxygen Consumption or EPOC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies that were printed in the likes of the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12567725/#:~:text=Excess%20post%2Dexercise%20oxygen%20consumption%20(EPOC)%20is%20significantly,the%20volume%20of%20muscle%20recruitment%20%5B%207%5D." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Journal of Applied Physiology and Sports Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; have found that intense exercises can increase resting energy levels for as long as 24 to 36 hours. This is dependent upon the intensity of the exercises, total efforts, fitness levels, and recovery conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;During this phase, metabolic rates are higher than usual even at rest. Both fat, carbohydrates, and proteins work collectively for energy release. This is where the term “fat burning for 36 hours” originates from, despite being a bit too simplistic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the science actually suggests&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research comparing sprint intervals to moderate aerobic activities demonstrates a more significant metabolic response after the exercise for sprinting. In one study in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC1995688/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;European Journal of Applied Physiology,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;it was found that shorter bursts of sprinting triggered a more substantial afterburn effect than longer endurance exercises despite shorter total exercise times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A body of research also identifies enhanced insulin sensitivity with sprint training. Improved insulin regulation translates to the body becoming more adept at dealing with glucose levels, reducing the possibility of fat accumulation from excess calories. This, in turn, leads to positive body composition without necessarily engaging in weight loss or gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is also the role of hormonal responses. In sprinting, there is the elevation of adrenaline levels as well as noradrenaline, which is attributed to the breakdown of fat. These hormones continue to be high even after training, contributing to the additional burning of calories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What this does not mean for fat loss&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A degree of realism is in order here. One sprint session will never produce enough fat loss for you to actually see it. This is true even with the extra calorie burn that occurs during recovery. This is important to understand about fat loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sprinting is more effective as it is incorporated into a balanced regimen that includes proper eating, weight training, and resting. If any of these factors are missing, no amount of vigorous exercise is effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who should be careful when sprinting&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sprinting is a demanding activity for the joints, tendons, and nervous system. It is not advisable for either beginners or injured persons to immediately engage in maximal-effort sprinting, as this could enhance the risk of injury. Research suggests that gradual progression is advisable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A number of people would potentially get the same metabolic benefits through modified intervals or intensive cycling.Sprinting can stimulate metabolism for as long as 36 hours by placing additional recovery demands on the body. This is an indirect way of fat loss that does not occur instantly. Science explains the process, not the magic. When sprinting is utilized effectively, it is a great productivity tool. When it is pitched as a fix for one event, it totally misses the point. That still requires repetition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 01:52:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2gFBVV95cUxNVGphSFNrVGRHTzZrZU5RTHVGazNZNjVrRmV1cUVFNmJKNk9TTG1hR2hqN3JKSUEzaHlTSFZQMWxCYkJUeHM5LUFVR21Uc2VmQy1CQ2k4a0FIWThkUHVYTFdnQlFpZmU5TGtDSkIwUFZ3MllTcXAycGkxcW9hcHhpNDJvMkRCZ1RyQ01nb0hhdU5QN0VYcGdrZ2ZxS3JhbGdvOEdwaWprRE5zWDQzMXNPNWxBalVNYkZnZVVGZGhSVjdTbW9JU0xWNnhBcXdQdmM3VXBHNjdyc25CQQ</guid></item><item><title>专家解释如何为英国“超级流感”浪潮做好准备- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/expert-explains-how-to-prepare-for-wave-of-uk-super-flu</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The NHS is facing severe pressure this winter as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt; cases surge earlier than usual, with some calling it "super flu".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here's what you need to know about this year's flu season and how to protect yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is 'super flu'?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Professor Meghana Pandit, NHS national medical director, &lt;a href="https://www.england.nhs.uk/2025/12/nhs-facing-worst-case-scenario-december-amid-super-flu-surge/"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;: "With record demand for A&amp;amp;E and ambulances and an impending resident doctors strike, this unprecedented wave of super flu is leaving the NHS facing a worst-case scenario for this time of year."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/worlds-first-death-from-h5n5-bird-flu-strain-reported-in-us"&gt;World's First Death From H5N5 Bird Flu Strain Reported in US&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although this term has now been repeated frequently in the media, it was not intended as a new scientific designation. Although the flu season began early, both the spread of the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;virus&lt;/a&gt; and the severity of illness remain within what experts consider normal for a flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-influenza" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="103478" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Influenza&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/virus" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73053" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;viruses&lt;/a&gt; are constantly evolving to evade our immune system, which is why the flu vaccine must be updated regularly. Some years the virus mutates more than others, and it typically undergoes a major change every &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/15218094/"&gt;four to five years&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The "subtype" of flu that is dominant this year, called influenza A/H3N2, has been around since &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7144439/"&gt;1968&lt;/a&gt;, and there have been over a dozen such changes in that time. By this definition, we see "super flu" every few years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is the situation in the UK really as bad as some headlines suggest?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The situation isn't unprecedented – it falls within the range of what scientists would expect in a bad flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_185494" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185494" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/person_with_flu_642.jpg" alt="person with the flu on a couch " class="wp-image-185494 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/person_with_flu_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/person_with_flu_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-185494" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The winter flu season in the UK might be bad, but it's not unprecedented. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADerLg27AE/"&gt;tommaso79/Getty Images Pro/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the season started early, it is misleading to directly compare the number of cases and hospitalisations to the same week in previous years. In fact, the situation is comparable to previous years after taking the early season start into account, as a &lt;a href="https://zenodo.org/records/17704679"&gt;recent analysis&lt;/a&gt; my colleagues and I conducted shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Which areas of the UK are worst affected?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most important consideration from a public health perspective is the burden on healthcare systems in different regions, which is determined by what the virus is doing and what resources are available in those regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The available data only provides general infection trends at regional levels. England's influenza season started &lt;a href="https://scotland.shinyapps.io/phs-respiratory-covid-19/"&gt;earlier than in Scotland&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://phw.nhs.wales/topics/immunisation-and-vaccines/fluvaccine/weekly-influenza-and-acute-respiratory-infection-report/"&gt;Wales&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.publichealth.hscni.net/services-and-teams/public-health-services/health-protection/surveillance-data/respiratory-0"&gt;Northern Ireland&lt;/a&gt;, so we might expect the situation to turn earlier in England than elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on the &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/statistics/national-flu-and-covid-19-surveillance-reports-2025-to-2026-season"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; for England from the UK Health Security Agency, the north and the Midlands are possibly experiencing higher flu rates – but not significantly so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why are we seeing more flu cases in younger people?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children and teens are more likely to get infected due to their high contact rates in schools, where a lot of spread happens, and also because their immune systems are less experienced at dealing with flu viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adults are less likely to become infected overall, as they typically have lower contact rates and their immune systems have &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.3002864"&gt;more experience with influenza&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, people over 64 are more likely to have existing health conditions that put them at higher risk of severe illness if they do become infected, and their immune systems have started to weaken in a process called &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8023351/"&gt;immunosenescence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Babies are also at greater risk of severe illness &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26702035/"&gt;as their immune systems are still undeveloped&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People of a similar age tend to have been infected with &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/article?id=10.1371/journal.ppat.1010317"&gt;similar flu viruses&lt;/a&gt;, which might explain why certain age groups are more affected by flu than others in some seasons. It might be that the virus this year happens to have found an immunity gap in children that isn't present in other age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Vaccine effectiveness is lower for older people, so should they still get the jab?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest data shows that the flu vaccine reduces the risk of being hospitalised with flu by about &lt;a href="https://www.eurosurveillance.org/content/10.2807/1560-7917.ES.2025.30.46.2500854#html_fulltext"&gt;30 to 40%&lt;/a&gt; in older people. That's lower than vaccines against some other viruses, but similar to previous years for flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_185492" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185492" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/feeling_syringe_vaccine_642.jpg" alt="person with blue gloves filling a hypodermic syringe from a vial" class="wp-image-185492 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/feeling_syringe_vaccine_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/feeling_syringe_vaccine_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-185492" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Flu vaccines reduce the risk of being hospitalised with flu by around 40% in older people. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGjcLdyAm0/"&gt;lovelyday12/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recommendations this year are therefore unchanged: vaccination is still the best thing you can do to protect yourself and help reduce the burden on the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why does the vaccine have different effectiveness in different age groups?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This season's vaccines are offering &lt;a href="https://ukhsa.blog.gov.uk/2025/11/11/how-well-will-i-be-protected-from-flu-this-year-with-the-current-uk-influenza-vaccines/#:%7E:text=The%20UK%20Health%20Security%20Agency%20(UKHSA)%20monitors,flu%20*%20Epidemiological%20studies%20of%20vaccine%20effectiveness"&gt;effective protection&lt;/a&gt; against severe flu. Children are around 70 to 75% less likely to attend or be admitted to hospital with flu if vaccinated, and, as mentioned above, adults are around 30 to 40% less likely to attend or be admitted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children are offered a nasal spray, whereas adults are given an injection. Studies have shown that the nasal spray vaccine works better in children and less well in adults, which is why the recommendations are different. So one reason for the difference is that we are comparing estimates from different vaccines as well as different age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another reason is differences in existing immunity. Adults have already been exposed to many flu viruses over their lives, so the incremental gain of one extra vaccine is probably smaller – but still beneficial – than for a child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What should I do if I think I've caught it: call 111, stay home, or go to A&amp;amp;E?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay home if you are sick, rest, and take sensible precautions to avoid spreading the virus to others. Getting influenza is very unpleasant, but everyone will get it roughly &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.3002864"&gt;once every five years&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the vast majority of cases, people get better on their own. But you should still follow the &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/flu/"&gt;NHS guidelines&lt;/a&gt; regarding seeking treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Are there test kits (lateral flow) I can buy at the pharmacy, as there were for COVID?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, very similar tests exist for the flu, and you can buy these at pharmacies and online. Although it's interesting to know if it's influenza or some other virus that is making you sick, if you have flu symptoms, the advice is the same regardless of which virus caused it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is it too late to get the vaccine – given that it takes two weeks for the vaccine to properly kick in?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;No, it's not too late, and the sooner the better! Even after the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pandemic" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73047" data-postid="185473" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;epidemic&lt;/a&gt; has peaked, it will take a few months before cases reach low levels again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is still a risk of infection in that time, so any extra protection from the vaccine is still helpful.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/271959/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/james-hay-2545553"&gt;James Hay&lt;/a&gt;, Research Fellow, Infectious Diseases Modelling, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-oxford-1260"&gt;University of Oxford&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/what-is-super-flu-and-other-questions-answered-271959"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 01:11:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPTklUMUxuanBWZzgtUDlXUGs4SHdiSzZQQlFIZVROX3FERlBzcGFlZmUyQ1ZlQWFTMFZZSzB2dHd5VlNaMl96eVBpVzJGZVItaEZwV2ZtTE42N0Z5YlJNWVV1RW9CY0VHMjBRV0o4UXcwYkJXNlpDMEFqUkhHeUhaVDg2bVEtdS1UcEhtVQ</guid></item><item><title>小RFK对疫苗的疯狂战争使儿童处于危险之中-纽约邮报</title><link>https://nypost.com/2025/12/14/opinion/rfk-jr-s-dangerous-war-on-vaccines-puts-kids-at-risk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. is still chipping away at one of the biggest public-health wins of the last century: the widespread use of disease-eradicating vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;On Dec. 5, his &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/06/10/us-news/rfk-jr-ousts-every-member-of-cdc-vaccine-advisory-committee/"&gt;handpicked Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices&lt;/a&gt; tossed the recommendation for universal hepatitis B vaccines for infants at birth, instead advising it only for babies whose mothers tested positive for the disease — and recommending that babies who don’t get the jab at birth don’t receive it earlier than two months.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But . . . why?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The hep B vaccine has a stellar safety record, and relying on testing is a bad plan; it’s usually done in the first trimester or during birth, but can go wrong in plenty of ways — like moms being exposed post-test, or not getting tested at all.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Universal at-birth vaccination is a low-risk,&lt;em&gt; very &lt;/em&gt;effective strategy for preventing a disease that has a 90% chance of becoming a chronic, liver-damaging, possibly deadly illness for babies who get infected. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry: Who wants &lt;em&gt;more&lt;/em&gt; kids with hep B? &lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;There’s &lt;em&gt;zero &lt;/em&gt;reason for the ACIP to change recommendations,&lt;em&gt; except&lt;/em&gt; to further RFK’s obsessive agenda to reduce the number of vaccines for tots — based&lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/08/07/opinion/rfk-jr-s-anti-vaccine-fixation-is-a-menace-to-public-health/"&gt; on his feverish belief that the jabs are dangerous.&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The White House is, at the very least, giving him a long leash to carry out his anti-vax campaign. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The same day as the ACIP’s hepatitis B decision, President Donald Trump signed a memo directing a review of the vaccine schedules of “peer, developed countries,” noting that places like Denmark, Germany and Japan recommend fewer early childhood vaccines than the United States.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But that’s because Japan, Germany and Denmark are smaller countries with entirely different health-care systems and disease risks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;By the way, the rate of chickenpox in Denmark — frequently praised by anti-vaxxers for its sparse vaccine schedule — is sky-high compared to the United States.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s all part and parcel of RFK Jr.’s dangerous and &lt;em&gt;plain dumb &lt;/em&gt;war on vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Earlier this month, the CDC &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/11/21/us-news/rfk-jr-says-he-ordered-cdc-language-change-on-vaccines-autism-not-supported-by-science/"&gt;updated its vaccine safety section&lt;/a&gt; to read that: “The claim ‘vaccines do not cause autism’ is not an evidence-based claim because studies have not ruled out the possibility that infant vaccines cause autism” — when in fact the claim that vaccines &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; cause autism &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2010/02/03/vaccine-autistic-link-kod/"&gt;has been thoroughly shredded.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;div class="single__inline-module inline-module inline-module--newsletter aligncenter inline-module--nypostbusinessunit aligncenter wp-block-nypost-editor-newsletter" data-source-unit="Inline Newsletter Module Post Opinion"&gt;
	&lt;div class="inline-module__inner"&gt;
		&lt;div class="inline-module__title-wrapper"&gt;
							
			
							&lt;div class="inline-module__unsubmitted-title-wrapper"&gt;
											&lt;h3 class="inline-module__title headline headline--combo-sm-md"&gt;
							Get opinions and commentary from our columnists						&lt;/h3&gt;
					
											&lt;p class="inline-module__cta"&gt;
							Subscribe to our daily Post Opinion newsletter!						&lt;/p&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
			
							&lt;p class="inline-module__success-title-wrapper"&gt;
					&lt;h3 class="inline-module__title headline headline--combo-sm-md"&gt;
						Thanks for signing up!					&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;

		

	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And on Dec. 10, the FDA announced that it’s “rigorously reviewing” the safety of the RSV vaccine for infants, despite a complete lack of reported safety issues — and the fact that the virus is consistently the leading cause of hospitalization for infants.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Objective, evidence-based safety checks are a good thing, but&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;public-health agencies under &lt;em&gt;this&lt;/em&gt; secretary have been anything but objective when it comes to vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Terrifying young parents by suggesting, based on debunked nonsense, that vaxxing their kids could ruin their health forever when the opposite is true isn’t just mind-bogglingly irresponsible, it’s downright &lt;em&gt;cruel.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And that is exactly what the public-health bureaucracy under RFK Jr. is doing every time it casts doubt on vaccines that are &lt;em&gt;proven&lt;/em&gt; safe.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The ugly truth: The only end result will be more sick and dead kids. &lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 01:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPa0RMV0pSMW9qNmZlb3RIb2JZSVRjQ3FuS3dvRFpmck92NGxoU0Q3Vll1eHEyR1dnaWI5STNNYktralVqWVFxaXR0Qy1PcDBPdW12ZE9UbWRxOWE2bnRzMnh0YjMzblpqUWZnbkxmaV96dUVzbXB0azZ4cVg2ZjV0cTBrcjRjN1FJdHpsSEt6STk3aGREMkE</guid></item><item><title>我们的大脑仍然可以使用一个巧妙的技巧来超越人工智能- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/our-brains-can-still-outsmart-ai-using-one-clever-trick</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Despite the rapid advances in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence"&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt; in recent years, the humble human brain still has the edge over computers in its ability to transfer skills and learn across tasks. A new study reveals how we likely do this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Led by a team from Princeton University, the researchers behind the new study didn't actually run tests on humans, but instead used animals that are very close to us in terms of biology and brain function: rhesus macaques &lt;span&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rhesus_macaque"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;Macaca mulatta&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These monkeys were asked to identify shapes and colors on a screen, and to look in particular directions to give their answers. While this was happening, brain scans were used to check for overlapping patterns and shared areas of activity in the animals' brains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/computers-made-from-human-brain-tissue-are-coming-are-we-prepared"&gt;Computers Made From Human Brain Tissue Are Coming. Are We Prepared?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those scans showed the monkey brains using different blocks of neurons – 'cognitive Legos', in the words of the researchers – across tasks. Existing blocks can be repurposed and recombined across new tasks, showing a neural flexibility that even the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/does-using-artificial-intelligence-ruin-your-actual-intelligence-scientists-investigated"&gt;best AI models&lt;/a&gt; can't compete with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"State-of-the-art AI models can reach human, or even super-human, performance on individual tasks," &lt;a href="https://pni.princeton.edu/news/2025/cognitive-legos"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Tim Buschman, from Princeton University. "But they struggle to learn and perform many different tasks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We found that the brain is flexible because it can reuse components of cognition in many different tasks. By snapping together these 'cognitive Legos', the brain is able to build new tasks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you can see in the video below, the animals had to discriminate between shapes and colors in three separate but related tasks that required the animals to continually learn and apply what they knew from one task to the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cognitive Lego blocks the researchers identified were concentrated in the brain's &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prefrontal_cortex"&gt;prefrontal cortex&lt;/a&gt;. The region is linked to higher cognition – solving problems, planning, making decisions – and seems to play an important role in cognitive flexibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found that when certain cognitive blocks weren't needed, activity in them was reduced, suggesting the brain can file away the neural Legos that it doesn't immediately need to better focus on the task at hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think about a cognitive block like a function in a computer program," &lt;a href="https://pni.princeton.edu/news/2025/cognitive-legos"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Buschman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"One set of neurons might discriminate color, and its output can be mapped onto another function that drives an action. That organization allows the brain to perform a task by sequentially performing each component of that task."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It explains how monkeys and possibly humans can &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-brain-has-a-hidden-rhythm-and-it-may-reveal-how-smart-you-are"&gt;adapt to challenges&lt;/a&gt; and tasks they haven't seen before, and use &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-critical-boom-in-technology-traced-back-more-than-half-a-million-years"&gt;existing knowledge&lt;/a&gt; to tackle them – something that  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73092" data-postid="185062" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt; in its current form struggles with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further down the line, the researchers suggest their findings could help train AIs to be more adaptable to new tasks. Their work could also be useful in developing treatments for neurological and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/several-psychiatric-disorders-share-the-same-root-cause-study-reveals"&gt;psychiatric disorders&lt;/a&gt; where people struggle to apply skills to new settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, these cognitive Legos show, on a fundamental level, how our brains are more flexible and adaptable than AI models, which exhibit so-called &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.1611835114"&gt;catastrophic forgetting&lt;/a&gt;: a weakness that means neural networks can't learn consecutive tasks without forgetting how to perform the last one they trained on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/heres-why-multitasking-gets-trickier-and-even-dangerous-as-we-age"&gt;task-switching&lt;/a&gt; isn't exactly great &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-multitasking-drains-your-energy-reserves-and-what-you-can-do-about-it"&gt;for our brains,&lt;/a&gt; applying what we know from one task to another can be a useful shortcut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If, as suggested by our results, the brain can reuse representations and computations across tasks, then this could allow one to rapidly adapt to changes in the environment, either by learning the appropriate task representation through reward feedback or by recalling it from long-term memory," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09805-2"&gt;conclude&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09805-2"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 00:02:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPWFNBLWJ3VzNKaW9oY0xGS3Bpc1Vrc0prY1ZINWgzM3p6T3BOR0kxVUg1bGhWNnhBNUJ6SWF0VGMwRzFHQ055bnNTQTRWQjRqSnNyNHBDa2JsRFEtM3UtU3djNTNweEJNWGhrQ1FLZjZFRVdDajlocDRtOWx2dHd0WXB6OVRfRDlaQmRsZw</guid></item><item><title>随着研究发现“地球上最致命的动物”可能正在崛起，专家们发出警告： “我们刚刚被活活吃掉了” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/experts-sound-alarm-studies-deadliest-223000612.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While warmer months offer plenty of fun activities like beach trips, hikes, and sitting on your porch, they also bring pesky mosquitoes. According to &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/06/24/1266983858/weather-climate-mosquito-repellent-worse#" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:NPR;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;NPR&lt;/a&gt;, the warmer, wetter weather is helping mosquitoes thrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;East Middlesex Mosquito Control Project entomologist Doug Bidlack said that the warmer weather is causing a shift in mosquito populations. Other entomologists noted that higher temperatures could alter their behaviors, their habitat, and "even change how pathogens incubate and spread inside their bodies," per NPR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The changing weather is linked to rising temperatures caused by planet-warming gases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Locals in Massachusetts are noticing the shift in behavior. Abigail Krich-Starr, who lives in eastern Massachusetts, told NPR, "Just being in our backyard each year, in recent years, has become harder and harder."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She added, "Last year … we were just getting eaten alive out there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is changing mosquito behavior concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Mosquitoes aren't just pesky insects that annoy you and make you itch. They also carry diseases, such as "malaria, dengue, West Nile virus, chikungunya, yellow fever, and Zika," according to the &lt;a href="https://www.worldmosquitoprogram.org/en/learn/mosquito-borne-diseases" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:World Mosquito Program;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;World Mosquito Program&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It's no surprise NPR reported that mosquitoes are the "deadliest animal on the planet."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2024, a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/climate-environment/interactive/2024/mosquito-season-state-change-global-warming/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Washington Post;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Washington Post&lt;/a&gt; analysis showed that the average number of mosquito days — days with an average humidity of at least 42 percent combined with temperatures between 50 and 95 degrees Fahrenheit — is lengthening by multiple days, weeks, or even longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In Wilmington, North Carolina, mosquito days have increased by 11 days since 1979.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, mosquitoes are breeding and creating hybrid species. According to Utah State University researchers, southern house mosquitoes have migrated north and are breeding with northern house mosquitoes. Both of these species carry West Nile Virus, and the new hybrid mosquito is better at spreading it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about mosquitoes changing their behaviors?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Director of Public Health for Sudbury, Mass, Vivian Zeng, has some tips for keeping yourself safe during &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/explore-critical-climate-issues/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:mosquito season;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;mosquito season&lt;/a&gt;. She suggested checking whether your area has a mosquito surveillance program, which can help you monitor the risk level in your neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you plan to be outside between dusk and dawn, consider rescheduling, as this is when mosquitoes are most active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, you can limit exposure by wearing long sleeves and pants. Lastly, "Use an EPA-approved DEET repellent, and/or a permethrin spray for clothing and outdoor gear," per NPR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Get TCD's &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/newsletter/?utm_source=rec4B2UGWtfAcJXJd" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletters;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletters&lt;/a&gt; for easy tips to save more, waste less, and make smarter choices — and earn up to $5,000 toward clean upgrades in TCD's exclusive &lt;a href="https://links.thecooldown.com/rewards-club" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Rewards Club;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Rewards Club&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxNYnRWTTRQUjAzVHVneW1BQThlbzZ3U0RrYVprZ19MQkN1Vkk2X1loWWp5RXZ3aXJ1N0ZpQUdHaW5UMlFLUFdlR01tamw2Q2xfVnF1b0lic1JwOGtob1hYd2dNejJNZzljLUpHelhqU044RDJSUmhPNmRHdVg3UnVRU1hYd3NMNWFSaC1zY25tSzNpQQ</guid></item><item><title>这位RFK Jr.的疫苗顾问对他的批评者有一些选择-Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/14/vaccine-adviser-retsef-levi-acip-rfk-kennedy-00688979</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOMGJYVDBwc01LUWwxMjk0REcxZXlQRUFpanZrRHZnRHdEbnR3M19rTTBsY1lLLVhRLW5jbnRMaFpwZlk5WEdGUVZMMWtHQXNFLWdZR3k3ZWpTT3VETWFORVh0V0VVQWpFZ2laOW1CQ0ZTbWk4SEVsMHFwV243UEdCa3phZUdVWVJ2YUhfNXNvQWlfWWQxdk42Tm93</guid></item><item><title>首次使用3D打印的人类角膜移植，实验室培养的组织在数百万盲人的“游戏规则改变者”中恢复视力-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/first-human-cornea-transplant-using-3d-printed-lab-grown-tissue-restores-sight-in-a-game-changer-for-millions-who-are-blind/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_226802" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-226802" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-226802" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash.jpg 1400w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-326x182.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-1024x571.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-768x428.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-696x388.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-1068x595.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-754x420.jpg 754w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/Eyeball-cornea-image-by-Maria-Maximova_ZSdYDQoNY4-unsplash-530x295.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-226802" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;File photo – credit: Maria Maximova&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first successful human implant of a 3D-printed cornea made from human eye cells cultured in a laboratory has restored a patient’s sight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The North Carolina-based company that developed the cornea described the procedure as a ‘world first’—and a major milestone toward its goal of alleviating the lack of available donor tissue and long wait-times for people seeking transplants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Precise Bio, its robotic bio-fabrication approach could potentially turn a single donated cornea into hundreds of lab-grown grafts, at a time when there’s currently only one available for an estimated 70 patients who need one to see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This achievement marks a turning point for regenerative ophthalmology—a moment of real hope for millions living with corneal blindness,” Aryeh Batt, Precise Bio’s co-founder and CEO, &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/medtech/precise-bio-completes-first-human-cornea-transplant-using-3d-printed-lab-grown-tissue" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said in a statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“For the first time, a corneal implant manufactured entirely in the lab from cultured human corneal cells, rather than direct donor tissue, has been successfully implanted in a patient.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company said the transplant was performed Oct. 29 in one eye of a patient who was considered legally blind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This is a game changer. We’ve witnessed a cornea created in the lab, from living human cells, bring sight back to a human being,” said Dr. Michael Mimouni, director of the cornea unit at Rambam Medical Center in Israel, who performed the procedure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;JUST WOW&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Tooth Is Implanted in 34-year-old’s Eye to Restore His Vision After Two Decades" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/tooth-is-implanted-in-34-year-olds-eye-to-restore-his-vision-after-two-decades/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Tooth Is Implanted in 34-year-old’s Eye to Restore His Vision After Two Decades&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was an unforgettable moment—a glimpse into a future where no one will have to live in darkness because of a shortage of donor tissue.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dubbed PB-001, the implant is designed to match the optical clarity, transparency and bio-mechanical properties of a native cornea. Previously tested in animal models, the company said its graft is capable of integrating with a patient’s own tissue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outer layer of the eye—covering the iris and pupil—can end up clouding a person’s vision following injuries, infections, scarring and other conditions. PB-001 is currently being tested in a single-arm phase 1 trial in Israel, which aims to enroll between 10 and 15 participants with excess fluid buildups in the cornea due to dysfunction within its inner cell layers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Precise Bio said it plans to announce top-line results from the study in the second half of 2026, tracking six-month efficacy outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGHT RESTORED WITH STEM CELLS&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Sight Restored to People Blinded in Eye Accidents Using New Stem Cell Treatment" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/sight-restored-to-people-blinded-in-eye-accidents-using-new-stem-cell-treatment/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Sight Restored to People Blinded in Eye Accidents Using New Stem Cell Treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The corneas are designed to be compatible with current surgery hardware and workflows. Shipped under long-term cryopreservation, it is delivered preloaded on standard delivery devices and unrolls during implantation to form a natural corneal shape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“PB-001 has the potential to offer a new, standardized solution to one of ophthalmology’s most urgent needs—reliable, safe, and effective corneal replacement,” said Anthony Atala, M.D., co-founder of Precise Bio and director of the Wake Forest Institute for Regenerative Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;STAR POWER&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Kate Winslet Makes Dreams Come True for Girl Losing Her Sight–Bringing Her to the Theater and Funding a Safari" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/kate-winslet-makes-dreams-come-true-for-girl-losing-her-sight-bringing-her-to-the-theater/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Kate Winslet Makes Dreams Come True for Girl Losing Her Sight–Bringing Her to the Theater and Funding a Safari&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The ability to produce patient-ready tissue on demand could lead the way towards reshaping transplant medicine as we know it.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;(Edited from &lt;a href="https://www.fiercebiotech.com/medtech/precise-bio-completes-first-human-cornea-transplant-using-3d-printed-lab-grown-tissue" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt; by Conor Hale)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 18:00:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7AFBVV95cUxNSUg3Qld5d0RRRklLV1kxWmd3M2MzYnVUZG9ValpNQ3BNQWp5Sm1IeVUzdGJpWWpIdWhIY2JwMVhYTHVjaTFDN3lqME9fNFZxNVVWQnNZcDVaNTQ0TDl0eTNnNnFvZDBTUEZLYlkyMnBaRk94SHNhRDlVR2NrZVRlamR4VFNSYmlZRjBWcGc1ZklfZXVtMlBrRmladFhPS0JQSVhrVlZzQTVjQmdmOTRGVXdMYTZuTlRUWkxZMFh6Zk1tQ0pxUUtSOXpvaENFRXlvYnBqVFBvbHNPcG9jbEprMkFCQm1Db2pVT2h2dQ</guid></item><item><title>防热禽流感变异可能助长下一次大流行- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/fever-proof-bird-flu-variant-could-fuel-the-next-pandemic/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:27:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOX2RuOXl0OUVBTEQ0OTNyTVZEYnBWczlMNHlBVWJacmt5Y0UxZ0dqS0JsaFN0ZnBqZC1tZ2lvUVRxclFBMnRQaWptNjFNcW1FN0daelU0QjhfQWttNG5FSW1jTkJnc1lwdmM5b0dLdWpSWkFLUndqbHJDMVVTZGIyUk9wZEZXX1o1c2VV</guid></item><item><title>我丈夫在未经我允许的情况下向我释放了他的幻想。我不知道我们的婚姻能否幸存下来。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/sex-husband-bed-advice-bathroom-fight.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4iu6hd005pyum21bx5p45j@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhbih001v3b786hv4re0b@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do it,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="103" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3y001y3b78pxeqfuzt@published"&gt;My husband recently surprised me with something unexpected when we were in bed. We had just finished having sex when he stood up and gave me a golden shower. I was shocked and disgusted and fled the room. After I had washed off, I angrily demanded to know why the hell he would do such a thing. He said he had been fantasizing about it for more than a year and needed to “get it out of his system.” I’m not sure if I can trust him again and we haven’t had sex or slept in the same room since. Is it worth trying to save my marriage?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3z001z3b78t4ttc906@published"&gt;—Pissed Off&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3z00203b78t4uw0fs2@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Pissed Off,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="111" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs3z00213b78tumkn8xt@published"&gt;It’s worth doing what you’re doing now—refusing sex and sleeping in separate rooms—while you sort out your feelings. Sometimes, it’s unfair to judge people based on their worst behavior; at other times, the worst behavior is so scarring that it ends up defining the relationship for us, like it or not. Now is the time to take stock. Is the relationship otherwise loving, with open communication and a strong sense of equality/both partners’ needs being met? Or was this a leak from a torrent of domineering behavior that disregards your ability to consent in favor of his comfort/pleasure? That is, is this plausibly a one-time thing, or part of a pattern?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="237" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jhs4100223b78wvgjqh7i@published"&gt;His peeing on you without discussing it with you first was not OK. Though there are plenty of piss enthusiasts out there, many people are disgusted by the notion for good reasons: Most of us are taught from an early age that such waste is dirty and should be avoided at all costs. As with any kink or fetish, though, regardless of the cultural associations around it, it should have been discussed ahead of time and you should have been given the opportunity to voice your disinterest. You had no reason to expect that your husband would do this, especially because you were still in bed. Those who are into piss tend to arrange for such play to be carried out in a manner that is easy to clean after—they may love it, but they typically don’t want to live in the smell of it. This may involve doing it in the shower/bathtub or putting special sheets on the bed that contain the liquid without absorbing it. There was an overall lack of consideration on your husband’s part by not discussing his interest with you ahead of time and by then &lt;em&gt;pissing in the bed you sleep in&lt;/em&gt;. It’s “out of his system,” fine—just make sure that’s true and make clear that these kinds of surprises are not welcome. If you have a hard time moving forward, you may want to enlist the help of a counselor.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jhx7s00243b78jryngibu@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmj4ji4e900263b78l6izgfzo@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jibbn00293b78wxw6ghli@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jierp002b3b783453xkof@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="145" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs8002e3b78c5wh6h76@published"&gt;I am pretty happy in my marriage of over 30 years. My question is how to deal with the fact that my husband loves to have sex early in the morning and before we go to sleep. I wouldn’t mind but, our sex is hindered by the fact that it’s hard for my husband to maintain an erection. If he takes a pill, it will get hard but he says it gives him headaches. I hate to say this, but without the pill, his penis is either half hard or gives out in the middle of us making love—so I am very seldom satisfied. Afterward, he just goes to sleep. He thinks it’s great. I don’t want to hurt his feelings. It’s funny because I used to be the one with a low sex drive, but now I want more sex! How can I make this better?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002f3b78q8sgo572@published"&gt;—Somebody Tell Me What to Say&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002g3b78si2t2fgk@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Somebody Tell Me What to Say,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="114" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002h3b78fd08yj98@published"&gt;Definitely prioritize not hurting your husband’s feelings. This does not mean letting him off the hook for not being a thoroughly considerate partner, but you want to communicate so that he can hear you. I think first, you must determine what it is that you want. You are “dealing” with your husband’s penchant for early morning and late night sex. What would be better for you? Figure it out and ask for it. You’ve been doing it his way as a matter of default—that has bought you leverage. “I think it would be really hot if we …” is a positive way to frame this as a potentially pleasurable experience for both of you.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="127" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivs9002i3b787n3ychj7@published"&gt;Other people’s erections are, uh, hard to manage. He’s talked about getting a headache from pills before, so maybe that’s your way in. I don’t know how extensively he’s sampled the different PDE5 inhibitors on the market, but sometimes people tolerate them differently. So if sildenafil (Viagra) gave him a headache, he may want to try tadalafil (Cialis) and/or vardenafil (Levitra) to see if he has better results. He could also try a cock ring. This is a delicate topic and you should handle it as sensitively as possible. It is fair for you to want a more reliable dick, but in attempting to achieve that, don’t insult him. You might ask him if he’s satisfied with his erection quality. If he’s not, there’s an in, too.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jivsa002j3b78yvb1qf7z@published"&gt;Say he has no designs to do anything about the erections that underwhelm you. Are there other means of getting off that would suit you? If so, request them: oral, manual, toys, etc. You have every right to ask him to help you orgasm before he turns over and falls asleep. You can say something like, “I’m happy that you find our sex so satisfying—can you help me get off, too?” And then tell him how you want him to do that. Be specific.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jizb4002l3b78t0u6t4yc@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmj4jj5le002n3b7874c91s3q@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Us Your Questions About the Workplace!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="36" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jjgqg002q3b78r8o3cucc@published"&gt;The columnists behind our advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmj4jjkks002t3b782uirr9pd@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jjobl002w3b78qu4voslp@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="43" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g300303b78bcyxmonb@published"&gt;I am a newly married gay man, and I thought my husband and I were going to be spending Christmas with my sister and her family. Except, she just added a condition that has me wondering whether to speak to her ever again.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g300313b78foq8tbk1@published"&gt;She and her husband have a son who just turned 3, and she said that she wants my husband and me to sleep in separate bedrooms while we stay over. Her claim is that he’s “too young to understand” why we would be sharing a room. My brother and his wife have stayed over at their place before, and when I asked him, he said they have never been faced with this sort of request (luckily he’s on my side). I have a suspicion that my sister’s husband is behind this, as he’s very Catholic.  This feels like a slap in the face to put it mildly. Is it worth reconsidering our relationship?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400323b785fpqtwnf@published"&gt;—I Thought I Had a Supportive Sister&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="8" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400333b78nh9uv866@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear I Thought I Had a Supportive Sister,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="222" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400343b78svsjulg9@published"&gt;Your sister’s condition is rude and discriminatory. I think it is also based on a fallacy. Her son is not too young to understand why you’d be sleeping in the same room. If he notices at all, which is unlikely as he is 3 and still exists mostly in his own head, all his parents would have to say to him is that his uncle is staying in the same room as another man because they are married. Unless a huge deal is made about something like this, kids tend to roll with the punches. Some uncles marry women, others marry men, still others marry people who don’t fit neatly into either category. Some never get married. Easy. If for some reason, this isn’t easy, there are several picture books made for kids that explain LGBTQ+ identities—&lt;a href="https://www.readbrightly.com/30-great-lgbtq-books-kids/"&gt;here’s a big list of them&lt;/a&gt;. Gay people are a part of the world this kid lives in, and shielding it from him is an exercise in futility. In fact, your presence in his life and household gives his parents the opportunity to explain that some people are gay, which may be different than what he is used to, but makes you no less worthy of familial bonds and love. That your sister and her husband seem to want to bury this truth is very disappointing.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400353b78f90gejd5@published"&gt;I don’t know if this is worth completely burning a bridge, though. There’s a middle ground to explore where you refuse discriminatory boarding terms but keep your sister in your life. It seems like this is the first time you’ve come up against something so overtly steeped in homophobia from this family member—you haven’t yet pushed back nor seen her reaction to the pushback. I don’t think you should tolerate sustained bigotry, but I also know that sisters are hard to come by and it’s worth finding a solution to keep family members in your life. It’s not always possible, but you should at least try.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="103" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk5g400363b78q3b4h2eq@published"&gt;I would tell her that you and your husband will not be sleeping in separate rooms, nor should you have to change your way of life for the sake of a 3-year-old. (Incidentally, I have no time for people who talk about how queerness risks confusing children. To be a child is to be in a state of perpetual confusion, and as detailed above, this one’s particularly easy to clear up.) But you could get a hotel/Airbnb nearby so that you can spend time with your family during the holidays. This way you don’t have to compromise your marriage &lt;em&gt;or&lt;/em&gt; your holiday plans.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4jk8g400393b78xm7r1qlp@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmj4j7mih001n3b786vzo892s@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmj4j7ukn001r3b78q1f4mlo8@published"&gt;Growing up, I was really into kink. When I met my late husband, it was a big part of my life, and he and I were heavily involved in our local BDSM scene. When he died in 2019, I felt like that part of my life died with me. I’ve gotten back into sex and dating, and I’ve mostly been having vanilla sex. It’s … not satisfying. I find myself missing kink, but it’s also caught up in missing my husband. My friends think I’m just mourning and confused, but I’m not so sure. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/12/new-sex-interests-friends-grief-advice.html"&gt;Is there a way to get back into kink after what I’ve been through?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmj4iu6hd005syum2ar5pu42m@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQbnJJUm9lRHhwZ3FCQ1JqSjZxZ3pnbFJJckZidmhCSTg0UDRlVDhTYkI1QTZLbWFMWkJZVi1ZUlZtVkt0ZjI4Q2t1UTlMeXIwUDVjSUpFS3hxcGdINWo3OFp6UzJwcVRwNndkeDNwVFNkcUV0Y1BVTmp2NDd2S1B0MQ</guid></item></channel></rss>