<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>人们正在分享卑鄙的健康威胁，这些威胁实际上正在摧毁你的身体- buzzfeed.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTFBUbFgzUlZCaDVNRU81RFVOMjU3STR3Ny1hdTFBRTdjZXpnRnlCeVowR3RhYzlmTWM1WWowQVdhQmJ6czhVcnl1NEZ0SlpKQlNxQWN0dlpvdld6R2R1UXVNSGFyNkNCNF9XV2hBdmNoNWprT2dJV1hvSnI1cUtTS00?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-14
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="cleaning" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="138917702" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;12.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/heart-health/how-does-sleep-apnea-affect-the-heart" target="_blank"&gt;Sleep Apnea&lt;/a&gt;. People think it's just snoring and annoying, but it's WAY worse."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;"When you're asleep and have obstructed breathing, your body panics a little bit, releasing a bit of adrenaline into your bloodstream to wake you up enough to breathe. With Apnea, this can happen hundreds of times a night. Adrenaline is not good for you 300 times a night. It's great if you get surprised by a wild animal and need to run away or climb a tree, but otherwise, no good for you at all. It debilitates almost every major organ and metabolic system in your body. Long-term repeated exposure can really mess you up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you even THINK you might have a problem, get it checked out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;–&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1l51rha/comment/mwe4b3y/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;amp;utm_term=1&amp;amp;utm_content=share_button" target="_blank"&gt;u/JetScreamerBaby&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>buzzfeed.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:31:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFBUbFgzUlZCaDVNRU81RFVOMjU3STR3Ny1hdTFBRTdjZXpnRnlCeVowR3RhYzlmTWM1WWowQVdhQmJ6czhVcnl1NEZ0SlpKQlNxQWN0dlpvdld6R2R1UXVNSGFyNkNCNF9XV2hBdmNoNWprT2dJV1hvSnI1cUtTS00</guid></item><item><title>一名青少年足球运动员在脑震荡后出现了数月的症状。医生发现了一种罕见的脑部畸形。- CBS新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxNRHFjWXNlWHhBRkZGUFVneWMxVWp1b3k3UWIwYUdjT1BjQS1xc1RsZHJOUEhwXzdZQm9ET0tYaGtzdXNtajBKR1ZmaUdXa2MySTg1WFBQckF4MV9VY3RwR19TMXF2S3d0ckROWXUzTURVdTdtZWZMQnc1Z3pkbEFuOHBaNWhGeDFvVlpzcVhYY1lSUdIBlwFBVV95cUxPaTZ4ZWU3MlNjZVRqbW1YZUMwNTJRVW45V1JYd0tXMkhZTHVHUF9QT1ZSY3kxeTJzZjIxV3RIWkhvX1BFc1V6OVJWY2FnVXJhYW1rdWFEN0FFM2dMamQwT2FySnRUQmZGMXEwTEx5dEFiNHRlOHpFUmNtbVVTSXhoXzBWNXBqNndaV2xRZ0RsMVp0Zm1HRTFz?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Logan Coleridge was used to taking hits in football. He'd been playing since he was 6 years old and had sustained several &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/football-new-helmets-reduce-concussions-cte/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;concussions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. But after a helmet-to-helmet impact during his freshman year of high school in August 2023, he started having debilitating symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New Jersey teen said he was very dizzy and had trouble balancing. His memory was "terrible," and he had a "severe" light sensitivity, he said, along with "terrible headaches." Previously a strong student, he now struggled to focus in the classroom and couldn't remember school assignments or what he read in class. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I've got concussions in my past, and it wasn't like a normal one," Logan said. "I knew it was something else." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/9ab1c183-c863-4fef-b720-26be765fafa7/thumbnail/620x728/c69a1b07e8923ab60919a3028363a07e/logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg#" alt="logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/9ab1c183-c863-4fef-b720-26be765fafa7/thumbnail/620x728/c69a1b07e8923ab60919a3028363a07e/logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/9ab1c183-c863-4fef-b720-26be765fafa7/thumbnail/1240x1456/e8bda2ae9f78307dc2d63b942d957ef0/logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Logan Coleridge (#9) on the field.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More alarmingly, Logan wasn't getting better. Several months of physical therapy had no effect, said Becky Coleridge, Logan's mom. A neurologist who had been treating Logan since his diagnosis with abdominal migraines the year before prescribed two medications, both of which had negative side effects. An orthopedic doctor suggested looking at his neck. Other practitioners had no answers. Coleridge wanted doctors to prescribe an MRI, but wasn't able to get one. Meanwhile, Logan was missing school almost every week. Over-the-counter medications couldn't dull the headaches, and they were becoming more frequent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In early spring 2024, Logan was able to see a concussion specialist after a particularly bad headache kept him from going to school. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The first thing he said was 'Nobody's given this kid an MRI?'" Becky Coleridge remembered. The specialist prescribed the scan, as well as an X-ray of Logan's neck. The Coleridges thought the scans might show Logan had an issue with his occipital nerve, which runs from the neck to the scalp. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results were much harder to hear: Logan was diagnosed with an arteriovenous malformation, or AVM. It was a condition that he and his parents had never heard of before. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everything we read was very scary," Becky Coleridge said. "At that moment, we realized the danger he had been in." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/67a3229a-84a5-4eaa-b0ee-548828a778c3/thumbnail/620x710/4903f4fb42fea400e6e3336bab6777bd/img-8052.jpg#" alt="img-8052.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/67a3229a-84a5-4eaa-b0ee-548828a778c3/thumbnail/620x710/4903f4fb42fea400e6e3336bab6777bd/img-8052.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/67a3229a-84a5-4eaa-b0ee-548828a778c3/thumbnail/1240x1420/109ba89cc57b1d6ef0bc305857629a82/img-8052.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;The Coleridge family. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What is an arteriovenous malformation? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;An AVM is an abnormal tangle of blood vessels in the brain, said Dr. Andrew Russman, head of the Cleveland Clinic's stroke program, who was not involved in Logan's care. AVMs put "a lot of pressure on the vein side" and can produce a variety of symptoms, he said. The biggest risk with an AVM is rupture, where the vessels burst and cause bleeding in the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a case like Logan's, where the AVM hasn't ruptured, there can still be symptoms. Those symptoms can affect a person's motor skills, sensory and visual perception, language abilities and the way they walk, Russman said. The effects can vary depending on where in the brain the AVM has formed, Russman said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc3" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Coleridges had two options to treat Logan: Radiation therapy, a non-invasive technique that uses focused radiation beams to target and slowly destroy the AVM, or surgery. Radiation therapy could take too long, the family decided, and so they decided to have Logan treated by Dr. Howard Riina, a cerebrovascular neurosurgeon at NYU Langone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/2484440c-a91b-4cd3-8b65-e7bad875203c/thumbnail/620x629/05b2f3ec7decbc75791a5259d415896b/logan-coleridge-avm.jpg#" alt="logan-coleridge-avm.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/2484440c-a91b-4cd3-8b65-e7bad875203c/thumbnail/620x629/05b2f3ec7decbc75791a5259d415896b/logan-coleridge-avm.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/2484440c-a91b-4cd3-8b65-e7bad875203c/thumbnail/1240x1258/c5f2db71a5fca39862dd28f04a104bf4/logan-coleridge-avm.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Logan Coleridge's AVM.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge / NYU Langone

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"He couldn't go to school. His whole life was impacted by these headaches," Riina said. "They wanted an immediate solution." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Riina said the AVM, which was on a "headache spot" in the occipital region of the brain, was likely the root of Logan's symptoms. People are born with AVMs, Riina said, and they grow as the body grows, which can cause increased symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Obviously, you don't want to have multiple things going on in your head, but the concussion is what led to the imaging, which led to the diagnosis of the AVM, which was probably what was causing the headaches all along," he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Raising awareness and "focusing on a new beginning" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Logan underwent surgery on July 17, 2024, nearly a year after his symptoms began. Riina performed a craniotomy and removed the AVM. Three days later, Logan was discharged from the hospital to continue his recovery at home. Logan said it was a "lonely" way to spend his summer vacation. Even as his recovery progressed, he couldn't participate in the sports he loved. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I couldn't really do the things that I love normally doing, like exercising, playing football was a big thing for me. I was just stuck in bed, pretty much having minimal activity," Logan said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/d487edeb-98dc-4ba1-86b0-b75d840396b9/thumbnail/620x725/255c0ebc497ada6dad8cc71e6fd24dfe/logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg#" alt="logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/d487edeb-98dc-4ba1-86b0-b75d840396b9/thumbnail/620x725/255c0ebc497ada6dad8cc71e6fd24dfe/logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/d487edeb-98dc-4ba1-86b0-b75d840396b9/thumbnail/1240x1450/f2a657243d12b0d1734c29b52bfd03c5/logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Logan Coleridge recovering at NYU Langone after surgery.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, Logan has only the occasional headache, and the pain can be treated with medication. He has follow-ups at NYU Langone, but Riina said everything has come back clear. The Coleridges are working to encourage early testing: Becky Coleridge said she wishes Logan had received an MRI earlier so that months of suffering and confusion could have been avoided. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc4" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year has been a complete turnaround, Logan said. He no longer misses school. He celebrated his 16th birthday and took driving lessons. This summer, he spent almost every day at the beach with friends. This month, he's gearing up for a return to the football field. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The whole experience was a fork in the road for me that I had to get through," Logan said. "I'm leaving that time in my life in the past and focusing on a new beginning." &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
                  
    

    


    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxNRHFjWXNlWHhBRkZGUFVneWMxVWp1b3k3UWIwYUdjT1BjQS1xc1RsZHJOUEhwXzdZQm9ET0tYaGtzdXNtajBKR1ZmaUdXa2MySTg1WFBQckF4MV9VY3RwR19TMXF2S3d0ckROWXUzTURVdTdtZWZMQnc1Z3pkbEFuOHBaNWhGeDFvVlpzcVhYY1lSUdIBlwFBVV95cUxPaTZ4ZWU3MlNjZVRqbW1YZUMwNTJRVW45V1JYd0tXMkhZTHVHUF9QT1ZSY3kxeTJzZjIxV3RIWkhvX1BFc1V6OVJWY2FnVXJhYW1rdWFEN0FFM2dMamQwT2FySnRUQmZGMXEwTEx5dEFiNHRlOHpFUmNtbVVTSXhoXzBWNXBqNndaV2xRZ0RsMVp0Zm1HRTFz</guid></item><item><title>家长建议：我找到了爸爸的Reddit账号。我希望我从来没有读过它。- Slate Magazine</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxQZWZLamJjbE9FREFqNkhENERNWVN2N2ZxQ1hodVc0Nk9vZXdpamRPVHppR0tnbG5mZlgybGM0czNwOFpHdXBrRUY3em8tS0Y0bXYyWmwxRTlKVGU5SnpORHg5YmJsWS14LUNJRGxwOEMwUEgtZ2hJbnY4WENHUDVLcE53?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="16" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bjb14000owtm74fbsl4zx@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bm709003m3b79i92iz2jh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bky1v00123b79nm86xv6o@published"&gt;I’m a 15-year-old girl, the older of two siblings. I was using the family computer and wanted to check my Reddit, and that’s when I found out that Dad has a Reddit account too. I didn’t snoop then, but I did write down his account name and then checked it out on my phone later.&lt;br&gt;I shouldn’t have done that. I should have realized it was private because he had never mentioned it.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="107" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bl3t000183b79ajj2ip3a@published"&gt;A lot of his posts were heavy. They consisted of complaints about his life, how he resents his family, and then feels guilty about feeling so resentful. How he can’t stand Mom anymore but thinks it’s important to put up a good front for us kids, and how he wishes just once his kids would come to him with something other than a problem we expected him to solve. He said some nasty things specifically about me, too, about some personal incidents I don’t want to share here, but that I had shrugged off as just normal interactions—I hadn’t realized how much I had hurt his feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bl661001e3b796kznxyt2@published"&gt;I feel like I’d know the answer to the question of what to do about this (NOTHING) if that was all there was to it. It wasn’t meant for my eyes, I know. But the thing is, there’s also this undercurrent about how terrible he feels for having these thoughts and feelings and how he needs to “stay strong” for his family. It makes me really uneasy and worried about him. I had no idea he was going through any of this. I feel like I pried open his diary! I don’t know what to do now. Should I just pretend I saw nothing? Or should I tell him?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bl8xi001k3b79pfgcfptz@published"&gt;—Really Stepped Into It&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blets001y3b79wm4s995v@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Stepped,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="123" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blgn000253b79eunxdanu@published"&gt;Is there an adult you feel close to, who knows and loves your father—but who is not your mother—with whom you could talk this over? It’s really beyond the scope of what a 15-year-old should be doing for a parent for you to take responsibility for your father’s mental health—and to carry the burden of guilt you now feel for having “snooped.” Of course, if your dad put all of this on Reddit—&lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; your whole family shares one computer—he had to know, at some level, that someone (if not everyone) in the family would read it. At the very least, he was making his confessions in a public space: Reddit is not a diary, as much as it may sometimes feel like one.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="150" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bliva002c3b79igstsakc@published"&gt;I don’t know why people reveal their most private thoughts to strangers on the internet (this may be a generational blind spot of mine; I am acquainted with a number of 40-somethings who seem to share &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt;, no matter how private, on Facebook), but I do know that writing about (what sounds like) one’s depression on a shared computer is a not-so-subtle cry for help from those who have access to it. &lt;em&gt;You&lt;/em&gt; are not the right person to help him, but his best friend or a sibling of his might be. (And for all you know, he is just using Reddit to blow off steam. Some of those 40-somethings I mentioned definitely use Facebook that way. I read their posts and become alarmed—then learn that they’re just fine, really; they were just having “a dramatic moment.” Again, I’ll acknowledge that this mystifies me. But it is apparently a thing.)&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="46" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blld9002j3b791t2xtql2@published"&gt;In the meantime, can you make every effort to be kind to your dad? You might even approach him with something other than a problem for him to solve. It won’t fix him—as I say, it’s not for you to fix him—but it certainly couldn’t hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bln64002q3b79y13rv8i5@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Michelle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cme3blzse003c3b79919stloi@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blx8800343b79f8wj2q12@published"&gt;Up until two weeks ago, my husband “Jeff” (39) was a model family man and father to “Jenny” (8) and “Kyle” (6). About the only problem in our marriage was his insomnia, and while it was difficult to deal with him getting up 5-6 times a night, every night, it was hardly his fault. Still, after over a decade of trying to treat the insomnia with nothing working except for drugs that had side effects worse than the insomnia itself, we eventually decided on adding a bedroom annex to the home office, and Jeff sleeping there instead of with me. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2022/11/insomnia-sleep-apart-marriage.html"&gt;Ever since then, he’s been half-assing as a father.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cme3bjb14000rwtm7zk2fct1u@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;The latest sex, parenting, and money advice from our columnists delivered to your inbox three times a week.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate Magazine</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQZWZLamJjbE9FREFqNkhENERNWVN2N2ZxQ1hodVc0Nk9vZXdpamRPVHppR0tnbG5mZlgybGM0czNwOFpHdXBrRUY3em8tS0Y0bXYyWmwxRTlKVGU5SnpORHg5YmJsWS14LUNJRGxwOEMwUEgtZ2hJbnY4WENHUDVLcE53</guid></item><item><title>幼儿父母需要了解的高度传染性夏季疾病- NJ.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxQSEhxbWZDb2JOZDZSdUlPd0l2NTFmSGJ6dlRZb29Rb1hnYUd3RFJJaG1hRmVqcWVMZWVnXzJMWlFMczFOT3N1QjZlWF93azdaWWZfcnUteGRuN3haTWNHZE9jWExfWHdxTWJoY2txdnNUTnVEM2FqZnF3VEJjUFVnNy1peVJzQkJXMWswNUlWLVJlSzdjOENNRUhxQjM3ZVJLNG81alNMV0pNMDNpWlZvSzc1SjdrVEJNY2tB0gHPAUFVX3lxTE5iWTNKbDFpeEJHdmlrbkh0b3ZLVk9rWk04MVQzZlRCb0lBaWNabDZJalktYldFRlRtRUFMa1RVUmNQYjMyMGZzNFZyNkdlR2xHMzJJODYzZ3BJYVBKM2R0N29UZl9HeEZ0bGxfbkpZdTItWG1rSWlzY1Q3VUJZUlg5Yml6OTcyV1ZFbkJkS2lKWi11aEtFZDNJelFPYVpvTUU0OFMtaExTWldfMU9NYUNIQlFCQUdDNmh6aVB0Z2gzQUxlSXBGbGpjUlZqTlU4RQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QBWJUST3PZE47JS5IMH6MECN7Y"&gt;When summer comes around, you can count on a few things. A Bruce Springsteen spotting at the Jersey Shore. Energy bills &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/news/2025/08/my-energy-bill-is-insane-how-recent-price-hikes-temperature-spikes-are-hurting-nj-residents.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.nj.com/news/2025/08/my-energy-bill-is-insane-how-recent-price-hikes-temperature-spikes-are-hurting-nj-residents.html"&gt;going up&lt;/a&gt;. And lots of kids getting sick with hand, foot, and mouth disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="33TJ5RE26FAVTPMTT4VG5IEUWA"&gt;Doctors are currently seeing a surge in cases of the disease, which is more common in the summer and early fall, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DEZ5H7U4DRCODERPIZSWSC74JY"&gt;“Everyone feels like they know somebody who has it, one way or the other,” said Katharine Clouser, a pediatrician at Hackensack University Medical Center who also serves as president of the New Jersey Chapter of the American Academy of Pediatrics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5KOJ7KXXXRC3DMDZFRGFDTKIPM"&gt;The United States doesn’t currently track individual cases of the disease, so it’s hard to get an exact case count. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="P4J7UQ44KFEGTM7V2CFYLLELR4"&gt;But in a statement sent to NJ Advance Media, a spokeswoman for the New Jersey Department of Health said, “Compared to recent years, for reasons that are not clear, we have seen an increase in the number of HFMD outbreaks from May to July of this year.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NQCRYSTF6JGXPERU24P4GHYJXE"&gt;As of Aug. 1, 127 outbreaks of hand, foot and mouth disease have been reported statewide, according to data provided by the state health department. That’s more than quadruple the number of outbreaks reported during the same time period last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RZX77Y3H3BFCXBIL2UUTCGLSQA"&gt;Hand, foot and mouth disease is caused by viruses that belong to the enterovirus family, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6VNT6EFOCBG57IIOT7TUJS5QTY"&gt;There are many types of enterovirus, but coxsackievirus is typically the most common cause of hand, foot and mouth disease in the U.S. It mostly causes illness in babies and children under the age of 5, with outbreaks frequently occurring in childcare and preschool settings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AYUGSCY44VB4DLY23ABJS2RLWU"&gt;Most adults have already been exposed to many enteroviruses in their lifetime and so they have built up immunity. But, that doesn’t mean it’s impossible for adults to get sick. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="V4OI2HLMABGEJKSUOTT52F7YFI"&gt;“Anyone of any age really can be infected by hand, foot and mouth disease,” said Clouser. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2OJFYE4Y7RHNFG6WWH3RCJRHXA"&gt;If someone is exposed to the highly contagious illness, symptoms usually develop within three to five days. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WPJQH2PIL5ACNPZMADCEAXBM4M"&gt;Symptoms include fever, sore throat, painful mouth sores that blister, and a skin rash commonly found on the hands and feet. The rash may also appear on the knees, elbows, buttocks or genital areas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="77N52566ANCIFLSDU2ULD4HFM4"&gt;Most kids have mild symptoms and get better on their own in seven to 10 days. However, in rare cases the illness can cause serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N5BG24OG4FDLFOAUKXZXIV6OZI"&gt;“Any virus can be serious,” said Clouser. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6PEVJKWJDZCCFGJO5RTS6QGRRU"&gt;If a parent starts to notice that their kid is refusing liquids, going to the bathroom less, and sleeping more, Clouser said “that would be a reason to seek medical attention.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NGOOUSWFGZCWDO6VEBEK7ZNADE"&gt;Hand, foot and mouth disease is highly contagious and spreads three main ways:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="RDEMGQ4P7ZFPFGBF7OJEAAIOPQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;By touching an infected person or making other close contact, like kissing, hugging, or sharing cups or eating utensils.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="3LVABWDQCNATFFEL5ASRALHO54"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Through touching objects and surfaces with the virus on them, like doorknobs or toys, then touching your eyes, nose, or mouth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="3LSWUWTRLJEYVKHM3RQMXSQF5A"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Through respiratory droplets after a sick person coughs, sneezes, or talks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WOU3GKAZ45HJRM7MX4BAT7WKTI"&gt;Although rare, people can also get the virus by swallowing recreational water, like in swimming pools. This can happen if the water is not properly treated with chlorine, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WITA4PJ2PVA3HHPF4HHEWX3JDE"&gt;A sick person is most contagious during the first week of illness and should stay away from others during this time. This means keeping kids out of childcare and school until the fever is gone and mouth sores have healed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D3UIEYOCPJDSRLDFHRINPK35CI"&gt;While hand, foot and mouth disease may make people feel self-conscious, Clouser said people shouldn’t feel ashamed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GWEK2J5HW5BKLFQFHAKGHPJXCE"&gt;“It’s nothing to be embarrassed about. It’s just a virus, and the best way to keep them at bay is to talk to your friends. Tell them ‘Jenny’s got hand, foot and mouth. We saw you last weekend, just be on the lookout,’”Clouser said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VGL7FRMOHZA4XF55K4EXFALH44"&gt;“Just make sure you’re being honest with those around you, so we can prevent this spread,” said Clouser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EPU3ZNOVK5EK7JQJRTJYTGCF6A"&gt;There is no vaccine in the U.S. to protect against the viruses that cause hand, foot and mouth disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PTLOTEXLPVHOJAS27FKBYQ6UHM"&gt;The best way to prevent catching or spreading the illness is to practice good hygiene, clean and disinfect surfaces, and avoid close contact with others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:4FKJGX6T6BGFFF6SR5E6PDAZOU" data-fusion-component="4FKJGX6T6BGFFF6SR5E6PDAZOU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:4FKJGX6T6BGFFF6SR5E6PDAZOU" data-fusion-component="4FKJGX6T6BGFFF6SR5E6PDAZOU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JDZB7HTYRRHITMBYYV4PVBBUXA"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Our journalism needs your support. Please subscribe today to&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt; NJ.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZZT64DQ5RVF3NH3A34MCKL2B4U"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/staff/jroman/posts.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;Jackie Roman&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; may be reached at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:jroman@njadvancemedia.com" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;jroman@njadvancemedia.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;. Find &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/NJ.com" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;NJ.com on Facebook&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxQSEhxbWZDb2JOZDZSdUlPd0l2NTFmSGJ6dlRZb29Rb1hnYUd3RFJJaG1hRmVqcWVMZWVnXzJMWlFMczFOT3N1QjZlWF93azdaWWZfcnUteGRuN3haTWNHZE9jWExfWHdxTWJoY2txdnNUTnVEM2FqZnF3VEJjUFVnNy1peVJzQkJXMWswNUlWLVJlSzdjOENNRUhxQjM3ZVJLNG81alNMV0pNMDNpWlZvSzc1SjdrVEJNY2tB0gHPAUFVX3lxTE5iWTNKbDFpeEJHdmlrbkh0b3ZLVk9rWk04MVQzZlRCb0lBaWNabDZJalktYldFRlRtRUFMa1RVUmNQYjMyMGZzNFZyNkdlR2xHMzJJODYzZ3BJYVBKM2R0N29UZl9HeEZ0bGxfbkpZdTItWG1rSWlzY1Q3VUJZUlg5Yml6OTcyV1ZFbkJkS2lKWi11aEtFZDNJelFPYVpvTUU0OFMtaExTWldfMU9NYUNIQlFCQUdDNmh6aVB0Z2gzQUxlSXBGbGpjUlZqTlU4RQ</guid></item><item><title>高蛋白饮食可能导致癌症：你应该吃多少-每日邮报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAJBVV95cUxNcnFYUG54eDU4UWFYNG1rNWFWVUF4Q1ROS2hxcl9CaENOeWhvSC1CUUNIZDRGZ0RxTFI1X29fYzEyZjBaMFEteXRCajNCRV9SdWJVcVR6eXh6N2pUZ2IwbFdDNERuMVozQkRpVWhvX0JrY3NfSDhFMnczU0l1b1l4TTR1YVdEUzdMY19XeUJJaGNqZVlyYWdZd2M4VW5seFpObTVUYTF3cjB4el9qUk1QSEJPbUZkblBkUEYxd3c1RkF4cFZTZGtGYTVkamFxWUNRVS1wZXNIXzU5STIxaURqaTB5M3JYWVlnSEZCampoVzJWX1QxM1JwaWc0enFCT0VXSGptQWhsTDZQM0dlR1lnYmhROFlPTC1t?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A social media trend encouraging women to double their protein intake could be putting them at risk of a range of cancers, one of Britain’s top diet experts has warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Increasing protein levels has been touted as a way to build muscle and protect against mid-life diseases such as osteoporosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In recent years, the number of supermarket products with ‘added protein’ has surged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to market research firm Mintel, the number of food and drink launches claiming to be high-protein nearly doubled between 2016 and 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the same time, social media is awash with influencers advising viewers on how to boost their protein intake – with menopausal women, who are prone to muscle loss, often targeted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But claims that women need to eat significantly more protein during &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/menopause/index.html" id="mol-31f15f30-74ff-11f0-9400-03163cbeacc0"&gt;menopause&lt;/a&gt; are not only misleading, they could be harmful, warns nutritionist Dr Federica Amati. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Going through the menopause puts women at higher risk of developing osteoporosis and makes it harder to gain and maintain muscle mass,’ says Dr Amati, one of the scientists behind the popular diet app ZOE. ‘But simply increasing your protein intake won’t address this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;But claims that women need to eat significantly more protein during menopause are not only misleading, they could be harmful, warns nutritionist Dr Federica Amati&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Research shows that high intakes of animal protein in mid-life are associated with cancer. For most women, eating more and more protein is not the answer to staying healthy after menopause.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;UK guidelines recommend adults consume about 0.75g of protein per kilogram of body weight. For the average 72kg woman, that equates to approximately 54g a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts agree this is relatively easy to meet: a typical 150g chicken breast contains around 36g of protein, an egg about 6g, a 170–200g serving of Greek yogurt up to 20g, and a portion of kidney beans between 7g and 10g.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Yet some influencers recommend as much as 150g a day to ‘help prevent’ bone fractures and muscle decline in later life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In one Instagram post, an American doctor with 1.3 million followers outlines a daily meal plan that includes egg whites, protein shakes, beef sticks and large servings of meat – totalling more than 140g of protein. And in a TikTok clip viewed more than 430,000 times a UK-based influencer boasts of eating 130g of protein daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘As a personal trainer and a woman navigating perimenopause, I base my meals around some form of protein,’ her caption reads. ‘Our bodies don’t process and metabolise protein the same way as they did in our 20s and 30s, so we need to eat more of it.’ She adds: ‘If I reach 150g, I’m really pleased with myself.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;UK guidelines recommend adults consume about 0.75g of protein per kilogram of body weight. For the average 72kg woman, that equates to approximately 54g a day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Dr Amati says this approach is misguided. ‘Our protein needs do change over time – but the highest requirement is during infancy and childhood, not menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘As we age, we produce less growth hormone, so simply eating more protein doesn’t prevent muscle loss. In fact, studies suggest that higher protein intake after the age of 50 can raise the risk of cancer.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2014 study from the University of Southern California involving more than 6,000 adults over 50 found that a high-protein diet – where protein accounted for roughly 20 per cent of total calories – was linked to increased risks of cancer, diabetes and mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Adults with the highest protein intake were four times more likely to die of cancer compared with those on a low-protein diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other research suggests that tumours, including melanoma and breast cancer, may grow faster if a patient is on a high-protein diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This, Dr Amati explains, is due to overstimulation of a key cellular pathway responsible for growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Cancer is the uncontrolled proliferation of cells – so overactivating this pathway increases the risk,’ she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Cancer is the uncontrolledproliferation of cells – so overactivating this pathway increases the risk,’ she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Protein from animal sources carries additional risks, she warns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Up to 80 per cent of the protein we eat in the UK comes from animals. But research from Denmark shows that animal protein is richer in certain amino acids that promote fat cell growth and produce compounds linked to heart disease. These amino acids have also been shown to damage cells and tissues, and are linked to neurodegenerative diseases and cancer.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, cutting back too far is not advised either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Amati says middle-aged women should aim for 1.2g to 1.4g of protein per kg of body weight – more than the NHS guidance, but still easily achievable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She also encourages shifting towards plant-based protein sources, which help boost fibre intake. These include beans, peas, nuts, seeds and oats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:55:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAJBVV95cUxNcnFYUG54eDU4UWFYNG1rNWFWVUF4Q1ROS2hxcl9CaENOeWhvSC1CUUNIZDRGZ0RxTFI1X29fYzEyZjBaMFEteXRCajNCRV9SdWJVcVR6eXh6N2pUZ2IwbFdDNERuMVozQkRpVWhvX0JrY3NfSDhFMnczU0l1b1l4TTR1YVdEUzdMY19XeUJJaGNqZVlyYWdZd2M4VW5seFpObTVUYTF3cjB4el9qUk1QSEJPbUZkblBkUEYxd3c1RkF4cFZTZGtGYTVkamFxWUNRVS1wZXNIXzU5STIxaURqaTB5M3JYWVlnSEZCampoVzJWX1QxM1JwaWc0enFCT0VXSGptQWhsTDZQM0dlR1lnYmhROFlPTC1t</guid></item><item><title>房客专栏|一种疾病袭击了我的整个身体。我的医生告诉我要减肥。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxNalFZT2ZiLU5zaWotckpCVE9HclE2SlZ6bGpNMDZaQXBRTlVGQlY4WEdkaTdDYXY3SXcwUEJRdFBLTWFsUHRoRVNxVXBmODgwZ2xJNVZsSVg2VkxyeUtkMmYway1zdGx6WFhXTXFsakhjUWtwd3JfRnBGN2s0eXhkVU9nNmFzYkNyak5LVEUycUtXZmh2b0xr?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="K2QDRKE2MFBNNM5MCIZXHYZTAU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In 2022, I gained 40 pounds in one year and was tired all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7PPOUFUCFNCK3MTR5QB2AHLD7Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Before these changes, at 47, I biked and walked everywhere in my Los Angeles neighborhood. I wrote articles frequently. And I raised my daughter with ease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AF6L7RQKTNF7ZPDGSNKUPC6RP4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When I told my doctor about my health issues, she sighed, reeled off obesity risks and admonished, “Lose weight. &lt;i&gt;For your daughter&lt;/i&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QXC5UO3DRRD63PI3EI6MFCGCPA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I also met with several other doctors, most of whom blamed stress, weight gain or age for my poor health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CHYJUV3DQRAVDIMDKUZGWFWXWI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;It took three years, thousands of dollars and two inches of height for me to get the right diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3NN657XFNZE5XKV3GZRMT2BO54" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My health journey may read like a medical mystery, but it wasn’t. At least seven doctors saw my abnormal lab results over three years, and only the very last one followed the protocol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="FRQ43IG7A5FXNJTZSADG7YEGSI" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="FRQ43IG7A5FXNJTZSADG7YEGSI" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Weight gain and anemia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RYO44DLXJNFRVM4L5PAREFX4SU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My 2022 labs were flagged for high calcium. But my doctor said everything was “normal” and prescribed metformin, a diabetes drug sometimes used off-label for weight loss. I wasn’t diabetic, just overweight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3NT2K6GEO5AUNMRLPN5LB7AAGM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I took the metformin and logged every calorie, but the weight wouldn’t budge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LT5PVJUY7VGI3E6HTWR7MFZLNE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;By 2023, my periods turned erratic and were so heavy I sometimes changed tampons every hour and thought I was hemorrhaging. But my gynecologist didn’t seem to believe me when I told them how much blood I was losing, saying, “If that were true, you’d be dead.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OHZLQWEFFFELJIENI3ZA47QH4Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;On a trip, breathless, I could not make it up a small hill near the Tower of London and begged my family to slow down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MJTERZLHHBGFZNFXCFRDRM3DSA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In 2024, I found a new primary care doctor, who promised to treat “the whole person.” She, too, urged me to keep losing weight. I started a GLP-1 injection, paying $550 a month out of pocket that insurance wouldn’t cover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LEV6NURXNVA6LK4NHFIKCNXNKQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The weight began to drop, but soon I was breathless again just making my bed or showering. I returned to my doctor, insistent that something was still not right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="5LB3JDMYF5GVREG6LG5BMSIPYI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Fresh labs showed severe anemia from chronic blood loss. After trying iron pills, iron infusions and tranexamic acid to clot the bleeding, I opted for a uterine artery embolization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3MC2ILJNTFDAJC4OETL3XJ45WQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The pain was excruciating. But it worked, the anemia was resolved, and my hematologist wrote in my chart: “Patient says she can’t remember the last time she felt this good.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GUCV6IMEBFEWHOJKSBZ4VGYGRE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But by fall, I had severe hot flashes, night sweats and persistent insomnia. Again, I went for tests. My thyroid was fine, and my hormones did not indicate menopause. My chart notes read: “Weight. Stress.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ODEHS2TNUJEMHDMV3TQHNPCRGA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Desperate, I turned to hormone replacement therapy. It soon calmed the flashes and sweats, but not the insomnia, exhaustion, or the new symptom of extreme thirst. Even with hormones balanced, I lay awake for hours, my nerves frayed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="V3XGFLIVLJECTN3RBREZIPXKGM" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="V3XGFLIVLJECTN3RBREZIPXKGM" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Memory loss and anxiety&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MYS34Y7JVFGK3BYRCESGAGI3JQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;By early 2025, I thought I was losing my mind. I was certainly losing my memory. Names and words escaped me. I lived in a state of buzzing exhaustion that left me unable to work, drive safely or attend my daughter’s school events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CMGTIQRKBBFRHGY3HS7WEBCERA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The weight kept dropping. Now I was lighter, but workouts I’d once conquered were impossible. My bones and joints began to scream with pain. Lying down was all that felt good, and, soon, lying down was all I did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="T4VE7DJYMJEB5OVWGFI4AU663A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I once read four papers a day and suggested story ideas to publications constantly. Now, I could barely scan headlines, much less summon the mental acuity to generate ideas, and when I did manage to write, my brain was so fried that I collapsed afterward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GMYKPSYMYNGJ3BKAJOYG23JYQQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Sleep became torture. I woke up hourly throughout the night. By morning, I was too exhausted to get my daughter to school. My partner took over every aspect of the household.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="J7OHY7U4KRF2BA7Y3XD4XVS3MQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Then, a crawling, physical anxiety began tearing through me at random.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="FALRIOVLCJDK7FT6VO55H7IFOY" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="FALRIOVLCJDK7FT6VO55H7IFOY" data-testid="article-header"&gt;A chance diagnosis based on calcium spikes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WX5JHGMI4FG6JPMY6QI43XHCP4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In April, I saw a new doctor who was covering for my regular one. I’d lost all the weight, but I cried explaining how my body felt hijacked by relentless dread and anxiety. She prescribed a beta blocker for my racing heart and, crucially, drew blood for new tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NDMAFOXZFZACXGMVHOIFQVVVRE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The next day she messaged me: “Your calcium is elevated. We need to check your parathyroid.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="T2IRANRNYZFUBNTSGDY6ARXC5Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I raced to my medical records. My calcium had been steadily climbing since 2022. I could chart each new terrible symptom alongside every spike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AUSUUB2LCNCYNP7UDQ7Q2NVXCQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A follow-up test confirmed my parathyroid hormone (PTH) was elevated. It was textbook biochemical primary hyperparathyroidism (PHPT).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RTKFHE2PLRGQVAGPRUUEQ2MKIY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There are four tiny rice-size glands near your thyroid, called the parathyroid glands. They have one job: to regulate the calcium and phosphorus in your blood. Calcium builds bones and teeth, but it’s also the electrical current powering the heart, muscles and brain and is essential for nerve signaling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FLQQUPQVIBC45DACF6B6U3O7OQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If even one of those glands goes rogue, often because a benign tumor raises the parathyroid hormone, it tricks the body into pulling more calcium from bones, weakening the skeleton, damaging kidneys, disrupting heart function and altering mood. It also comes with a&lt;a href="https://www.hyperparathyroidmd.com/hyperparathyroidism-symptoms/" target="_blank"&gt; host of possible symptoms&lt;/a&gt;: fatigue, insomnia, thirst, memory issues, hair loss — symptoms doctors call “nonspecific” because they &lt;a href="https://www.southwestparathyroid.com/blog/why-your-doctor-doesn-t-recognize-the-symptoms-of-parathyroid-disease#:~:text=In%20addition%20to%20%E2%80%9Cstones%2C%20bones,just%20%E2%80%9Cmild%E2%80%9D%20calcium%20elevations." target="_blank"&gt;overlap with hundreds of other conditions&lt;/a&gt;. Left untreated, PHPT is progressive and even fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="43IMQDA32FFMVNI4ZECNCNYKVQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;PHPT is the third most common endocrine disorder after diabetes and thyroid disease, &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/endocrine-diseases/primary-hyperparathyroidism" target="_blank"&gt;affecting about 100,000 Americans each&lt;/a&gt; year. Historically, PHPT was diagnosed by late-stage symptoms: kidney stones or fractures. Now, routine blood tests catch elevated calcium levels earlier. (Some experts warn that calcium even &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@drmichaelljohnson1/video/7355875607881796910?_r=1&amp;amp;_t=ZT-8y55OxCg31p" target="_blank"&gt;at 10 mg/dL&lt;/a&gt; can signal trouble.) But this means many patients now present with “nonspecific” symptoms, so doctors may ignore mildly elevated calcium and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/a-bad-diagnosis/2015/08/24/b17606c2-12ac-11e5-89f3-61410da94eb1_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;miss the parathyroid connection&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="K4FYDURXTJHE3HFSMS3JDZ3JBE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jbmr/article/37/11/2293/7512381" target="_blank"&gt; standard of care&lt;/a&gt; for elevated calcium is clear: Repeat the calcium test, and check the parathyroid hormone. That protocol is posted on the websites of most major hospitals, including the one where I was a patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7JDSCH2FFZH4PLPCHHBAJEVCXQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Yet one&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6738291/" target="_blank"&gt; study&lt;/a&gt; found half of the patients with high calcium got no further testing, and even when both calcium and PTH were high — the definition of PHPT — 40 percent still went undiagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="T3XBHM56MVHFRIX2CU4ISXDVFM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Delayed diagnosis is costly, because managing PHPT damage&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6561104/#:~:text=Failure%20to%20diagnose%20primary%20hyperparathyroidism,and%20under%2Dreferral%20to%20surgeons." target="_blank"&gt; costs far more&lt;/a&gt; than its &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; cure: a parathyroidectomy to remove the bad gland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="3YK6ZQETIFDQJHCYWUWSSB6H7Y" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="3YK6ZQETIFDQJHCYWUWSSB6H7Y" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Lost inches&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QIIEFBARA5HCNNE7GUIYNDF6NE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;And then, I learned I was shorter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CIBUT2EIP5E5PCKZODXJIABMHU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;At my next follow-up, a nurse measured my height. As I stood up as straight as I could, pain shot through my mid-back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KNJWFOQP5BG73CWMIQ5P3B24BA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“5’9,” she said. “What?!” I blurted. “I’m 5’11.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3Y6FHJY5KZF6DPEXAZBT57NNRA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Maybe you were measured with shoes on before,” she said, shrugging. We lose about a half-inch of height per decade after age 40, yet I’d lost two inches in a year from bone loss from hypercalcemia, or excess calcium, and probably from &lt;a href="http://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/1555067/" target="_blank"&gt;muscle deconditioning&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4NJK5XDCP5EATICLIJHQJBASTU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A bone density scan delivered the final blow: I now had osteopenia. My bones were thinner, more fragile and prone to fracture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="OOJOLVHXNJAAVEZWXQB7YL2H3E" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="OOJOLVHXNJAAVEZWXQB7YL2H3E" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Surgery for primary hyperparathyroidism&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MRPYBWAADZDUXABUQRWX7MUWGA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To cure the condition, I needed a parathyroidectomy and opted for an approach in which the surgeon uses a smaller incision, explores all four glands, removes the bad one and confirms success by checking hormone levels during surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XLAXAXFCHNGVHOOX7YBC2MYRZQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My doctor, &lt;a href="https://larianmd.com/about-dr-larian/" target="_blank"&gt;Babak Larian&lt;/a&gt;, a head and neck surgeon and the clinical chief of the division of otolaryngology at Cedars-Sinai Hospital in Los Angeles, said his cure rate is up to 98 percent with this technique. (It’s important to find a highly skilled surgeon, and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3224988/" target="_blank"&gt;research suggests&lt;/a&gt; the outcomes are better if you use a doctor who performs more than 50 of these procedures each year.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="E5ZGJDJADZH3ZFOBALEVXN3UUY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My PTH dropped to normal within minutes, confirming success. Recovery was mild: some pain, a sore throat, a small scar, and a strict regimen of calcium supplementation until my remaining glands took over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2KFVI43SBFBELP53VVW7BCBRS4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Soon, the world snapped back into focus. I slept deeply within a week, the bone and joint pain vanished. My back still aches from bone loss, but I can walk the block, do laundry and remember things again&lt;del&gt;.&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AG7JELMTJBGOVL3BVOBURJBS2E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My thoughts have cleared enough to read, converse and write this essay. On the Fourth of July, I even made it to the beach and a barbecue. I have a long road of physical therapy ahead, but it feels as if my life has been handed back to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WFQMCKRPIFGLBBP55N2EBJJU5Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I asked my surgeon why no one talks about this condition. “Because it’s not sexy,” he said. “Angelina Jolie would have to get this disease for people to notice. I call it an orphan disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RM3JIORJ6VCYJF337FSX3HQYUA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;And why do so many doctors miss it? It may be training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YEHHOMUUH5AETBUOUPYUSFIBPY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In medical school, students spend only&lt;a href="https://www.endocrinepractice.org/article/S1530-891X(22)00486-4/fulltext" target="_blank"&gt; 20 to 60 hours&lt;/a&gt; on all endocrine diseases, memorizing the mnemonic “stones, bones, groans and moans,” short for kidney stones, bone pain (or fractures), abdominal pain and neurocognitive changes. PHPT is diagnosed by blood tests, so doctors who rely on the mnemonic may overlook biochemical results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MLTDFZJLIJCRXGPSDVKRCECLQ4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Women are&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK441895/" target="_blank"&gt; three to four times as likely&lt;/a&gt; to have PHPT and don’t often present with kidney stones but with brain fog or mood changes, symptoms &lt;a href="https://www.parathyroid.com/blog/top-5-symptoms-of-hyperparathyroidism-in-women#:~:text=And%20since%20we%20know%20women,a%20fog%20that%20lifts%20overnight%E2%80%9D." target="_blank"&gt;easily dismissed&lt;/a&gt; as menopause or issues with mental health. Older patients are often told it’s “&lt;a href="https://www.parathyroid.com/blog/the-top-10-symptoms-of-hyperparathyroidism-presented-with-real-patient-examples" target="_blank"&gt;just aging&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TKMCZHIR7JCW5B5BZITS2VDNJI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The experience has infuriated me. I believe doctors saw my weight gain and age and made assumptions that allowed them to look no further. I chased every symptom but the true cause and may have even had a surgery I did not need because of high calcium’s &lt;a href="https://www.factsaboutfertility.org/endocrine-disorders-and-menstrual-disturbances-a-review/" target="_blank"&gt;impact on my menstrual cycles&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="D3BVDML7LBDEBNG2L2ZKHK26UI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I’m not alone. Parathyroid support forums are&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Parathyroid_Awareness/" target="_blank"&gt; full of people&lt;/a&gt; who’ve suffered longer than I did, dismissed while losing their minds and bodies to “nonspecific symptoms” or told their calcium wasn’t high enough to explain their symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="E47KV6AOW5BWHH4CN5VERQHU6I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;They urge people, and now I do, too: If your calcium is high and your doctor dismisses it, find another doctor. I can’t get back the years — or probably the inches — I lost. But maybe telling my story will help someone else keep theirs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNalFZT2ZiLU5zaWotckpCVE9HclE2SlZ6bGpNMDZaQXBRTlVGQlY4WEdkaTdDYXY3SXcwUEJRdFBLTWFsUHRoRVNxVXBmODgwZ2xJNVZsSVg2VkxyeUtkMmYway1zdGx6WFhXTXFsakhjUWtwd3JfRnBGN2s0eXhkVU9nNmFzYkNyak5LVEUycUtXZmh2b0xr</guid></item><item><title>锂如何从7Up转变为精神疾病的治疗—可能还有阿尔茨海默氏症-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxPeHNYVWl1S1FqRHNxalFMNWR6UEdhaXEyN3FBZldZMU9Tb1QyU3dQc1hGQWN0dDE5UkZ3SGtGVUk2NUFKVk8xWWFZRXJONzVSZ1Rzdnc1WDdFNm9lUEcyMklJN09YTWtvYkZsdC1kNWN2RWpyeEkzcGRUMEt6M3pGX2NVNEJ0WlA2LVUwZ1RWdW80UVlLVWFENnlpalA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="U6NGJRUHAVBD7AURRISXUMGHJU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2025/08/06/lithium-reverses-alzheimers-mice/?utm_campaign=wp_the7&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=newsletter&amp;amp;carta-url=https%3A%2F%2Fs2.washingtonpost.com%2Fcar-ln-tr%2F4406f76%2F689484deaed508115aca0314%2F62d55c2a560643501904a9ea%2F59%2F108%2F689484deaed508115aca0314"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;this week in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-09335-x"&gt;Nature &lt;/a&gt;found that the loss of lithium, a naturally occurring element in the brain, could be an early sign of Alzheimer’s and a powerful driver of the disease, which afflicts more than 7 million Americans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MRDTC4RDRNGOFMSHXQ2FVYCR7Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The study, led by Bruce A. Yankner, a professor of genetics and neurology at Harvard Medical School, found that lithium is important to the health of all  the major types of brain cells in mice. Depletion of lithium in the brain also seems to be a factor in almost all of the major deterioration that occurs with Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KVJK76GBF5FLFCWQ63HV3NO3MA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;While the latest study of lithium is novel in pointing toward a potential Alzheimer’s treatment, the use of lithium to treat other conditions is not. Here’s a look at what it has worked for and how its use is being researched in new ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="list-header-JEQCBXAFSZD6PCNCCSODA6VKV4-3" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;h2 id="JEQCBXAFSZD6PCNCCSODA6VKV4" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="JEQCBXAFSZD6PCNCCSODA6VKV4" data-testid="article-header"&gt;What is lithium?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#secondary-nav" class="skip-link sr-only sr-only-focusable black underline brad-md pa-lg mb-xs border-box font-sans-serif font-bold"&gt;Return to menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="53LQYKE7PVGHJB2CNWEQOJMPCE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lithium, soft and silvery, is nature’s lightest metal, enabling it to store energy at high density and discharge electrons rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DX9T3K8UU52BX7HCGBZE77AE1G" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“This is the basis of the lithium battery that powers our phones, laptops and electric vehicles,” Yankner said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ADRQ47QZUZEQNCKDUTRBI7L4GI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Less well known is that the original formulation of the soft drink 7Up contained lithium; the drink was marketed under the name Bib-Label Lithiated Lemon-Lime Soda. The lithium was removed in 1948 after the &lt;a href="https://www.psychiatrictimes.com/view/lithium-past-present-and-future"&gt;Food and Drug Administration banned&lt;/a&gt; the use of lithium citrate in soft drinks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SEOAI6TYZRALZFB2ML3HCB2WBA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;As of 2024, Australia was the world’s largest producer of lithium, though Bolivia, Chile and Argentina are known as the “lithium triangle.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="list-header-BTFEVA76ABGRFEQ6WXHLXH4HRQ-8" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;h2 id="BTFEVA76ABGRFEQ6WXHLXH4HRQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="BTFEVA76ABGRFEQ6WXHLXH4HRQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;How has lithium been used for mental health treatment?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#secondary-nav" class="skip-link sr-only sr-only-focusable black underline brad-md pa-lg mb-xs border-box font-sans-serif font-bold"&gt;Return to menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MFD37JP5LZBT3JDVJVKVK5JE5A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A form of lithium, lithium carbonate, has been widely prescribed in the treatment of bipolar disease&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;in the United States since it was first approved by the FDA in 1970. It is believed to be a mood stabilizer and can also be prescribed for long-term treatment of depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2LG3XUNAG5FRXOMMI7XCTFDQEA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;While the precise mechanism of lithium carbonate isn’t known, it is believed to suppress stress in the brain and help restore neuroplasticity — the brain’s ability to change and adapt as we get older. One of the findings of the Nature study was that our brains contain a small amount of naturally occurring lithium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2OGLMZASQJGETKUBZJW7MIAYSQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There are cases of lithium being used in psychiatry going back to the mid-19th century, but the study of lithium for mood disorders took a larger step in the late 1940s when an Australian psychiatrist, John Cade, found that it helped many bipolar patients stabilize quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3E4GGKQZ7VHZPFEMHFBXPHSN5I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“It’s been around for decades, and we have a lot of research and a lot of evidence supporting its use,” said Elizabeth Hoge, a professor of psychiatry at Georgetown University School of Medicine. “The most important thing is that it does help patients. We know that it works from randomized, controlled trials.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3IHWR7BSNRGULC5LHI7ZZSJGZI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Hoge said the use of lithium does require &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0140673614618420#:~:text=Lithium%20treatment%20is%20associated%20with,and%20regular%20long%2Dterm%20monitoring."&gt;monitoring&lt;/a&gt; of renal and thyroid function, which can decline in some cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OK4L7M7XIFFVFFDCXXDEFQJTTI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Balwinder Singh, an assistant professor of psychiatry at the Mayo Clinic, said lithium remains the “gold standard” medication for bipolar disorder, though it is under-prescribed in his view. About 10 to 15 percent of Americans with bipolar disorder take lithium, compared with about 35 percent of patients in &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10813799/#:~:text=This%20review%20included%2055%20articles,e.g.%2C%20lower%20suicide%20risk)."&gt;Europe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FLUHDY2D7VFLLBZZRNOUCCVEIU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Lithium is the only mood stabilizer consistently shown to reduce suicidality in individuals with bipolar disorder,” according to a recent comment Singh wrote in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpsy/article/PIIS2215-0366(25)00026-4/abstract"&gt;Lancet Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2TZ5RLIREZCMPM7FZC4UP5KGKI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Although lithium has been widely prescribed and its use is supported in many studies,&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0165032722003962?via%3Dihub"&gt; a 2022 paper&lt;/a&gt; argued that its effect on bipolar depression, a part of bipolar disorder, does not represent a statistically significant improvement over a placebo or antidepressants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="list-header-NBYXGUTOPJFUHLP3ODQVR6UPGE-17" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;h2 id="NBYXGUTOPJFUHLP3ODQVR6UPGE" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="NBYXGUTOPJFUHLP3ODQVR6UPGE" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Why is lithium being researched for Alzheimer’s?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#secondary-nav" class="skip-link sr-only sr-only-focusable black underline brad-md pa-lg mb-xs border-box font-sans-serif font-bold"&gt;Return to menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VSYXBRNOVRGW5MV45UWHXOQXCI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lithium had been investigated previously as a potential Alzheimer’s treatment and antiaging medication. A &lt;a href="https://psychiatryonline.org/doi/10.1176/appi.pn.2017.10a17#:~:text=Sc.%2C%20of%20the%20University%20of,but%20this%20association%20was%20nonlinear."&gt;2017 study&lt;/a&gt; in Denmark found that the presence of lithium in drinking water might be linked to a lower incidence of dementia in the population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="432MJIP32JG2RN7ETSAMCR7JEM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Yankner’s lab became interested in lithium after measuring the levels of 30 different metals in the brain and blood of people who were cognitively healthy, people in a very early stage of dementia and people with full-blown Alzheimer’s disease. Of the 30 metals, only lithium changed significantly among the three groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="76LSB4DJHBFOZFFY3OS3G5MCMM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lithium maintains the connections and communication lines that allow neurons in a healthy brain to talk with one another. The metal also helps form the myelin that coats and insulates the communication lines and helps microglial cells clear cellular debris that can impede brain function. All this adds up to promoting good memory function both in mice and in humans, researchers said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="list-header-NN3IPKIRVNEBTEJI5QSTXDIQUQ-21" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;h2 id="NN3IPKIRVNEBTEJI5QSTXDIQUQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="NN3IPKIRVNEBTEJI5QSTXDIQUQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;How could the research translate to treatment?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#secondary-nav" class="skip-link sr-only sr-only-focusable black underline brad-md pa-lg mb-xs border-box font-sans-serif font-bold"&gt;Return to menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6UGYQESATBEXFIA5RQZZP7LL4A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Yankner’s lab found that small amounts of the compound lithium orotate were able to reverse a mouse model of Alzheimer’s disease and restore brain function. Researchers said the discovery should be enough to spur clinical trials for testing the compound in people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HPEHNDE6WBE4HNE3UIUJNEXRDM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But Yankner said he could not recommend at this point that people start taking lithium because its use for Alzheimer’s has not been validated in people, and “things can change as you go from mice to humans.” Lithium can also be toxic if not regulated properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZA66D7HYGFDKDGQGEWHCC22ZOY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;And because this research is nascent, it’s unlikely that a treatment will be available anytime soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:01:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPeHNYVWl1S1FqRHNxalFMNWR6UEdhaXEyN3FBZldZMU9Tb1QyU3dQc1hGQWN0dDE5UkZ3SGtGVUk2NUFKVk8xWWFZRXJONzVSZ1Rzdnc1WDdFNm9lUEcyMklJN09YTWtvYkZsdC1kNWN2RWpyeEkzcGRUMEt6M3pGX2NVNEJ0WlA2LVUwZ1RWdW80UVlLVWFENnlpalA</guid></item><item><title>它们影响着40%的人口。没有人会认真对待他们。- Slate杂志</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxNcWI0ZVZiN2c3YllkaWN5ZlQyOVgwTzN2QkxXNnpGdGpsakl6Vzh3YmZYQldVa3poSUt0bE5sOXF4ZXR0Rk1yLXBkeUdOMklkOWJFbXdLZ1FPZi1Gd09HVE9YZm01S0hPcmJwLW1kUERiSmt6eEdxOHg0OE1TdmY4c3d2ZkdVQlV1SjNNTVljdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="129" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6f9t0029cym6rvzc9ydo@published"&gt;On one of the most memorable days of my life, I walked into a doctor’s office with an incipient migraine and walked out half an hour later pain-free. It was the early ’90s, and I’d been suffering from the headaches—often accompanied by nausea and vomiting, occasionally somewhat eased by ibuprofen—since the age of 14. I can’t recall why on that day I decided to request an appointment, but I can still see the doctor fumbling with the wrapping of a cartridge encasing a hypodermic needle filled with a new drug. She got migraines, too, she’d told me, so when she placed the cartridge on my arm and pressed the button delivering the shot, we both exhibited the curious anticipation of experimenters, wondering if something miraculous was in the offing.&lt;/p&gt;

  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="105" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6ydo000o357afbb0aip8@published"&gt;It was. Within five minutes, the nagging throb that had bloomed on my right temple a few hours earlier had vanished. That made us both giddy. Whether the new drug, sumatriptan (marketed as Imitrex), also worked for that doctor, I’ll never know. But I was lucky. Over the decades that followed, sumatriptan has reliably tamed the migraines that have intermittently plagued me, rescuing me from countless hours of misery. Whenever anyone complains about Big Pharma or fantasizes about having been born in an earlier era, my ironclad response is that I can’t imagine my life without sumatriptan—or, rather, I can, and the thought is chilling.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="124" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6yfz000p357aoax6hew9@published"&gt;I’m lucky. As the journalist Tom Zeller Jr. recounts in his illuminating new book, &lt;a href="https://bookshop.org/a/2181/9780358507758"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Headache&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, people with migraines or cluster headaches (Zeller’s own affliction) often find that recommended treatments either don’t work or decline in effectiveness over the course of months. Cluster headaches, like migraines, are called “primary headaches,” Zeller explains, “meaning the head pain and accompanying battery of other neurological effects constitute disorders unto themselves, rather than symptoms of some other underlying disease.” Even the fairly common migraine is poorly understood by those who don’t get them. I once worked with a colleague who was convinced I was being careless with my health because I didn’t regard my headaches as symptoms of some grave condition that could, and ought, to be cured.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section data-uri="slate.com/_components/product/instances/cme3a7xxz001z357a8jiai7tt@published" class="product " data-product-name="&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;The Headache: The Science of a Most Confounding Affliction—and a Search for Relief&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;" data-product-price="$27.89"&gt;
    
  &lt;div class="product__info"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="product__description"&gt;
      By Tom Zeller Jr. Mariner Books.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;


  &lt;p class="disclaimer" data-word-count="19" data-uri="slate.com/_components/disclaimer/instances/cme3a7yfk002d357ayere4nev@published"&gt;
    Slate receives a commission when you purchase items using the links on this page.
    Thank you for your support.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="91" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6z8s0010357ajbw46zyr@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Headache&lt;/em&gt; is an account of what we have learned about migraine and cluster headaches (less than you’d think) and the state of research developing treatments. The newest of those treatments are blockers that inhibit the uptake of calcitonin gene-related peptide, CGRP, a “key chemical messenger in the nervous system’s pain communication pathway,” according to Zeller. Researchers knew that CGRP could induce migraines in experimental subjects (all praise the sacrifices of those heroes!), and this new class of drugs binds to the chemical to prevent it from binding to neural receptors.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="134" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zbb0011357a7sdg11tr@published"&gt;Cluster headaches are relatively rare, but migraines are not, and one study calculated the cost to the U.S. economy of migraines alone is as much as $1 trillion. Yet research into the causes and cures for primary headaches has been sluggish, for reasons that are highly contested. While the medical explanations in &lt;em&gt;The Headache&lt;/em&gt; occasionally made my eyes glaze over, Zeller’s accounts of feuds among headache researchers and their combined wrath at what they insist is inadequate National Institutes of Health funding for their work offers a delectable blend of dish and substance. When one scientist likened migraine research to a massive Airbus plane requiring four fully fueled engines to get it off the ground, Zeller asked him what, exactly, was keeping the plane on the tarmac. “Too many female passengers,” was the reply.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="138" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zhk0012357akvwvuqfc@published"&gt;Female migraineurs outnumber their male counterparts by 3 to 1, while the gender breakdown is reversed for cluster headaches. Many headache experts believe that this explains why migraine isn’t taken seriously by the medical establishment, whose tendency to dismiss pain in female patients has been well documented. Zeller observes that cluster headache sufferers, by contrast, tend to hide their condition, something he himself did during an early stint at the New York Times&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;The Headache&lt;/em&gt; includes the story of an air traffic controller who concealed his cluster headaches for three decades, knowing that the condition would trigger an automatic medical disqualification from a job he loved. He resorted to keeping his medications (which did not impair his performance) secret and ducking out of work during an episode to inhale oxygen from a tank he kept in his car.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;figure data-uri="slate.com/_components/image/instances/cme3aqnlr007e357agq500338@published" class="image image--right" data-editable="imageInfo"&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="image__meta"&gt;
&lt;span class="image__caption"&gt;Tom Zeller&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="image__credit"&gt;Kristine Paulsen&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="187" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zjs0013357awcsrulpp@published"&gt;For Zeller’s part, he found it difficult to admit how debilitated he was by a disorder that many people conflate with the discomfort caused by a hangover. Cluster headaches, however, are often ranked among the worst pain a human can experience. While migraineurs tend to retreat to dark quiet rooms to wait out their affliction, people with cluster headaches are restless, often pacing, rocking, and pounding their heads. While cluster headaches don’t last all day like a migraine, they can recur every day or multiple times per day within the window of a period that can last weeks or months, followed by a period of remission. In &lt;em&gt;The Headache, &lt;/em&gt;Zeller relates the story of a young man whose cluster headaches proved so relentless and tormenting that he took his own life, grimly confirming the disorder’s nickname: suicide headaches. Zeller himself recounts a period when, while working on a demanding story, he experienced a cluster attack and resorted to “medicating myself with absurd tides of chemical experimentation and excess,” ranging from caffeine, steroids, and magnesium to a CGRP blocker called verapamil—a drug on which he overdosed, passing out.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="181" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zm60014357aorphcbgz@published"&gt;Though we have different kinds of headaches, there’s much that’s familiar to me in Zeller’s account. I, too, have found it difficult to convey just how disabling a mere headache can be. And I certainly recognized Zeller’s almost superstitious hoarding of medication doses, splitting them to stretch the supply, and the way Zeller would “jealously count those blue injections like a Scrooge, worrying over their limited number, wondering whether they’d last.” These drugs are the treasure we require to placate an angry god. Insurance companies can be stingy with the number of doses they allow per month, so it’s imperative to keep renewing the prescription regularly, even in the absence of headaches, so that you hit any future bad period with an ample supply. The fear of running out is petrifying—although, thankfully, well in the past for me now that sumatriptan has gone generic and can be bought online. The more recently developed CGRP blockers, however, can be brutally expensive. And most primary headache medications only work for half the people who try them, and then often only half the time.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="155" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zom0015357akhjz65q4@published"&gt;Maddeningly, scientists still can’t say what causes primary headaches. Fierce debate rages among them over whether these are disorders of the vascular system—dilated blood vessels pressing against nerves—or of the central nervous system, arising from some dysfunction in the brain. The hypothalamus, which regulates the autonomic nervous system, seems implicated in cluster headaches, with their mysterious link to the body’s circadian rhythms. Migraines vary widely from person to person, but also in the same person during the course of a lifetime. My migraines once were synced to hormonal cycles. Now they only come at night, and especially when it rains or the humidity tops 75 percent. Or when my blood sugar gets too low. Or when I drink wine. I never experienced migraine aura—a disturbance in vision—until about 15 years ago. Now, my eyesight will occasionally be marred by a crescent of shimmering silver triangles (a classic migraine aura), but with no subsequent headache attached.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="119" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zr30016357aowvy3zdh@published"&gt;No wonder headache scientists are stumped, although several of the sources Zeller spoke with also complained that the stigma attached to primary headaches as an “unserious” medical condition has kept gifted researchers away from the field. Former NIH director Story Landis told Zeller that the agency—which has demonstrably underfunded headache research relative to the impact primary headaches have on society—simply didn’t get enough high-quality grant proposals in the area. Landis suggested, Zeller writes, “that headache researchers had been poorly conditioned by industry to focus on pills and shots, rather than foundational science,” such as identifying the cause or causes of the disorders. But if Big Pharma is the only source of funding for headache research, who can blame them?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zti0017357aojan5x70@published"&gt;When an advocate for headache sufferers asked Zeller what he’d learned in all his admirably extensive research for &lt;em&gt;The Headache,&lt;/em&gt; the author found himself stammering and backtracking, qualifying his own suffering as not “the worst of what cluster headaches can inflict on a person,” adding that “there are bigger problems.” Then he pulled up. For millions of people of all races and genders—including Zeller himself!—primary headaches are a literal torment. Though I seldom endure that myself now, I remember all too well what a full-blown migraine was like. “It’s not just a headache” is the answer Zeller finally comes up with, and on that we should all &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;agree.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Culture" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cme3a6f9t002ccym6x2xlwprs@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Get the best of culture&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the best of movies, TV, books, music, and more.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate Magazine</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNcWI0ZVZiN2c3YllkaWN5ZlQyOVgwTzN2QkxXNnpGdGpsakl6Vzh3YmZYQldVa3poSUt0bE5sOXF4ZXR0Rk1yLXBkeUdOMklkOWJFbXdLZ1FPZi1Gd09HVE9YZm01S0hPcmJwLW1kUERiSmt6eEdxOHg0OE1TdmY4c3d2ZkdVQlV1SjNNTVljdw</guid></item><item><title>FDA可能不会续签针对幼儿的辉瑞新冠疫苗-《卫报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxNcWpBQzNxeTJGZU5keV80OTRMODJZb3ViMnI4SEtzcEhpdHhrVHdSR1Q4OF9CYlJLclU2cEt4S1llbHF4UmdOeVlCS3JQeS00UHdSMnI4SkUwbjdPd3dHWXJTT2ZEcVdUSXNjQ3RsSkNkRWE3TU1qWGpjWFNPNzFrQUJmOU1qNVQ1endGaW1R?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Pfizer’s Covid vaccine for young children may not be renewed by the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) this fall, prompting Moderna to fill possible gaps in supply, according to an email obtained by the Guardian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The move would pull the only remaining Covid vaccine for all children under five from the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"us-news","tags":[{"id":"us-news/us-news","type":"Keyword","title":"US news"},{"id":"world/coronavirus-outbreak","type":"Keyword","title":"Coronavirus"},{"id":"business/pfizer","type":"Keyword","title":"Pfizer"},{"id":"us-news/healthcare","type":"Keyword","title":"US healthcare"},{"id":"world/world","type":"Keyword","title":"World news"},{"id":"science/science","type":"Keyword","title":"Science"},{"id":"business/business","type":"Keyword","title":"Business"},{"id":"science/medical-research","type":"Keyword","title":"Medical research"},{"id":"society/vaccines","type":"Keyword","title":"Vaccines and immunisation"},{"id":"society/society","type":"Keyword","title":"Society"},{"id":"business/pharmaceuticals-industry","type":"Keyword","title":"Pharmaceuticals industry"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"profile/melody-schreiber","type":"Contributor","title":"Melody Schreiber"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/us-news","type":"Tracking","title":"US News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"us-news/2025/aug/09/pfizer-covid-vaccine-fda-children-dfa","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Moderna vaccine is only approved for children with one or more health conditions, and the pediatric Covid vaccine from Novavax is only available for children aged 12 and up with health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It certainly would create a hole in the availability of vaccines,” said Georges Benjamin, executive director of the American Public Health Association.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“And to do it this late in the season – I think clearly it’s inappropriate.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;According to an email from the National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases (NCIRD), Pfizer said the FDA recently informed the pharmaceutical company that it may not renew the emergency use authorization for its pediatric Covid vaccine for the 2025 respiratory season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The email was sent on Friday to state and local vaccination grantees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Pfizer vaccine is given to children between the ages of six months and four years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Pfizer expects its Covid vaccine for children aged five to 11 to be fully licensed this fall, the email said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) is “in discussions” with Moderna about rapidly increasing its Covid vaccine supply for young children, according to the email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;That includes internal planning about volume, timing, and potential supply gaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We are working to ensure there will be sufficient supply,” said Chris Ridley, a Moderna spokesperson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The CDC, the US Department for Health and Human Services (HHS), and Pfizer did not respond to media inquiries by publication time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In July, Moderna received FDA approval of its Covid pediatric shot. But the vaccine was only approved for children with one or more health conditions that make them more vulnerable to Covid. This move could limit access to Covid vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We already have a low number of people using the vaccines to start with,” Benjamin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There hasn’t been enough promotion of vaccinations for kids, and then you have Mr [Robert F] Kennedy’s [Jr] unscientific statements about the safety and efficacy of vaccines, particularly Covid vaccines, for both pregnant women and kids. It has muddied the waters of what people know about the safety and efficacy of the vaccine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The vaccine is extremely effective, especially against hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Yet only 5.6% of children aged six months to four years are vaccinated against Covid, and about 15% of children aged five to 17 are vaccinated, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While older adults have the highest rates of hospitalization and death, children continue seeing &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/php/covid-net/index.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;hospitalization rates&lt;/a&gt; from Covid similar to rates in 2020 and 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;And there are other concerns with Covid infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We don’t know the long-term impact for kids who have gotten Covid as a disease. We do know it does cause a multi-systemic inflammatory process in a number of kids, which is very severe, and we don’t know the long-term implications for long Covid in kids,” Benjamin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Covid cases are &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/aug/05/us-covid-cases-rising" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;rising&lt;/a&gt; in many parts of the US amid other vaccine restrictions proposed and implemented by health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNcWpBQzNxeTJGZU5keV80OTRMODJZb3ViMnI4SEtzcEhpdHhrVHdSR1Q4OF9CYlJLclU2cEt4S1llbHF4UmdOeVlCS3JQeS00UHdSMnI4SkUwbjdPd3dHWXJTT2ZEcVdUSXNjQ3RsSkNkRWE3TU1qWGpjWFNPNzFrQUJmOU1qNVQ1endGaW1R</guid></item><item><title>随着“Stratus”变种爆发， COVID-19病例激增- Axios</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxNLUFGMGpBa3p4OGxYWE5Tb2oxTDJvUDZHNm16aUd4d3ZPWDQ5UW1YaHY3eFhsemhZWjhvMWVMZ3hIczB4VlVLb0lGc0ZHc1ZYcEFBeDFGakFDNTBnZzh6V0ZrOEt3VGlSZ09rZXo2T1o4c0Fvd2VGZGptUlcyU1dZWnB3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 05:53:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxNLUFGMGpBa3p4OGxYWE5Tb2oxTDJvUDZHNm16aUd4d3ZPWDQ5UW1YaHY3eFhsemhZWjhvMWVMZ3hIczB4VlVLb0lGc0ZHc1ZYcEFBeDFGakFDNTBnZzh6V0ZrOEt3VGlSZ09rZXo2T1o4c0Fvd2VGZGptUlcyU1dZWnB3</guid></item><item><title>中国在抗击基孔肯雅病毒的斗争中重新开放新冠肺炎工具箱-英国《金融时报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMicEFVX3lxTE9nd3pGam5YdlNLY2xYZFUxaG9JeDY0UkZfWkZsaW9sVjBpaHQzcVNjSVV4dXdHeEhOdllwaUpVU3I4V05fVXoyVDZoZGJKWHBXdzlYaHZmQ2E0Ul9LdWxlUGxhS2pNNnpLR0JfbkpBZzU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Complete digital access to quality analysis and expert insights, complemented with our award-winning Weekend Print edition.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:44:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9nd3pGam5YdlNLY2xYZFUxaG9JeDY0UkZfWkZsaW9sVjBpaHQzcVNjSVV4dXdHeEhOdllwaUpVU3I4V05fVXoyVDZoZGJKWHBXdzlYaHZmQ2E0Ul9LdWxlUGxhS2pNNnpLR0JfbkpBZzU</guid></item><item><title>顶部还是底部？不同的前列腺癌治疗以不同的方式影响男同性恋者- Queerty</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNN0V3UVUzbE1FWnRRa3pTXzM4TjhfaGRvMU01d01rR1hqbDVONEtlc0VMb1pFRU91TzZhbzl3c3pWT0pOXzVyNlNKbXV1eHNUUm92Zmw1XzZ0dFFXbVQ1cl84RXZOMWhhQmRscU53T3JHSm1sejJFTGJDdnBNTk5aRWk2LTgtS1F5ajlyclEtbFNPTmhtbkE4NUZtQmdkSlZ4czYxYnJuWU1CS2NLMkRPM3hoRUtRYUZ0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="cf-column"&gt;
            &lt;h2 data-translate="blocked_why_headline"&gt;Why have I been blocked?&lt;/h2&gt;

            &lt;p data-translate="blocked_why_detail"&gt;This website is using a security service to protect itself from online attacks. The action you just performed triggered the security solution. There are several actions that could trigger this block including submitting a certain word or phrase, a SQL command or malformed data.&lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;

          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Queerty</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNN0V3UVUzbE1FWnRRa3pTXzM4TjhfaGRvMU01d01rR1hqbDVONEtlc0VMb1pFRU91TzZhbzl3c3pWT0pOXzVyNlNKbXV1eHNUUm92Zmw1XzZ0dFFXbVQ1cl84RXZOMWhhQmRscU53T3JHSm1sejJFTGJDdnBNTk5aRWk2LTgtS1F5ajlyclEtbFNPTmhtbkE4NUZtQmdkSlZ4czYxYnJuWU1CS2NLMkRPM3hoRUtRYUZ0</guid></item><item><title>常见的膳食补充剂可以从体内去除“永久化学物质” - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxOMEVieWJCREdRdTRrVXJJamlYSTNfSDFiM2pIc0JwWjNWSXNqU3h4Q01YWEJQTk0tclptalBXRnZUbHhjazhQa2JMOFg5aEM5bGowdFZsTF9XU1FvWm52eDBZNXh6T3FSLXMtc3U5eWVqSlVDeUZDZEcxQXpUNXhqUmpkbnFFR2JfUnlmVTItZHhJS1ItTUcxRFRmbEtRS1dBNmtRemVLa0dYd2k4WGc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;PFAS – often called “forever chemicals” – show up in food, water, and even the air. An analysis by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;) found PFAS in the blood of an estimated 97% of Americans. These chemicals have been linked to cancer, cardiovascular and liver diseases, and immune suppression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PFAS are persistent because most can take years to leave the body, and while they are there, they can do some serious damage to your health because they constantly recirculate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The liver sends PFAS substances &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/gut-bacteria-offer-new-hope-against-forever-chemicals/"&gt;into the intestines&lt;/a&gt;, and transport proteins pull some back into the bloodstream. A similar recapture can occur in the kidneys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-it-can-t-be-that-easy"&gt;It can’t be that easy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After asking what people can do about PFAS, a team tested a simple option using a very common and readily available &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/eating-enough-fiber-prevents-cancer-in-a-surprising-way/"&gt;dietary supplement&lt;/a&gt;: soluble, gel-forming fiber taken with meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two recent pilot studies suggest that regularly consuming such fiber can reduce &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/wqc/aquatic-life-criteria-perfluorooctanoic-acid-pfoa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;PFOA&lt;/a&gt; (perfluorooctanoic acid) and &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/wqc/aquatic-life-criteria-perfluorooctane-sulfonate-pfos" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;PFOS&lt;/a&gt; (perfluorooctane sulfonate) – two of the most studied PFAS in a family of over 15,000 human-made chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work involves Professor Dhimiter Bello, associate dean of research in the &lt;a href="https://www.uml.edu/health-sciences/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Zuckerberg College of Health Sciences&lt;/a&gt; at UML, and Professor of Environmental Health Jennifer Schlezinger at &lt;a href="https://www.bu.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Boston University&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By consuming gel-forming fibers such as psyllium with a meal, we can trap PFAS inside the fiber gel, which can then be removed in feces,” explains Bello, whose lab developed methods for measuring PFAS in human tissues and biological fluids while documenting PFAS exposure sources. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Professor Schlezinger and I have complementary expertise, a shared common interest and the same drive to produce impactful research,” says Bello.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-pfas-reacts-with-fiber"&gt;How PFAS reacts with fiber&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers used male mice on diets modeled after typical U.S. eating patterns. Some received inulin as a control fiber and others received &lt;a href="https://ift.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/j.1541-4337.2012.00189.x" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;oat beta-glucan&lt;/a&gt;, a soluble dietary fiber found naturally in the cell walls of oats, as the test fiber. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mice drank water containing a mix of seven PFAS for six weeks, then switched to clean water for four weeks to see how much PFAS cleared during this washout period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the beta-glucan mice &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/forever-chemicals-found-in-tap-and-bottled-water-worldwide/"&gt;drank more water&lt;/a&gt;, they took in more PFAS. The team adjusted the results to account for that. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the adjustment, their blood levels of PFOA and PFOS trended lower (p &amp;lt; 0.1). These mice also had a slightly lower body fat percentage and lower fat in the liver and small intestine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PFAS turned on some liver genes that help process chemicals; after the clean-water period, only one of those genes, &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/gene/13112" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cyp3a11&lt;/a&gt;, moved back toward normal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-fiber-reduces-pfas"&gt;Why fiber reduces PFAS&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the better-known PFAS, like PFOA and PFOS, have been linked to higher &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/just-one-handful-of-pecan-nuts-each-day-can-lower-cholesterol-heart-health/"&gt;LDL cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;, lower vaccine responses, and certain cancers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soluble fibers such as beta-glucan and psyllium form gels in the gut that can bind bile acids. That action is known to help lower LDL cholesterol by pushing the body to make new bile acids instead of reusing old ones. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because PFAS share some chemical features with bile acids, trapping them in the same gel is a reasonable approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As a scientist, I had a life-meets-science moment while looking for ways to control bad cholesterol,” says Schlezinger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In published research studies, I found that consuming gel-forming fibers can increase the elimination of bile acids, which in turn reduces cholesterol in the blood.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The liver then pulls cholesterol out of the blood to replace the lost bile acids. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It occurred to me that bile acids and PFAS have similar &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/bacteria-strain-identified-that-can-eat-forever-chemicals/"&gt;chemical characteristics&lt;/a&gt;, and both are recirculated between the liver, the bile and the gut,” Schlezinger continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-migrating-from-mice-to-people"&gt;Migrating from mice to people&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier research linked high-fiber eating patterns with lower PFAS levels. The new pilot work tested fiber supplements with meals, using beta-glucan and psyllium. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one pilot study, the researchers documented an 8% decrease in PFOS and PFOA after four weeks among people who took a fiber supplement. The researchers are running additional studies to replicate the results. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Increasing fiber intake with a supplement could be a win-win situation, reducing PFAS in the body with a supplement that’s available and economical,” Schlezinger enthused. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Before beginning any fiber supplement routine, however, you should consult with your physician.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-it-all-came-together"&gt;How it all came together&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The collaboration between the two universities started as part of a larger effort to build research capabilities for PFAS biomonitoring and develop solutions to the PFAS &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/some-popular-beers-in-the-u-s-contain-forever-chemicals/"&gt;contamination problem&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Funding from a &lt;a href="https://www.uml.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UMass Lowell&lt;/a&gt; seed grant allowed Bello to develop laboratory methods for quantifying PFAS in tissues, blood, stool, and urine in support of the pilot studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Within three years, we amended our analytical method twice to expand biomonitoring from an initial list of 15 common targets to about 50 PFAS,” says Bello. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Then we built additional expertise to conduct untargeted PFAS analysis and offered in-kind PFAS testing to several research groups to promote initial data generation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-pfas-fiber-and-human-health"&gt;PFAS, fiber, and human health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;PFAS are everywhere and stubbornly stick around, but this research points to a practical, low-cost way to nudge them out: take gel-forming soluble fiber like psyllium or beta-glucan with meals to trap PFAS in the gut and send them out of the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers are now testing novel and inexpensive PFAS removal and detoxification strategies such as multiple fibers, different diets, and cholestyramine – a medication used to lower cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The field of PFAS testing continues to change as labs refine methods and standards. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“With thousands of PFAS species in use, we as a society have a long way to go before we can claim that we have fully understood the real scope of PFAS exposures to humans and the environment and their &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/forever-chemicals-in-tap-water-increase-cancer-risk-by-up-to-33/"&gt;health impact&lt;/a&gt;,” Bello concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s early, not a cure-all, and anyone considering supplements should talk to a clinician, but the signal is promising and actionable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0041008X24003879?via%3Dihub" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Toxicology and Applied Pharmacology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://ehjournal.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s12940-025-01165-8" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Environmental Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 23:38:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxOMEVieWJCREdRdTRrVXJJamlYSTNfSDFiM2pIc0JwWjNWSXNqU3h4Q01YWEJQTk0tclptalBXRnZUbHhjazhQa2JMOFg5aEM5bGowdFZsTF9XU1FvWm52eDBZNXh6T3FSLXMtc3U5eWVqSlVDeUZDZEcxQXpUNXhqUmpkbnFFR2JfUnlmVTItZHhJS1ItTUcxRFRmbEtRS1dBNmtRemVLa0dYd2k4WGc</guid></item><item><title>在柯林斯堡发现头上长着“触手”或“角”的兔子- 9News.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqwFBVV95cUxNM0VzNFNoTlpjR2lVeTJyeFdXVmY1aE5Lc1Z0WHRXLTZUSUxvcGt0X1JEOGRwbGNzQzl3ajRKOTFqcWZRdlZFVmR3U3J3dkxTNmNRR1pRTWxXNUFGaENDcW12UzhaN1otRTQyUmpMODhlNzJNU1YyMS1RVGR4OUNOaGd2MEh1ZlF0OWpQbF80R0VzWFpNRXMyRmhkbFROaHd3a0E5YmlvM1RzZUk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Access Denied&lt;/h1&gt;
 
You don't have permission to access "http://www.9news.com/article/news/local/fort-collins-rabbits-virus/73-a3afc465-4296-4f2b-8491-023d10295661" on this server.&lt;p&gt;
Reference #18.25643017.1754706085.888344d
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://errors.edgesuite.net/18.25643017.1754706085.888344d&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>9News.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 23:07:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxNM0VzNFNoTlpjR2lVeTJyeFdXVmY1aE5Lc1Z0WHRXLTZUSUxvcGt0X1JEOGRwbGNzQzl3ajRKOTFqcWZRdlZFVmR3U3J3dkxTNmNRR1pRTWxXNUFGaENDcW12UzhaN1otRTQyUmpMODhlNzJNU1YyMS1RVGR4OUNOaGd2MEh1ZlF0OWpQbF80R0VzWFpNRXMyRmhkbFROaHd3a0E5YmlvM1RzZUk</guid></item><item><title>2025年需要卷土重来的9种自制小吃习惯- VegOut</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxOQTZ6ODBxTnpqYXNvOFR3MTRtMnpobU9jdFZmckNMU1RNazYwRnVzcE9rTUdiWVJnMTEyUFI3NmQ2VVhhd1F3Mm90cV9PWFdwLThwVURmQ0xwdy1jNVgxbUstT1JtRHhjaHJwVmFCc3hOeEE3eExzVG5yMVFfcmZMX2s0dWxCMWhZTWF0aE1nVTI2YjdjNlU3V0lRcGdHa0VzVUE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p data-start="155" data-end="1073"&gt;The smell of hot corn oil popping against a dented saucepan lid is my earliest after‑school soundtrack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="155" data-end="1073"&gt;Mom never bought the ready‑to‑microwave bags; she said the stove kept her “on speaking terms” with the food.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="155" data-end="1073"&gt;Somewhere between corporate life and grocery delivery, I drifted into the single‑serve snack aisle and forgot that lesson — until last spring, when a routine health check told me my daily handful of neon‑orange crisps had turned into a full‑fledged habit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="155" data-end="1073"&gt;I opened a cupboard that evening and realized nothing &lt;em data-start="676" data-end="686"&gt;crunched&lt;/em&gt; without crinkling plastic first.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="155" data-end="1073"&gt;That epiphany met a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d42473-024-00020-7.pdf"&gt;Nature headline &lt;/a&gt;on my feed: home cooks eat far fewer ultra‑processed snacks and load up on nutrient‑dense whole foods instead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="155" data-end="1073"&gt;The science echoed my nostalgia, so I began reviving nine old‑school snack habits—each one stepped, storied, and rooted in new research that shows why the comeback matters more than ever.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="1075" data-end="1114"&gt;1. Sunday‑batch stove‑top popcorn&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1115" data-end="2096"&gt;When I was twelve, Dad counted kernels into a pot like loose change, then waited for the first pop before he shook the pan in joyful paranoia: &lt;em data-start="1258" data-end="1282"&gt;don’t burn, don’t burn&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1115" data-end="2096"&gt;I’ve resurrected that ritual, but I season a week’s worth at once — smoked paprika on Monday, cinnamon‑cacao on Tuesday, nutritional yeast mid‑week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1115" data-end="2096"&gt;Making popcorn this way forces me to watch, listen, and eventually cut the heat before the last kernel risks scorching—built‑in mindful eating.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1115" data-end="2096"&gt;Planning snacks in advance is more than quaint — &lt;a href="https://nutritionsource.hsph.harvard.edu/snacking/"&gt;Harvard nutrition experts&lt;/a&gt; note that prepping go‑to items like popcorn, nuts, or yogurt ahead of time reins in calories, evens out hunger, and slips extra nutrients into an otherwise grab‑and‑go day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="1115" data-end="2096"&gt;A single Sunday pot fills four mason jars cheaper than one supermarket multipack, and because the seasoning lives on the kernel, I don’t reflexively shovel handful after handful—the flavor’s intense enough to slow me down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="2098" data-end="2148"&gt;2. Apple arcs with two‑ingredient nut butter&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2149" data-end="3160"&gt;On a high‑school field trip, my friend Hana unveiled a tiny metal tin: thin apple slices fanned around a dollop of peanut butter she’d blended at home with nothing but peanuts and a drizzle of maple.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2149" data-end="3160"&gt;Decades later, I’ve upgraded the butter — half roasted almonds, half hazelnuts, blitzed with a pinch of salt.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2149" data-end="3160"&gt;The apples get cut into crescent “arcs” my daughter learned from a YouTube geometry video.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2149" data-end="3160"&gt;They still brown, and that’s fine — we dip faster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2149" data-end="3160"&gt;A recent &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/aug/04/home-cooking-and-minimally-processed-foods-best-for-weight-loss-upf-study-finds"&gt;eight‑week trial&lt;/a&gt; reported that volunteers eating scratch‑cooked, minimally processed meals shed twice the weight and clocked 290 fewer daily calories than peers on an ultra‑processed diet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2149" data-end="3160"&gt;Homemade nut butter dodges the added oils and stabilizers that can turn a healthy dip into a dessert. Step by step: roast nuts 10 minutes, cool, blend until runny, store in small jars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="2149" data-end="3160"&gt;A spoonful over apples beats vending‑machine candy for staying power—protein, fiber, and a crunch that sounds like biting into self‑respect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="3162" data-end="3215"&gt;3. Chili‑lime roasted chickpeas for the commute&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3216" data-end="4019"&gt;My first grown‑up job had a 40‑minute train ride flanked by pastry kiosks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3216" data-end="4019"&gt;One mentor—an accountant named Luis—always popped crunchy chickpeas instead. “Keeps the spreadsheets away,” he joked. I now roast two cans of chickpeas every Wednesday: pat dry, toss with olive oil, smoked paprika, lime zest, and sea salt; bake at 400 °F until brittle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3216" data-end="4019"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.gov.uk/government/publications/processed-foods-and-health-sacns-rapid-evidence-update/processed-foods-and-health-sacns-rapid-evidence-update-summary"&gt;UK Scientific Advisory Committee&lt;/a&gt; on Nutrition’s 2025 rapid evidence update urges cutting back on processed snack packs heavy in sugar, salt, and saturated fat; homemade pulses sidestep that red‑flag trio entirely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="3216" data-end="4019"&gt;Roasted chickpeas ride well in a pocket‑sized jar; they’re humble but heroic—protein to curb the 5 p.m. drive‑thru lure, fiber to delay the next hunger bell, and a flavor punch that makes savored bites, not autopilot grazing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="4021" data-end="4075"&gt;4. Rainbow veggie sticks with kid‑whipped hummus&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4076" data-end="4975"&gt;Years ago, my niece refused carrots unless they came pre‑shaped like cartoon stars. Then we tried a parent‑child cooking class that let her blitz chickpeas and lemon in a child‑safe mini‑processor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4076" data-end="4975"&gt;She licked the spoon, claimed ownership, and—statistically unsurprising—ate the carrots too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4076" data-end="4975"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/15/22/4851"&gt;2023 parent‑child cooking program&lt;/a&gt; showed that when children prepare snacks, their vegetable intake rises meaningfully.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4076" data-end="4975"&gt;Every Friday, my own daughter lines up rainbow veggie sticks—purple carrot, yellow pepper, green cucumber—while I set out garlic, tahini, and chickpeas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4076" data-end="4975"&gt;We taste as we blend: more lemon? extra cumin?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4076" data-end="4975"&gt;The hummus thickens, pride balloons, and a plateful of raw produce disappears faster than a gaming livestream.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4076" data-end="4975"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steps&lt;/strong&gt;: rinse chickpeas, blitz with tahini, water, lemon, garlic, salt; slice veggies; eat immediately or pack into lunch tins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="4076" data-end="4975"&gt;Ownership is the secret seasoning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="4977" data-end="5035"&gt;5. Yogurt‑parfait jars with “choose‑your‑own crunch”&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5036" data-end="5937"&gt;In college, I bought parfaits layered in plastic cups—granola glued to the lid, fruit puree at the bottom. They felt fancy until the label revealed more sugar than a glazed doughnut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5036" data-end="5937"&gt;My 2025 revival uses plain Greek yogurt spooned into glass jars on Sunday night, topped with frozen berries (they thaw by lunch), and sealed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5036" data-end="5937"&gt;The crunch stays separate: toasted oats, pumpkin seeds, and a dark‑chocolate shaving stashed in a tiny side tin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5036" data-end="5937"&gt;When afternoon slump hits, I assemble, swirl, and taste a dessert disguised as nourishment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5036" data-end="5937"&gt;Again, Harvard’s snacking guidelines highlight portion‑controlled, protein‑rich options like yogurt to keep hunger predictable and nutrients high.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5036" data-end="5937"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The step‑by‑step is foolproof&lt;/strong&gt;: toast oats for five minutes, cool, store; layer jars; pack. Cost per serving: less than the price of a gas‑station latte, and the jar’s weight reminds me to take it slow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="5939" data-end="5996"&gt;6. Cinnamon‑dusted frozen banana “nice‑cream” coins&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5997" data-end="6795"&gt;During a heatwave childhood, Mom froze banana halves on sticks; we bit into icy centers and pretended we were at the county fair.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5997" data-end="6795"&gt;My adult freezer now holds banana “coins”: sliced rounds tossed in cinnamon, frozen on parchment, then bagged. They taste like mini ice‑cream bites but register as fruit in any ledger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5997" data-end="6795"&gt;The earlier UCL trial’s calorie gap was partly credited to reduced high‑sugar extras when people cooked from scratch—frozen bananas are Exhibit A of scratch dessert that replaces pint‑diving at midnight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5997" data-end="6795"&gt;Portion planning—one small handful in a ramekin—echoes Harvard’s note that pre‑planned servings tame calories without joy‑thieving austerity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="5997" data-end="6795"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiny steps:&lt;/strong&gt; slice ripe bananas, dust with cinnamon, freeze flat, transfer to reuseable bag. Midnight craving solved; spoon unnecessary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="6797" data-end="6830"&gt;7. DIY “campfire” trail mix&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6831" data-end="7653"&gt;I once paid airport prices for a designer trail mix that turned out to be mostly chocolate‑coated cereal. Now I recreate the campfire mixes of youth groups: equal parts roasted almonds, hazelnuts, sunflower seeds, chopped dried apricot, and a smattering of dark chocolate shards.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6831" data-end="7653"&gt;The Nature Research that I mentioned above spotlight on home cooking notes that people who prep snacks at home naturally gravitate to whole, nutrient‑dense ingredients and dodge the engineered bliss points of ultra‑processed blends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6831" data-end="7653"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step‑wise&lt;/strong&gt;: roast nuts at 325 °F for ten minutes, cool, combine with unsweetened fruit, store in screw‑top jars.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6831" data-end="7653"&gt;Portion into micro‑bags before a hike or long Zoom day; the pre‑split servings check the “planning” box the Harvard team says curbs mindless handfuls. T&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="6831" data-end="7653"&gt;he result tastes like a forest walk and chews like accountability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="7655" data-end="7711"&gt;8. Whole‑grain toast soldiers with smashed avocado&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7712" data-end="8453"&gt;Toast “soldiers” were my grandmother’s trick for toddlers — fingers of toast dunked in soft‑boiled egg. I’ve modernized the idea: wide fingers of seeded whole‑grain bread toasted crisp, topped with smashed avocado, lime, and chili flakes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7712" data-end="8453"&gt;They store surprisingly well wrapped in wax paper for three hours—perfect for school pickup.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7712" data-end="8453"&gt;The UK rapid review’s warning about processed snack packs hits hardest in children’s lunchboxes; mini toasts sidestep that sodium‑sugar pitfall while teaching the palate to enjoy fat’s satiety when it comes wrapped in fiber.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="7712" data-end="8453"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steps&lt;/strong&gt;: toast bread, mash avocado with lime and salt, spread, slice into “soldiers,” wrap. They offer handheld calm—chewy, fatty, tart—and keep me from raiding the drive‑thru chip tray.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="8455" data-end="8515"&gt;9. Oven‑dried fruit leather you can actually pronounce&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8516" data-end="9287"&gt;As a kid I loved neon fruit rolls that stuck to my teeth until Halloween. But their ingredient list reads like a chemistry set.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8516" data-end="9287"&gt;This comeback item sprang from a rainy Saturday experiment: purée ripe peaches and strawberries, spread thin on a silicone mat, and bake at 175 °F for four hours until tacky. Cut into strips, roll in parchment, stash.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8516" data-end="9287"&gt;The Nature home‑cooking report plus the SACN review both hammer the same nail—ultra‑processed sweets pack hidden sugars and additives; homemade treats give sweetness with fiber attached.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8516" data-end="9287"&gt;Planning portioned rolls means I don’t inhale a whole bag of gummy candy while editing late at night.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="8516" data-end="9287"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Step‑wise&lt;/strong&gt;: blend fruit, sweeten only if absolutely necessary, spread, bake low, cool, slice, roll. Flavor? Think sunset in paper form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 data-start="9289" data-end="9358"&gt;Final words: from research to real life—why the revival matters&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9359" data-end="9920"&gt;Reviving these nine snack habits didn’t just trim plastic or novelty; it rewired my day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9359" data-end="9920"&gt;Preparing snacks ahead satisfied the Harvard checklist for portion control, while the Nature and UCL findings played out in real time—I stopped defaulting to vending‑machine options and felt my afternoon energy stabilize.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9359" data-end="9920"&gt;Watching my daughter whirl hummus echoed the MDPI study on kids cooking: her carrot intake skyrocketed without a single lecture. And every time I roasted chickpeas instead of cracking open a foil bag, I imagined the UK scientists nodding approval.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9922" data-end="10388"&gt;The common denominator is agency. Homemade snacks put my hands back in the story, turning feed‑scroll cravings into small, tactile rituals: shaking popcorn, peeling fruit leather, dusting banana coins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="9922" data-end="10388"&gt;Research may validate the benefits, but the lived reward is quieter: the smell of cinnamon when I crack open a jar at 3 p.m., the pride in my kid’s eyes when she packs her rainbow veggies, the almost meditative hush that falls when kernels pop in an even rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="10390" data-end="10732"&gt;So here’s the plan B to processed snacking fatigue: pick one habit, prep it this weekend, and notice how the craving conversation changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-start="10390" data-end="10732"&gt;Science says it’ll help your waistline; experience says it will also feed parts of you an algorithm can’t measure—memory, presence, and the silent joy of hearing frogs and knowing it’s time to turn left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-3411918273"&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Your Plant-Powered Archetype?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what your everyday habits say about your deeper purpose—and how they ripple out to impact the planet?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This 90-second quiz reveals the plant-powered role you’re here to play, and the tiny shift that makes it even more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12 fun questions. Instant results. Surprisingly accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 23:02:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOQTZ6ODBxTnpqYXNvOFR3MTRtMnpobU9jdFZmckNMU1RNazYwRnVzcE9rTUdiWVJnMTEyUFI3NmQ2VVhhd1F3Mm90cV9PWFdwLThwVURmQ0xwdy1jNVgxbUstT1JtRHhjaHJwVmFCc3hOeEE3eExzVG5yMVFfcmZMX2s0dWxCMWhZTWF0aE1nVTI2YjdjNlU3V0lRcGdHa0VzVUE</guid></item><item><title>继路易斯安那州之后，佛罗里达州拥有全国最多的食肉细菌病例-WPLG Local 10</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNUGhab1ZsR25zUlBWQ21jaXk5dnNkQks5ZFZ5VmlSc2cxbDdMbG1NSHRpRjBIcFhlczB4bWZKeVdoN2FiSF9GTi00NUVXN3BEb1lRQ0dnZXdMSTdhOUxqZlRvbXRuaDdUSDJrOXFoQjlxVkoyVTlUVWxNamVRZG5KUG9CeWJkSVYwUlExUTBROWd6OWhFd2dnM0N4NVc3ZjdDMzJEaXh2cm1PUnlpRE9rZlBFODFtUlZ0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="b-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;MIAMI — The Florida Department of Health&lt;a href="https://www.floridahealth.gov/diseases-and-conditions/vibrio-infections/vibrio-vulnificus/index.html" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.floridahealth.gov/diseases-and-conditions/vibrio-infections/vibrio-vulnificus/index.html"&gt; reported&lt;/a&gt; that a flesh-eating bacteria that lives in warm seawater is responsible for 16 infections in 12 counties in Florida. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The bacteria, known as&lt;a href="https://www.local10.com/news/local/2025/07/17/experts-warn-against-dangerous-flesh-eating-bacteria-in-florida/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.local10.com/news/local/2025/07/17/experts-warn-against-dangerous-flesh-eating-bacteria-in-florida/"&gt; Vibrio vulnificusis&lt;/a&gt;, has been the cause of five deaths, including one in Broward County, so far this year in Florida, according to the latest data released by DOH. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The other deaths in Florida were in St. Johns, Hillsborough, and Bay counties. The symptoms include watery diarrhea, stomach cramps, nausea, vomiting, fever, and chills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;To avoid infections, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vibrio/about/index.html" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/vibrio/about/index.html"&gt;warned&lt;/a&gt; against eating raw seafood and being near saltwater or brackish water, where rivers meet the ocean, with open wounds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The cases nationwide add up to at least 60. Florida has the second most cases after &lt;a href="https://ldh.la.gov/news/vibrio-vulnificus-2025" target="_self" rel="" title="https://ldh.la.gov/news/vibrio-vulnificus-2025"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt; where there have been 17. There were 7 in North Carolina, 6 in Virginia, 5 in Texas, 3 in Alabama,&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and 2 in Georgia. The other cases were&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Mississippi, South Carolina, Massachusetts, and Arizona. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;table class="b-article-body__table"&gt;&lt;thead&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;State&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Cases &lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;Deaths&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/thead&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Florida&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;16&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Louisiana&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;17&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;4&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;North Carolina&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;7&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Virginia&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;6&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Texas&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;5&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Alabama&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;3&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Georgia&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;2&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;h3 class="b-article-body__h3"&gt;Steps to prevent infection&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Do not let raw seafood, its drippings, or its juices contaminate other foods.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Always wash your hands with soap and water after handling raw shellfish.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you are at increased risk for infection, wear protective gloves when handling raw seafood.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protect wounds from coastal water. Open wounds include recent cuts and scrapes, recent surgery sites, and recent piercings and tattoos.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cover your wound with a waterproof bandage if it could come into contact with coastal waters or raw seafood, its drippings, or its juices.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This contact can happen during everyday activities, such as swimming, fishing, or walking on the beach.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;It could happen when a hurricane or storm surge causes flooding.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Source: CDC&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph b-article-body__copyright"&gt;Copyright 2025 by WPLG Local10.com - All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WPLG Local 10</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 22:38:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNUGhab1ZsR25zUlBWQ21jaXk5dnNkQks5ZFZ5VmlSc2cxbDdMbG1NSHRpRjBIcFhlczB4bWZKeVdoN2FiSF9GTi00NUVXN3BEb1lRQ0dnZXdMSTdhOUxqZlRvbXRuaDdUSDJrOXFoQjlxVkoyVTlUVWxNamVRZG5KUG9CeWJkSVYwUlExUTBROWd6OWhFd2dnM0N4NVc3ZjdDMzJEaXh2cm1PUnlpRE9rZlBFODFtUlZ0</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心的数据显示，随着美国各地病例的增加，西海岸的Covid-19水平最高-卫报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPZC1QOWdZN2hVWlhwVFRGUUtlXzBLZ1FDcE43Tm85Q1lrLXFYMENpamJLcWUycVIzX0FKYzl5cGhQMldubVdCNkU0WXJGQkpXdmJmNncwVWgyUEdmRi1JRzdUb1FIQk0xMUJ6eE5jb0tIcl9VbkxweTIxaVBEZ3pGV2dSNjk3MHBWNllN?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Several states in the western US are experiencing a surge in new &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/coronavirus-outbreak" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Covid-19 infections&lt;/a&gt;, according to the latest data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;An &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nwss/rv/COVID19-national-data.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;update&lt;/a&gt; released on Friday shows Covid-19 activity in wastewater has risen to a “moderate” level nationwide, up from “low” the week before. The highest levels are in the western US, including in states such as Alaska, California, Colorado, Nevada and Utah, all of which are marked as “high”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"us-news","tags":[{"id":"us-news/us-news","type":"Keyword","title":"US news"},{"id":"world/coronavirus-outbreak","type":"Keyword","title":"Coronavirus"},{"id":"us-news/west-coast","type":"Keyword","title":"West Coast"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"profile/coral-murphy-marcos","type":"Contributor","title":"Coral Murphy Marcos"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/west-coast-news","type":"Tracking","title":"West Coast News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"us-news/2025/aug/08/west-coast-high-covid-19-levels-cdc","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Wastewater monitoring can detect viruses spreading from one person to another within a community earlier than clinical testing and before people who are sick go to their doctor or hospital,” the CDC notes. “If you see increased wastewater viral activity levels, it might indicate that there is a higher risk of infection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Wastewater tracking is often used as an early detection tool for monitoring potential future upticks. According to &lt;a href="https://skylab.cdph.ca.gov/calwws/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the California department of public health’s own wastewater tracking&lt;/a&gt;, statewide infection numbers have now surpassed winter highs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Other metrics are also showing increases in the illness. As of Tuesday, the CDC estimates Covid-19 infections are &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/cfa-modeling-and-forecasting/rt-estimates/index.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;growing or probably growing in 45 states&lt;/a&gt;, which is up from 40 last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A new Covid-19 variant, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nwss/rv/COVID19-variants.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;XFG, or “Stratus”&lt;/a&gt;, is on the rise in the US, becoming the third-most common strain of the summer. The variant was first detected in south-east Asia in January but was barely detected in the US until May. By late June, it was estimated to account for up to 14%, according to the &lt;a href="https://covid.cdc.gov/covid-data-tracker/#variant-proportions" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;During a &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-cases-rise-summer-2025-cdc-data/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;CBS interview&lt;/a&gt; in July, physician Jon LaPook said that this type of rise was typical for the summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We now know that there’s a winter spike and then there’s a summer spike,” the outlet’s chief medical correspondent said in the interview. “And every year, the number of deaths, the number of hospitalizations, is gradually going down each season. So that’s the good news.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Still, experts caution it is &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/aug/05/us-covid-cases-rising" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;too soon to know how big the developing late-summer wave&lt;/a&gt; could get. While cases are rising more slowly than at the start of previous surges, varied immune responses from prior infections and vaccinations make it difficult to predict how severe illnesses could be. The risks are further compounded by new vaccine restrictions from the Trump administration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The rise in Covid-19 cases comes as the US Department of Health and Human Services announced on Tuesday it will &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/aug/05/rfk-jr-hhs-mrna-vaccine-research" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;terminate 22 federal contracts for mRNA-based vaccines&lt;/a&gt;, raising questions about the safety of a technology credited with helping end the pandemic and saving millions of lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The CDC did not immediately respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 22:25:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPZC1QOWdZN2hVWlhwVFRGUUtlXzBLZ1FDcE43Tm85Q1lrLXFYMENpamJLcWUycVIzX0FKYzl5cGhQMldubVdCNkU0WXJGQkpXdmJmNncwVWgyUEdmRi1JRzdUb1FIQk0xMUJ6eE5jb0tIcl9VbkxweTIxaVBEZ3pGV2dSNjk3MHBWNllN</guid></item><item><title>在热门度假目的地发生更多致命的“食肉”细菌感染病例- FOX 13 Tampa Bay</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuAFBVV95cUxPdXpacW9NVVIzNlJXdEh3bnFTT2oyQUlyU05NcDhnVmM1NzM1enV5Mk5Yb3JRb3V1ekdjcE4wTnB6QU9FZ1gtRWFsUndLVHQteDNHQXpDdDdydzFRMjhwd1REcDRKY1F2d0RNZ1RSUFZ0OWhyRllXV1Z3LTQ0RXNBX090TzB6QVZwMnFJVzBzS0xCWHo1QndtR1JDMS1lQmQ3SG9uYzQ3UWUwMEJ6S2ZiY2ZvNGo5ZnNM0gG-AUFVX3lxTFBYN3RGR3d0bG1UcWRkcUYxcUxkd2NfWTNENV9jRTd2WHBjbzFHbDhWZUpPQkxPNlRSU3hiTUtVcGNyRlRBOU0zSWNqajYtVE5uRTU1bHMzVk9qUzJhLUdkSzVmZjExdXBBZmlZanpJOFhJT3JSb255VHBzR2s4VmJxRFFGZFNOVHdFbXlHb2NXVndSWFdYNTY0ZXpheWl2eWktMnJhcDZPRndFQS1KZENnRnAzUDJXZFZ3Y3ZCaXc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body" data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PANAMA CITY, Fla.&lt;/strong&gt; - &lt;/span&gt;Eight deaths have been reported in Florida due to a "flesh-eating" &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/science/wild-nature/bacteria" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;bacterial infection&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, according to state health officials.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;The Florida Department of Health has confirmed 13 total cases of Vibrio vulnificus across 11 counties, as reported by local outlets.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Last year, the state reported even higher numbers: 82 cases and 19 deaths.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails" data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-js" data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-ad-pos="inread" data-ad-size="1x1" class="ad gpt" data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/deadly-bacterial-outbreak-infects-dozens-city-neighborhood-officials-sound-alarm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;DEADLY BACTERIAL OUTBREAK INFECTS DOZENS IN CITY NEIGHBORHOOD AS OFFICIALS SOUND ALARM&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Louisiana is also seeing a higher-than-average case count, with the health department reporting 17 infections and four deaths so far in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;The U.S. sees an average of 150 to 200 infections per year, according to data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). Most &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/infectious-disease" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cases of the infection&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; occur in the Gulf Coast states (Alabama, Florida, Louisiana, Mississippi and Texas).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Vibrio vulnificus?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Vibrio vulnificus is part of a wider group of Vibrio bacteria, which are found in coastal waters, the CDC states. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;This specific bacterium, Vibrio vulnificus, can enter open wounds when people are swimming.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/death-confirmed-rare-deadly-brain-eating-amoeba-southern-lake" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;DEATH CONFIRMED FROM RARE AND DEADLY 'BRAIN-EATING AMOEBA' IN SOUTHERN LAKE&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;"Warmer waters provide a ready incubator for Vibrio growth," Dr. Nathan Goodyear, an integrative medicine physician at the Williams Cancer Institute in California, told Fox News Digital. "Flesh-eating bacteria are thermophilic halophiles, readily populating in &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/us/environment/water" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;warm, salty, brackish water&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;." &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Additionally, an increase in plankton blooms, which harbor Vibrio bacteria, is associated with increased cases. Increased flooding and hurricanes, as well as other natural disasters, can also spread the medium in which the flesh-eating bacteria exist, Goodyear noted.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div original-article-post="" class="full-width-image" data-v-0dea8073 data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;img src="https://images.foxtv.com/static.fox13news.com/www.fox13news.com/content/uploads/2025/08/932/524/vibrio-vulnificus-getty-image-scaled.jpg?ve=1&amp;amp;tl=1" alt='This Scanning Electron Micrograph Sem Depicts A Grouping Of Vibrio Vulnificus Bacteria; Mag. 13184X. Vibrio Vulnificus Is A Bacterium In The Same Family As Those That Cause Cholera. It Normally Lives In Warm Seawater And Is Part Of A Group Of Vibrios That Are Called "Halophilic" Because They Require Salt. V. Vulnificus Can Cause Disease In Those Who Eat Contaminated Seafood Or Have An Open Wound That Is Exposed To Contaminated Seawater. Among Healthy People, Ingestion Of V. Vulnificus Can Cause Vomiting, Diarrhea, And Abdominal Pain. In Immunocompromised Persons, Particularly Those With Chronic Liver Disease, V. Vulnificus Can Infect The Bloodstream, Causing A Severe And Life Threatening Illness Characterized By Fever And Chills, Decreased Blood Pressure Septic Shock, And Blistering Skin Lesions. V. Vulnificus Bloodstream Infections Are Fatal About 50% Of The Time. (Photo By BSIP/UIG Via Getty Images)' data-v-0dea8073&gt; &lt;div class="info" data-v-0dea8073&gt;&lt;p data-v-0dea8073&gt;&lt;span data-v-0dea8073&gt;This Scanning Electron Micrograph Sem Depicts A Grouping Of Vibrio Vulnificus Bacteria; Mag. 13184X. Vibrio Vulnificus Is A Bacterium In The Same Family As Those That Cause Cholera. It Normally Lives In Warm Seawater And Is Part Of A Group Of Vibrios &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Vibrio has the potential to cause severe infections, according to Dr. Andrew Handel, pediatric infectious diseases specialist at Stony Brook Children's Hospital in New York. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Those include invasive soft tissue infections (sometimes called "necrotizing fasciitis" or "flesh-eating bacteria") and bloodstream infections.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;aside original-article-post="" class="pull-quote" data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;p class="quote-text"&gt;"People who have skin infections often have high fevers and intense pain, swelling and redness at the site of infection."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;cite&gt;&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/aside&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Groups at highest risk include &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/geriatric-health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;older adults&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and people who are immunocompromised or have chronic liver disease, Handel cautioned. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;"Raw oysters and other shellfish can also be infected with Vibrio, leading to severe gastroenteritis or food poisoning," he told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Symptoms to watch for&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Vibrio symptoms depend on the type of infection, according to Handel. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;"People who have skin infections often have high fevers and intense pain, swelling and redness at the site of infection, which usually occurs after an open wound is exposed to infected water," he told Fox News Digital.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/doctors-reveal-key-signs-lyme-disease-tick-season-intensifies-across-us" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;DOCTORS REVEAL KEY SIGNS OF LYME DISEASE AS TICK SEASON INTENSIFIES ACROSS US&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;"The symptoms from &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/beauty-and-skin" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;skin infections&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; can progress very quickly and quickly become life-threatening in a short time. Thankfully, those infections are rare."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;People who have eaten contaminated shellfish will have severe vomiting and diarrhea, which can lead to dehydration, the doctor warned.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;While &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;healthy people&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; generally experience only mild symptoms, those who are immunocompromised or have chronic liver disease can face serious health risks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;If Vibrio vulnificus enters the bloodstream, it can cause severe illness marked by fever, chills, septic shock and blistering skin lesions, according to Florida Health. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/apps-products?pid=AppArticleLink" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CLICK HERE TO GET THE FOX NEWS APP&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;About half of these bloodstream infections are fatal.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Some severe cases can cause an infection called necrotizing fasciitis, which is when the flesh around an open wound dies, the CDC cautions. This rare side effect has led to Vibrio vulnificus being described as a "flesh-eating bacteria."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2 data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diagnosis and treatment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;The bacterial infection is diagnosed by testing cultures obtained from stool, wounds or blood, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;For mild infections, the CDC recommends increasing fluid intake to prevent dehydration.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Those with severe or prolonged infections should &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/healthy-living/medications" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;receive antibiotics&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to improve survival rates. For people with infected wounds, surgery may be necessary to remove dead tissue.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;CLICK HERE TO SIGN UP FOR OUR HEALTH NEWSLETTER&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;"Antibiotics alone are not enough to calm the flesh-eating storm, Goodyear told Fox News Digital. "Early &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research/surgery" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;surgical debridement&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to remove infection sources is readily required."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;About one in five people will die from the infection, sometimes within a day or two of illness, the CDC states.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h2 data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preventing infection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;To prevent Vibrio infections, experts recommend against swimming in open bodies of water like the ocean, rivers and estuaries if you have any open wounds. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;"To prevent Vibrio food poisoning, avoid eating raw shellfish, especially if you are immunocompromised or have chronic liver disease," Handel advised. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;For more Health articles, visit&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foxnews.com/health" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt; www.foxnews.com/health&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;"If you do eat shellfish, make sure it has not been sitting out for a long time and comes from a hygienic source."&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;The doctor noted that Vibrio infections &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/medical-research/rare-diseases" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;u&gt;are rare&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and "should not be a major cause of alarm."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;"For up-to-date information in your state and location, always check with your state and regional health departments for updates," Goodyear advised.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Fox News Digital reached out to the Florida Department of Public Health for comment.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-v-7f0a623e&gt;Read more at &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/more-cases-deadly-flesh-eating-bacterial-infection-popular-vacation-destination" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;FOXNews.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;     &lt;p data-uid="fts-ar-17" class="vendor-unit" data-v-7f0a623e&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>FOX 13 Tampa Bay</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 21:44:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxPdXpacW9NVVIzNlJXdEh3bnFTT2oyQUlyU05NcDhnVmM1NzM1enV5Mk5Yb3JRb3V1ekdjcE4wTnB6QU9FZ1gtRWFsUndLVHQteDNHQXpDdDdydzFRMjhwd1REcDRKY1F2d0RNZ1RSUFZ0OWhyRllXV1Z3LTQ0RXNBX090TzB6QVZwMnFJVzBzS0xCWHo1QndtR1JDMS1lQmQ3SG9uYzQ3UWUwMEJ6S2ZiY2ZvNGo5ZnNM0gG-AUFVX3lxTFBYN3RGR3d0bG1UcWRkcUYxcUxkd2NfWTNENV9jRTd2WHBjbzFHbDhWZUpPQkxPNlRSU3hiTUtVcGNyRlRBOU0zSWNqajYtVE5uRTU1bHMzVk9qUzJhLUdkSzVmZjExdXBBZmlZanpJOFhJT3JSb255VHBzR2s4VmJxRFFGZFNOVHdFbXlHb2NXVndSWFdYNTY0ZXpheWl2eWktMnJhcDZPRndFQS1KZENnRnAzUDJXZFZ3Y3ZCaXc</guid></item><item><title>新研究表明，这种习惯可能会使痴呆风险增加43 ％ - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMibkFVX3lxTFBZVEotZ3pBNEtDVmY3dzdUOEg4djJ6dElDaEJvUkdkaTdhdTg1ZHplV081Zm5KUDlxbXJMQTZPRFdrQ2ItQk1qakJrdXByUExfek01UW12TnlhYldxQ1AxMmdJYjdWQVZHX2s1YmVB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High sugar intake was linked to a 43% higher risk of dementia in a long-term study of 158,000 adults.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Genetics influenced how added sugar affected brain health—some people were more vulnerable than others.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most participants were healthier than average, limiting how widely the results may apply.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A new study suggests that &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7914285/ways-to-eat-less-sugar-without-missing-it/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;eating a lot of sugar (particularly added sugar) may&lt;/a&gt; raise your risk of developing dementia—and your genes could make that risk even higher. For a new study, researchers tracked more than 158,000 mostly middle-aged adults over nearly a decade and found that higher sugar intakes were linked to a significantly greater chance of developing dementia, with certain &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/dementia-risk-doubling-study-8776659" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;genetic traits amplifying that risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While dementia is often viewed as a disease of old age, its biological groundwork can be laid decades earlier. In the United States, about 1.7% of adults aged 65 to 74 are living with a diagnosed form of dementia, with rates climbing sharply after age 75.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This study followed people in their mid-50s to assess whether sugar intake at that stage of life was linked to a greater risk of developing dementia over the following decade—before symptoms typically appear.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Previous research has linked high added sugar intake to a greater risk of dementia, but few studies have explored how that risk may vary based on a person’s genetic makeup.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; This new study helps fill that gap, offering a more personalized view of how sugar and genetics may work together to influence &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/worst-habits-for-brain-health-11773249" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;long-term brain health&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-was-the-study-conducted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Was the Study Conducted? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The study was conducted by a team of medical researchers based in China with expertise in nutrition, epidemiology and chronic disease. They used data from the UK Biobank, a large ongoing health study that includes over 500,000 adults ages 37 to 73 from England, Scotland and Wales. For this analysis, the researchers focused on 158,408 participants—with an average age of 56—who had completed repeated 24-hour dietary recalls and provided genetic samples. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This allowed the team to estimate each person’s intake of added sugars (like those added to soda, candy and baked goods) and naturally-occurring sugars (naturally found in fruit and dairy) and to calculate genetic risk scores for traits related to &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/sneaky-signs-eating-too-much-sugar-11721349" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;sugar metabolism&lt;/a&gt;, gut bacteria and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/early-onset-dementia-study-11723661" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;dementia susceptibility&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Participants were followed for almost 10 years, and dementia cases were identified through national health records including hospital and death registry data.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-the-study-find"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Did the Study Find? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Over the follow-up period, about 0.7% of participants were &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/multidisciplinary-diabetes-management-may-lead-to-28-percent-lower-dementia-risk-8580567" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;diagnosed with dementia&lt;/a&gt;. That may sound low, but it’s notable considering most people were in their 50s at the start—an age when dementia is still rare.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In addition, the researchers found that people who consumed the most added sugar had a 43% higher risk of developing dementia compared to those who consumed the least. Even sugars naturally found in foods were linked to some increased risk, though the effect was smaller.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Genetics also appeared to make a difference. Participants with certain gut-related genetic traits—specifically a lower score for &lt;em&gt;Ruminococcaceae UCG-014&lt;/em&gt; or a higher score for &lt;em&gt;Oscillospira&lt;/em&gt;—were more sensitive to the effects of sugar on dementia risk. These gene-diet interactions suggest consequences depending on their biology.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That said, like all research, this study has limitations. UK Biobank participants are, on average, more health-conscious, less likely to have obesity and more affluent than the general UK population, which means the results may not apply equally to all groups.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It’s also worth noting that about 90% of participants were white. This study didn't include a racially diverse enough population to explore how sugar, genetics and dementia risk may differ across racial or ethnic groups. Finally, the dietary information was also self-reported, which can introduce some inaccuracy. And while the study found strong links between sugar intake and dementia risk, it doesn't prove that sugar directly causes the disease. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Dementia affects millions of people and their families. This study suggests that what you eat in your 50s—especially your sugar intake—might influence your brain health years down the road. Sugar intake is a adjustable risk factor, and cutting back on added sugars is smart advice for most people. For those with a genetic predisposition for dementia, doing so might be especially important.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And just because you decide to cut back on added sugar doesn’t mean you can’t satisfy your sweet tooth. Added sugars had a larger impact on dementia than &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/whats-the-difference-between-natural-and-added-sugars-11694001" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;natural sugars&lt;/a&gt;, like those found in fruit, so fruit-forward options like &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/lemon-raspberry-frozen-yogurt-bites-11687804" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Lemon-Raspberry Frozen Yogurt Bites&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/268407/no-sugar-added-mini-apple-pies/" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;No-Sugar-Added Mini Apple Pies&lt;/a&gt; can be great recipes to work into your routine.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; And we have some other &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/3-step-dessert-recipes-11758461" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;simple dessert options&lt;/a&gt;—like &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/black-bean-brownies-8761128" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;High-Fiber Black Bean Brownies&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/256097/mini-new-york-cheesecakes/" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Mini New York Cheesecakes&lt;/a&gt;—that can add sweetness to your day without giving you a major sugar rush. If you need help resetting your routine to have less added sugar, a meal plan like our weeklong &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/7-day-no-sugar-high-protein-meal-plan-for-beginners-11688630" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;No-Sugar, High-Protein Meal Plan for Beginners&lt;/a&gt; could do the trick.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; What you eat in midlife may have long-term effects on brain health. This study suggests that higher sugar intake—especially in combination with certain genetic traits—may increase the risk of developing dementia. While more research is needed, particularly in more diverse populations, reducing added sugars is a simple, proactive way to support &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/top-mistakes-to-avoid-for-cognitive-health-11779797" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;cognitive health as you age&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 20:28:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTFBZVEotZ3pBNEtDVmY3dzdUOEg4djJ6dElDaEJvUkdkaTdhdTg1ZHplV081Zm5KUDlxbXJMQTZPRFdrQ2ItQk1qakJrdXByUExfek01UW12TnlhYldxQ1AxMmdJYjdWQVZHX2s1YmVB</guid></item><item><title>中国对基孔肯雅病毒宣战。威胁有多大？ ：山羊和苏打水- NPR</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxOS3l4MXVzU25tVlhDVUVTcldUNmVudVVLYkxHUG83UzhMZ0E4bXl5LXJfcUFrY1hkM3BremZSdC1qYkZKYl91b3BrendBQzRQc3NINnd5WldXMlh4M3NCcWhsaExzU1RrQlFTMS1GcXNNcEdtNzdjVDQxMFhzN1lhbW1TZ05TVWdZNlRPNUJ5dDU1Zkc3UF95c2U2bVNUSndHR3c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-81722" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                A worker uses a sprayer to eradicate mosquitos at a park in order to prevent the spread of mosquito-borne disease Chikungunya  in Guangdong Province of China.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Visual China Group/via Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Visual China Group/via Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Health officials in Guangdong province in southern China are waging an all-out war against mosquitoes in response to an outbreak of the chikungunya virus that's sickened thousands with fever, rashes and joint pain over the past month.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Soldiers are fogging streets and parks in the city of Foshan with insecticide. Community workers are going door-to-door to look for stagnant water, where mosquitoes can breed. People who test positive are reportedly being forced to hospitalize to isolate themselves, says &lt;a href="https://www.cfr.org/expert/yanzhong-huang" target="_blank"&gt;Yanzhong Huang&lt;/a&gt;, senior fellow for global health at the Council on Foreign Relations.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;div id="resg-s1-81726" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                A drone sprays insecticide on August 1 in Guangzhou, Guangdong Province of China — part of the effort to curb an outbreak of Chikungunya fever, a mosquito-borne viral disease. Joint pain is a notable symptom.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Chen Chuhong/China News Service via Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Chen Chuhong/China News Service via Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;"It's reminiscent of the COVID-19 tactics," he says, where citizens were extremely restricted in their activities to slow the spread of SARS-CoV-2.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Some of the current measures are likely overkill, says Huang. Chikungunya is rarely fatal, and the mosquito-borne virus can't spread through the air. But mosquitoes easily pick it up from infected people. And because chikungunya outbreaks are rare in China, he says "some of the measures are justified given the population has no immunity." Typically, the virus is found in Africa, southeast Asia and South America.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So far, more than 8,000 people have been infected in Guangdong, making it the largest chikungunya outbreak in China's history. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Here's what you should know about chikungunya (whose name is pronounced "chick'n-GOON-ya").&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is chikungunya and how does it spread?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Chikungunya disease is caused by the &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2015/12/01/458003755/chikungunya-a-mosquito-borne-virus-might-be-scarier-than-we-thought" target="_blank"&gt;chikungunya virus&lt;/a&gt;. It's spread through infected &lt;em&gt;Aedes aegypti&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;Aedes albopictus&lt;/em&gt; mosquitoes. People can get sick within 3 to 7 days of a bite from a mosquito carrying the virus.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The virus can cause fever, rash and fatigue, but the most notable symptom is joint pain. "It can be debilitating, where people cannot get out of bed, they are laid out," says &lt;a href="https://www.pediatrics.pitt.edu/people/laurie-silva-phd" target="_blank"&gt;Laurie Silva&lt;/a&gt;, a virologist at the University of Pittsburgh. The virus is named for a word from the Kimakonde language of Tanzania — where the virus was first discovered in 1952 — that means "that which bends up," because of the distorted posture of those suffering from the pain.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Symptoms tend to resolve within a week or so, but some patients can go on to have chronic illness, says Silva. "They can have prolonged joint pain that can last for weeks or months, and in some cases years," she says. "That's one of the main concerns for this virus."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are there treatments or vaccines?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There are no specific antivirals for chikangunva. "It's really just rest, hydration and pain medicine," says Silva.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There are two &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2023/08/21/1194974088/advancements-may-help-fight-the-chikungunya-virus-wave-in-south-america" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;licensed vaccines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, but they're not widely available or used, according to the World Health Organization. In the U.S., they're only recommended for travelers or lab workers likely to be exposed to the virus. The U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has issued a notice for travelers to Guangdong, urging them to exercise precautions including mosquito repellent and vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The vaccines aren't currently available in China.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How common are chikungunya outbreaks?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The disease was first detected in 1952 in Tanzania, and began popping up in other African and Asian countries over the subsequent decades.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;More global outbreaks have occurred since 2004, and the virus has &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2013/12/18/255216192/trouble-in-paradise-chikungunya-outbreak-grows-in-caribbean" target="_blank"&gt;been reported&lt;/a&gt; in more than 110 countries. Cases and outbreaks are most common in tropical and subtropical regions where mosquitoes thrive year round. Climate change and increased global travel are contributing to chikungunya's growing footprint, says Silva.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For example, the United States gets a handful of cases most years, mostly in returning travelers. There hasn't been a locally acquired case of chikungunya in the U.S. &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chikungunya/data-maps/chikungunya-us.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;since 2019&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So far this year, there have been roughly 240,000 cases of chikungunya and 90 deaths from the virus, mostly in South America. Compared to other outbreaks, China's is so far small. La Réunion, an island in the Indian Ocean, has reported nearly 50,000 cases so far this year.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But chikungunya can spread quickly in dense, urban areas where mosquitoes can thrive. That's why China is taking such extreme measures to tamp down the mosquito population in Foshan.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Over the past few days, confirmed cases appear to be declining, says Huang. "That seems to indicate that the disease is plateauing in Foshan," he says. But with hot and humid weather conditions in the region and travel, he adds, "we cannot rule out the possibility that the disease will spread beyond Guangdong."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 20:16:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxOS3l4MXVzU25tVlhDVUVTcldUNmVudVVLYkxHUG83UzhMZ0E4bXl5LXJfcUFrY1hkM3BremZSdC1qYkZKYl91b3BrendBQzRQc3NINnd5WldXMlh4M3NCcWhsaExzU1RrQlFTMS1GcXNNcEdtNzdjVDQxMFhzN1lhbW1TZ05TVWdZNlRPNUJ5dDU1Zkc3UF95c2U2bVNUSndHR3c</guid></item><item><title>与性自恋和性欲过度行为有关的童年创伤- PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxOcHBfSzlGR1FFamYzRnVVMzZxRkhHNE9uNlBJQjV1bGJoY2w2c0pVR2pTNk1BUk0yVDRZX1FGRmhBZDNyNmtMZDBSeVotNXZNRXFjVXdyc2tsNDctcTFpTDlKc205anVQVUx0UEZXQzBwVUh1ejg3aTlKbjRHOHNIb2dKeVpTa2lzSjNMd2VRTlBjRnJIYXhN?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study conducted in Israel found that higher levels of childhood trauma were associated with heightened sexual narcissism and hypersexual behavior. Statistical analysis indicated that sexual narcissism may mediate the link between childhood trauma and hypersexual behavior. The paper was published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10508-025-03137-y"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Archives of Sexual Behavior&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hypersexual behavior refers to unusually frequent or intense sexual thoughts, urges, or actions that can interfere with daily life. It may include excessive masturbation, compulsive use of pornography, frequent pursuit of casual sex, or persistent sexual preoccupation. While high sexual desire alone is not necessarily problematic, hypersexual behavior becomes a concern when it causes distress, relationship issues, or other harmful consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some individuals use sexual activity as a coping mechanism for stress, anxiety, depression, or trauma. Hypersexuality can occur as a symptom of certain mental health conditions, such as bipolar disorder or borderline personality disorder, especially during manic episodes. It can also be associated with substance use, impulsivity, and poor emotional regulation. Not everyone who engages in hypersexual behavior meets the criteria for a mental disorder, and a diagnosis typically requires that the behavior is persistent, distressing, and difficult to control. The term is sometimes used interchangeably with compulsive sexual behavior, though definitions vary among experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study authors Rotem Yaakov and Aviv Weinstein sought to examine the relationship between childhood trauma and neglect, sexual narcissism, and hypersexual behavior in individuals seeking psychological support for compulsive sexual behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sexual narcissism is a subtype of narcissism characterized by an inflated sense of sexual self-importance, entitlement, and a lack of empathy for sexual partners. Individuals high in sexual narcissism may view sex primarily as a means to boost their ego or gain power rather than as an expression of intimacy. They tend to overestimate their sexual abilities and seek frequent validation of their desirability. Such individuals may also be manipulative in sexual relationships, using charm or coercion to achieve their goals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study participants were 118 individuals from Israel. Half were classified as meeting the criteria for compulsive sexual behavior, while the other half were not. The average age of participants was around 31–32 years, and 72 participants were men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants completed self-report questionnaires assessing hypersexual behavior (Hypersexual Behavior Inventory), sexual narcissism (Sexual Narcissism Scale), and childhood trauma (Childhood Trauma Questionnaire).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results showed that the group with compulsive sexual behavior scored higher not only on hypersexual behavior but also on measures of childhood trauma and sexual narcissism. Men scored somewhat higher than women on hypersexual behavior, but there were no significant sex differences in sexual narcissism or trauma. Among participants with compulsive sexual behavior, religious individuals scored higher on sexual narcissism and hypersexual behavior than their non-religious counterparts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further analysis suggested that childhood trauma was linked to higher sexual narcissism, which in turn was linked to increased hypersexual behavior. Statistical modeling supported the possibility that sexual narcissism serves as a mediating factor between childhood trauma and hypersexual behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In summary, this study indicates that sexual narcissism mediated the relationships between childhood trauma and hypersexual behavior. These findings explain the role of sexual narcissism and childhood maltreatment and abuse in hypersexual behavior and it may have clinical implications for the treatment of CSB [compulsive sexual behavior] disorder,” the study authors concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study contributes to the scientific understanding of the consequences of childhood abuse. However, all the data were collected using self-reports and childhood abuse was assessed retrospectively i.e., based on current memories of participants. This leaves room for reporting bias and recall bias to affect the results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10508-025-03137-y"&gt;A Study on Childhood Trauma and Sexual Narcissism in Individuals with Compulsive Sexual Behavior Receiving Counseling&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Rotem Yaakov and Aviv Weinstein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 20:04:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxOcHBfSzlGR1FFamYzRnVVMzZxRkhHNE9uNlBJQjV1bGJoY2w2c0pVR2pTNk1BUk0yVDRZX1FGRmhBZDNyNmtMZDBSeVotNXZNRXFjVXdyc2tsNDctcTFpTDlKc205anVQVUx0UEZXQzBwVUh1ejg3aTlKbjRHOHNIb2dKeVpTa2lzSjNMd2VRTlBjRnJIYXhN</guid></item><item><title>男性向ChatGPT寻求饮食建议，最终导致“溴化物中毒” - Live Science</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxQaWpxenlEcEZ0NEVNUGtjMVdsY2ZmbnY5T1pPR2FpTmlubkIyR1JDMUxhSEQtUG9qZWJ5clFDajVnczlfVF9XeWxQS0VtUWpwNm9GWThWSkpvR0dFaDJTX3Ixb3QzYXBYalkxZWh0SEVsYUkxRnEzaG9oRE5kUC01dU5XZE00MGRMWXR6aHZfYjFBYUJQN3A5cEl4Q1BiQnBIa1lIRXVOZVdreTl1NlB6SHQxWWlKd3RLN2xj?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p id="02752cdf-74e6-4978-9f73-c02f415e90a0"&gt;A man consulted ChatGPT prior to changing his diet. Three months later, after consistently sticking with that dietary change, he ended up in the emergency department with concerning new psychiatric symptoms, including paranoia and hallucinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turned out that the 60-year-old had bromism, a syndrome brought about by chronic overexposure to the chemical compound bromide or its close cousin bromine. In this case, the man had been consuming sodium bromide that he had purchased online.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="02752cdf-74e6-4978-9f73-c02f415e90a0-2"&gt;A report of the man's case was published Tuesday (Aug. 5) in the journal &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/aimcc.2024.1260" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.acpjournals.org/doi/10.7326/aimcc.2024.1260" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Annals of Internal Medicine Clinical Cases&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="2c429408-2f3d-4a99-8dbb-77844f9b81ba"&gt;Live Science contacted OpenAI, the developer of ChatGPT, about this case. A spokesperson directed the reporter to the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://openai.com/policies/service-terms/" target="_blank" data-url="https://openai.com/policies/service-terms/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;company's service terms&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which state that its services are not intended for use in the diagnosis or treatment of any health condition, and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://openai.com/policies/row-terms-of-use/" target="_blank" data-url="https://openai.com/policies/row-terms-of-use/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;their terms of use&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which state, "You should not rely on Output from our Services as a sole source of truth or factual information, or as a substitute for professional advice." The spokesperson added that OpenAI's safety teams aim to reduce the risk of using the company's services and to train the products to prompt users to seek professional advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-9ff30dd4-8fec-4983-bdb0-d95624b2ba5b" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="a-personal-experiment-3"&gt;"A personal experiment"&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="f3de3fce-1655-44af-ba3c-0a56c217080a"&gt;In the 19th and 20th centuries, bromide was &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/instance/3550397/pdf/13181_2009_Article_BF03161228.pdf" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/instance/3550397/pdf/13181_2009_Article_BF03161228.pdf" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;widely used in prescription and over-the-counter (OTC) drugs&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, including sedatives, anticonvulsants and sleep aids. Over time, though, it &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/307736" target="_blank" data-url="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/307736" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;became clear that chronic exposure&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, such as through the abuse of these medicines, caused bromism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/food-diet/what-is-brominated-vegetable-oil-and-why-did-the-fda-ban-it-in-food" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/food-diet/what-is-brominated-vegetable-oil-and-why-did-the-fda-ban-it-in-food"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is brominated vegetable oil, and why did the FDA ban it in food?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This "toxidrome" — a syndrome triggered by an accumulation of toxins — can cause neuropsychiatric symptoms, including psychosis, agitation, mania and delusions, as well as issues with memory, thinking and muscle coordination. Bromide can trigger these symptoms because, with long-term exposure, it builds up in the body and impairs the function of neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-jykgnzHdRz2jQTbn8sfNwS" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-jykgnzHdRz2jQTbn8sfNwS slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the 1970s and 1980s, U.S. regulators removed several forms of bromide from OTC medicines, including sodium bromide. Bromism rates fell significantly thereafter, and the condition remains relatively rare today. However, occasional cases still occur, with some recent ones being tied to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0735675722005071" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0735675722005071" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;bromide-containing dietary supplements that people purchased online&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prior to the man's recent case, he'd been reading about the negative health effects of consuming too much table salt, also called sodium chloride. "He was surprised that he could only find literature related to reducing sodium from one's diet," as opposed to reducing chloride, the report noted. "Inspired by his history of studying nutrition in college, he decided to conduct a personal experiment to eliminate chloride from his diet."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Note that chloride is important for &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/symptoms/24019-electrolyte-imbalance" target="_blank" data-url="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/symptoms/24019-electrolyte-imbalance" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;maintaining healthy blood volume and blood pressure&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and health issues can emerge if chloride levels in the blood &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.urmc.rochester.edu/encyclopedia/content?ContentTypeID=167&amp;amp;ContentID=chloride" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.urmc.rochester.edu/encyclopedia/content?ContentTypeID=167&amp;amp;ContentID=chloride" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;become too low or too high&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The patient consulted ChatGPT — either ChatGPT 3.5 or 4.0, based on the timeline of the case. The report authors didn't get access to the patient's conversation log, so the exact wording that the large language model (LLM) generated is unknown. But the man reported that ChatGPT said chloride can be swapped for bromide, so he swapped all the sodium chloride in his diet with sodium bromide. The authors noted that this swap likely works in the context of using sodium bromide for cleaning, rather than dietary use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an attempt to simulate what might have happened with their patient, the man's doctors tried asking ChatGPT 3.5 what chloride can be replaced with, and they also got a response that included bromide. The LLM did note that "context matters," but it neither provided a specific health warning nor sought more context about why the question was being asked, "as we presume a medical professional would do," the authors wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-67532682-9d07-4ce6-9c09-069462d211fe" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="recovering-from-bromism-3"&gt;Recovering from bromism&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="b656ee7f-f5de-402e-bcb4-aca3b701b99e"&gt;After three months of consuming sodium bromide instead of table salt, the man reported to the emergency department with concerns that his neighbor was poisoning him. His labs at the time showed a buildup of carbon dioxide in his blood, as well as a rise in alkalinity (the opposite of acidity).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also appeared to have elevated levels of chloride in his blood but normal sodium levels. Upon further investigation, this turned out to be a case of "pseudohyperchloremia," meaning the lab test for chloride gave a false result because other compounds in the blood — namely, large amounts of bromide — had interfered with the measurement. After consulting the medical literature and Poison Control, the man's doctors determined the most likely diagnosis was bromism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-less-accurate-than-a-coin-toss-at-medical-diagnosis-new-study-finds" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/technology/artificial-intelligence/chatgpt-less-accurate-than-a-coin-toss-at-medical-diagnosis-new-study-finds"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ChatGPT is truly awful at diagnosing medical conditions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After being admitted for electrolyte monitoring and repletion, the man said he was very thirsty but was paranoid about the water he was offered. After a full day in the hospital, his paranoia intensified and he began experiencing hallucinations. He then tried to escape the hospital, which resulted in an involuntary psychiatric hold, during which he started receiving &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a694015.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://medlineplus.gov/druginfo/meds/a694015.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;an antipsychotic&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The man's vitals stabilized after he was given fluids and electrolytes, and as his mental state improved on the antipsychotic, he was able to inform the doctors about his use of ChatGPT. He also noted additional symptoms he'd noticed recently, such as facial acne and small red growths on his skin, which could be a hypersensitivity reaction to the bromide. He also noted insomnia, fatigue, muscle coordination issues and excessive thirst, "further suggesting bromism," his doctors wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was tapered off the antipsychotic medication over the course of three weeks and then discharged from the hospital. He remained stable at a check-in two weeks later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"While it is a tool with much potential to provide a bridge between scientists and the nonacademic population, AI also carries the risk for promulgating decontextualized information," the report authors concluded. "It is highly unlikely that a medical expert would have mentioned sodium bromide when faced with a patient looking for a viable substitute for sodium chloride."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="3ec76a9d-604d-42d3-954b-907c9363d997"&gt;They emphasized that, "as the use of AI tools increases, providers will need to consider this when screening for where their patients are consuming health information."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding to the concerns raised by the case report, a different group of scientists &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=livescience_us_5003716623671526018&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs43856-025-01021-3&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Ffood-diet%2Fman-sought-diet-advice-from-chatgpt-and-ended-up-with-bromide-intoxication" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43856-025-01021-3" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="skimlinks" data-placeholder-url="https://go.redirectingat.com/?id=92X1590019&amp;amp;xcust=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs43856-025-01021-3&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.livescience.com%2Fhealth%2Ffood-diet%2Fman-sought-diet-advice-from-chatgpt-and-ended-up-with-bromide-intoxication" data-google-interstitial="false" data-merchant-name="nature.com" data-merchant-network="SkimLinks"&gt;&lt;u&gt;recently tested six LLMs&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, including ChatGPT, by having the models interpret clinical notes written by doctors. They found that LLMs are "highly susceptible to adversarial hallucination attacks," meaning they often generate "false clinical details that pose risks when used without safeguards." Applying engineering fixes can reduce the rate of errors but does not eliminate them, the researchers found. This highlights another way in which LLMs could introduce risks into medical decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-freeText-jykgnzHdRz2jQTbn8sfNwS-MDmzy6EjtXN5ufalnkBk1wEsST0tlPiz" class="slice-container freeText-wrapper freeText-jykgnzHdRz2jQTbn8sfNwS-MDmzy6EjtXN5ufalnkBk1wEsST0tlPiz slice-container-freeText"&gt;&lt;div class="info-block"&gt;&lt;p class="infoDisclaimer"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and is not meant to offer medical or dietary advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 20:01:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxQaWpxenlEcEZ0NEVNUGtjMVdsY2ZmbnY5T1pPR2FpTmlubkIyR1JDMUxhSEQtUG9qZWJ5clFDajVnczlfVF9XeWxQS0VtUWpwNm9GWThWSkpvR0dFaDJTX3Ixb3QzYXBYalkxZWh0SEVsYUkxRnEzaG9oRE5kUC01dU5XZE00MGRMWXR6aHZfYjFBYUJQN3A5cEl4Q1BiQnBIa1lIRXVOZVdreTl1NlB6SHQxWWlKd3RLN2xj</guid></item><item><title>新凝胶可以在2周内治愈顽固的糖尿病伤口- Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxOYlVqSGl3ZFZISVdDME1PM183X2NDX3R0WVhDUGlwb2hTWDh1b2JOSU4tRUhBcFpoRmttWkZlRF9nQUJ1aUY5RTFHUWt0Sk9oYndZV181b1otd2dSRWNuRzZOdG81V0lXVGxwWktLQXpmLXlmbU1USkpDWVdFcndJN1J2SGxyREtuYkdMR2RERENhQVJqVmc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none"&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;For people with diabetes, high blood sugar can damage blood vessels and nerves, leading to chronic wounds that stay open for months. But a new gel-based treatment could massively speed up the healing process for people with diabetes, allowing wounds to close in just days, according to a new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-4 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The new treatment targets thrombospondin-1 (TSP-1), a protein that inhibits the growth of new blood vessels, a crucial step in the healing process. Targeting this protein increased new blood vessel formation in human endothelial cells and in diabetic mouse models, leading to a remarkable wound closure rate in less than two weeks. A team of researchers from various institutes in China unveiled the new technology in a study published in the journal &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/burnstrauma/advance-article/doi/10.1093/burnst/tkaf036/8161322"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Burns &amp;amp; Trauma&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Our results demonstrate the power of combining advanced tissue engineering with molecular biology. By targeting TSP-1 with miR-221OE-sEVs encapsulated in GelMA, we’ve not only improved endothelial cell function but also ensured a sustained and localized therapeutic effect,” Chuan’an Shen, a researcher at The Fourth Medical Center of Chinese PLA General Hospital, said in a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/08/250807233035.htm"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Diabetic wounds have increased levels of TSP-1 in endothelial cells, the cells that line blood vessels, according to previous studies. TSP-1 hinders their ability to divide and go where they need to go. The study researchers developed a way to decrease levels of TSP-1.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The technology uses small extracellular vesicles (sEVs)—teeny membrane-bound sacs usually released by cells—loaded with miR-221-3p, a microRNA that disrupts the production of TSP-1 in endothelial cells.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers encapsulated these sEVs in a hydrogel, which mimics the extracellular environment and provides a sustained, controlled release of miR-221-3p at the wound site. In diabetic mouse models, the gel significantly accelerated healing, leading to a 90% wound closure rate within 12 days—compared to just 20% in untreated mice over the same period.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The next steps are to bring the new gel into clinical trials, according to the authors. “This breakthrough could revolutionize how we approach diabetic wound care, with the potential to improve patients’ quality of life significantly,” Shen said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:55:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxOYlVqSGl3ZFZISVdDME1PM183X2NDX3R0WVhDUGlwb2hTWDh1b2JOSU4tRUhBcFpoRmttWkZlRF9nQUJ1aUY5RTFHUWt0Sk9oYndZV181b1otd2dSRWNuRzZOdG81V0lXVGxwWktLQXpmLXlmbU1USkpDWVdFcndJN1J2SGxyREtuYkdMR2RERENhQVJqVmc</guid></item><item><title>一旦“非常亲疫苗” ，特朗普对肯尼迪的mRNA切割不屑一顾-纽约时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTFA2SEN2VFc2TjdEUFU5djF1dXloU3dQMndSQ2MwUjVLQkNsREdyRmpvaUdwSmY5TDBlZVp5cVRiaU91aDhxMVVuSE1xRE1QblRiVENteU13OUplUUc4UWhlMWJfTzNFNHNfaW5IMm9ZVU5SbHp0WU1PUVBEdTR0SFE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:41:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFA2SEN2VFc2TjdEUFU5djF1dXloU3dQMndSQ2MwUjVLQkNsREdyRmpvaUdwSmY5TDBlZVp5cVRiaU91aDhxMVVuSE1xRE1QblRiVENteU13OUplUUc4UWhlMWJfTzNFNHNfaW5IMm9ZVU5SbHp0WU1PUVBEdTR0SFE</guid></item><item><title>HHS引用研究清单作为取消mRNA疫苗合同的科学理由- statnews.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPWUxWQ000LWI2amdtNmo0UzBaYW1ORHRPZzVvbEc2QTFhTWNjUGgyWF9Hdkd5NzFITGx2SUFmcDdoRG1sOVJZeWp4SEhXZ0ZqcXdkXzlOalY3Q0F3dGExWHdPTUxGbGFOMVRMR3B1cmlTQlBNdmp1VGlQSUhfWDBXZU5KUlBhRWZtRV9Z?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON — Federal health officials are citing an extensive list of studies purported to document harms caused by messenger RNA vaccines as scientific justification for &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/08/05/mrna-vaccine-development-canceled-by-kennedy-hhs/"&gt;canceling hundreds of millions of dollars in investment in the technology&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Health secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. provided only a brief explanation for the decision earlier this week, arguing the mRNA vaccines are not effective and not as safe as alternatives, and referencing a review of scientific research on mRNA by “experts,” without identifying them. On Friday, when asked if the Department of Health and Human Services had a scientific justification, a spokesperson provided a link to a 181-page &lt;a href="https://zenodo.org/records/15787612" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;list of studies&lt;/a&gt; compiled by a number of people, including a current Trump administration adviser who served in the president’s first administration and was the subject of controversy for pushing unproven Covid-19 treatments. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The other contributors are people who have all previously criticized Covid-19 public health interventions, such as lockdowns and mRNA vaccines. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Taken together, the studies cited generally appear to advance research that has been disputed by other scientists, who argue that mRNA vaccines are overwhelmingly safe.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The list appears to have been initially used as research for the publication of a 2024 book titled “Toxic Shot: Facing the Dangers of the COVID ‘Vaccines.’” A note at the top of the document said the list had last been updated on July 1. One of the named authors of the book, Byram Bridle, is among the individuals who compiled the citation list that HHS sent to STAT.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Another person credited on the list is HHS adviser &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2025/05/04/hatfill-covid-hydroxychloroquine-anthrax/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Steven Hatfill&lt;/a&gt;, a virologist who was criticized during Trump’s first administration  in the first administration for recommending hydroxychloroquine as a Covid-19 treatment, despite a lack of evidence to show its effectiveness. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In a video announcement Tuesday, Kennedy said he was directing the Biomedical Advanced Research and Development Authority, better known as BARDA, to begin canceling 22 grants &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/08/05/mrna-vaccine-development-canceled-by-kennedy-hhs/"&gt;supporting development of mRNA vaccines&lt;/a&gt;, totaling $500 million in research. Instead, he said, the administration would support research using a &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/05/03/nih-500-million-univeral-flu-vaccine-project-uses-old-technology/"&gt;whole killed virus approach&lt;/a&gt; to develop vaccines. That approach has been advanced by the deputy director of the National Institutes of Health, Matthew Memoli, and the acting director of the National Institute for Allergy and Infectious Diseases, Jeffery Taubenberger.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The announcement alarmed many public health experts, who say that mRNA vaccine technology, first used to develop Covid vaccines, saved countless lives during the pandemic in part because it can be used to deliver shots far faster than other approaches.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The list shared by HHS includes references to a number of studies purportedly showing that, by training the immune system to recognize spike proteins produced by a Covid-19 infection, the spike protein produced by an mRNA vaccine is “harmful by itself, independent of the rest of the virus.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Other Covid vaccines that don’t use mRNA technology also train the immune system to detect and protect against the SARS-CoV-2 spike protein. And any individual who has been infected with Covid will have encountered the spike protein as well.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Beyond Hatfill, the list’s contributors include Martin Wucher, a dentist based in Namibia, who was described in media reports as a onetime member of &lt;a href="https://www.namibian.com.na/health-legal-professions-unhappy-with-govt-over-covid-19-handling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;the Health Defence League&lt;/a&gt;, a group that criticized Covid lockdowns in the African country, as well as Bridle, a viral immunologist.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Another contributor, Erik Sass, who has also argued hydroxychloroquine is an effective Covid treatment, told STAT via email that the list is “general reference for interested researchers,” and it originated as a supplement to the book co-authored by Bridle. That book includes a foreword by Sen. Ron Johnson (R-Wisc.), who has &lt;a href="https://www.hsgac.senate.gov/wp-content/uploads/2025.05.21-Chair-Johnson-Opening-Statement.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;invited vaccine critics to Capitol Hill&lt;/a&gt; previously to testify on the safety of vaccines. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Helen Branswell contributed reporting.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:28:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPWUxWQ000LWI2amdtNmo0UzBaYW1ORHRPZzVvbEc2QTFhTWNjUGgyWF9Hdkd5NzFITGx2SUFmcDdoRG1sOVJZeWp4SEhXZ0ZqcXdkXzlOalY3Q0F3dGExWHdPTUxGbGFOMVRMR3B1cmlTQlBNdmp1VGlQSUhfWDBXZU5KUlBhRWZtRV9Z</guid></item><item><title>研究人员：少量锂可能有助于预防阿尔茨海默氏症-upi.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimwFBVV95cUxQQmoycTRIV3AzOUFILUFjdzM2MzctQzlTYkVpVW5obC1EbEV1cTRuWC1xX3BBMC1tWWJERTg2ZjFvMWs3aUlqNWE2SkQzZmJkYXhWbmtKdWNPTXF5ZTQtdzdwQjJsZFdrdzktVzFscXhiQ3EtaDA3d1FiYkZ6VUQzZnk5dXVKRldEQ0Z2REkzLVVRWXE5MGlqNW0tcw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="stph_caption"&gt;A Harvard Medical School and Rush University study suggests tiny amounts of lithium may help protect the brain from Alzheimer's and signs of aging. Photo by Adobe Stock/HealthDay News&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;article itemprop="articleBody"&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tiny amounts of lithium -- a natural metal -- may help protect the brain from &lt;a href="https://www.healthday.com/a-to-z-health/neurology/alzheimers-disease-what-it-is-causes-symptoms-stages-treatments-prevention" target="_blank"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; and signs of aging, new research shows.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists at Harvard Medical School and Rush University found that when mice were fed a low-lithium diet, their brains developed more inflammation and signs of aging accelerated.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings were published Wednesday in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-09335-x" target="_blank"&gt;Nature&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Turns out, lithium may play a critical role in how the brain stays healthy, the researchers found.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the study, they compared normal mice to mice bred to develop brain changes linked to Alzheimer's, including a build-up of sticky proteins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mice on low-lithium diets developed problems more quickly, while those given a specific lithium compound called lithium orotate saw signs of brain improvement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When given lithium orotate, mice had fewer memory problems and fewer of the sticky clumps known as beta amyloid plaques. In people, those plaques are hallmarks of Alzheimer's.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people know lithium as a drug used to treat bipolar disorder and &lt;a href="https://www.healthday.com/a-to-z-health/mental-health/how-to-deal-with-depression-2659464053.html" target="_blank"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;. It's been used for decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But this study suggests that very small amounts of lithium are naturally present in the body, and it may be essential for brain health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers suspect that beta amyloid binds to lithium and prevents it from reaching brain cells that need it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Without enough lithium, cells called microglia, which help clean up waste in the brain, stop working properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This creates a sort of cycle: As beta amyloid builds up, even less lithium is available and the brain has a harder time clearing the damaging proteins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the first stage of the study, scientists tested brain tissue and blood samples from people with and without Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They looked at 27 metals and found a key difference: Lithium levels were much lower in the brains of people with memory problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They repeated this test using brain samples from multiple hospitals and universities and found the same results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"At first, frankly, we were skeptical of the result because it wasn't expected," &lt;a href="https://yankner.hms.harvard.edu/people/bruce-yankner" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Bruce Yankner&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of genetics at Harvard, told CNN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Experts warn that people should not take lithium supplements without medical advice. The doses used in this study were about 1,000 times lower than the doses used to treat mental illnesses such as bipolar disorder.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"A mouse is not a human. Nobody should take anything based just on mouse studies," Yankner said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The lithium treatment data we have is in mice, and it needs to be replicated in humans. We need to find the right dose in humans," he added.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Still, the findings are promising. Mice who received low doses of lithium orotate did not show any signs of toxicity or organ damage. Yankner hopes human trials will start soon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many healthy foods contain small amounts of lithium. These include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leafy green vegetables&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nuts and legumes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Certain spices like turmeric and cumin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some mineral waters&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previous studies have hinted at lithium's benefits. One large Danish &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28832877/" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found people with higher lithium levels in their tap water were less likely to be diagnosed with &lt;a href="https://www.healthday.com/a-to-z-health/caregiving/caregiving-for-someone-with-dementia" target="_blank"&gt;dementia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8929585/#:~:text=We%20found%20that%20lithium%20was,with%20either%20AD%20or%20VD." target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; in the U.K. found people prescribed lithium were about half as likely to get Alzheimer's as those who were not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://florey.edu.au/researcher/ashley-bush/" target="_blank"&gt;Ashley Bush&lt;/a&gt;, a neuroscientist in Australia, wrote an editorial that accompanied the new research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He said it presents "compelling evidence that lithium does in fact have a physiological role and that normal aging might impair the regulation of lithium levels in the brain."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yankner pointed to the possible benefit.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It is a potential candidate for a common mechanism leading to the multisystem degeneration of the brain that precedes dementia," he told CNN.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It will take a lot more science to determine whether this is a common pathway... or one of several pathways," to Alzheimer's, he added. "The data are very intriguing."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;More information&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Mayo Clinic has more on &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/drugs-supplements/lithium-oral-route/description/drg-20064603" target="_blank"&gt;lithium&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Copyright © 2025 HealthDay. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class="lazy" data-src="https://www.upi.com/img/healthday.jpg"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
			&lt;/article&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>upi.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:26:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQQmoycTRIV3AzOUFILUFjdzM2MzctQzlTYkVpVW5obC1EbEV1cTRuWC1xX3BBMC1tWWJERTg2ZjFvMWs3aUlqNWE2SkQzZmJkYXhWbmtKdWNPTXF5ZTQtdzdwQjJsZFdrdzktVzFscXhiQ3EtaDA3d1FiYkZ6VUQzZnk5dXVKRldEQ0Z2REkzLVVRWXE5MGlqNW0tcw</guid></item><item><title>人们担心潜在的癌症与Ozempic等药物的联系- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgFBVV95cUxOal9qMmZjTW1SUGtKQlhERnNTdnI3WGJYcUJnSW1kR1g2eHlDNGkyZ2FZc25JajFzdVVweFhqM0tISTlPVG9vT3F2cTNPcEh6UFdQX19YcmVPMDdGSjdOOURDRUhrOG9NeUdsb25SR09yWTMyU3A1MmpwRDkxdktORmlQTzFncnBIUjRna0RIMERzY0huc2R0NS1B?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;So many people in western countries are turning to weight loss drugs such as Wegovy/Ozempic and Mounjaro that concerns have &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/weight-loss-drug-demand-continues-to-grow-in-the-uk-heres-whats-being-done-to-keep-supplies-readily-available-262065"&gt;started to emerge&lt;/a&gt; about maintaining ready supplies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But with popularity comes scrutiny, and rising demand isn't the only potential problem with weight loss jabs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gastrointestinal side-effects such as nausea, vomiting and constipation are common across these drugs, which are known as GLP-1 receptor agonists. Then there's the now infamous "&lt;a href="https://www.jprasurg.com/article/S1748-6815(23)00214-0/abstract"&gt;Ozempic face&lt;/a&gt;" – a gaunt, aged appearance that can result from rapid weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ozempic-type-drugs-may-trigger-brain-changes-linked-to-depression"&gt;Ozempic-Type Drugs May Trigger Brain Changes Linked to Depression&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_163853" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-163853" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/chewing_gum_ozempic_642.jpg" alt="Weight-Loss Drugs Like Ozempic Can Leave Lasting Damage in Your Mouth" class="wp-image-163853 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/chewing_gum_ozempic_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/chewing_gum_ozempic_642-600x388.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-163853" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;These drugs can also leave you with a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/weight-loss-drugs-like-ozempic-can-leave-lasting-damage-in-your-mouth"&gt;dry mouth&lt;/a&gt;. Chewing gum can help. (Eva-Katalin/Getty Images Signature/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;More serious concerns have also begun to surface, including possible links to &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/14740338.2024.2419989"&gt;eye disease&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12144364/"&gt;reduced libido&lt;/a&gt; and a potential increased risk of certain cancers. However, we're still in the early days of understanding what the risks might be and the evidence for them is limited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most significant cancer-related worry is thyroid  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="170682" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;. Studies in rodents found that high doses of GLP-1 drugs caused thyroid tumors, although this &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/endocrinology/articles/10.3389/fendo.2022.927859/full"&gt;hasn't been definitively proven in humans&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, a &lt;a href="https://diabetesjournals.org/care/article/46/2/384/147888/GLP-1-Receptor-Agonists-and-the-Risk-of-Thyroid"&gt;large-scale French study&lt;/a&gt; did find a potential link between GLP-1 use and thyroid cancer, especially in patients who used the drug for more than a year. As a precaution, these medications are not recommended for people with a personal or family history of thyroid cancer or specific genetic conditions that increase the risk of thyroid tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have also been concerns about pancreatic cancer, mostly because of early reports of pancreatitis: inflammation of the pancreas, which can, in some cases, be fatal. However, current studies have not confirmed a direct link between GLP-1 drugs and pancreatic cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Concerns here are particularly relevant because of how the drugs work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-discover-a-viral-cause-of-one-of-the-worlds-most-common-cancers"&gt;Scientists Discover a Viral Cause of One of The World's Most Common Cancers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wegovy and Ozempic are brand names for a type of GLP-1 receptor agonist known as semaglutide. Originally developed to treat type 2  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="170682" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, it works by activating receptors in the pancreas to increase insulin release and reduce glucagon – a hormone that raises blood sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, these effects help lower blood-sugar levels. The weight loss effects come from the drug's ability to act on &lt;a href="https://diabetesjournals.org/diabetes/article/63/12/4186/40422/GLP-1-Receptor-Activation-Modulates-Appetite-and"&gt;receptors in the brain&lt;/a&gt; as well as in &lt;a href="https://diabetesjournals.org/diabetes/article/60/5/1561/33533/Rapid-Tachyphylaxis-of-the-Glucagon-Like-Peptide-1"&gt;gut&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.jbc.org/article/S0021-9258(20)61128-0/fulltext"&gt;fat cells&lt;/a&gt;, to help to reduce appetite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mounjaro (the brand name for the compound tirzepatide) takes things a step further. It works not only on the GLP-1 receptor but also on a second one – the GIP (glucose-dependent insulinotropic polypeptide) receptor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By stimulating both, tirzepatide &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jcem/article/106/2/388/6000489"&gt;boosts the pancreas's ability to produce insulin&lt;/a&gt; and improves insulin sensitivity – meaning the body's cells respond more effectively to insulin, helping regulate blood sugar more efficiently. This &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s12982-024-00200-2"&gt;dual action&lt;/a&gt; results in even greater weight loss than semaglutide alone, making Mounjaro the latest star in the fight against obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tirzepatide has not been associated with increased cancer risk in  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="170682" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; so far. However, like other GLP-1 drugs, it still carries the thyroid cancer warning based on earlier animal research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, preliminary studies in animals suggest tirzepatide might even &lt;a href="https://journals.lww.com/oncology-times/fulltext/2024/07000/tirzepatide__weight_loss_treatment_shows_promise.22.aspx?context=latestarticles&amp;amp;casa_token=oXuRRSYN6rkAAAAA:mpuDWTwDhd2nDND16AvRXkfITcSC8YGg0b0cxpPHlnBH4JmnK06U7P03gIIw70JlBK6F6_P9UE7tYWRSwISS4h-qMViEMg&amp;amp;casa_token=giULyz6VeZMAAAAA:hnyZdH9xXehdKQ4HLHQLm2pq-fD05S87AWphjZxPRZd8MA54bYLyMVDk3Evg9p3UxqkTgCEeH5xDeSNLvYrIcFw1J7dGUg"&gt;shrink certain tumors&lt;/a&gt;, including breast cancer, but these findings are still very early and not yet applicable to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_169031" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-169031" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/WeightLoss.jpg" alt="Graph showing how your weight can bounce back once you stop Ozempic" class="wp-image-169031 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/WeightLoss.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/WeightLoss-488x415.jpg 488w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/WeightLoss-600x510.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-169031" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Weight &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/weight-comes-back-when-you-stop-taking-drugs-like-ozempic-study-finds"&gt;tends to bounce back&lt;/a&gt; once you stop taking these drugs. (&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12916-025-04200-0"&gt;Wu et al., &lt;em&gt;BMC Med.,&lt;/em&gt; 2025&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Obesity is also a cancer risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to remember that obesity itself is a well established risk factor for several cancers, including breast, colon, liver and uterine cancers. By helping people lose significant amounts of weight and improve their metabolic health, GLP-1 drugs could indirectly reduce the risk of developing these conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, some &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6694/17/1/78"&gt;population studies&lt;/a&gt; have found lower rates of obesity-related cancers in people using GLP-1 medications compared to those taking other treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it's still unclear whether the reduced cancer risk comes from the drug's action or from the weight loss itself. More research is needed to fully understand this connection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, the current picture is reassuring, yet tinged with uncertainty. The overall cancer risk associated with GLP-1 drugs and tirzepatide appears to be low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it's important to emphasize that these medications are not recommended for people with a personal or family history of certain types of &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jcem/article/110/6/e2080/7821115?login=true#no-access-message#no-access-message"&gt;thyroid cancer, or also endocrine conditions&lt;/a&gt; such as multiple endocrine neoplasia syndrome, because these conditions may increase sensitivity to hormone-related tumor growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Weight-loss injections are not risk free, but they also hold enormous potential. It remains to be unraveled whether they're miracle cures or just the latest chapter in the long saga of weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One thing is certain: the conversation is far from over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These drugs are rewriting the rules on how we think about weight, health, and risk. In the battle to outsmart the scales, they offer hope, science and a fair bit of gamble amidst the hype.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/262146/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/nadine-wehida-2438437"&gt;Nadine Wehida&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer in Genetics and Molecular Biology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/kingston-university-949"&gt;Kingston University&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/ahmed-elbediwy-2418189"&gt;Ahmed Elbediwy&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer in Clinical Biochemistry / Cancer Biology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/kingston-university-949"&gt;Kingston University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/weight-loss-jabs-and-cancer-risk-heres-what-you-need-to-know-about-the-research-so-far-262146"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 19:04:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxOal9qMmZjTW1SUGtKQlhERnNTdnI3WGJYcUJnSW1kR1g2eHlDNGkyZ2FZc25JajFzdVVweFhqM0tISTlPVG9vT3F2cTNPcEh6UFdQX19YcmVPMDdGSjdOOURDRUhrOG9NeUdsb25SR09yWTMyU3A1MmpwRDkxdktORmlQTzFncnBIUjRna0RIMERzY0huc2R0NS1B</guid></item><item><title>随着病例激增，致命的食肉细菌蔓延到整个海滩-每日邮报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixwFBVV95cUxOT1RqZmRJTmhmT3Z6SFFzN1I0Y2p6VXJiZ1ZZZ0R2ZTFCM01JNlVvUnhGVGdqa1FxaDFsT05PeHZERldNNE1rMUdZSFBUcnprZlBtMHk4SmNnOXhYSkxtN1hvY19QZk1pYmxSVGZuZkdmOUg5NXBjcXAtdDBIZ2lnWW5oVThsZlhFZTJmcnNmSDZITGVBQVZPcjc1cEd5eU9nVUhaOXpJX3FWUjR4Y2pNT3FJNFMtRWNKclZhamVFQ3YtemlGTHpR0gHMAUFVX3lxTE5RY1ktTEpuaUczbmNPU0taOWdiZWZVTDhlNS1VbnF1U1U5ZVVfeGd4S3RMZ1M1MlVuTENBbmh0ZkpRQUcwMV8zSUU4clV4MWlWTmljOEhRdDVZWWFvbzZnNmpLUUdjMEdjNVhFU3BWNlRwTlhOeTlTZlNxa19ELTdXcVBvZG1reVdsX0hqcDllSm04aGVlY0FIUnRWaldfblBDaFM3WTlYS2ptV3pHZm9BeGZvQjUyYVBTVlk0dDFfUDRKb2VKY2VQSXYtMw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The threat posed by flesh-eating bacteria lurking on beaches and in rivers this summer is looming larger by the week, as cases climb into the double digits and deaths are following suit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Vibrio vulnificus eats away at tissues in the skin until they shrivel, turn black, and die, a condition called necrotizing fasciitis, requiring lengthy surgery to strip the dead skin from the patient’s body or amputation to remove the limb to save the person's life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The bacteria typically populates the waters off the Gulf Coast, but has slowly made its way northward, appearing in the waters off &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/north-carolina/index.html" id="mol-786c5590-7465-11f0-8b23-81ab9c3d81ee" class=""&gt;North Carolina&lt;/a&gt;, where it has infected 59 people and killed one since January 1, according to state health records. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="/news/florida/index.html" id="mol-786a0ba0-7465-11f0-8b23-81ab9c3d81ee"&gt;Florida&lt;/a&gt;, meanwhile, has reported 16 cases this year and a death toll of five. And &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/louisiana/index.html" id="mol-786b6b30-7465-11f0-8b23-81ab9c3d81ee"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt; health officials have reported 17 cases of Vibrio vulnificus so far this year, four of which have proven fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Deadly bacteria living in coastal and brackish waters (a mix of fresh and salt water) can infect swimmers &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-12628269/The-skin-gone-just-bone-Woman-72-leg-amputated-catching-flesh-eating-bacteria-Vibrio-vulnificus-swimming-coast-Florida.html"&gt;through open wounds&lt;/a&gt; or strike unsuspecting diners who eat raw or undercooked seafood like oysters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Health experts warn the bug can cause everything from nasty bouts of stomach illness to dangerous wound infections and, in the most severe cases, it can trigger life-threatening blood poisoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The bacteria’s steady rise is, experts believe, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-13033607/cdc-deadly-flesh-eating-bacterial-infection-climate-change.html"&gt;a consequence of warming&lt;/a&gt; waters. The bacteria thrive in waters between 68 degrees Fahrenheit and 95 degrees Fahrenheit (20 degrees Celsius to 35 degrees Celsius).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These temperatures are becoming more common as the planet warms, and as ocean temperatures rise, Vibrio is spreading further north and remaining on coasts longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;V. vulnificus thrives in warm coastal waters, such as Florida Gulf Coast beaches. In Florida, 16 people have been infected and five have died&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Worsening storms and flooding are also washing the bacteria into freshwater, putting swimmers and seafood lovers at higher risk. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While Florida's tally thus far falls short of the annual average of 48 cases and 11 deaths, in Louisiana, the state's averages for both have been dwarfed by the current figures. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There have been 17 cases so far this year, including four deaths. By comparison, an average of seven V. vulnificus cases and one death have been reported each year in Louisiana &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://ldh.la.gov/news/vibrio-vulnificus-2025"&gt;over the previous 10 years&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;All 17 patients have been hospitalized, according to the Louisiana Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Texas saw an average number of Vibrio cases of about 33 per year from 2015 to 2019, the latest year available. Annually, cases have fluctuated between 22 to 36. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2019 in Texas, Adam Perez, 42, was hospitalized and lost most of the flesh on the lower half of his right leg after a dangerous dip in Waters Edge Park in Corpus Christi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He had to undergo four different life-saving surgeries, including skin grafts over his leg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘This is a very scary-sounding bacteria, Vibrio vulnificus. Fortunately, it is rare, but it can be very deadly,’ Dr Alok Patel, a pediatrician at Stanford Children's Health, told &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/deadly-flesh-eating-bacteria-cases-rise-gulf-coast/story?id=124296398"&gt;ABC News&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption" aria-label="To enrich screen reader interactions, please activate Accessibility in Grammarly extension settings"&gt;The CDC map shows cases of V. vulnificus in 2019, when the US reported a total of 194 cases. The bacteria typically populates the waters off the Gulf Coast, but the map shows that it has slowly made its way northward &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Vibrio kills, on average, 20 percent of its victims, though in people with compromised immune systems, that figure jumps to at least 30 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In severe cases, when it causes sepsis or necrotizing fasciitis, the risk of death climbs to 70 percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 80 percent of people who become infected contract it from contact with seawater, while 20 percent of infections are caused by consumption of raw seafood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 150 to 200 V. vulnificus infections are reported to the CDC each year and trends suggest cases are rising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A sweeping review of CDC data from 1988 to 2018 revealed that Vibrio wound infections on the East Coast surged eightfold, from about 10 to over 80 cases per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rachel Noble, a microbiologist at UNC-Chapel Hill’s Institute of Marine Sciences, &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://college.unc.edu/inthemedia/flesh-eating-bacteria/"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;: ‘Every water sample we collect along the [North Carolina] coast now contains some kind of Vibrio. That wasn’t true two decades ago.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When V. vulnificus is not fatal, it still can leave lifelong complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When it enters a wound, the bacteria proliferate quickly and release toxins that tear tissue and blood vessels apart. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;After Adam Perez stuck his toes into some water at a Corpus Christi park, his foot and leg swelled enormously and a giant blister formed, due to vibriosis &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Perez had strolled into Waters Edge Park in Corpus Christi and dipped his toes into some water there&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The infection can penetrate deeper layers of the skin, muscle, and bloodstream in a matter of hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;From there, the skin develops blisters and open sores. It becomes red, then purple, then black. Blood pressure plummets, and the body becomes feverish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If the bacteria enter the bloodstream, they cause sepsis, a life-threatening condition that ravages the organs until they fail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Urgent medical care is needed to stop this process in its tracks, including antibiotics, emergency surgery to remove the dead tissue, and, potentially, amputation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:39:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxOT1RqZmRJTmhmT3Z6SFFzN1I0Y2p6VXJiZ1ZZZ0R2ZTFCM01JNlVvUnhGVGdqa1FxaDFsT05PeHZERldNNE1rMUdZSFBUcnprZlBtMHk4SmNnOXhYSkxtN1hvY19QZk1pYmxSVGZuZkdmOUg5NXBjcXAtdDBIZ2lnWW5oVThsZlhFZTJmcnNmSDZITGVBQVZPcjc1cEd5eU9nVUhaOXpJX3FWUjR4Y2pNT3FJNFMtRWNKclZhamVFQ3YtemlGTHpR0gHMAUFVX3lxTE5RY1ktTEpuaUczbmNPU0taOWdiZWZVTDhlNS1VbnF1U1U5ZVVfeGd4S3RMZ1M1MlVuTENBbmh0ZkpRQUcwMV8zSUU4clV4MWlWTmljOEhRdDVZWWFvbzZnNmpLUUdjMEdjNVhFU3BWNlRwTlhOeTlTZlNxa19ELTdXcVBvZG1reVdsX0hqcDllSm04aGVlY0FIUnRWaldfblBDaFM3WTlYS2ptV3pHZm9BeGZvQjUyYVBTVlk0dDFfUDRKb2VKY2VQSXYtMw</guid></item><item><title>令人惊叹的模拟显示，当您停止食用糖两周时，您的身体会发生什么- LADbible</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxPZFVCWUlvdFA1bjRRR2FLeVhMVE9pSVRoTURkRG1zY2dZZm1YMnhnY082YWVNYmxwTFlwQVdoWDJaMGgxb0hxYnJxaUFjU3MxX2VRaG5PeW1QZWp1cHIyMklFWk5yN3BsakstYVhSLUdDNGpCZTNybWhaWWxXSXdfX3kwNnJUc2JrazBnYTNnbDNYeEF2MnpiaHBGYkJLWlk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;A jaw-dropping simulation shows what happens to your body when you cut out sugar for two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Yeah, that’s another one of those lifestyle changes that’s constantly doing the rounds on &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/social-media"&gt;social media&lt;/a&gt; despite different people having different &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Eating too much sugar can cause you to gain weight and can also have a bad impact on our teeth but there’s a difference in the types you consume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It’s widely agreed that the sugars most adults and kids in the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/uk-news"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt; eat too much of are ‘free sugars’ - those added to &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/food-and-drink"&gt;food and drinks&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;But the sugar naturally found in milk, fruit and vegetables don’t count as ‘free sugars’ on the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/nhs"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; says: “We do not need to cut down on these sugars.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;But for dietary reasons or to follow trends, some people decide to go about totally cutting sugar out of their life, and this is what will happen to your body if you do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Reckon you'd manage two weeks without sugar? (Getty Stock)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Days one and two&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;A simulation from &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.youtube.com/shorts/tqldDuN4Y5Y"&gt;GrowFit Health&lt;/a&gt; (not a professional medical outlet) breaks down the changes in the body over time without sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;And in the first two days it says your ‘blood sugars starts to stabilise’ and you’ll experience ‘lesser energy crashes or sudden spikes’.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“Your body stored fat for energy,” it adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Days three to six&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;You might find yourself craving sugar the longer you go, but experts say that if you manage to resist, then those cravings will get weaker and eventually disappear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Healthline &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.healthline.com/health/sugar-detox-symptoms#symptoms"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt; that you could experience low mood due to reduced dopamine release, anxiety, changes in sleep patterns, difficulty concentrating, and cravings for carbs on top of sugary foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;You could also be hit with headaches, lightheadedness, nausea and fatigue - that's why it can be helpful for some people to gradually cut sugar out rather than going cold turkey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“[These symptoms are] because your body is detoxifying and adjusting and these symptoms will pass,” the simulation says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Days seven to nine&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;By this point, it says your taste buds experience ‘a reset’.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“Your palate becomes sensitive to subtle flavours,” the simulation claims, “and you’ll find fruits tasting extra sweet.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Days 10 to 14&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Approaching the end of the two weeks, it claims your energy ‘shoots up’ and you’ll notice there won’t be any ‘sugar crashes’.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“Just steady, clean fuel as your body becomes more efficient at burning fats for your fuel,” it concludes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How much sugar is too much for adults?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;If you want to go about making dietary changes like this one, it’s important to check out legitimate medical health advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The UK government recommends that free sugars (sugars added to food and drinks and sugars found naturally in honey syrups and unsweetened fruit and vegetable juices, smoothies and purees) shouldn’t make up more than five percent of the energy you get from food and drink each day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;So, the NHS says adults shouldn’t have more than 30g of free sugars a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;If you do plan to cut out those 'free sugars', it might be better to take it slowly and have lower amounts of sugar before no sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It's also important that you ensure you're still getting enough nutrients in your diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:34:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPZFVCWUlvdFA1bjRRR2FLeVhMVE9pSVRoTURkRG1zY2dZZm1YMnhnY082YWVNYmxwTFlwQVdoWDJaMGgxb0hxYnJxaUFjU3MxX2VRaG5PeW1QZWp1cHIyMklFWk5yN3BsakstYVhSLUdDNGpCZTNybWhaWWxXSXdfX3kwNnJUc2JrazBnYTNnbDNYeEF2MnpiaHBGYkJLWlk</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心表示，美国大部分地区的COVID水平上升，其中西部地区最高- CBS新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMigwFBVV95cUxQYnVkQ1VmUklYdWVjLUtoZDExcjF2ekdpS05LYW1XT192Tnd4aFk1cS1ldGlfajdURFVpZG9JMnNSQ01ONWxZb0VVbU52T3I2RFNnTGFtVTA1dldjSnpYV3BLcVZQN2lrdU9wQ01PN1lyQm5RRjJuMU45a1YtcEdPVkp0NNIBiAFBVV95cUxNanNyNWN0T3lBaXBuV2ZIQ1c5TjdYVkhQSWowZERLd2dZcFlBQjJ1WTVKOTFjTGZzXzF2cUhJd2J0Q2E1d2JaQ3JKTzNzbG1HS1MxVGhiSmJFTzNzSmhLOFk5WXNha1JIVy16VlZFNzJEOERnbVNLdmpMdlg5MGVLUEg2Ukhtdl9u?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;The &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-cases-rise-summer-2025-cdc-data/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;summer surge of COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; doesn't appear to be slowing down — instead, a key indicator for tracking the spread of the virus has increased, according to the latest data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nwss/rv/COVID19-national-data.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;In an update&lt;/a&gt; shared Friday, official data showed wastewater activity for COVID-19 is now at a "moderate" level nationwide, up from "low" the previous week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wastewater levels for the virus are currently the highest in the Western U.S., the data also showed. States in this region showing high levels include: Alaska, California, Colorado, Nevada and Utah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Wastewater monitoring can detect viruses spreading from one person to another within a community earlier than clinical testing and before people who are sick go to their doctor or hospital," the CDC notes. "If you see increased wastewater viral activity levels, it might indicate that there is a higher risk of infection."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other metrics are also showing increases in the illness. As of Tuesday, the CDC estimates COVID-19 infections are &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/cfa-modeling-and-forecasting/rt-estimates/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;growing or likely growing in 45 states&lt;/a&gt;, which is up from 40 states last week. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And although the weekly percentage of emergency room visits for COVID-19 is overall low — compared to the week before, ER visits for the infection &lt;a href="https://covid.cdc.gov/covid-data-tracker/#maps_percent-covid-ed" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;have also risen&lt;/a&gt; from last week.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the nation saw the number of COVID cases increase last month, CBS News chief medical correspondent &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-cases-rise-summer-2025-cdc-data/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Dr. Jon LaPook told "CBS Mornings"&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that this is typical of what we've come to understand about summer spikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We now know that there's a winter spike and then there's a summer spike," he said at the time. "And every year, the number of deaths, the number of hospitalizations, is gradually going down each season. So that's the good news."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, people shouldn't ignore the increases, he said, adding if it strikes — especially those vulnerable like the elderly, young people and those immunocompromised — as they can still get really sick. &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
        
    

    &lt;aside class="component list recirculation component--type-recirculation component--type-recirculation-collection"&gt;
                    
                                            
        &lt;div class="component__heading-wrapper"&gt;
          &lt;h3 class="component__title"&gt;Coronavirus Pandemic
                          &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/feature/coronavirus/?intcid=CNI-00-10aaa3a" class="component__view-more component__view-more--lg" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;
                More
                &lt;svg viewbox="0 0 32 32" class="icon__caret-right" aria-hidden="true"&gt;
                  &lt;use xlink:href="#icon-caret-down"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
                &lt;/svg&gt;
              &lt;/a&gt;
                      &lt;/h3&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;

        
                    &lt;/aside&gt;


    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/sara-moniuszko/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Sara  Moniuszko&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Sara Moniuszko is a health and lifestyle reporter at CBSNews.com. Previously, she wrote for USA Today, where she was selected to help launch the newspaper's wellness vertical. She now covers breaking and trending news for CBS News' HealthWatch.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 18:30:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxQYnVkQ1VmUklYdWVjLUtoZDExcjF2ekdpS05LYW1XT192Tnd4aFk1cS1ldGlfajdURFVpZG9JMnNSQ01ONWxZb0VVbU52T3I2RFNnTGFtVTA1dldjSnpYV3BLcVZQN2lrdU9wQ01PN1lyQm5RRjJuMU45a1YtcEdPVkp0NNIBiAFBVV95cUxNanNyNWN0T3lBaXBuV2ZIQ1c5TjdYVkhQSWowZERLd2dZcFlBQjJ1WTVKOTFjTGZzXzF2cUhJd2J0Q2E1d2JaQ3JKTzNzbG1HS1MxVGhiSmJFTzNzSmhLOFk5WXNha1JIVy16VlZFNzJEOERnbVNLdmpMdlg5MGVLUEg2Ukhtdl9u</guid></item><item><title>责任心令人不安的下降- Slashdot</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxPbmlsMzdxX1dfb3o4bU5lT0dKTUMzdm5ydGQ3ZWVtUFJXZWdpeHFOMXh3eGxhLW02UXpGWTA4UmY5U2pReXJvNHhvNkhWUFNWOV9rUGRZOWUtNFlfUlA0NE9wYXNMaEZ6T1VLUTV3dGFVNkx3bmVBYUhmTXpUMXpiZHpnMzRvSC1qclZLeWRnU0t2eEFTQmc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body" id="fhbody-178615758"&gt;
	
		
	

	
		
		&lt;div id="text-178615758" class="p"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
			
		 	
				Conscientiousness levels among young adults have &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/5cd77ef0-b546-4105-8946-36db3f84dc43"&gt;fallen substantially since 2014&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; as people in their twenties and thirties report increased distractibility and carelessness alongside decreased tenacity and commitment-making, according to Financial Times analysis of Understanding America Study data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

The personality trait, which research links to longer lifespans, career success, and relationship durability, has witnessed its steepest decline during and after the pandemic. Young adults simultaneously showed rising neuroticism scores and declining extroversion measures, transforming from society's most outgoing age group to its most introverted.
		 	
		&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

		

		

		
			
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slashdot</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:52:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPbmlsMzdxX1dfb3o4bU5lT0dKTUMzdm5ydGQ3ZWVtUFJXZWdpeHFOMXh3eGxhLW02UXpGWTA4UmY5U2pReXJvNHhvNkhWUFNWOV9rUGRZOWUtNFlfUlA0NE9wYXNMaEZ6T1VLUTV3dGFVNkx3bmVBYUhmTXpUMXpiZHpnMzRvSC1qclZLeWRnU0t2eEFTQmc</guid></item><item><title>当音乐消失时：为什么有些大脑不喜欢音乐-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTFBxSnJBNWNCajdkVS1wN2NlSGZIWG5PNjVQY2JUQzY5bVBDaUY2OF93dzJqMzIxQ3RQRzRLSUVXUmVUeGJqZ3ZrX2hTQXh2RGpoUXB2bkY4ZGNiR0E3c1FGRHA2Um9fRXdhd2liQTRpRXFUMWt6MHhxeFhKWVZkUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Some people feel absolutely nothing when listening to music—and not because of bad taste. A rare condition called specific musical anhedonia involves a disconnect between the brain’s auditory and reward systems, making music emotionally flat even though other rewards like food or money still trigger pleasure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New insights from researchers explore how this condition reveals the nuanced ways our brain processes different types of rewards. It challenges the idea that our reward system is all-or-nothing, and opens doors to studying other highly specific anhedonias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Auditory-Reward Disconnect:&lt;/strong&gt; People with musical anhedonia have intact hearing and reward circuits, but the two don’t communicate effectively during music.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Selective Pleasure Deficit:&lt;/strong&gt; These individuals enjoy other rewards like food or money, showing the deficit is music-specific.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Broader Implications:&lt;/strong&gt; The condition may point to other “specific anhedonias,” offering new ways to study reward processing and tailor treatments for disorders like addiction and depression.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Cell Press&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ten years ago, researchers discovered a small group of people who derive no pleasure from music despite having normal hearing and the ability to enjoy other experiences or stimuli. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The condition, “specific musical anhedonia,” is caused by a disconnect between the brain’s auditory and reward networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a paper publishing August 7 in the Cell Press journal &lt;em&gt;Trends in Cognitive Sciences&lt;/em&gt;, the team that discovered specific musical anhedonia describes the brain mechanisms behind the condition and discusses how understanding it could reveal other differences in how people experience pleasure and joy.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A similar mechanism could underlie individual differences in responses to other rewarding stimuli,” says author and neuroscientist Josep Marco-Pallarés of the University of Barcelona.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Investigating these circuits could pave the way for new research on individual differences and reward-related disorders such as anhedonia, addiction, or eating disorders.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To identify musical anhedonia, the team developed a tool called the Barcelona Music Reward Questionnaire (BMRQ) that measures how rewarding a person finds music.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The questionnaire examines five different ways in which music can be rewarding: by evoking emotion; by helping regulate mood; by fostering social connections; through dance or movement; and as something novel to seek, collect, or experience. People with musical anhedonia generally score low on all five aspects of the BMRQ. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behavioral and brain imaging studies have both supported the idea that specific musical anhedonia is due to a disconnection between brain regions. People with the condition can perceive and process musical melodies, meaning that their auditory brain circuits are intact—they simply don’t derive pleasure from doing so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, fMRI scans show that when listening to music, people with musical anhedonia have reduced activity in the reward circuit—the part of the brain that processes rewards including food, sex, and art—but a normal level of activity in response to other rewarding stimuli, such as winning money, indicating that their reward circuit is also intact. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This lack of pleasure for music is explained by disconnectivity between the reward circuit and the auditory network—not by the functioning of their reward circuit, per se,” says Marco-Pallarés. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If the reward circuit is not working well, you get less pleasure from all kinds of rewards,” says author and neuroscientist Ernest Mas-Herrero of the University of Barcelona. “Here, what we point out is that it might be not only the engagement of this circuitry that is important but also how it interacts with other brain regions that are relevant for the processing of each reward type.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why people develop the condition is still unclear, but studies have shown that genetics and environment could both play a role. A recently published study in twins shows that genetic effects could be responsible for up to 54% of how much an individual enjoys music.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even among healthy people, there is a lot of variation in how responsive people are to rewards, but research into specific reward types is relatively rare given that most research into the reward circuit has assumed that reward responsiveness is an all-or-nothing phenomenon—which is not the case. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We propose that using our methodology to study other reward types could yield the discovery of other specific anhedonias,” says Marco-Pallarés.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s possible, for instance, that people with specific food anhedonia may have some deficit in the connectivity between brain regions involved in food processing and the reward circuitry.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team is currently collaborating with geneticists to identify specific genes that might be involved in specific musical anhedonia. They also plan to investigate whether the condition is a stable trait or something that changes throughout life—and whether musical anhedonia or other similar conditions can be reversed.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was supported by funding from the European Regional Development Fund, the Spanish Ministry of Science and Innovation, the Government of Catalonia, the Canadian Institutes of Health Research, and the Fondation pour l’Audition, Paris. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this musical anhedonia and auditory neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#1767657264645774727b7b3974787a" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Julia Grimmett&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://cell.com" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Cell Press&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Julia Grimmett – Cell Press&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.tics.2025.06.015" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Understanding individual differences to specific rewards through music&lt;/a&gt;” by Josep Marco-Pallarés et al. &lt;em&gt;Trends in Cognitive Sciences&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Understanding individual differences to specific rewards through music&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding reward processing is essential for comprehending human behavior, from motivation and learning to affective disorders and addiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most research assumes a global sensitivity to reward, overlooking specific sensitivities to different stimuli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, recent studies have revealed variability in music reward sensitivity, including healthy individuals with specific musical anhedonia – an impaired ability to derive pleasure from music despite intact responses to other rewards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This review explores individual differences in music reward and potential causes of musical anhedonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We propose a brain model suggesting that reward experiences depend on both the overall functioning of the reward system and specific perceptual–reward network interactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, we discuss how this model and methodologies from music research can be applied to other rewarding stimuli.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:50:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBxSnJBNWNCajdkVS1wN2NlSGZIWG5PNjVQY2JUQzY5bVBDaUY2OF93dzJqMzIxQ3RQRzRLSUVXUmVUeGJqZ3ZrX2hTQXh2RGpoUXB2bkY4ZGNiR0E3c1FGRHA2Um9fRXdhd2liQTRpRXFUMWt6MHhxeFhKWVZkUQ</guid></item><item><title>研究表明， MS的迹象可能在诊断前15年出现-许多女性错过了这些早期线索-女性健康</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifkFVX3lxTFBUS3BoY1loc0RLR1lPNzhUcVpuZkVaSEhmcXFWZk9Xa2R2NXVIcURESE5oWmlYd2x5eFVfZFFQbU5fWDBWZGFUdzBTOHhTUzI1MWNfd2RFZTkwYzNyUWlkS1hFQWoxclg4bG1nSTU0SENuc0xuSUVGanBYbjVYUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-zl6cs0 et2g3wt6"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="0" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;It’s easy to assume that you’d know when you’re dealing with a disease as serious as multiple sclerosis. But it can take &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10580682/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10580682/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="years" data-node-id="0.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;years&lt;/a&gt; for people with MS to get a proper diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="1" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Now, new research suggests that subtle symptoms of the disease may show up even 15 years before someone gets diagnosed with MS. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;In case you’re not familiar with it, MS (multiple sclerosis) is a chronic condition where the body’s immune system mistakenly attacks the protective covering of nerve fibers. People can experience a range of symptoms with MS, including vision problems, muscle weakness, tingling in the arms and legs, and muscle spasms, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.ninds.nih.gov/health-information/disorders/multiple-sclerosis" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.ninds.nih.gov/health-information/disorders/multiple-sclerosis" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="National Institute of Neurological Disorders and Stroke" data-node-id="2.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;National Institute of Neurological Disorders and Stroke&lt;/a&gt; (NINDS). Some people with MS will eventually develop partial or complete paralysis, per NINDS. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;The findings of the new &lt;em data-node-id="4.1"&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2837128" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2837128" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="JAMA Network Open" data-node-id="4.1.0" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; study are shocking, and raise a lot of questions about how people can tell if their symptoms are due to something minor or a condition as serious as MS. Here’s what neurologists want you to know. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="5" class="body-tip css-18qyn7q emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="5.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.providence.org/doctors/profile/203880-clifford-segil" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.providence.org/doctors/profile/203880-clifford-segil" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Clifford Segil," data-node-id="5.2" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="5.2.0"&gt;Clifford Segil,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; DO, is a neurologist at Providence Saint John’s Health Center in Santa Monica, CA; &lt;a href="https://neurology.msu.edu/directory/amit-sachdev" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-node-id="5.4" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://neurology.msu.edu/directory/amit-sachdev" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Amit Sachdev," class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="5.4.0"&gt;Amit Sachdev,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; MD, MS, is the medical director in the Department of Neurology at Michigan State University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-did-the-study-find" data-node-id="6" class="body-h2 css-1eo7s1x emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="6.0"&gt;What did the study find?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="7" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;For the study, researchers analyzed the health records of  about 2,000 people in British Columbia. They discovered that people who were eventually diagnosed with MS started interacting with the healthcare system more frequently 15 years before they first had symptoms that were later identified as being due to MS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="8" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Every person’s health journey was different, but the researchers were able to pick up general trends. People who were eventually diagnosed with MS started seeing general practitioners more frequently 15 years before they were diagnosed for symptoms like fatigue, pain, dizziness, and mental health conditions like anxiety and depression. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="10" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;In the 12 years before their diagnosis, the patients saw a psychiatrist more often. Eight to nine years before a diagnosis, they had more frequent visits to neurologists and eye doctors, which may have been linked to blurry &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a28675876/selma-blair-chemo-ms-treatment-vision-instagram/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a28675876/selma-blair-chemo-ms-treatment-vision-instagram/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="vision" data-node-id="10.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;vision&lt;/a&gt; or eye pain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="11" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Three to five years before they were diagnosed, they visited the ER and had radiology visits more often. A year before their diagnosis, the patients saw physicians more often across a range of specialties, including neurology, emergency medicine, and radiology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="12" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;This suggests “that MS may have started earlier than previously thought,” the researchers wrote in the conclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-might-ms-be-so-hard-to-detect-this-early" data-node-id="13" class="body-h2 css-1eo7s1x emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="13.0"&gt;Why might MS be so hard to detect this early?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="14" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;MS can look slightly different for everyone, and there is a wide range of symptoms, points out &lt;a href="https://neurology.msu.edu/directory/amit-sachdev" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://neurology.msu.edu/directory/amit-sachdev" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Amit Sachdev," data-node-id="14.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.1.0"&gt;Amit Sachdev,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; MD, MS, medical director in the Department of Neurology at Michigan State University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;MS is an autoimmune disease, and it can cause &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a64523770/how-to-naturally-reduce-inflammation/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/health/a64523770/how-to-naturally-reduce-inflammation/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="inflammation" data-node-id="15.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt; throughout the body, he explains. “With excess inflammation, the body may feel generally dysfunctional,” Sachdev says. Meaning, you can feel lousy overall or in a lot of areas, making it hard for doctors (and you) to pin down what could be behind this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="16" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;People with MS can also struggle with fatigue, which can be a tough symptom to tie to any one condition, Sachdev says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="17" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Symptoms like pain, mood changes, and fatigue tend to be linked more to an MS diagnosis after it's made, because they can be due to a range of health conditions, says &lt;a href="https://www.providence.org/doctors/profile/203880-clifford-segil" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.providence.org/doctors/profile/203880-clifford-segil" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Clifford Segil," data-node-id="17.1" class="body-link css-7bauu1 emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="17.1.0"&gt;Clifford Segil,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; DO, a neurologist at Providence Saint John’s Health Center in Santa Monica, CA. He says he tends to discover these symptoms when he looks back at patient’s health history after an MS diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-should-you-do-if-youre-having-these-symptoms" data-node-id="18" class="body-h2 css-1eo7s1x emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="18.0"&gt;What should you do if you’re having these symptoms?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="19" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;Doctors say it’s a stretch to suggest that you should assume you have MS if you’re only dealing with fatigue or mood changes. But Sachdev says you also shouldn’t brush off symptoms that just don’t quit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="20" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;“Health is deeply personal. To manage it, you need to begin with a provider that connects with you,” he says. “Ideally, you would begin with a single observation or concern that is bothersome. Focusing on this issue with that provider is the place to start.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="21" class="css-i9p093 emevuu60"&gt;But Segil stresses the importance of seeing a specialist if you’re dealing with several symptoms you really can’t explain. “Whenever you have a constellation of symptoms which are without a clear medical diagnosis, seeing a neurologist may be wise,” he says. They can help take a careful assessment of your health history, along with ordering testing, to see what could be going on. &lt;br data-node-id="21.1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-journey-blur="partial" data-ad-exclude="true" class="css-19m4yzp e1jy25xv0"&gt;&lt;div class="css-sfzxfp ev8dhu59"&gt;&lt;span class="css-3mrz81 ev8dhu51"&gt;&lt;img src="https://hips.hearstapps.com/rover/profile_photos/ea27d1a6-ecd9-4da8-b2a7-049a03b4ab93_1528214135.file?fill=1:1&amp;amp;resize=120:*" alt="Headshot of Korin Miller" title="Headshot of Korin Miller" decoding="async" loading="lazy" class="css-o0wq4v ev8dhu53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="css-1dsojn8 ev8dhu55"&gt;&lt;p class="css-1y37fga ev8dhu54"&gt;Korin Miller is a freelance writer specializing in general wellness, sexual health and relationships, and lifestyle trends, with work appearing in Men’s Health, Women’s Health, Self, Glamour, and more. She has a master’s degree from American University, lives by the beach, and hopes to own a teacup pig and taco truck one day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Women's Health</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFBUS3BoY1loc0RLR1lPNzhUcVpuZkVaSEhmcXFWZk9Xa2R2NXVIcURESE5oWmlYd2x5eFVfZFFQbU5fWDBWZGFUdzBTOHhTUzI1MWNfd2RFZTkwYzNyUWlkS1hFQWoxclg4bG1nSTU0SENuc0xuSUVGanBYbjVYUQ</guid></item><item><title>鸡蛋不是高胆固醇传奇中的恶棍：研究-德撒律新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqwFBVV95cUxObVV0SFkwdHlLS3FqbjJubnVVZWVHLXlYRUJiS2h0SFQ5eXVVbTBWQVFsUWkzYjFnR1gzOTF3M3AyVTVFbVZzM0RxcTZOUzRDcTROVy0zcXltUlBxT04tSGZUSXM1MXROdnB6M1JBQ0tWbHdrS0N2dGkwb21qanZLajBSYkNxRm8zSU1OeHhMbUJFRUpnRmJKZzFhYS10cVpMSHl4X3VoWkxJS2s?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dn-article-body mt-4"&gt;&lt;div class="dn-article-body__key-points-list col-12"&gt;&lt;div class="key-points-list-content"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new study found it's not cholesterol from eggs, but saturated fat that's the real health concern.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bacon, sausage and other foods typically eaten with eggs raise adverse LDL cholesterol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eating two eggs a day alongside a low saturated fat diet can help reduce LDL cholesterol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;A new study adds to the growing notion that advice to limit egg consumption to avoid increasing bad cholesterol and risk of heart disease was based on scrambled data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;What raises bad LDL cholesterol is actually the types of food we tend to eat alongside our eggs, such as bacon and sausage, according to a study from the University of South Australia that finds eggs have been unfairly beaten up for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Advice has long been to limit egg consumption — especially the cholesterol-containing yolks — to avoid developing cardiovascular disease, which is the leading cause of death globally, killing about 18 million each year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The new study’s findings are published in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0002916525002539?via%3Dihub" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0002916525002539?via%3Dihub"&gt;The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“In a world-first study, researchers showed that eating two eggs a day, as part of a low saturated fat diet, can even help reduce LDL cholesterol, challenging outdated guidelines and offering heart-healthy news for breakfast lovers everywhere,” per a &lt;a href="https://sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250727235827.htm" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/07/250727235827.htm"&gt;news release&lt;/a&gt; on Science Daily. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The researchers “have shown definitively that it’s not dietary cholesterol in eggs but the saturated fat in our diets that’s the real heart health concern,” according to the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;In fact, the researchers concluded that eating two eggs a day in a high cholesterol but low saturated fat diet seems to reduce LDL levels and, consequently, the risk of heart disease. The study advocates eating more, not fewer eggs than have been recommended in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Jon Buckley, the lead researcher and a professor at the university, said the research team was able to unscramble the effects of cholesterol and saturated fat, “finding that high dietary cholesterol from eggs, when eaten as part of a low saturated fat diet, does not raise bad cholesterol levels.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Saturated fat, he said, drives elevation of bad cholesterol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;This is not the first study to suggest that the long-held view that eggs are potentially harmful exaggerated the risk. Dr. Howard LeWine, editor of Harvard Men’s Health Watch, in 2022 disputed advice to eat no more than one or two whole eggs a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“More recent research found that dietary cholesterol had little influence on blood levels of total and ‘bad’ LDL cholesterol,” he wrote in a &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/newsletter_article/how-many-eggs-can-i-safely-eat" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.health.harvard.edu/newsletter_article/how-many-eggs-can-i-safely-eat"&gt;Harvard newsletter.&lt;/a&gt; “Instead, it is dietary saturated fats that raise these blood levels. The reason? Most of the cholesterol in your body does not come from your diet but is made by your liver. And saturated fat in the diet can cause your liver to make lots of cholesterol.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="Conflicting-findings" class="dn-article-body__h3"&gt;Conflicting findings&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/how-many-eggs-should-you-eat#cholesterol-levels" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/how-many-eggs-should-you-eat#cholesterol-levels"&gt;Healthline reports&lt;/a&gt; that the risk from eating eggs likely varies some depending on the person and notes that there are conflicting studies, which suggests more research is needed on the topic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“For a healthy adult with normal cholesterol levels and no significant underlying heart disease risk factors, some research suggests that 1–2 eggs per day can be safe. It may even be healthy and benefit your heart health," the article said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;As for trying to limit potential risks by skipping the yolk and only eating egg whites, Healthline says that misses some of the goodness contained in the yolk: iron, vitamin D and carotenoids, among others. “These bioactive nutrients are thought to be responsible for many of the health-promoting qualities of eggs, like reduced inflammation, increased HDL cholesterol levels, and improved metabolic health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Deseret News</author><pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 17:07:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxObVV0SFkwdHlLS3FqbjJubnVVZWVHLXlYRUJiS2h0SFQ5eXVVbTBWQVFsUWkzYjFnR1gzOTF3M3AyVTVFbVZzM0RxcTZOUzRDcTROVy0zcXltUlBxT04tSGZUSXM1MXROdnB6M1JBQ0tWbHdrS0N2dGkwb21qanZLajBSYkNxRm8zSU1OeHhMbUJFRUpnRmJKZzFhYS10cVpMSHl4X3VoWkxJS2s</guid></item></channel></rss>