<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>你的阴茎真的是长寿的指标吗？布莱恩·约翰逊是这么认为的—真正的专家权衡-纽约邮报</title><link>https://nypost.com/2026/01/26/health/is-your-penis-an-indicator-of-longevity-experts-weigh-in/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;World-renowned biohacker Bryan Johnson is raising eyebrows for his &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/03/28/health/bryan-johnson-credits-shockwave-therapy-and-botox-for-titanic-erections/"&gt;shocking approach&lt;/a&gt; to erectile health.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Johnson — whose mantra is, “Don’t Die” — takes Cialis, receives penile Botox and even undergoes low-intensity shockwave therapy to his, uh, johnson to improve blood flow, enhance erections and achieve sexual performance comparable to a teenager’s.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Nighttime erections are, like, a really important health marker,” Johnson, 48, &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7qriveAV7BY" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;said in 2024&lt;/a&gt;. “Men who do not have nighttime erections are 70% more likely to die prematurely. It predicts death.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-video is-provider-youtube wp-block-embed-youtube wp-embed-aspect-16-9 wp-has-aspect-ratio"&gt;&lt;p class="wp-block-embed__wrapper"&gt;
&lt;span class="embed-youtube"&gt;&lt;iframe loading="lazy" title="Video" class="youtube-player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/7qriveAV7BY?version=3&amp;amp;rel=1&amp;amp;showsearch=0&amp;amp;showinfo=1&amp;amp;iv_load_policy=1&amp;amp;fs=1&amp;amp;hl=en-US&amp;amp;autohide=2&amp;amp;start=73&amp;amp;wmode=transparent" allowfullscreen="true" sandbox="allow-scripts allow-same-origin allow-popups allow-presentation allow-popups-to-escape-sandbox"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Biohacker Bryan Johnson is a big proponent of penile health as a key marker of biological age. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;YouTube/, The Diary Of A CEO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He’s not the only longevity-seeker making waves with his rigid regimen.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Fitness guru Ben Greenfield, 44, has experimented with &lt;a href="https://bengreenfieldlife.com/article/biohacking-articles/the-most-potent-natural-alternative-to-viagra/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;acoustic wave therapy&lt;/a&gt; and, stunningly, &lt;a href="https://bengreenfieldlife.com/article/get-effects-stem-cell-dick-injectionwithout-actually-getting-stem-cell-dick-injection/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;stem cell injections&lt;/a&gt; to optimize sexual performance and vitality.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;So is penile health a true barometer of longevity? Are these biohackers playing the long game &lt;strong&gt;—&lt;/strong&gt; or overextending themselves for a pipe dream?&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The Post spoke with two experts about the rising interest in biohacking the penis — they shared their tip-down philosophies for protecting the crown jewels for the decades to come.&lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;How does penile health reflect overall health?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Penis health is &lt;a href="https://www.browardurologycenter.com/pdf/International-Index-of-Erectile-Function-IIEF-Questionnaire.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;measured in many ways&lt;/a&gt;, [namely] erectile dysfunction (ED), orgasmic function, libido, satisfaction with intercourse and overall satisfaction,” &lt;a href="https://ryanweltermd.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Dr. Ryan Welter&lt;/a&gt;, a pioneer in regenerative cellular therapy and founder of &lt;a href="https://regenerismedical.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Regeneris Medical&lt;/a&gt;, told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Declines in penile health — particularly ED — have been established as an early predictor of cardiovascular disease, often appearing two to five years before a heart attack, Welter added.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Penile arteries are significantly smaller than the arteries that supply the heart and brain, meaning they often show the first signs of plaque buildup.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;High cholesterol and plaque buildup reduce the blood flow needed for an erection.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Penile arteries are significantly smaller than the arteries that supply the heart and brain, meaning they often show the first signs of plaque buildup. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;creativebubble – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nerve damage is also a major reason for ED because it affects signals from the brain to the pelvis.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nerve degeneration is common with age — it’s also a hallmark of diabetes, multiple sclerosis, spinal cord injury, Parkinson’s disease, stroke and Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And finally, imbalances in sex hormones can pave the way for ED. &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/09/12/health/the-truth-about-manopause-and-slow-insidious-signs-men-overlook/"&gt;Low testosterone&lt;/a&gt; reduces libido and the ability to get and maintain erections.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;“Furthermore, and this is important, happiness is one of the best predictors of longevity,” Welter said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Sexual dysfunction and depressed sexual satisfaction are indicators of unhappiness and need to be treated if longevity is the goal.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What are the red flags of poor erectile health?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Typically, men, over time, will experience erections that are not as firm as they used to be, difficulty maintaining the erection over time [and] changes in nocturnal and morning erections,” aesthetic nurse practitioner &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/injectorchris/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Chris Bustamante&lt;/a&gt;, founder of the NYC men’s clinic &lt;a href="https://www.lushfulaesthetics.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Lushful Aesthetics&lt;/a&gt;, told The Post.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It might take them longer to ejaculate or [they] may ejaculate faster. Typically, longer is more normal with age.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Sudden, drastic changes to the quality, frequency and duration of erections — especially when accompanied by symptoms like rapid weight gain, shortness of breath or fatigue — should warrant an urgent visit to the doctor, who will evaluate the cardiovascular system, hormone levels and the presence of any tumors, Bustamante said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That’s why it’s important to track morning and nocturnal erections and their general hardness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Semen is not as good of a biomarker as erections, some experts say. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;RHJ – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For his part, Johnson uses an &lt;a href="https://www.talktoadam.com/products/adam-sensor" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Adam Health sensor&lt;/a&gt; ($249) to measure his nighttime erections, garnering data on their duration, frequency and quality to generate an erection health score.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He said he also tracks his sperm count, movement and shape, penile blood flow, urination speed and prostate size.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Bustamante said erections are stronger benchmarks than semen characteristics.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It is just kind of normal sometimes for [the] volume of semen to decline with age,” he explained.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It also varies a lot from man to man, already from the beginning. So some men naturally have higher volume loads of semen versus others.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What are the common treatments for ED?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“The single most important treatment for longevity and health span, particularly for the penis, is diet and exercise and maintaining good metabolic health,” Welter said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As a hard-and-fast rule, Bustamante said, you need to focus on consuming fruits, vegetables and fiber and limit red meat for its saturated fat content and processed foods for their trans fats.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Red meat and processed foods can raise blood pressure because of their high levels of sodium, saturated fats and preservatives. High blood pressure causes ED by damaging and narrowing blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Strength training is critical for penile health because it enhances blood flow, boosts testosterone and improves vascular function. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Chanakon – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In terms of exercise, Bustamante said it’s important to build muscle since “muscle is the organ of longevity.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;He recommends 30 minutes of daily cardio, but warns against one popular activity.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We do see a higher correlation of ED when it comes to cyclists,” Bustamante said.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;“It doesn’t matter if you have a special, fancy seat or not,” he added. “Putting all that pressure on your perineum (the skin and tissue between your genitals and your anus) does sort of damage these nerves and vessels over time.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Lifestyle changes aside, Bustamante said low doses of Cialis relax smooth muscles in the prostate, bladder neck and penis to boost urine flow and facilitate erections.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What about those expensive biohacker tools?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Over time, men’s penises become desensitized — part of that is through sex and masturbation, and part of it is just through general aging,” Bustamante said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Helping to resensitize that tissue is a really important factor in terms of overall performance.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That’s why some biohackers are going so far as to embrace low-intensity focused shockwave devices. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Bustamante said these gizmos emit sound waves that cause micro-injuries in penile tissue, triggering the growth of new blood vessels and increased blood circulation to improve penile sensitivity and function.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Shockwave therapy and acoustic wave therapy are often used interchangeably, so it’s important to know what you’re really getting.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;This is an example of a shockwave device. Thankfully, it’s being used on a person’s shin in this picture. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;puhimec – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In general, shockwave therapy uses intense, high-energy acoustic waves, while acoustic therapy often refers to gentler, lower-intensity waves.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It is not going to be strong enough to actually penetrate the depth of this tissue,” Bustamante said of acoustic wave therapy.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It’s going to be very, very superficial, and so, therefore, it just really is not impactful.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For its part, Botox temporarily relaxes muscles by blocking nerve signals that cause muscle contraction.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Bustamante said that when it’s injected into the penis, patients tend to notice they can achieve firmer, quicker erections. But Botox typically lasts only three to four months.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“This treatment is really great to just improve someone’s quality of life when it comes to erectile function,” Bustamante said, adding that it can enhance the effectiveness of Cialis and Viagra.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;As for penile stem cell injections, this treatment has not been approved by the Food and Drug Administration.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It’s considered experimental, with no strong evidence of safety or effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Bustamante also warns against the increasingly popular practice of injecting salmon sperm derivatives into the penile area, as it can cause infections, allergic reactions and probably some funky smells.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Instead, he recommends and administers &lt;a href="https://www.lushfulaesthetics.com/sexual-enhancement-services/p-shot/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;“P-shots,”&lt;/a&gt; injections of platelet-rich plasma from the patient’s own blood into the penis to boost blood flow and stimulate tissue repair.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“These modalities, such as shockwave and P-shot, are really beneficial in terms of people experiencing better sex lives,” Bustamante said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Worth a shot — or a shock — to get up and running?&lt;/p&gt;





		
				
								&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPVmlWQmhkMDRTS0RxZWNqa0FuTldiVDV2WFVqcThhSENYNlZDcm1uQ0dYTzd3dHZIUlpJZnBycTNTTWNhNHdod1NrM2cySWZxc3A3eURvVi1wQlRSanB0clUzMlpCbVRRWm1zNWVOUWQyRFJvRm5CVm1CZ0lRVjZaXzdQWXAtcWtMVFUwcm1aVTg2eWZZMlB3X0ZB</guid></item><item><title>根除天花的领导者William Foege博士去世- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/wireStory/dr-william-foege-leader-smallpox-eradication-dies-129543666</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;ATLANTA -- &lt;/span&gt;Dr. William Foege, a leader of one of humanity's greatest public health victories — the global eradication of smallpox — has died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Foege died Saturday in Atlanta at the age of 89, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.taskforce.org/bill-foege-tribute/"&gt;according to&lt;/a&gt; the Task Force for Global Health, which he co-founded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The 6-foot-7 inch Foege literally stood out in the field of public health. A whip-smart medical doctor with a calm demeanor, he had a canny knack for beating back infectious diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He was director of the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention in the late 1970s and early 1980s, and later held other key leadership roles in campaigns against international health problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;But his greatest achievement came before all that, with his work on smallpox, one of the most lethal diseases in human history. For centuries, it killed about one-third of the people it infected and left most survivors with deep scars on their faces from the pus-filled lesions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Smallpox vaccination campaigns were well established by the time Foege was a young doctor. Indeed, it was no longer seen in the United States. But infections were still occurring elsewhere, and efforts to stamp them out were stalling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Working as a medical missionary in Nigeria in the 1960s, Foege and his colleagues developed a "ring containment" strategy, in which a smallpox outbreak was contained by identifying each smallpox case and vaccinating everyone who the patients might come into contact with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The method relied heavily on quick detective work and was born out of necessity. There simply wasn't enough vaccine available to immunize everyone, Foege wrote in "House on Fire," his 2011 book about the smallpox eradication effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;It worked, and became pivotal in helping rid the world of smallpox for good. The last naturally occurring case was seen in Somalia in 1977. In 1980, the World Health Organization declared smallpox eradicated from the Earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"If you look at the simple metric of who has saved the most lives, he is right up there with the pantheon. Smallpox eradication has prevented hundreds of millions of deaths," said former CDC director Dr. Tom Frieden, who consulted with Foege regularly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Foege was born March 12, 1936. His father was a Lutheran minister, but he became interested in medicine at 13 while working at a drugstore in Colville, Washington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He got his medical degree from the University of Washington in 1961 and a master's in public health from Harvard in 1965.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;He was director of the Atlanta-based CDC from 1977 to 1983, then held other international public health leadership roles, including stints as executive director at The Carter Center and senior fellow at the Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In 2012, President Barack Obama presented Foege with the Medal of Freedom, the nation's highest civilian honor. In 2016, while awarding Foege an honorary degree, Duke University President President Richard Brodhead called him "the Father of Global Health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“Bill Foege had an unflagging commitment to improving the health of people across the world, through powerful, purpose-driven coalitions applying the best science available,” Task Force for Global Health CEO Dr. Patrick O’Carroll said in a statement. "We try to honor that commitment in every one of our programs, every day.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Jack Dura contributed to this report from Bismarck, North Dakota.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:22:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxPbnA1ZEE1TUcybEpVczRVVWRpTlUwVDZzMWdWX0Zfc1NCemN4UWNYMnNLRDZ2Mlktb25IMWw3Ymdpald6UF8temlzTHZaVmJTdDRZdl9IMjhXVHZtRFE5eHZVSl95TnJXV3JvZFhGdkpWWk4zbUt5YXRpUjJXQXRBbnlKbEtZeGNPMXloVXdOZXFRUFJlRlg2LVVnMVg4UGo10gGmAUFVX3lxTE5wTnNyT1JHVURWUFdyeVo5UzdYZHhnUWs2dVVpVHBmMnVuQUZRYlRXMmdiWWc3S1p1NVF5RjdDMnhnOTRiZ29wLTJ2aDgxbEExV3dpSmt4NzluUm1XcjBPNnNpVTNneGJMaVJrSkxvWXZzczhwR2k2VFpfVTV6cW03czRoOGVVN1RTMDZKOG5GZkhubktMSGV4VWJUY0JKM29DYzY3bWc</guid></item><item><title>医生无视新的联邦疫苗建议，坚持科学- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/26/health/vaccine-recommendations-cdc-aap</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrffriy000x26p77v68f0xs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The American Academy of Pediatrics on Monday released its updated recommendations for what vaccines children should get. It’s a routine revision, hardly different from last year’s recommendations, but it carries more significance this year: More states and doctors are relying on it instead of a controversial new schedule from the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrpy4bv00033b6s31z7ozt1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The AAP’s newest recommendations include a new immunization against respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) and a few other minor adjustments — a stark difference from the sweeping changes abruptly made to the CDC vaccine schedule this month.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksq9pwd00013b6sp58ql1sw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Although the CDC schedule has long been the default guide to vaccination across the country, many doctors say they’re now choosing the AAP’s guidelines instead.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70006336po0aq7tw5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The science hasn’t changed,” said Dr. Claudia Hoyen, a pediatric infectious disease specialist and director of pediatric innovation at UH Rainbow Babies and Children’s Hospital in Cleveland. “We will continue to follow the science.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70003336pd2qqmt53@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The AAP continues to broadly recommend routine immunization against RSV, hepatitis A, hepatitis B, rotavirus, flu and meningococcal disease. Twelve major medical and health care organizations have formally endorsed its recommendations, including the American Medical Association, the National Medical Association and the American Academy of Family Physicians.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkst331000043b6swrnvdk62@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In contrast, the updated CDC schedule narrowed recommendations for protection against meningococcal disease, hepatitis B and hepatitis A to children who are at higher risk for infections. It also recommends that choices on vaccinations against flu, Covid-19 and rotavirus be based on “shared clinical decision-making,” which means people who want one must consult with a health care provider.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkslzh9l00003b6s6nq03rvw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “After an exhaustive review of the evidence, we are aligning the U.S. childhood vaccine schedule with international consensus while strengthening transparency and informed consent,” US Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. said after the vaccine schedule update. “This decision protects children, respects families, and rebuilds trust in public health.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrgx0330003336pq4kt2xtr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There were no safety issues or new research to suggest that the vaccines on the CDC’s previous schedule weren’t necessary.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70004336pwfwo7g2x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For now, unfortunately, we have to ignore everything about vaccines that is coming from our federal government,” said Dr. Sean O’Leary, chair of the AAP’s Committee on Infectious Diseases. “Parents should trust their pediatrician, trust the professional societies like the American Academy of Pediatrics.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70005336pku0unz2c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The half-dozen pediatricians who spoke with CNN they said they’ll stick with the AAP’s guidance.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70007336p1l18yxtr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Sarah Elizabeth DeRoo, a pediatrician at Children’s National in Washington, DC, says that she will continue to share “very candidly” with families about vaccines and that “we know they’re safe and effective.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksvg0fn000b3b6sm35p9dwi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When the CDC’s vaccine schedule changed this month, she said, it undermined some parents’ confidence.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70008336p76t2jpzt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We have families that come into our clinic that traditionally have been very accepting of vaccines and they want to know, ‘is this new recommendation, is this evidence-based, or do I need to think differently about these vaccines’ that they’ve accepted previously?” DeRoo said. “We’ve been giving messaging to our patients that we’re continuing to follow the recommended schedule by the American Academy of Pediatrics, which is an evidence- based schedule.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrso6q1000a3b6scfhomac4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The disconnect between advice from the CDC and from doctors has confused and even scared some parents.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70002336pj5zbjyga@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We are seeing the vaccine conversation come up more and more frequently because of&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;fear of this and general misinformation spreading online,” said Dr. Nina Alfieri, Continuity Clinic director with Lurie Children’s Pediatrics at Uptown in Chicago. “We always want families to feel welcome coming to clinic with their questions.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r70009336p6xgky1u9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Adam Ratner, a pediatric infectious disease specialist at NYU, said he gets why parents are asking more questions.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksv4zcv00053b6sgnhd6yrb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We’ve had so many years of the CDC being a reliable source of information,” he said. “It’s understandable why families are confused.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000a336phoe299i5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Historically, states have followed CDC recommendations, but most say they will now follow AAP recommendations instead, &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/state-health-policy-data/state-recommendations-for-routine-childhood-vaccines-increasing-departure-from-federal-guidelines/" target="_blank"&gt;according to KFF&lt;/a&gt;, a health policy organization.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000b336p9inc8k93@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As of January 20, KFF found, 28 states were giving advice that deviates from federal guidelines for some or all childhood vaccines. Although it’s not clear how states will handle vaccine requirements for schools, what is clear is that there is a real blue/red divide on which vaccine advice to follow, according to Jen Kates, a co-author of the analysis.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000c336prcu8ic9f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            All states with Democratic governors have announced that they won’t follow federal guidelines. Only four states led by Republicans have done the same.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000d336phnzmyi44@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For the first time in our country, we’re going to have really varying laws, policies and attitudes about vaccines based on where people live,” Kates said. “It’s a major sea change in public health policy.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000e336p8ops78zy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Hoyen&lt;strong&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; of UH Rainbow Babies and Children’s, has been practicing medicine for 30 years and said she doesn’t want to go back to the pre-vaccine days. She remembers a colleague&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;who was deaf in one ear because of a childhood case of mumps and another in the same class who was deaf in one ear because of meningitis.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksv7ut000073b6saolln0i0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Meningitis was so common before the Haemophilus influenzae type b (Hib) vaccine came into use in 1987, she remembers, that pediatricians routinely kept spinal tap equipment on hand.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000f336p5xbeqzs5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “They’d do the taps in the office, give them a dose of penicillin or whatever and send them straight to the hospital,” Hoyen said. “There’s a reason why these vaccines were created. It’s to help kids thrive and not to have to worry about complications from these childhood illnesses.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000g336pcgyyhilg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            O’Leary also doesn’t want to go back to the pre-vaccine era. He trained to be a doctor in the 1990s, before there was a vaccine against rotavirus.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmksvae9f00093b6s9ub0ul28@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We had three seasons. In the winter, we had influenza season, we had RSV season, and we had rotavirus season. Heaven forbid if they all hit at the same time, because we’d be overwhelmed. Now, we don’t have a rotavirus season, and we’re seeing a very big impact on RSV season with the new product,” O’Leary said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000h336pdv9s6b5c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            DeRoo, who has only been caring for children during what she called “the vaccine era,” says she’s been trying to refresh her knowledge of what vaccine-preventable diseases look like.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkstb4lj000c3b6s72fb2fl4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We have to rethink how we’re approaching people who walk in and are sick in the clinic, to make sure that we take all the appropriate precautions in the event that they may not be fully immunized,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000i336p36h6kzak@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Ratner said a measles outbreak in New York a few years ago was the first time many of his colleagues had ever seen a case.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkstbn7b000e3b6ss4msiw9e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I think, given the way that things are going in this country, that is likely to change,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkrfg1r7000j336p1qe5s2w1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The idea of going backwards is horrifying because you don’t want to lose hard-won progress, but also because we’re not talking about something abstract,” Ratner said. “We’re talking about actual children and families.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 05:01:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE9hNS1uYUtOTkk1cGgzQWhGd2dlWVRLeE91N2UyM0hua3dqNUNyX2szWFNvUDltdDFTdE4yYThRNmFZSE5sU0FpMFR6dW1sXzFJUTZYdm1oczNuRkF3SFkxVk9KV29SUDJ2Z1BxS1FMYlc4U3N1bk41NA</guid></item><item><title>这是小RFK的疫苗故事不想让你听到-壁垒</title><link>https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div dir="auto" class="body markup"&gt;&lt;div class="captioned-image-container"&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/$s_!NtdN!,f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2F12ba8ba3-6b12-420d-a4ea-30ba4e5b8362_2100x1500.jpeg" data-component-name="Image2ToDOM" rel class="image-link image2 is-viewable-img can-restack"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="image-caption"&gt;(Composite by Hannah Yoest / Photos: Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS ABOUT FIVE IN THE MORNING on April 1, 2025, when Antoine Archambault heard his four-month-old son, Isaac, fussing from the bedside crib inside their first-floor suburban Paris apartment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was more of a whimper than a wail, as Antoine recalls it, which was pretty typical for a baby even strangers said was unusually upbeat and given to giggling. Isaac was running a fever, but it was a mild one. Antoine gave him paracetamol (acetaminophen) and soon Isaac fell back asleep, seemingly at peace in his fuzzy sleep sack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antoine headed back to bed, hoping to get a little more rest before daybreak. But soon Isaac was up again, because the fever wasn’t going away. Claire Fauvet—Antoine’s partner and Isaac’s mother—had to take an early train to Strasbourg for work, so Antoine bundled up the baby for a short walk to a nearby medical clinic. Father and son arrived right as the doors opened at 8 a.m. and Antoine had no reason to think Isaac had anything more than a routine illness—until staff called an ambulance, for speedy transfer to the university children’s hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why, a panicked Antoine wanted to know. Because, a doctor told him, Isaac might have meningococcal disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nfid.org/infectious-disease/meningococcal/" rel&gt;Meningococcal disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is the ultimate nightmare for pediatricians, and for parents who know about it. It is caused by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Neisseria meningitidis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a bacterium that can invade the bloodstream, the spinal cord, or both. It is spread through close contact with respiratory or oral secretions, colonizing nasal and throat linings. Many people carry it harmlessly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But in rare cases it transforms into invasive disease, striking even healthy people with shocking speed. In a matter of hours, what seems like a routine, flu-like illness transforms into a full-body emergency of shock, blood clotting, and swelling of the brain. Between &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pinkbook/hcp/table-of-contents/chapter-14-meningococcal-disease.html" rel&gt;10 and 15 percent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; of those who get meningococcal disease will die, even with rapid treatment. Many more will suffer permanent &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.meningitis.org/meningitis-in-your-words-home/?types-of-meningitis=132&amp;amp;location-during-illness=&amp;amp;age-at-time-of-illness=&amp;amp;outcome-of-illness=&amp;amp;person-type=&amp;amp;after-effect=&amp;amp;search=1" rel&gt;physical or cognitive impairments&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="captioned-image-container"&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://substackcdn.com/image/fetch/$s_!d82c!,f_auto,q_auto:good,fl_progressive:steep/https%3A%2F%2Fsubstack-post-media.s3.amazonaws.com%2Fpublic%2Fimages%2Fa65e03b6-062c-419e-9173-81e034c5da56_1200x1027.jpeg" data-component-name="Image2ToDOM" rel class="image-link image2 is-viewable-img can-restack"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption class="image-caption"&gt;Antoine and Isaac. (Courtesy Antoine Archambault and Claire Fauvet.)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Antoine knew a bit about the disease, he explained to me, because he remembered a documentary he had seen about a paralympic &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2019/11/05/sport/theo-curin-france-paralympics-spt-intl" rel&gt;swimmer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; who’d lost the outer parts of all four limbs as a child. Antoine also recalls thinking that Isaac was protected against it, because he and Claire were so diligent about getting Isaac his immunizations as soon as he was eligible. “I texted Claire, they suspect meningitis, but wasn’t he vaccinated?” Antoine told me. “And Claire was like, yes he is.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But France’s “schedule”—the list of vaccines required for public child care and school, and covered by national health insurance—had until recently excluded one of the two available meningococcal shots, each one being necessary for protection against different biological strains. A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.service-public.gouv.fr/particuliers/actualites/A17982?lang=en" rel&gt;new requirement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; for the second version had taken effect on January 1, right after Isaac was born, and his appointment to get the vaccine was on the books. But it was not for another six weeks. That meant he remained at the mercy of the community around him, which—without widespread vaccination—included plenty of meningococcal carriers. Evidently one had given it to him.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next few hours remain a blur, Antoine told me. “I lost my footing, I lost my step, my legs were shaking all day,” he said, reaching for the English words to capture a state of mind as much as anything physical. Less than twenty-four hours before, Antoine had been playing with Isaac at an outdoor café, drawing out the baby’s smile with a favorite stuffed monkey that played music when you squeezed it. When Claire had rocked Isaac to sleep by holding him close to her chest, in what had become their routine, he had seemed absolutely fine. Now doctors were putting him into a medical coma, which they said was his best hope for survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Claire, who had rushed back to Paris by train, arrived at the hospital not long after that and for a while it looked like treatment might work. Isaac’s vital signs even improved for a bit. But the recovery was illusory and his condition deteriorated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His heart stopped three times. Doctors were able to revive him after the first two. They were not after the third. At 6:35 p.m., Isaac was gone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;EARLIER THIS MONTH, Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. announced the CDC would be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/05/childhood-vaccine-schedule-new-cdc-recommendation-11-shots/" rel&gt;removing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; several &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/news/article/cdc-childhood-vaccine-schedule-changes-diseases-history-data/" rel&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; from the list that it recommends for all American children. Among those CDC took off the list is the newer meningococcal vaccine, which has an excellent safety record and since its introduction had reduced the incidence of the disease in this country by &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/vaccines/vpd/mening/hcp/about-vaccine.html#:~:text=Immunogenicity%20and%20Vaccine%20Effectiveness,at%20risk%20for%20meningococcal%20disease." rel&gt;90 percent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Under the new guidelines, the agency recommends the shot only for high-risk groups (like people who are immunocompromised or college freshmen living in close quarters). For others, the agency suggests “&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/20/shared-decision-making-vaccine-guidance-twists-meaning-of-term/" rel&gt;shared clinical decision-making&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;,” meaning parents should discuss with their doctors whether the shots are advisable for their children.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exactly how much will change—and exactly when—is hard to say. Insurers will continue to pay for the vaccines, administration officials said, as will a government-run program that administers immunizations to low-income children. Decisions about whether to require shots for school will remain with states, as they always have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But physicians, state officials, and insurers all use CDC recommendations to guide their own decisions and advice. That’s one reason the recommendations &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/06/what-new-vaccine-schedule-means-doctors-parents-kids/" rel&gt;matter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; so much, including to people like Kennedy with long histories of hostility to vaccines. Another is that the guidelines make it possible for Americans without medical training to know what the nation’s most trusted scientists believe, based on their assessment of the latest and best available research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Or at least that’s how it is supposed to work. This month’s retrenchment on vaccine policy—arguably the biggest in American history—is not based on new data or research that’s suddenly become available. Rather, it is based on a reassessment &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/presidential-actions/2025/12/aligning-united-states-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/" rel&gt;ordered up&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; by Kennedy’s boss, President Donald Trump, that compared U.S. recommendations to those in peer countries around the world. “After an exhaustive review of the evidence,” Kennedy said in a statement, “we are aligning the U.S. childhood vaccine schedule with international consensus while strengthening transparency and informed consent.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Like so many other arguments Kennedy has made about vaccines, this claim about “consensus” is simply &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2026/01/09/childhood-vaccination-fact-check-denmark-not-america-is-the-outlier/" rel&gt;not true&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. In reality, vaccine recommendations vary across Europe, North America, and Asia, even among peer countries. Before the Trump administration issued its directive this January, the United States was at the high end of the spectrum, with a recommendation of immunization against seventeen diseases. Now it’s at the low end, with a recommendation for twelve—or just one more than Denmark, the European country with the fewest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/robert-kennedy-rfk-jr-denmark-vaccines-hhs-maga-trump" rel&gt;no coincidence&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Trump administration officials have said repeatedly that Denmark was their model, and arranged for a full presentation on the Danish recommendations during December’s meeting of the committee of outsiders that officially advises the CDC. The text of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/assessment-of-the-us-childhood-and-adolescent-immunization-schedule-compared-to-other-countries.pdf" rel&gt;assessment memo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; justifying the decision that the Trump administration released in early January cites “Denmark” or “Danish” authorities thirteen times—by far the most references for any country. A coauthor of the assessment is the same physician who gave the advisory committee presentation—&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/05/19/tracy-beth-hoeg-fda-advisor-marty-makary-vinay-prasad-vaccine-policy/" rel&gt;Tracy Beth Høeg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a sports-medicine specialist who spent part of her career in Copenhagen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/robert-kennedy-rfk-jr-denmark-vaccines-hhs-maga-trump" rel&gt;Denmark&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2025/12/26/nx-s1-5656214/childhood-vaccination-denmark-rfk-policy" rel&gt;an&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://kffhealthnews.org/morning-breakout/viewpoints-denmarks-vaccine-success-cant-be-copied-in-the-us-new-dietary-guidelines-dont-make-sense/" rel&gt;odd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/12/19/denmark-vaccine-schedule-vs-us/" rel&gt;choice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to be such a singular example given its relatively tiny population of six million people living in a quasi-socialist paradise. A truly “exhaustive” review of the evidence would have also considered some of the larger countries on the continent, especially anywhere the public has been arguing about vaccines or where officials recently changed recommendations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;France turns out to be one such country—and in the case of the vaccine for meningococcal disease, an especially useful one for understanding both the policy debate and very personal meaning it has for families like Antoine’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-attrs='{"url":"https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=share&amp;amp;action=share","text":"Share","action":null,"class":null}' data-component-name="ButtonCreateButton" class="button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=share&amp;amp;action=share" rel class="button primary"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Share&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE OBVIOUS REASON to consider France is that it simply looks a lot more like the United States than Denmark does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It has Western Europe’s third-largest economy, with a population of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.statista.com/topics/5677/demography-in-france/?srsltid=AfmBOoqjCMvVTyaJSjkS0bWnfv4aNtMPVk2hjNKxln2OuRC1-QpvHR5p#editorsPicks" rel&gt;nearly 70 million&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that is literally ten times larger than Denmark’s. France doesn’t have the kind of economic inequality that you find in the United States, because no Western or Northern European democracy does, but its &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://worldpopulationreview.com/country-rankings/gini-coefficient-by-country" rel&gt;socioeconomic breakdown&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; looks more like America’s than Denmark’s. Even the French health care system is a better analogue to that of the United States. It delivers universal coverage through a mixed public-private system in which access can vary depending on insurance type and wealth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But there’s something else about France that makes its experience relevant. Like the United States, France has a vocal &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/01/14/956705043/france-has-1-of-the-highest-rates-of-vaccine-skepticism" rel&gt;anti-vaccination movement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, rooted partly in a political culture supportive of a strong central government but distrustful (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.truedem.eu/resources-and-deliverables/online-survey-2025" rel&gt;by European standards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;) of the people and institutions who run them. “I think we are one of the world champions when it comes to vaccine hesitancy,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://research.pasteur.fr/en/member/muhamed-kheir-taha/" rel&gt;Muhamed Kheir-Taha&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, who directs the invasive bacterial infections unit at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.pasteur.fr/en" rel&gt;Institut Pasteur&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in Paris, told me. There’s &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S235239641630398X" rel&gt;survey data&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; to back that up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That tradition helps explain the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.doi.org/10.1016/j.vaccine.2018.02.095" rel&gt;evolution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.jle.com/en/revues/vir/e-docs/les_nouvelles_obligations_vaccinales_un_tournant_dans_la_politique_de_sante_publique_francaise_311395/article.phtml" rel&gt;French&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://infos.rtl.lu/news/frontieres/la-vaccination-obligatoire-interdite-en-droit-francais-pas-vraiment-1761203" rel&gt;vaccine laws&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. When the earliest vaccines for diseases like smallpox and polio became available during the early and mid-twentieth century, France made them mandatory, meaning they were a requirement for attending school. But as newer vaccines like the measles shot became available, French authorities merely “recommended” the vaccines—which meant, among other things, the national health system didn’t always pay for them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But agitation to change the policies reached a critical mass about twenty years ago, in part because physicians and public health experts worried vaccination rates for diseases like measles and pertussis would fall below herd immunity levels. French officials reacted by commissioning expert reports, and then convening public meetings so that the public had a chance both to hear the recommendations and offer feedback. The effort culminated in a 2017 law that added eight new vaccines to the mandatory list.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The newer meningococcal shot was initially not one of them, because for each vaccine French authorities were weighing the costs and benefits in the context of allocating money in the national health insurance system. They decided those other strains of meningococcal disease were too rare to justify the expense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But the disease turned out to be not so rare after all, with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.santepubliquefrance.fr/les-actualites/2024/infections-invasives-a-meningocoque-recrudescence-de-cas-en-france-en-2023" rel&gt;rising&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.santepubliquefrance.fr/maladies-et-traumatismes/maladies-a-prevention-vaccinale/infections-invasives-a-meningocoque/documents/bulletin-national2/infections-invasives-a-meningocoque-en-france-en-2024" rel&gt;caseloads&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s12889-020-09487-7" rel&gt;outbreaks&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in communal settings like schools. “We would get a lot of attention from the media for these, even when it was a single case, because they would be touching children or young adults in very good health, and then they may die within hours,” Taha said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;French authorities had a playbook for these situations: They would surge vaccination to the affected areas, aiming to protect people before they could get exposed and develop the condition, while rushing treatment to the afflicted. But meningococcal disease acts so quickly that the surges inevitably were too late for some.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“The best way to avoid this disease—we told them—is to prevent the disease, not to treat it afterwards,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gpip.fr/organisation/" rel&gt;Hervé Haas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, president of the French pediatric infectious disease association, explained to me.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Once again, French authorities listened to the doctors and public health experts: In 2024, they added the second meningococcal vaccine to the mandatory list. The hope is that the requirement will dramatically improve uptake, which is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6607743/" rel&gt;what happened&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; with the vaccines that France made mandatory in 2017.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;THE STRATEGY THAT FRANCE ABANDONED—making the vaccine strictly voluntary, and then surging resources to stop outbreaks once they start—is similar to the one that Kennedy and the Trump administration just embraced. But if you look at that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/assessment-of-the-us-childhood-and-adolescent-immunization-schedule-compared-to-other-countries.pdf" rel&gt;assessment memo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that HHS released in January, you won’t find acknowledgement that the French recently adopted the meningococcal vaccine, let alone an explanation for why the authors believe the United States should be moving in precisely the opposite direction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, you won’t find any references to France—or any signs that memo’s authors seriously studied the experience of European countries other than Denmark. When I asked HHS about this explicitly—whether larger, more comparable nations like France, Germany, and the U.K. had been given the consideration that Denmark had—I got a boilerplate response: “Many peer nations achieve high vaccination rates without mandates by relying on trust, education, and strong doctor-patient relationships,” HHS Press Secretary Emily Hilliard wrote in an email, “and HHS will work with states and clinicians to ensure families have clear, accurate information to make their own informed decisions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hilliard also described the review as “thorough,” echoing what Kennedy has said, although it is a bit difficult to take that seriously when the entirety of the assessment is just thirty pages long. And because it’s a memo justifying decisions on several vaccinations, it gives only scant attention to each. The explanatory section on meningococcal disease is just four paragraphs, or barely 200 words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just for comparison, the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/pdf/rr/rr6202.pdf" rel&gt;document&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; the CDC used in 2013 when first recommending the newer meningococcal vaccine had roughly 18,000 words—on the meningococcal vaccine alone—with highly detailed reviews of research, projections of how different recommendations would play out in the real world, and other sorts of information you’d want officials to consider in making these kinds of decisions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That document is a reflection of the work that went into it—literally years of study and debating, with the CDC director ultimately making decisions after public votes by the outside committee of experts. Nothing like that happened this year, despite Kennedy’s promises of “radical transparency.” The CDC simply announced the decision one day, without warning, with the director signing off on a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/sites/default/files/decision-memo-adopting-revised-childhood-adolescent-immunization-schedule.pdf" rel&gt;recommendation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; he got from the heads of three other government agencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Outside of a genuine emergency, our government should not be waking up in the morning, brushing its teeth, and abruptly announcing major shifts in longstanding policy,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/1781/joshua-m-sharfstein" rel&gt;Joshua Sharfstein&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a pediatrician and former deputy FDA commissioner now on faculty at Johns Hopkins University, told me. “The basis for changing course should be released well in advance, reviewed by independent experts, and modified as needed through careful consideration and explanation. It is a process with integrity that distinguishes thoughtful policymaking from a power grab.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-attrs='{"url":"https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=share&amp;amp;action=share","text":"Share","action":null,"class":null}' data-component-name="ButtonCreateButton" class="button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease?utm_source=substack&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_content=share&amp;amp;action=share" rel class="button primary"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Share&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;TO RATIONALIZE ITS DECISION, the Trump administration memo cites a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/WER8647" rel&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; from the World Health Organization, which recommended society-wide vaccination only in countries where the case level is higher than it is in the United States. But the primary audience for WHO guidance is officials trying to make the most of scarce medical resources.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;That’s not the way things work here, for better or worse depending on your perspective. The American system throws all kinds of money at saving lives—even for interventions that cost way more than vaccination—because that’s what &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://intuitionlabs.ai/articles/icer-vs-nice-drug-pricing-comparison" rel&gt;wealthier countries&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; do when they want to prioritize health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-state="closed"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Once you’ve seen a case of meningococcal disease, you are thinking my god, I never ever want to see a case like that again,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://advances.massgeneral.org/contributors/contributor.aspx?id=1818" rel&gt;Rochelle Walensky&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, the Harvard-affiliated pediatric infectious disease specialist and former CDC director, told me. “When you have seen a completely viable, young, vibrant person who suddenly obtunded [meaning barely responsive] with bacterial meningitis—and you know their life will never be the same—then the answer is that if there is anything I can do to prevent this, if I can prevent it safely, you’re going to do it.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;One other person who understands all too well the menace of the disease is Antoine. And he wants to do something about it. He and Claire have raised money to support research into the disease and to promote training for medical professionals, so they are better able to recognize it quickly. They’ve worked with local and national groups that are affiliated with the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.meningitis.org/como/" rel&gt;Confederation of Meningitis Organisations&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a U.K.-based international organization trying to promote awareness and research worldwide.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They’ve also tried to do what they can to spread the word about the vaccine among friends and professional contacts. (Antoine is a consultant who works with banks on regulatory compliance, and Claire a lawyer.) Antoine told me he got “pretty pissed off” recently when he heard a friend got advice from a doctor not to get the shot, because they were not part of a high-risk group. “This is a big fight for us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before our video call ended, Antoine shared some photos, all of them with Isaac smiling in exactly the way I had been told. And when Antoine was done recounting that awful day last April, he told me about the quiet memorial service they held at the hospital—and the burial, with about a hundred family and friends present. Antoine said that he and Claire were careful to bundle Isaac in his favorite blanket with sheep and stars on it, and to make sure he had his beloved stuffed monkey with him. The cemetery is near their apartment. Antoine said he visits every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-attrs='{"url":"https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease/comments","text":"Leave a comment","action":null,"class":null}' data-component-name="ButtonCreateButton" class="button-wrapper"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thebulwark.com/p/this-is-the-vaccine-story-rfk-jr-doesnt-want-you-to-hear-meningitis-meningococcal-disease/comments" rel class="button primary"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Leave a comment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Bulwark</author><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2026 00:00:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxQS1JnOURQelNqa19EQXNfaXVSSlhZMVdoR1pLM1hCNE9SRzRyUC14ZTlhcEhIXzdXdnk3dXJDMm9XYWJGQVRYMm9UTkI5QWFxZnM0ZktPZXR0RHNzaEYtZEpEeEFZMUxsSEJJUG1oWVlKenV2LU9DNFZDdFBTcnp6REItbHZxYnRuS0pVU2ZlNVhEblEwSDNiUXNxU1ljRC05ZHVUb0FtREVFa0Y3ZjB4dGRpSFd2ZWthTUE</guid></item><item><title>AHA表示，近90%的美国人患有无症状心脏病- NewsNation</title><link>https://www.newsnationnow.com/health/american-heart-association-cardiovascular-kidney-metabolic-syndrome/</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
    
    &lt;noscript&gt;
      
    &lt;/noscript&gt;
  &lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>NewsNation</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 23:03:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOWHNCdy1oSUlvV1hnRzIxalBtclRuZzZfQ19vdnZxRElWTFREYmd2cDA2STg5NVBPVlc0amhJdXFNS3NiNjZHRUJvNW9lb1ljZWpmUWJOVDJxNkZEa1prSEpYZTdyN1UzSnlhVHppTUpmXzBFeGJWNmU3OUVhWV9SQ2JYdmZzd0szaDFOaUNhXzR3eFVidDJXQnVUeURKMVJQZnkwZkFOU1LSAa4BQVVfeXFMT25PZ3EwZHgwS3lRcjF6Vi1iSWhJa0hGUktoUUVpY185ZVY2VlBXR3ZjMGZ2MkFPVjhMNkVKLVd6RXJBUVpfOWlfX1VGNWdvZXNQNm9VUnJrUlhydW5sdnBuSTZpV0NaRTJHSVhoM19FRnpBa2xNSzJTVnRGR2F5R2RWWjh6WmVGUl9peEZGM3NmQkRkTnVfbWlmWEVCbnlJRk1ZTDYwWmV5V2Q1UDhR</guid></item><item><title>蛋白质去年就是这样。为什么光纤是下一件大事- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51438056/protein-is-so-last-year-why-fiber-is-the-next-big-thing</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK CITY — Move over, protein. Fiber is on pace to be the next "it" nutrient of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumers — particularly Gen Z — are fixated on stomach health, leading to the "fibermaxxing" trend taking hold on TikTok. As people try to maximize the fiber in their meals, major food companies are capitalizing on the trend with new, fiber-focused products.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is a consumer need in terms of digestion and gut health, and that's something we've seen the last few years," said Sherry Frey, health and wellness thought leader at NIQ. The younger generation, she added, understands that digestive health is linked to better skin and improved cognitive function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dataessential, a food and beverage research firm, found that 52% of consumers were interested in trying "fibermaxxing" after learning about the trend and that 42% of shoppers think food labeled "high fiber" is healthier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiber builds on previous wellness-focused consumer trends, Frey told CNN. First was hydration, as seen with the rise of products like Liquid I.V. and Electrolit. Then protein, a trend that shows no sign of slowing down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The natural next step is for fiber," she said, calling the converging of trends a "perfect storm."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, fiber has been proven to trigger "a naturally occurring GLP-1 in our bodies," she added, referencing the appetite-suppressing hormone in weight-loss drugs like Wegovy that are flooding the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Big Food responds&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consumers' desire for fiber is already evident on grocery store shelves. Whole Foods' &lt;a href="https://www.wholefoodsmarket.com/trends/the-next-big-things-our-top-8-food-trend-predictions-for-2026" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;forecast&lt;/a&gt; for 2026 said there are "more fiber-forward callouts on packaging" as well as more products with added fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thrive Market, a membership-based online supermarket, has seen fiber-related terms surge 30% over the past year with shoppers gravitating toward snacks, bars and supplements, a spokesperson told CNN.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major food companies have taken notice: PepsiCo CEO Ramon Laguarta said on its most recent earnings call in October that "fiber will be the next protein."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Consumers are starting to understand that fiber is the benefit that they need. It's actually a deficiency in U.S. consumers' diets, and that will be elevated," Laguarta told analysts. (More than 90% of women and 97% of men don't get their recommended daily intake of fiber, the U.S. government &lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2020-12/Dietary_Guidelines_for_Americans_2020-2025.pdf" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; in 2020.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PepsiCo is already bolstering its soda portfolio with fiber-forward products. Last summer, it launched a gut-friendly soda following its purchase of Poppi with "Pepsi Prebiotic Cola," which includes added fiber. More products are on the way, including fiber-enhanced versions of its SunChips, Smartfood popcorn and Propel hydration packets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDonald's CEO Chris Kempczinski also recently predicted on his Instagram account that fiber "is going to be big" in 2026, perhaps signaling that the fast-food chain could dip its toes into the trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snacks, such as chips and puffed crackers, will be the battleground for fiber, Frey predicts, notably products made from legumes and beans. But taste is a factor, especially if it's made from plant-based ingredients.&lt;strong&gt;﻿&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Consumers are willing to make a trade, but they're not always willing to make the trade if the taste isn't there," Frey said. "Despite the economy, they're willing to pay a little more for these kinds of products."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's where private labels created by major grocery stores come in. They are also getting into the wellness sector with fiber-enchanced products, but without the premium prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aldi's recently relaunched in-house line includes knock-offs of "better for you" sodas and meal bars. Walmart is expanding its Bettergoods lineup, which encompasses several foods that have plant-based ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is this healthy?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recommended amount of fiber is 25 grams per day for adult women to 35 for adult males, according to medical experts, so "it's a generally good healthy trend," said Paul Kriegler, a registered dietician and senior director of nutritional products for Life Time Fitness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the prepackaged products hitting shelves are not a panacea for this deficiency. He would rather consumers gravitate toward the produce and vegetable section at the grocery store for their fiber needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. government's newly released dietary guidelines also urge people to prioritize "real food," including "fiber-rich whole grains," as well as curtail their intake of highly processed foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What I've taught clients for a long time is to eat a pile of vegetables the size of your head every day," Kreigler told CNN. "The irony is most of the foods that will help 'fibermaxxing' don't even have labels, and you have to go get them fresh."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 21:58:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPOUpkbVNRYVhJb3J3ZV9OMUFPLTNoX0FtYTN3aU9GSnE4MVI1TzBDNVFMaUpNcjdXRi02Tkh3RE0tWjJvZmJ5Ry1PS2g3SlFqdVlwa3V1YktNS0g2MjdwTjRUWmcxampNblhCR2dVWXdhTTR0SjhfN05SNmI1alF2aDY0aU1WcnpBZkFxa2U1U3BJcnhhUy04</guid></item><item><title>这种被遗忘的癌症疫苗的结果在20年后被科学家们重新审视- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/this-forgotten-cancer-vaccines-results-were-so-unusual-scientists-revisited-it-20-years-later/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 21:19:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxPbXhIXzhlN3owMTJJdVUtUTNTbmcwLU9ERzMxOXpGVFl0V0JEdzZvNTIxNzUxcDV1LTVyM3lfMVhWb1A0OGdPNzdXUklFbHZQbkZBd3lveGtKQ3NGLUlJYS1XTVlSQWx4M04xTFRsWFJjYzdZck0tUVYyN3hBblpOMHdwRFMxVmstcXhUU2l3OEIyZzBkZkY3bmZQVWpEWFpkckZYYlc0cGkwZGdBbWw4S1FXWWwtSjdiWEFN</guid></item><item><title>Penarth妈妈“乞求”进行核磁共振检查，发现宫颈癌- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cd9eeklq93go</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Mum with cervical cancer begged for scan after years of being 'fobbed off'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/496a/live/d7c5da40-f852-11f0-8ab6-81a112385ec5.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Jessica Mason Jessica, who has curly blonde hair and pink highlights, with blue eyes, smiles as she sits in a car" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Jessica Mason&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jessica says women-specific health issues are too often dismissed&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A woman with cervical cancer who waited years to be diagnosed says she has "lost her faith in doctors".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica Mason went back and forth to her GP and hospital with swelling, bleeding and pain in her vagina but says she was "fobbed off" before "begging" for a scan which revealed cancer requiring urgent treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The 44-year-old believes she was only referred for an MRI because she "broke down in tears" to a doctor, adding: "I knew there was something wrong."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A Senedd &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://laiddocuments.senedd.wales/cr-ld17744-en.pdf" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;health committee report &lt;/a&gt;into gynaecological cancer has found women have been "let down by the Welsh government's inaction". The Welsh government said it was working with the NHS to improve gynaecological cancer outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'I wasn't being believed'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica, from Penarth in the Vale of Glamorgan, was experiencing pain and vaginal bleeding which became serious in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I knew there was something wrong," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said doctors gave her ultrasounds which did not pick up any issues, and she was also given various diagnoses including a cyst, endometriosis and prolapse, for which she was advised to perform pelvic floor exercises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was so confusing because you trust in the doctors and you think if it was something serious they would have known," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/fe62/live/149695c0-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Jessica Mason Jessica, who has long blonde hair, smiles in a selfie with her husband Dan, who is wearing a black jumper and has short silvery hair and stubble. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Jessica Mason&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jessica with her husband, Dan&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica said a smear test six months before she was diagnosed also picked up nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It was only in May 2022 when she went to the University Hospital of Wales in Cardiff for the results of an ultrasound that she broke down in tears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"They said there was something on the lining of the womb but it all looked OK," said Jessica, who begged them to do something more to check what could be causing her symptoms as she felt she "wasn't being believed".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was only at that point they offered me an MRI," she added, which she said was offered as a way to give her "peace of mind".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The results came back a couple of weeks later in June 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Cancer didn't cross my mind to be honest, I thought it would be something like an infection, I didn't think it was going to be that serious."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In fact the doctor told her that she had stage 1 B3 cervical cancer and needed to start treatment urgently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica started a programme of chemotherapy and radiotherapy in August 2022 for five weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/d1fe/live/00ed2b10-f85f-11f0-933b-47b4ddaac6f0.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Jessica Mason Jessica wearing a hospital gown, lies in a hospital bed with nasal tubes attached. Her blonde hair is tied back. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Jessica Mason&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Jessica says cancer treatment caused her to have an early menopause&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica said the treatment took its toll on her 13-year-old son and also pushed her into early menopause, meaning she had to give up her plans to have another child.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I couldn't cook and couldn't clean, I couldn't even iron my son's uniform or take him to school," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica believes she should have been referred for an MRI sooner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The cost of the MRI is probably just as much as the amount spent on treatment, GP and doctor appointments," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But that wasn't the end of Jessica's ordeal, after a further MRI in February 2023 found the tumour was still there and meant she needed to have a hysterectomy in July 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I lost my faith in the doctors," said Jessica. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's horrible because obviously I'm not a medical expert and you've got to put your faith in them but I'm always questioning them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica used to work full time but said she could now only manage three days a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It took over our lives. My body is wrecked from everything I've been through but mentally too, my friends, my family, my home life, everything just revolves around that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Jessica said she still experienced bleeding occasionally and will need further biopsies, describing the situation as "never-ending".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I've always got this worry in the back of my head, what if they miss something again and this time I don't survive it?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She has accused the health board of "dragging their heels" over sharing her medical records while she considers whether to take legal action against them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"A lot of women-specific issues are just not recognised [quickly] enough. They just dismiss it as 'your time of the month' or 'women's issues'," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A spokesperson for Cardiff and Vale University Health Board said: "We are sorry to hear about Jessica's experience while in our care and acknowledge the challenges surrounding her cancer diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"As it would be inappropriate to comment on an individual patient case, and due to ongoing legal proceedings, we are unable to comment further."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'Critical failures'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A recent Senedd health committee report into gynaecological cancer care in Wales found that women were "still being let down by the Welsh government's inaction".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The report found a failure to deliver on a number of recommendations made in December 2023 as part of a landmark report uncovering "critical failures".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It said despite accepting the majority of the committee's 2023 recommendations, the Welsh government had not allocated specific ring-fenced funding for gynaecological cancer services or published measurable NHS targets for improving outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It also found that Wales had fallen short on waiting times, with only 41% of patients starting treatment within the 62-day target in October 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cancer charity Tenovus said it was "deeply concerning to see in black and white just how little progress has been made".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Welsh government said: "We are committed to working with the NHS to improve access to timely diagnosis and treatment for women with gynaecological cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We have made changes to support earlier referrals and we are investing in new equipment and new treatments to improve women's outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The current performance against the 62-day target is simply not good enough and must improve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The Women's Health Plan is driving real change in women's healthcare in Wales."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 21:02:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBZV0RtakcybGhlaFVCQlNhdmc1N0Fqcmg1ZmdOOUhQWDMzZ1pTajhQTUdRcnBPVDI2NkpPM2xwSFpxVWc5bHJIcjhKTk1aeVEzVEk1Szhtd3hxUdIBX0FVX3lxTE5Td1c5YllhTks2UUxicG1mSjI3d3FRaTI4ejkyUFhfYWx5OHdXR29PeFF0MC1hbkRhMTVPTkphWDhuQXVKblJyWERMcEZDVnBFQ0V5Y1NOc1l3X2RIcUFj</guid></item><item><title>房客专栏|我是营养师。这就是为什么您不应该将食物标记为“好”或“坏”的原因。’-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2026/01/25/nutrition-healthy-eating-good-bad-foods/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="D4EFSZFECFHIDPSODJK7UUW6ZA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Eat this, avoid that. This one food will cure everything. But this one you should NEVER eat. You can eat these foods, but &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; during strictly controlled times of day. Statements like these are all over social media, gyms and even health care offices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNTy1DemY2QU1sSktpLTVteFRPTl8zTExsc1AtZS1GNVpoSy1MOFJFYTE4MkpjZ3dfbjhsXzlwYjR6NHhyN043SzZCNDUxZmtNYm1FeHRaNDdZR09oYlZtelBhWkZnX2p1ampNUjJIak1mSEZFSGI5eXhQbGhNcy1YQzlIVVNYNXpONkpHMHkxVjVob2REWHc</guid></item><item><title>科学家说前进，继续前进-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/scientists-gooning</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;Adult content has never been as accessible as it is now, thanks to the internet. Hell, online smut &lt;a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/porn-behind-internet-technologies-2017-5" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;played a major role&lt;/a&gt; in the rise of the web itself in the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;With that glut of porn, some have voiced concerns that some people are &lt;a href="https://www.apa.org/monitor/2014/04/pornography" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;consuming too much&lt;/a&gt; of the stuff or even becoming addicted, which they claim could have consequences like regulating emotions or impaired sexual functioning.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;But as &lt;a href="https://www.psypost.org/frequent-pornography-use-does-not-always-indicate-a-problem-new-study-suggests/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;PsyPost&lt;/em&gt; reports&lt;/a&gt;, these concerns may be overblown. Researchers at the University of Pécs in Hungary have found that it doesn’t matter how frequently one watches porn; the reasons why somebody indulges in the stuff are far more predictive of their sexual health.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;As detailed in a &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/19317611.2025.2605517" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;new paper&lt;/a&gt; published in the &lt;em&gt;International Journal of Sexual Health&lt;/em&gt;, the researchers found that positive motivations, such as “enhancing sexual pleasure, exploring fantasies, or deepening intimacy,” were “associated with frequent but non-problematic pornography use and with adaptive sexual regulation.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;However, those with “negative motivations,” such as “stress reduction, emotional escape, or avoidance of discomfort,” were strongly linked to “sexual system hyperactivation, emotion regulation difficulties, and impaired relational functioning.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;The study involved  890 adult participants in Hungary, including 600 individuals assigned female at birth and 290 assigned male at birth. The participants submitted answers anonymously through an online survey.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“A major gap in the literature is that pornography use is often evaluated mainly by how frequently people use it, even though frequency alone tells us very little about whether use is actually harmful,” University of Pécs psychology professor Norbert Meskó told &lt;em&gt;PsyPost&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“We were interested in whether these different motivations are linked to different patterns of sexual and emotional functioning,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Most strikingly, the researchers found that participants who reported frequent pornography use were less likely to experience problematic outcomes. However, those who primarily used it for coping and managing stress were more likely to experience symptoms of problematic use, indicating that frequency isn’t the main indicator of whether it’s actually harmful.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“One somewhat surprising finding was that frequent use, when driven by positive motivations, was linked to less sexual deactivation — meaning less emotional withdrawal from sexuality,” Meskó told &lt;em&gt;PsyPost&lt;/em&gt;. “In contrast, only problematic use — not frequent use — was associated with these kinds of disengaged or avoidant sexual patterns.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Importantly, problematic use showed much stronger links to difficulties in sexual and emotional functioning than simple frequency did,” he added. “This suggests that from a practical standpoint, it is more useful to look at whether someone feels out of control or distressed by their use than at how often they watch pornography.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Of course, as the researchers note in their paper, there are some limitations to their research. For one, the self-reported nature of their data may not be reliable, as it relies on memory. It also may not be generalizable to a broader population as a result.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Multiple motivations for pornography use may also overlap — for instance, seeking pleasure while also distracting from stress — meaning that some cases may not neatly fit into either positive or negative motivations. One category may also quickly shift to another, further complicating the picture.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“We would caution against thinking of pornography as either simply ‘good’ or ‘bad,'” Meskó told &lt;em&gt;PsyPost&lt;/em&gt;. “For some people, it may be part of healthy sexual expression, while for others it may function as a way to avoid emotional problems or relationship difficulties.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on pornography:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/future-society/grok-violence-women"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Grok Is Being Used to Depict Horrific Violence Against Real Women&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZkFVX3lxTE9BNFJwSHJ6YXUwdmJZOVZ6Z3d2QXhnZnMxdkhvbzk3Sm54d3lPdFBIVUtlc3R4cFhzdE1ObEJGY3FuUnRGUDdjaElxaUxWT0Y1cENFaUVqUi1MbGR1R3dyRU54alp6Zw</guid></item><item><title>印度尼帕病毒爆发导致5人感染，近100人被隔离；泰国开始对来自印度的乘客进行筛查：媒体报道-环球时报</title><link>https://www.globaltimes.cn/page/202601/1354171.shtml</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article_right"&gt; &lt;center&gt;&lt;img id="759198" alt="Photo: VCG" src="https://www.globaltimes.cn/Portals/0/attachment/2026/2026-01-26/1ba5c80f-aed7-4740-bd95-c6d2634b6e9f.jpeg"&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p class="picture"&gt;Photo: VCG&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Thai Ministry of Public Health on Sunday began screening air passengers arriving from India for possible Nipah virus infection after five Nipah virus cases were reported and nearly 100 people were quarantined in India's eastern state of West Bengal, according to media reports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screening is being carried out at Suvarnabhumi and Don Mueang airports, focusing on travellers arriving from West Bengal. Authorities said passengers and relevant agencies have been cooperative, Thai media outlet The Nation Thailand reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ministry has also issued a "Health Beware Card" for travellers arriving from risk areas. It advises anyone who develops symptoms such as fever, headache, muscle aches, sore throat, cough, difficulty breathing, drowsiness, confusion or seizures—especially if they have had contact with bats, sick animals or an infected person within 21 days before arriving in Thailand—to seek medical attention immediately, The Nation Thailand reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier, Indian authorities are rushing to contain a Nipah virus outbreak after five cases were reported and nearly 100 people quarantined in the eastern state of West Bengal, The Independent reported Friday local time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three new infections were reported earlier this week, authorities said, adding to two existing cases of nurses, one male and one female, who had earlier tested positive. The nurses were working at a private hospital in Barasat near the state capital of Kolkata, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides Thailand screening air passengers arriving from India, the Government of Nepal has heightened nationwide alertness to prevent the possible entry of the Nipah virus, following its recent spread in India's neighboring state of West Bengal, according to Nepalese media outlet The Annapurna Express on January 22.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spokesperson for the Nepal Ministry of Health and Population, Prakash Budhathoki, said the government has put adequate preventive measures in place. Health screenings have been initiated for passengers arriving at Tribhuvan International Airport, as well as at major border points with India, The Annapurna Express reported. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have intensified surveillance particularly at border points in Koshi Province. Similar health checks have also been ordered at other border crossings," Budhathoki said, per the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the World Health Organisation (WHO), Nipah virus is classified as a priority pathogen owing to its epidemic potential. There are no vaccines or treatment for Nipah virus. Nipah virus infection in humans causes a range of clinical presentations, from asymptomatic infection (subclinical) to acute respiratory infection and fatal encephalitis, says WHO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A member of the Henipavirus genus, Nipah virus is mainly carried by fruit bats of the Pteropus species, creating a constant risk of spillover to humans through contaminated food or direct contact. With no approved vaccine or specific antiviral treatment available, and fatality rates in past outbreaks ranging between 40 percent and 75 percent, Nipah remains a serious public health threat wherever it emerges, according to the Indian local media the Economist Times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Global Times 
                        &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Global Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:25:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiYkFVX3lxTE5sZjJaMDhLREMtemxXbWhvOXFsT3NmQjRheGo5YlZlSjVlR3lhT2d0OU53clpDWkRJVUJOYmRxQjQ1NFkyeWVxeEl5OGJTU0trOHExNkxva1pwci1NX1VGNzJn</guid></item><item><title>症状被解释为未治愈的致命病毒爆发，并报告了“流行病潜力” - LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/world-news/nipah-virus-symptoms-india-468455-20260125</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;India is facing at least five confirmed cases of a Nipah virus outbreak, as nearly 100 people have been asked to quarantine at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It appears to be &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/india-nipah-virus-outbreak-symptoms-deadly-illness-no-cure-who-warning-577116-20260124"&gt;spreading in hospitals&lt;/a&gt; in the eastern state of West Bengal, with mainly doctors and nurses being affected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/scabies-cases-surge-health-uk-victorian-disease-879811-20260123"&gt;deadly virus&lt;/a&gt; has no cure, no vaccine and is classified as a high-risk pathogen by the World &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; Organisation (WHO).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;At least two cases have been reported at the private Narayana Multispeciality Hospital in Barasat, West Bengal, 16 miles from the capital city Kolkata.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“Two nurses at a private hospital are infected with Nipah virus, and one of them is in critical condition,” Mr Narayan Swaroop Nigam, Principal Secretary, Health and Family Welfare Department, West Bengal, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/global-health/science-and-disease/health-experts-scramble-to-contain-nipah-outbreak-india/"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; The Telegraph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The outlet reports that out of the 180 people tested, 20 high risk contacts have been quarantined, as one person is said to be in critical condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“All of them are asymptomatic and tested negative. We will again test them before their 21-day quarantine ends,” Nigam said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;At least five confirmed cases of a Nipah virus have been reported in West Bengal (C. K Thanseer/DeFodi images via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is the Nipah virus?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Nipah virus is a bat-borne pathogen transferred from &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/animals"&gt;animals&lt;/a&gt; to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Fruit bats, in particular, are natural hosts, with pigs acting as intermediate hosts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It can spread through direct contact with infected animals, contaminated food, or human-to-human contact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The WHO &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/nipah-virus"&gt;reports&lt;/a&gt; that the mortality rate is estimated at 40 percent to 75 percent, and that the 'there is no treatment or vaccine available for either people or animals'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Nipah virus is a bat-borne pathogen (Soumyabrata Roy/NurPhoto via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Symptoms of the Nipah virus&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Human infections range from asymptomatic infection to acute respiratory infection (mild, severe), and fatal encephalitis," the WHO said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Symptoms typically include 'fever, headaches, myalgia (muscle pain), vomiting and sore throat'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;This can be followed by 'dizziness, drowsiness, altered consciousness, and neurological signs that indicate acute encephalitis'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Some people can also experience atypical pneumonia and severe respiratory problems, including acute respiratory distress," the WHO adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Encephalitis and seizures occur in severe cases, progressing to coma within 24 to 48 hours."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;'Fever, headaches, myalgia (muscle pain), vomiting and sore throat' are the reported symptoms of Nipah virus (NIH-NIAID/Image Point FR/BSIP/Universal Images Group via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Past outbreaks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Nipah virus was first identified around 1998 during a severe outbreak in Malaysia and Singapore, where pigs acted as the intermediate host.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Since 2001, Bangladesh has experienced almost annual outbreaks, often linked to consumption of contaminated date palm sap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;India has reported repeated outbreaks, notably in West Bengal in 2001 and 2007, then in Kerala from 2018 onwards with several fatalities. Sporadic cases have also occurred in the Philippines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;A total of 754 human NiV cases with 435 deaths (fatality rate: 58 percent) were reported globally, according &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S277270762400105X"&gt;to&lt;/a&gt; 2024 stats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Bangladesh recorded the highest incidences (341 cases and 241 deaths; fatality rate: 71 percent).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 17:20:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQNVhzcHdMYWNXa3FyMDlGMlp0Y0E2U3Z3ekw3Z0Y5S2tFUEhTZkF4OGVxNG5MeW1wMUF5VjBQYWk0c2FreGxlQ2xnM0dFYTJCbkJJVHk5dURNdDdmMXJqN0ktUllwRXUxeHpsWmtGOEVyVTdRbVJDeXpIaFNPQ1V1NUJGTl9zRmV4VFQ0</guid></item><item><title>意见| Bill Foege的乐观态度帮助世界从天花中拯救出来-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2023/10/02/foege-smallpox-eradication-surveillance-containment/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QTUDFQQGN5CHHKKCXLG7AAIRUI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Celine Gounder is a physician and epidemiologist and a senior fellow at KFF. She is also the editor at large for public health at KFF Health News and the host of the podcast “Epidemic.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="M5W5GFRBB5GH5CGIWYB75RQCTM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Bill Foege had been summoned to the U.S. Embassy in New Delhi. The American ambassador to India, Daniel Patrick Moynihan, was not happy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 16:50:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxOcFVHRkI5R212bG1EbzhCQTJWNFdEOHh4d0RxSHhMd3VNSndrSUZ6Q3pROFhkVFh3V0Q1cWJFUkpwUjlrMWN0Um9va0FEMWRoeXY3YzVoS1htNXNYa1RsMnI3VUpjdFEzdmpxSjNUUWRsXzF0TERYRjBVTGNMakhDazBFcUNOUzdoRlZfRU1lRnpfLXZWU0ZsbzJxZ09Td1ZHNUNNWTFn</guid></item><item><title>令人担忧的服用欧米茄-3的副作用，尽管它是世界上最常见的补充剂之一- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/omega-3-supplement-side-effects-coronary-heart-disease-413957-20260124</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;New research has suggested there may be a worrying side effect to healthy people taking Omega-3 supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;From iron to Vitamin D and beyond, the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/lifestyle"&gt;supplements&lt;/a&gt; market has expanded rapidly in recent years, with the Smithfield Agency &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://smithfieldagency.com/insights/the-booming-uk-supplements-market-media-planning-and-buying-insights/"&gt;projecting&lt;/a&gt; an annual increase of 6.53 percent between 2024 and 2029.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Meanwhile, &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/money"&gt;revenue&lt;/a&gt; from the the sheer number of people - myself included - who take supplements reached $0.78bn (£585 million)&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;But how beneficial are these tiny pills really?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Concerns have been raised about taking Vitamin D, a supplement &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="http://www.nhs.uk/conditions/vitamins-and-minerals/vitamin-d/"&gt;recommended&lt;/a&gt; for daily intake by the NHS, with people urged to stop taking them if they &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/vitamin-d-dosage-nhs-symptoms-605918-20260124"&gt;notice certain symptoms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;And it's not just Vitamin D either, with a 2024 study highlighting worrying side effects which may be caused by Omega-3 supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Supplements such as fish or flaxseed oil provide the body with Omega-3, a fatty acid found in certain fish (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is Omega-3?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Omega-3 fatty acids are crucial for the body's ability to build brain cells, support heart health and reduce inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The body cannot produce these acids naturally, however it can be found in fish, such as salmon and mackerel, as well as algae and plant sources such as flaxseeds, chia seeds and walnuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;According to the NHS, it's &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.nhs.uk/live-well/eat-well/food-types/different-fats-nutrition/#:~:text=Most%20people%20get%20enough%20omega%2D6%20in%20their,more%20about%20healthy%20eating%20as%20a%20vegetarian."&gt;recommended&lt;/a&gt; that you eat two portions of fish each week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Omega-3 supplements - such as Cod Liver Oil or Flaxseed Oil - are also widely used to boost Omega levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What are the worrying side effects of Omega-3?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Given the importance of healthy fats in our diets, you'd think taking Omega-3 supplements would be a pretty safe bet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;However, one study has suggested there could be worrying side effects from taking the supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Research carried out at Sun Yat-Sen University in China and &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://bmjmedicine.bmj.com/content/3/1/e000451"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in the BMJ showed associations between healthy adults who'd taken fish oils and an increased risk of atrial fibrillation (irregular heartbeat); heart attack, stroke, and heart failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;After studying 400,000 participants in the UK Biobank across 12 years, the research found that healthy adults with no known heart conditions had a 13 percent heightened risk of developing atrial fibrillation and a five percent heightened risk of having a stroke after frequent use of fish oils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;One study suggested a link between Omega-3 supplements and an increased risk in heart issues in otherwise healthy people (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;However the study revealed the opposite in adults with pre-existing heart conditions, noting that patients had a 15 percent lower risk of progressing from atrial fibrillation to a heart attack, and a nine percent lower risk of progressing from heart failure to death when compared to those who did not take a supplement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Should we be worried about taking Omega-3 supplements?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Following the study, the British Heart Foundation &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.bhf.org.uk/informationsupport/heart-matters-magazine/news/behind-the-headlines/fish-oil-supplements"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; a response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The BHF pointed out that while the study does indeed show a link between fish oil and an increased risk of heart conditions in otherwise healthy people, it did not prove cause and effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It's also worth noting that the type of fish oil supplement and frequency in which participants had taken them were also not noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:35:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxOMHFoWTdjcFVZUGtuTXJUenF0akVYV1AyT0RWU01VNFowdl9MZ0NNNnhTdk5hSWdoaFE5WnhKbTRsQVpOeHhHaXhHUDRWNGVIYlJWQWZPWnVkYW90Z1Q3MEdXYTY4dFFYcXI1NVNfcEs4em5wVTE5bXU4TlN2c21BRGt2Z2daTm9aYTFLYmc4N0pvSW1mYmZSSVdTQTBaYkhiNURuZmFJbWpqVjg</guid></item><item><title>随着邻国加强筛查，印度报告了尼帕病毒病例- news.cgtn.com</title><link>https://news.cgtn.com/news/2026-01-25/India-reports-Nipah-virus-cases-as-neighbors-step-up-screening-1KegwyYCv4Y/p.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dialog-body"&gt;
                        
                        &lt;p class="dialog-content"&gt;
                            By continuing to browse our site you agree to our use of cookies, revised Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. You can change your cookie settings through your browser.
                        &lt;/p&gt;
                        
                        &lt;p class="dialog-clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                        &lt;p class="dialog-confirm"&gt;
                            &lt;span class="confirm-icon"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
                            &lt;span&gt;I agree&lt;/span&gt;
                        &lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>news.cgtn.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:17:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxNd2N6WDRxNENUOW11RXZqS0N6Yk1kRXEzOXRYWV9qMUQyMHNkbVRiYzNWQmlXZmFRTkxXcW0ySm80MzlXTVdnSm1WbUFMQ0tMTU4wS3FRcXNXUGUzZnByMEZ1UHBfWUdCT0FiOFdFZFM1d3RYZloxV3FkWVh4aEFIbXpyUmdZaGRnang2UGljOUE0WTFiYUJQOERSd2hKRF9NRXBuMG10Wk5sVWRJUl9QU1BOVWdreVg3ZU1v</guid></item><item><title>日本海滩上从未见过的有毒海洋物种，科学家以武士的名字命名-印度防务评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/venomous-sea-species-japanese-beach-scientists-named-after-samurai/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content dynamic-entry-content" itemprop="text"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;At first glance, it resembled the infamous Portuguese man o’ war. But after detailed analysis, researchers confirmed it was a completely new species, &lt;em&gt;Physalia mikazuki&lt;/em&gt;, a venomous tropical invader that found its way to the cooler waters of Sendai Bay.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Named after the crescent-moon-shaped helmet of the 16th-century warlord Date Masamune, this newly discovered siphonophore is raising alarms about shifting marine life patterns, climate-driven ocean currents, and potential risks to human safety.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Rare Find on a Temperate Beach&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In July 2024, locals strolling along Gamo Beach in Japan’s Tohoku region noticed something unusual, bright blue balloon-like creatures stranded in the sand. These beaches are historically too cold for tropical species, which made the sighting immediately curious. Among the first to investigate was researcher Yoshiki Ochiai, who happened to be in the area on an unrelated &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/marine-science/articles/10.3389/fmars.2025.1653958/full" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“&lt;em&gt;I scooped it up, put it in a ziplock bag, hopped on my scooter, and brought it back to the lab&lt;/em&gt;,” Ochiai explained. What followed was a meticulous examination that revealed clear structural differences between this creature and the known Portuguese man o’ war.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/morphological-characteristics-of-physalia-mikazuki-sp-nov-collected-from-gamo-beach-sendai-city-miyagi-prefecture-japan-1200x727.jpg" alt="Morphological Characteristics Of Physalia Mikazuki Sp. Nov. Collected From Gamo Beach, Sendai City, Miyagi Prefecture, Japan." class="wp-image-105212" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/morphological-characteristics-of-physalia-mikazuki-sp-nov-collected-from-gamo-beach-sendai-city-miyagi-prefecture-japan-scaled.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/morphological-characteristics-of-physalia-mikazuki-sp-nov-collected-from-gamo-beach-sendai-city-miyagi-prefecture-japan-420x255.jpg 420w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/morphological-characteristics-of-physalia-mikazuki-sp-nov-collected-from-gamo-beach-sendai-city-miyagi-prefecture-japan-520x315.jpg 520w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Morphological characteristics of Physalia mikazuki sp. nov. collected from Gamo Beach, Sendai City, Miyagi Prefecture, Japan – © Frontiers in Marine Science&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.zmescience.com/science/japanese-scientists-find-new-portuguese-man-of-war-and-give-it-a-samurai-name/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;ZME Science&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the new species’ float only reaches up to 72 mm, far smaller than the familiar &lt;em&gt;Physalia physalis&lt;/em&gt;, which can grow to 300 mm. Its colors range from deep blue to purple, and its translucent membrane shows bluish-green tones. Internally, its feeding and fishing tentacles are uniquely shaped and arranged, making it unmistakably distinct from its relatives.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;A Name Rooted in Local History&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The name &lt;em&gt;mikazuki&lt;/em&gt; comes from the Japanese word for “&lt;em&gt;crescent moon&lt;/em&gt;” and pays tribute to Date Masamune, the founder of Sendai City. The crescent-shaped float of the creature mirrors the warlord’s iconic helmet, linking this scientific discovery to a symbol of local cultural identity.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This connection between taxonomy and history adds another layer to the find. It’s not just a new species, it’s one that carries the region’s legacy in its name. As described by the &lt;a href="https://www.tohoku.ac.jp/en/press/researchers_in_japan_discover_new_jellyfish_species_deserving_of_a_samurai_warrior_name.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;research team at Tohoku University&lt;/a&gt;, the process of identification was slow and demanding. Lead author Chanikarn Yongstar highlighted the effort it took to match each anatomical detail with illustrations found in historical marine biology texts. “&lt;em&gt;A real challenge when you look at just how many tangled parts it has&lt;/em&gt;,” she remarked.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Until now, scientists believed the genus &lt;em&gt;Physalia&lt;/em&gt; only included one or two valid species. The emergence of &lt;em&gt;Physalia mikazuki&lt;/em&gt; not only adds to that list but shifts our understanding of where and how these creatures can survive.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Climate Shifts Enable Tropical Migration&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The sudden appearance of &lt;em&gt;Physalia mikazuki&lt;/em&gt; in northern Japan isn’t random. Scientists traced its journey using particle tracking simulations, which showed how abnormal heatwaves and warm ocean currents in 2024 likely carried the species far beyond its usual tropical range.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;This movement, driven by &lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/climate-hope-earths-ocean-current-stable/" data-type="post" data-id="71793"&gt;climate anomalies&lt;/a&gt;, brings not just a new species but new risks. Like its relatives, &lt;em&gt;mikazuki&lt;/em&gt; is venomous. Its tentacles can inflict painful stings on humans, raising public health concerns in an area that rarely faced such dangers in the past. This could impact tourism in the Tohoku region, especially along beaches unaccustomed to the presence of stinging marine life.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Ecologically, the impact could be deeper. As a carnivorous predator, &lt;em&gt;Physalia mikazuki&lt;/em&gt; feeds on fish larvae and small plankton, two critical components of the local marine food web. Its presence could destabilize predator-prey relationships and interfere with commercial fisheries in the region.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOQ3gyejRGdms2ak40UEJGamQ2dzNqN3V2WjBuQ0dwNXFSZ29FUE96RW9wS29uQ1VPREpuU0hCRDRsMG4xRTczS2tHYWQwQndiRk5ZWjBlMVRRWDNGdGtkODFFMUdXUm4wQldoSVRGS0NoWjE2dEFYdkxDMVh6b0R6OHhEUldGWWFIRWp4YlRfck8xeEN4UTBWUGh4ZENXdVA3</guid></item><item><title>当你吃像鸡蛋这样富含胆碱的食物时，你的大脑会发生什么-非常健康</title><link>https://www.verywellhealth.com/choline-in-eggs-brain-function-benefits-11884380</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="health-sc-page_1-0" class="comp health-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content article-content expert-content right-rail__offset lock-journey" data-sc-sticky-offset="60" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[400, 1400, 1400, 1700, 2000, 2200, 2400, 2600, 2800]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="health-sc-block-callout--key-takeaway_1-0" class="comp health-sc-block-callout--key-takeaway health-sc-block-callout-base mntl-sc-block-callout mntl-block theme-key-takeaway theme-key-takeaway" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-callout-heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block-callout-body_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-body mntl-text-block expert-content"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eating choline-rich foods like eggs may help slow brain aging and support overall brain health.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most Americans do not get enough choline in their diets.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choline deficiency is more prevalent among women.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Eggs contain a variety of essential nutrients, including protein and healthy fats, making them a popular breakfast staple. A new study has found that choline, specifically found in egg yolk, may be key to slower brain aging and improved health over time.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-low-choline-levels-may-signal-early-alzheimers-risk"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Low Choline Levels May Signal Early Alzheimer's Risk &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The study, published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Aging and Disease&lt;/em&gt;, found that people with obesity had significantly lower levels of choline in their blood than those at a healthy weight.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Lower choline levels were also associated with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/insulin-resistance-vs-diabetes-8423993" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;worse insulin resistance&lt;/a&gt;, inflammation, and liver dysfunction—all of which are established &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/simple-ways-to-prevent-dementia-and-alzheimers-disease-11790305" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;risk factors for Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt;, said the study co-author &lt;a href="https://search.asu.edu/profile/2336023" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Jessica M. Judd, PhD&lt;/a&gt;, an associate research scientist at the ASU-Banner Neurodegenerative Disease Research Center.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Strikingly, obese participants also showed changes in a blood marker called neurofilament light (NfL) chain, a marker of neuronal damage," Judd said. "Where we found higher levels of this marker, we also found lower levels of choline, which appeared many years before disorders such as Alzheimer’s are typically diagnosed."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Together, these findings suggest that &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/choline-5084871" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;improving low choline levels&lt;/a&gt; may help address an early, changeable risk factor for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/the-link-between-blood-sugar-and-dementia-11827745" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;metabolic and brain-related disease&lt;/a&gt;, Judd said.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-the-study-canand-canttell-us"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What the Study Can—and Can’t—Tell Us &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The study focused on relatively young adults with obesity, yet their combination of low choline and high NfL resembled patterns seen in older adults with cognitive impairment, said &lt;a href="https://www.american.edu/cas/faculty/dford.cfm" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Dara Ford, PhD, RD&lt;/a&gt;, program director of the Master of Science in Nutrition Education at American University.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This suggests that "metabolic stress earlier in life could affect the brain later in life," Ford added.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Still, Ford cautioned that many details remain unclear. The study was small, cross-sectional, and not demographically representative, meaning it could not establish cause and effect. It also did not account for participants’ diet or other lifestyle factors that may have influenced the results.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "It is too early to make any definitive statements about the role of choline in the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/alzheimers-disease-7111202" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;development of Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt;," Ford said. "There is much for us to learn."&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-its-important-to-get-enough-choline"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Why It's Important to Get Enough Choline &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While more evidence is needed to identify a definitive link between choline and Alzheimer’s, approximately 90% of Americans fail to meet the recommended daily amount of choline.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Choline deficiency is particularly pronounced in women, Judd said, and similar trends are seen worldwide. Therefore, Judd and Ford both emphasized that ensuring you get enough choline in your diet remains essential.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Choline is involved in the metabolism and transport of lipids and &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/neurotransmitters-8706506" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;neurotransmitter synthesis&lt;/a&gt;, and plays a role in brain function, heart health, and liver health," Ford said. "It may be beneficial to aim to increase choline consumption through a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/tips-for-a-balanced-diet-11802848" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;balanced and varied diet&lt;/a&gt; of whole foods."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-much-choline-do-you-need"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Much Choline Do You Need? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The adequate intake for choline for U.S. adults is 425 mg per day for women and 550 mg per day for men. The recommended intake increases to 450 mg per day during pregnancy and to 550 mg per day during lactation.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While egg yolks are the richest source of choline, Ford said other dietary sources also contain this nutrient, including:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Liver&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cruciferous vegetables, such as broccoli, cauliflower, collard greens, and Brussels sprouts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Beans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Peanuts&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Poultry&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fish&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dairy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pasta&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "We also do make some choline in the body, though not enough to meet needs," said Ford. "Choline is not a magical cure-all, but ensuring a balanced and varied diet rich in whole foods may increase intake and certainly improve health outcomes."&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="post-article_1-0" class="comp post-article mntl-block"&gt;

&lt;div id="author-bio_1-0" class="comp author-bio"&gt;

&lt;p class="author-bio__bio-text"&gt;
&lt;span class="author-bio__bio-title"&gt;By &lt;a href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/mira-miller-5202407"&gt;Mira Miller&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Miller is a journalist specializing in mental health, women's health, and culture. Her work is published in outlets ranging from Vice to Healthnews.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="trust-ribbon_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon trust-ribbon-expandable-block"&gt; 
&lt;div class="loc expandable-content"&gt;&lt;div id="trust-ribbon__feedback-block_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon__feedback-block article-feedback mntl-article-feedback"&gt; 
&lt;div class="article-feedback__success-section js-success-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;Thanks for your feedback!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="article-feedback__feedback-section js-feedback-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;What is your feedback?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;button id="helpful-button_1-0" class="comp helpful-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Helpful
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="report-error-button_1-0" class="comp report-error-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Report an Error
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="other-button_1-0" class="comp other-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Other
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-x close-button"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-x" href="#icon-x"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Verywell Health</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 14:03:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNbjZUdmt0V2RyYXRMaUVSWnlBY2FCTU0xdmgtNWt5SkpzeEFZc0xITm1XYVljRzN2c2tpMGMwazN6TkdYQ1Bza0MyY2JDZjJDa0ItTjJ0RGVjTUVnUDQwUzViQklNTnY4VjhaRGY1ZmxLbGVxZEhIX0J2blZ2bDIxN2dmLTJPdw</guid></item><item><title>拥有25年经验的心脏外科医生解释了当您的omega-3水平低时会发生什么： “风险增加15-30 ％......” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/heart-surgeon-with-25-years-of-experience-explains-what-happens-when-omega-3-levels-are-low-15-30-percent-higher-risk-101769347502707.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt;&lt;p class="content"&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/dicomega3-benefits-and-dosage-explained-by-a-doctor-find-top-rated-omega-3-supplements-on-amazon-india-for-daily-healt-101766122868355.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Omega-3"&gt;Omega-3 &lt;/a&gt;fatty acids play a critical role in protecting both heart and brain health, yet many people may be walking around with dangerously low levels without realising it. These essential fats are not only linked to reduced inflammation and healthier &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/fortis-cardiologist-warns-early-morning-walks-in-winters-may-increase-heart-attack-risks-blood-vessels-101766919666081.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="blood vessels"&gt;blood vessels&lt;/a&gt;, but are also considered an important biomarker for long-term cardiovascular risk. Despite their significance, omega-3 levels are rarely checked during routine health screenings, leaving deficiencies unnoticed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="artImage leadImage"&gt;&lt;figcaption class=""&gt;Read more to discover how you can improve your omega-3 levels! (Unsplash)&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span&gt;Also Read | &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/heart-surgeon-with-25-years-of-experience-shares-his-5-step-morning-routine-for-a-healthier-start-to-the-day-101769057990119.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Heart surgeon with 25 years of experience shares his 5-step morning routine for a healthier start to the day"&gt;Heart surgeon with 25 years of experience shares his 5-step morning routine for a healthier start to the day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dr Jeremy London, a board-certified cardiothoracic surgeon with over 25 years of experience, is breaking down the importance of omega-3 fatty acids for optimal &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/risk-of-cardiovascular-disease" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="cardiovascular"&gt;cardiovascular &lt;/a&gt;function and explaining why it’s essential to have your levels checked to ensure you’re not deficient. In an Instagram video shared on September 22, 2025, the heart surgeon outlines what happens when omega-3 levels are low and explains practical ways to improve them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why should you check your omega-3 levels?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;According to Dr London, nearly 80 to 90 per cent of the American population is deficient in omega-3s, with levels falling below the optimal omega-3 index required for effective cardiovascular protection.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; He explains that this is significant because low levels of omega-3 fatty acids have been consistently linked to a higher risk of heart disease and poorer &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/heart-surgeon-reveals-the-1-thing-you-should-absolutely-avoid-if-you-want-a-strong-heart-sedentary-lifestyle-101768789825286.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="cardiovascular"&gt;cardiovascular&lt;/a&gt; outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span&gt;He states, “80 to 90 percent of the US population falls below the optimal omega-3 index for cardiovascular protection. My wife recently had her levels tested, and she was actually deficient. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Now, having a low omega-3 index has been linked to higher rates of cardiovascular events and mortality, up to a 15 to 30 percent higher risk when compared to those with a higher index.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why are omega-3s important?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dr London highlights that omega-3 fatty acids - particularly EPA and DHA - have been shown to support heart health by lowering triglyceride levels, reducing inflammation and improving overall blood vessel function.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span&gt;He explains, “Omega-3 fatty acids, specifically EPA and DHA, have been shown to reduce serum triglycerides, reduce &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/lifestyle-coach-says-protein-obsession-in-india-is-causing-inflammation-blood-sugar-spikes-lists-3-harmful-ingredients-101768897900919.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="inflammation"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt;, and actually improve endothelial function, which is the lining of the blood vessel wall itself.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span&gt;The surgeon outlines the following risks linked to low levels of omega-3 fatty acids:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coronary heart disease (CHD) mortality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cardiovascular disease (CVD) events&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;All-cause mortality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Early-onset coronary atherosclerosis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to improve low levels?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to the heart surgeon, simple solutions can help improve your omega-3 index. He recommends the following:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Increase your intake of fatty fish: Salmon, mackerel, and trout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;High-quality omega-3 supplementation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. It is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 13:45:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAJBVV95cUxPNG5QbnQ5NTY5MHA1NVdjVExvZ0pnYlRPaFh0YlM0QWRETE5fWU5JMFJSRERLU3lRN0hDZnZCUjVPR2tSVHMzNHZCa3htejQ3dHZFNmpHTmNrWFlUMWlkWkpGbzFwQ2RfTE53bVdwSTlfTWhCNmtDMlJDOXBiQ0xTLTdSOE1GamtTbzhvVWQ2ZkFQMnVQdmtXY0IwZFpxS1RYLWZPc1p2SkxSQTJaeUhoTmh3UkxhLTJqbU5fTF9QQ1Y4YjJxemRPR3pqd3pJNnUxSUtPRDFqTVJUNE8xdEdOcGNyVzNqR05mczlQQUk2ZGpRaUtIN0NXa1ZNd3NVcE1WbVZKenhMV2MtOTMwc3NWVjJxLVPSAZoCQVVfeXFMTzB6NEVaNTNHSmRKVFkyZ3hkNkdsNnk1UWlNVWRZTE5SSFRKbG1IZFY2RG1CckRxTEMyM1VtSERHeGtMb0NGSTJCOU1UdTJteTJVNkJTY3R4a3FBRG56akFXcXlkbU1takxBWloxQzEtMjh3S1FIbGxBU2xnMGtNSEZOMTBXaTBON2p3SVN4cDk0UVZYanE3VmRSWlBib0djanFmNUxYSEZxVDFha0RqUXVSSlJROXRPOUFWVXppQ21ZdHktcmdvSGhGRmZZSlVMUWRaV2RoaXhLdXF6d19WeDNwWlRza251akszUjdDTXZ0RW9GSDhFLVJrUjltbkVTa1lvN1dhYnRzcDZ0bjdPWk9mQ1l4TFZidVVR</guid></item></channel></rss>