<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>橙汁对身体的影响可能远远超过科学家的想象- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/orange-juice-may-do-much-more-for-your-body-than-scientists-ever-realized</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Most of us think of orange juice as a simple breakfast habit, something you pour without much thought. Yet scientists are discovering that this everyday drink may be doing far more in the body than quenching thirst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study has shown that regular orange juice consumption can influence the activity of thousands of genes inside our immune cells. Many of these genes help control blood pressure, calm inflammation, and manage the way the body processes sugar, all of which play an important role in long-term &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/heart-health-60216"&gt;heart health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/mnfr.70299"&gt;The study&lt;/a&gt; followed adults who drank 500ml of pure pasteurised orange juice every day for two months. After 60 days, many genes associated with inflammation and higher blood pressure had become less active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cortisol-cocktails-are-the-latest-stress-busting-trend-heres-the-science"&gt;'Cortisol Cocktails' Are The Latest Stress-Busting Trend. Here's The Science.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These included NAMPT, IL6, IL1B and NLRP3, which usually switch on when the body is under stress. Another gene known as SGK1, which affects the kidneys' ability to hold onto sodium (salt), also became less active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such changes match &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/319862089_Health_Benefits_of_Orange_Juice_and_Citrus_Flavonoids_Applications_in_Functional_Foods"&gt;previous findings&lt;/a&gt; that daily orange juice drinking can reduce blood pressure in young adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is noteworthy because it offers a possible explanation for why orange juice has been linked to better heart health &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/10408398.2020.1865263"&gt;in several trials&lt;/a&gt;. The new work shows that the drink does not simply raise blood sugar. Instead, it appears to trigger small shifts in the body's regulatory systems that reduce inflammation and help blood vessels relax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Natural compounds in oranges, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7284956/"&gt;particularly hesperidin&lt;/a&gt;, a citrus flavonoid known for its antioxidant and anti-inflammatory effects, seem to influence processes related to high blood pressure, cholesterol balance and the way the body handles sugar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_183296" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-183296" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/orange_juice_642.jpg" alt="oranges and orange juice" class="wp-image-183296 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/orange_juice_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/orange_juice_642-600x421.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-183296" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Compounds in oranges affect pathways linked with high blood pressure. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADaqPcktq0/"&gt;La_Cruz/Getty Images Pro/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The response also varies by body size. People carrying more weight tended to show greater changes in genes involved in fat metabolism, while leaner volunteers showed stronger effects on inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34060162/"&gt;systematic review of controlled trials&lt;/a&gt; involving 639 participants from 15 studies found that regular orange juice consumption lowered insulin resistance and blood cholesterol levels. Insulin resistance is a key feature of pre- &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="183269" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, and high cholesterol is an established risk factor for heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36383179/"&gt;Another analysis&lt;/a&gt; focusing on overweight and obese adults found small reductions in systolic blood pressure and increases in &lt;a href="https://labtestsonline.org.uk/tests/hdl-cholesterol-test"&gt;high-density lipoprotein&lt;/a&gt; (HDL), often called the good cholesterol, after several weeks of daily orange juice consumption. Although these changes are modest, even slight improvements in blood pressure and cholesterol can make a meaningful difference when maintained over many years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More clues come from studies that examine metabolites, the tiny molecules produced as the body processes food. A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36383179/"&gt;recent review&lt;/a&gt; found that orange juice influences pathways related to energy use, communication between cells and inflammation. It may also affect the gut microbiome, which is increasingly understood to play a role in heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37469434/"&gt;One study&lt;/a&gt; showed that drinking blood orange juice for a month increased the number of gut bacteria that produce short-chain fatty acids. These compounds help maintain healthy blood pressure and reduce inflammation. Volunteers also showed improved blood sugar control and lower levels of inflammatory markers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/metabolic-syndrome/"&gt;metabolic syndrome&lt;/a&gt;, a cluster of risk factors that includes high blood pressure, raised blood sugar and excess body fat, may see particular benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one study, daily orange juice consumption improved the function of the lining of blood vessels, known as endothelial function, in &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/proceedings-of-the-nutrition-society/article/orange-juice-combined-to-a-healthyeating-pattern-improved-endothelial-function-and-reduced-global-risk-of-chd-in-metabolic-syndrome-patients/D712014D8B24A2CC37CB9A99059F41D2"&gt;68 obese participants&lt;/a&gt;. Endothelial function describes how well blood vessels relax and widen, and better function is associated with a lower risk of heart attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all studies report the same outcomes. A &lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/proceedings-of-the-nutrition-society/article/orange-juice-combined-to-a-healthyeating-pattern-improved-endothelial-function-and-reduced-global-risk-of-chd-in-metabolic-syndrome-patients/D712014D8B24A2CC37CB9A99059F41D2"&gt;broader analysis&lt;/a&gt; of blood fat concentrations found that although levels of &lt;a href="https://labtestsonline.org.uk/tests/ldl-cholesterol-test"&gt;low density lipoprotein&lt;/a&gt; (LDL), often called the bad cholesterol, often fall, other lipid measurements, such as triglycerides and HDL, may not change much. Even so, people who regularly drink orange juice may still benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://lipidworld.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/1476-511X-12-119"&gt;A study&lt;/a&gt; of 129 workers in an orange juice factory in Brazil reported lower blood concentrations of &lt;a href="https://labtestsonline.org.uk/tests/apo-b"&gt;apolipoprotein B&lt;/a&gt;, or apo-B, a marker that reflects the number of cholesterol-carrying particles linked to heart attack risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Altogether, the evidence challenges the idea that drinking citrus fruit juice is simply consuming sugar in a glass. Whole fruit remains the better choice because of its fibre, but a modest daily glass of pure orange juice appears to have effects that build up over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These include easing inflammation, supporting healthier blood flow and improving several blood markers linked to long-term heart health. It is a reminder that everyday foods can have more influence on the body than we might expect.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/270492/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/david-c-gaze-312661"&gt;David C. Gaze&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer in Chemical Pathology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-westminster-916"&gt;University of Westminster&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/your-daily-orange-juice-could-be-helping-your-heart-270492"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 01:04:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxPdkUtTGZKN1MzRGZzUjFPRFJSV1JMVnpZOTNRRWZ5Y2lPc0lTRy1GTUZLNmVSdlEyYW91VHRzNS1pLXNkcUxwNVIzVXFRNnRrTUFrZVJHakxIa3ZfVnlidUFubWRCZlV3VlFid0VpZDFEY1JDbXlhc2p3ZVBzS0YxRW9HVG02TUxRODlrbTcxUlhzbXh0R21HdzM0ZFRJNmo0cDN1SA</guid></item><item><title>睡眠专家揭示梦中牙齿脱落背后的令人不安的含义-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/sleep-expert-reveals-disturbing-meanings-behind-teeth-falling-out-in-your-dreams/articleshow/125662600.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’ve ever jolted awake convinced your teeth were crumbling out of your mouth, you’re in good company. A recent survey of 2,000 people in the UK, commissioned by Netflix in connection with its animated film In Your Dreams, suggests that teeth-falling-out dreams sit alongside falling, being chased and unexpectedly turning up naked in public as some of the nation’s most frequently reported nocturnal experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than dismissing them as random, one dream expert says they can act like a quiet guide to what’s really on your mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;5 Simple Bedtime Practices From Sadhguru For Better Health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;“Dreams are like a friend” &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Delphi Ellis, a qualified counsellor, mindfulness practitioner and author of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Answers In The Dark: Grief, Sleep and How Dreams Can Help You Heal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;, was asked to interpret the patterns that emerged from the Netflix survey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;She told the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Daily Mail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Dreams are like a friend, they can softly nudge us in the direction of what we want, point us towards what might help us heal, or offer insight, even answers, into a problem that's occupying our mind. It's one reason we say, 'sleep on it'.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;We may or may not act on them, but Ellis says it’s at least worth paying attention. “Like a friend, we can choose to acknowledge or ignore them, it's up to us what we do with the content of our dreams, but it's always worth listening to what a dream has to say.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One dream in particular clearly struck a nerve in the survey: teeth falling out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What it could mean when your teeth fall out in a dream &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the familiar catalogue of unsettling dreams, one stands out as uniquely distressing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While being chased or falling can feel metaphorically frightening, dreaming about your teeth feels bodily, primal, almost horror-coded. Around 21 percent of respondents said they’ve dreamt of their teeth falling out, sometimes crumbling like chalk, sometimes dropping into their hands, sometimes suddenly vanishing from their mouth. It’s one of the most upsetting dream types precisely because it feels so physical and intimately connected to identity, appearance and even survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellis suggests it may be linked to how secure you feel about status, money or what you’re “worth” in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the West we generally exchange our teeth for money when we are little,” she explained. That early swap, tooth for coin, can leave a symbolic trace: teeth become quietly linked in our minds with value, reward and what we “deserve”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In that light, a dream where they fall out might reflect anxiety about security or standing in life rather than dentistry itself. A promotion that didn’t happen, financial pressure, feeling like you’re losing your grip on a role or image you’ve worked hard for – any of those could show up in this sort of dream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For others, Ellis says, the symbolism leans more towards loss than money. “In some cultures, dreaming of teeth as they literally are (as bone) may symbolize anxiety about losing someone significant.” That could be a fear about a relationship changing, a loved one becoming more distant, or a general dread of grief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, if your teeth are falling out in a dream, your brain may be playing out deeper worries about what you might be about to lose – whether that’s status, stability or someone close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Falling, running, flying: other common dream themes&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Netflix-commissioned survey asked 2,000 UK adults about their most frequent dreams. Ellis emphasises that these aren’t definitive meanings, just recurring emotional patterns, but the data reveals how common these themes really are:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Falling – 53% Unable to run – 42% Partner cheating – 22% Someone dying – 21% Teeth falling out – 21% Snogging a celebrity – 20% Exam you haven't revised for – 19% Flying – 18% Friends/family being mean – 16% Being late – 15% Finding money – 14% Unable to find the toilet – 12% Naked in public – 12% &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Falling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common dream of all in the survey was falling – reported by more than half of those asked. Ellis links this to uncertainty and change:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It happens if we're not sure where we're going or where we'll end up,” she said. “It's especially common after redundancy, retirement and other major life changes. The adventure awaits, but can be scary as we venture into the unknown.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also draws a line between that lingering dream of falling and the sharp “jolt” some people feel just as they’re dropping off to sleep. That physical startle, she notes, “can (ironically) be caused by over tiredness or point to signs of stress”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Being chased but unable to run&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly 42 percent of people said they’ve dreamt of trying to run, but feeling as if their legs won’t move. Ellis says this can mirror feeling behind or hemmed in in waking life: “The feeling of not being able to run can symbolise being ‘stuck’ in a situation, that progress is too slow, or the fear that whatever it is will ‘catch up’ with them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Partners cheating and people dying&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just over a fifth of respondents said they had dreamt of a partner cheating. Ellis is clear that this usually speaks more to fear than to fact. “Dreaming about infidelity often signals a fear that it could occur, rather than serving as a warning that it already has, particularly for those who have experienced betrayal in the past,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;People dying&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Dreams of people dying, reported by a similar proportion, are often about change rather than literal death. Ellis notes that for many parents, dreaming about a child dying is really about watching a particular phase of childhood “end” as they become more independent, and the relationship shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Flying&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 18 percent of people reported dreams of flying. Ellis says how it feels in the dream is crucial. “If the dream is positive and they’re loving it – ‘flying high’ may signify someone enjoying a period of success.” If the mood is anxious or out of control, it might be a sign you feel you should “keep your feet on the ground” for now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="84"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Mean friends and families&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dreams where family or friends are unkind can reflect a quiet worry about belonging. Sixteen percent of people surveyed say they’ve experienced this, and Ellis suggests it may be tied to a fear of exclusion or strained social ties. “If people are being mean, the dream may be a prompt to reconsider who we include in our circle,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Being late&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="92"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dreams about being late, reported by 15 percent of respondents, tend to mirror real-life anxieties around time, performance or pressure. Ellis explains: “In today’s world, it’s natural to fear being late, so this may be a literal dream reflecting what we worry could happen.” But it can also signal the feeling of missing out, socially, professionally or personally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Finding money &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="97"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="98"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finding money in a dream, something 14 percent of people reported, may simply echo financial stress. Ellis notes: “If a person has money worries, it makes sense for them to have this dream; wealth is subjective though, so the money may also be a symbol for something else the dreamer feels might improve their life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="102"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Celebrity romance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="104"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="105"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dreaming of a romantic encounter with a celebrity, about one in five of us have, often reflects admiration or identification. “If we can relate to a particular celebrity’s struggle, or if we see someone… as a role model, or if we admire them – we may dream about them as if they are closer to us than they really are,” Ellis said. It’s less about desire and more about projection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="109"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Unprepared exam&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="111"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="112"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The dreaded no-revision exam dream, still experienced by 19 percent of adults, may reflect feeling unprepared for something in waking life, a conversation, a decision, a responsibility. But Ellis adds it may reach back into feelings from adolescence: “Exams usually happen at school… harking back to past anxieties.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="114"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Unable to find the toilet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="116"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="117"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being unable to find the toilet appears in 12 percent of people’s dreams. Sometimes it really is just your physical body saying Wake up, you need the bathroom. But Ellis notes: “This dream can signify you are in a time of your life where you lack privacy and searching for more private time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="121"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Naked in public&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="123"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="124"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;And finally, being naked in public, also reported by around 12 percent, can indicate vulnerability. Ellis said: “It may reflect the awareness of being ‘on show’ or in the spotlight for some reason… or that we’ve talked about something that left us feeling vulnerable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="127"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="128"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to make sense of your dreams &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="129"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Netflix survey and Ellis’s interpretations offer a useful starting point, but dream meaning is not one-size-fits-all. Two people can have the same dream and take away something completely different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="131"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clinical and cognitive hypnotherapist Sarah Bick, who works with the subconscious mind at Inna Therapies, suggests treating your dreams as personal messages rather than universal codes. She recommends writing your dream down in detail as soon as you wake, then noting what each element brings to mind &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;for you,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; without looking up generic meanings first.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="136"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A symbol like “teeth” might, for one person, immediately call up childhood memories of the tooth fairy and money; for another, it could evoke a painful dental experience, or a parent who worked in healthcare. The same image will sit on top of very different histories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="138"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bick advises connecting the dream back to what’s happening in your life now: current stresses, transitions, or unresolved feelings. From there, you can start to piece together a message that gives you that small “aha” moment, not a prediction of the future, but a reflection of where your mind is already working hard behind the scenes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="141"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="142"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Should you be worried? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="143"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the time, you don’t need to panic about a disturbing dream, even if it’s vivid. Having your teeth fall out at night doesn’t mean they’re about to fall out during the day; dreaming of a partner cheating rarely means they are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="145"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, Ellis and Bick both frame dreams as another channel of information about how you’re coping. A string of anxiety dreams might be your cue to look at stress, sleep routines or unspoken worries. A recurring teeth-falling-out dream might nudge you to examine where you feel insecure about status, money or loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="147"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If dreams are “like a friend”, as Ellis puts it, then even the unsettling ones may be on your side – not trying to frighten you, but drawing your attention to something you’ve been too busy, or too tired, to fully notice when you’re awake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAJBVV95cUxPLTRWekdJU3NLZ2FsOGY4Y0dZbmNrV1Nqa3dYVkJHd1lXN25yVDZMME4zNlZISjlmeWdIZFNtVFluMnhieWFEa2JMUDlWcjliLUhqX3FORnF6RHlMTnZLRGlRYy1uRnA3T1plT2V6dk5hR1lJX1JaM1Y3b1J1Tm1HU0V5cWFwZDZGcERjQk1lUTBibUVfUUVSRTRpRnl2dEl6Nl9ROGJjTlZaSGQ1ZDRoT0lBdnh4enVkZVdXNkZnTkFJaXIzSFRpSFU5aFB6aC1UOGJHWWc2dXF2WDlSVmVWejZHcGJYejY5RXdVN3pCbUhwM2lJaFRMZUZWd0JqM28tV1QxWUx2SFFLMmc5</guid></item><item><title>Golden Retriever的就寝时间公告让TikTok哭笑不得-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/golden-retrievers-bedtime-announcement-tiktok-234000543.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Growing up, my folks were strict about bedtime. When 9:30 p.m. hit, everything shut down with the force of a government mandate. The lights out, TV off, Nintendo put away, prayers said, and eyes glued shut, whether sleep was coming or not. As a lifelong night owl, it felt like torture lying there in the dark, tossing around like a rotisserie chicken, hoping sleep would magically happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Now, as a chronically exhausted adult who wishes I'd developed even one healthy sleep habit, I cannot help but laugh and relate when I see someone who takes bedtime more seriously than I ever did. And by someone, I mean a golden retriever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/dog-face" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐶;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🐶&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/parade-pets" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:SIGN UP to get "pawsitivity" delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP to get "pawsitivity" delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/paw-prints" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐾🐾;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;🐾🐾&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bedtime Announcement That Took Over TikTok&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the viral video, this Golden Retriever has decided that the household is done for the night, whether the guests agree or not. The overlay text reads, "My Dog coming to remind our guests that it is 9pm and lights better be out because he has a strict bedtime routine." With the seriousness of a hotel manager enforcing quiet hours, he trots out carrying two essential items: his favorite blanket and a plush Patrick Star from &lt;em&gt;SpongeBob SquarePants&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As he marches up to the lingering guests, the audio choice is comedic perfection: the iconic scene from &lt;em&gt;The Office&lt;/em&gt; where Dwight sings, "Learn your rules, you better learn your rules, if you don't, you'll be eaten in your sleep." The combination of his earnest little face, his bedtime gear, and Dwight Schrute threatening sleep-time consequences in the background? Pure PetTok gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;And TikTok agrees. One person wrote, "Omg how sweet! Goldens are so funny," while another joked, "Mr. grumpy is not grumpy 😍." Someone else added, "He runs a strict program," and honestly, the evidence supports the fact that this dog is the CEO of Lights Out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/articles/dog-emergency-text-mom-dad-154000376.html" data-ylk="slk:Related: Dog's Emergency Text to Mom About Dad Has TikTok Losing It;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;Related: Dog's Emergency Text to Mom About Dad Has TikTok Losing It&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why TikTok Can't Get Enough of This Sleep Sergeant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Part of the charm is how deeply committed he is to the role. He doesn't bark, whine or pace. Instead, he politely presents his blanket, stares directly at the humans, and waits. The message is clear: 9 p.m. means bedtime, and the lights better be out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It's a vibe that's both hilarious and painfully relatable. Plenty of pet parents chimed in with their own stories of pets enforcing nightly routines, from cats demanding sink water at tooth-brushing time to dogs who practically escort guests to the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This golden retriever may not run the household's social calendar, but he definitely runs the sleep schedule. And honestly, we could all use a little of his discipline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For more great golden retriever content, check out this Golden experience, &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/popcorn-explosion-tiktok-says-dog-014000429.html" data-ylk="slk:the popcorn explosion he will never forget;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;the popcorn explosion he will never forget&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/entertainment/articles/golden-retriever-stuns-tiktok-hockey-014000259.html" data-ylk="slk:this golden's shocking hockey skills.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;this golden's shocking hockey skills.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/health/sleep/articles/costcos-luxe-pet-bed-giving-204000366.html" data-ylk="slk:Related: Costco's Luxe Pet Bed Is Giving Dogs the Best Sleep of Their Lives;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;Related: Costco's Luxe Pet Bed Is Giving Dogs the Best Sleep of Their Lives&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally published by &lt;a href="https://pethelpful.com/pet-news/golden-retriever-bedtime-announcement-tiktok" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PetHelpful;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PetHelpful&lt;/a&gt; on Nov 29, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://pethelpful.com/pet-news" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Pet News;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Pet News&lt;/a&gt; section. Add PetHelpful as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=pethelpful.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 23:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQbmdmTGFiVG9WcnU2WEF2b3dSWlBsQ2JMTS1wa2dablRWVFc2QzZBZzBaZ3NmdUpzbDZfbGZSOXVXdU9kSnNId1gwV2QydFNOUklHdElOeTFtUks3NklUMkxxcFY1QkhNdldpeHdZVEtKUHFfdnlhZHkyZzNzbk9fZW11RnhiTUh2Q2tJMWZ4Q1RpTFdqVTV3N3RleW01M25xbnpN</guid></item><item><title>根据新的研究，比地中海更好的饮食-独立报</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/life-style/vegan-diet-mediterranean-health-benefits-b2874947.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 bxpovR sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 iBibVd"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 jVZWGn"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 eZqxmv"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 tawua"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 gZmYS"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 iCTyfe"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 cglitp"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 keLMOw sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 dIsmaL"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health experts have praised the &lt;a href="/life-style/health-and-families/healthy-living/diet-weight-loss-mediterranean-ageing-heart-brain-healthy-food-a8305481.html"&gt;Mediterranean diet for years&lt;/a&gt; — which emphasizes fresh produce, fish, and extra virgin olive oil, among other foods — for &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/health-and-families/healthy-living/diet-weight-loss-mediterranean-ageing-heart-brain-healthy-food-a8305481.html"&gt;those looking to lose weight&lt;/a&gt; or improve overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers have consistently pointed to the &lt;a href="/life-style/health-and-families/mediterranean-diet-nutrition-health-doctors-b2802397.html"&gt;nutritional value of the Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;’s meals, as well as its anti-inflammatory ingredients, such as dark leafy greens and olive oil, as reasons why it’s considered one of the healthiest dietary options for a long life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But new research is pointing to another regimen that may yield better weight-loss results. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in &lt;em&gt;Frontiers&lt;/em&gt; divided 62 adults into two groups. Half followed the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/news/health/mediterranean-diet-gum-disease-weight-loss-b2826640.html"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt; for 16 weeks, while the other consumed a &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/food-and-drink/what-is-a-vegan-diet-food-person-lifestyle-health-benefits-beginners-guide-what-not-to-eat-a8122181.html"&gt;low-fat vegan diet&lt;/a&gt;, including grains, beans, and fresh produce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the 16 weeks, participants resumed their regular diets for four weeks before spending another 16 weeks following the opposite regimen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 kpgaTc"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/08/26/3/13/GettyImages-2220708372.jpg" srcset="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/08/26/3/13/GettyImages-2220708372.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.the-independent.com/2025/08/26/3/13/GettyImages-2220708372.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="The Mediterranean diet has long been recommended by experts for overall health and weight loss" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-21514"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;The Mediterranean diet has long been recommended by experts for overall health and weight loss&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Adam Berry/Getty Images for iHeartMedia)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers concluded that the low-fat vegan diet was more effective for weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results were measured using the &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="/life-style/health-and-families/plant-based-diet-vegan-tips-b2849086.html"&gt;plant-based&lt;/a&gt; diet index (PDI) to examine how eating plant-based foods was associated with weight loss. PDI measured overall intake of plant-based foods, while hPDI represented consumption of healthful plant foods, and uPDI gauged consumption of unhealthful plant foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healthful foods included fruits, vegetables, whole grains, nuts, legumes, oils, coffee, and tea. Unhealthful items included potatoes, sweets, fruit juice, sugar-sweetened beverages, and refined grains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that participants’ PDI scores rose on the vegan diet but remained essentially unchanged on the Mediterranean diet, with higher scores indicating greater intake of plant-based foods. hPDI scores rose on both diets, while uPDI scores decreased on the Mediterranean diet but increased on the vegan diet, despite participants having lost more weight following the latter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="3" class="sc-awdjp1-0 dfOhoE"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/10/03/14/21/iStock-2150471415.jpeg" srcset="https://static.the-independent.com/2025/10/03/14/21/iStock-2150471415.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.the-independent.com/2025/10/03/14/21/iStock-2150471415.jpeg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="A new study showed that a low-fat vegan diet was more effective for weight loss than the Mediterranean diet" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-21515"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;A new study showed that a low-fat vegan diet was more effective for weight loss than the Mediterranean diet&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The increase in PDI scores likely came from avoiding animal products, researchers noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Replacing animal products even with the ‘unhealthful’ plant-based foods on a vegan diet was associated with weight loss,” researchers &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/nutrition/articles/10.3389/fnut.2025.1666807/full?gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=23272552553&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAAC_sJ7nsfb2KhFbNhSoM-ZLeeaYgV&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAiAraXJBhBJEiwAjz7MZQDgsj9ofxVj3NdfR6DZSVAHVuXaGC_NGq5ib4K77WXjyuDl9nkqWhoCAFUQAvD_BwE"&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-iii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These findings suggest that replacing animal products with plant-based foods, and reducing the consumption of oil and nuts, may be successful strategies for weight loss. These foods are rich in fiber, have a lower energy density, and have been shown to stimulate glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1) secretion and enhance satiety,” researchers said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, GLP-1 medications like &lt;a href="/news/health/ozempic-weight-loss-drugs-side-effect-pet-ct-scans-b2841389.html"&gt;Ozempic and Wegovy &lt;/a&gt;have become increasingly popular for weight loss, as they mimic the naturally occurring GLP-1 hormone on GLP-1 receptors in the brain and gut, which help regulate hunger and leave you feeling fuller for longer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:46:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQNFItZDROTzdQZnFJT25CWVhMYlUzVFVpSzlUbVBQZU1mdW54SnNDTzBlZDJ4YmpNeU9PV1pYVDdKeERHdm1qelNYaGlGODk5UUZmaEJPMG1OdlFZYlQxTldVelRtVHB6ODZMUGdxUHA2SlcxSFp3cG9NZ1hnQWxkUTNtSUJDa1pfakd1cHZCM08zN1BCR0JKS2Zlcw</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，增强一种蛋白质可重新唤醒老化的小鼠脑细胞- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/boosting-one-protein-reawakens-aging-brain-cells-in-mice-study-shows</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A discovery by researchers from the Baylor College of Medicine in the US could lead to treatments that clear the troublesome &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Amyloid_beta"&gt;aggregations of protein&lt;/a&gt; thought to play a key role in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimer-s-disease"&gt;Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Using mice bred to have a condition similar to the neurodegenerative disorder, the team found &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;that elevated levels of a protein called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/SOX9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Sox9&lt;/a&gt; triggered specialized brain cells &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;to go into clean-up overdrive, 'vacuuming' up plaques with increased efficiency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In behavioral and memory tests, the treated mice also performed better, suggesting that the intervention can help protect the brain and reverse cognitive decline – a process that typically occurs in  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="183244" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease as neurons are damaged and destroyed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/theres-one-critical-thing-you-can-do-to-keep-alzheimers-symptoms-at-bay"&gt;There's One Critical Thing You Can Do to Keep Alzheimer's Symptoms at Bay&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that the benefits of Sox9 &lt;span&gt;stemmed from increased expression of a receptor called MEGF10, exclusively expressed in the membranes of brain maintenance cells &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-cells-we-thought-were-just-fillers-might-actually-be-the-key-to-our-body-clocks" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;called astrocytes&lt;/a&gt;, which are deployed to remove&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-of-our-biggest-hopes-for-alzheimers-treatment-doesnt-seem-to-work"&gt;amyloid-beta plaques&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Astrocytes perform diverse tasks that are essential for normal brain function, including facilitating brain communications and memory storage," &lt;a href="https://www.bcm.edu/news/brain-stars-hold-the-power-to-preserve-cognitive-function-in-model-of-alzheimers-disease"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Dong-Joo Choi, previously at the Baylor College of Medicine and now at the University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As the brain ages, astrocytes show profound functional alterations. However, the role these alterations play in aging and neurodegeneration is not yet understood."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_183247" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-183247" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/BrainScans.jpg" alt="Mouse brain scan" class="wp-image-183247 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/BrainScans.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/BrainScans-600x251.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-183247" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Boosting the production of Sox9 (right) reduced plaques (in red) in mouse brains. (Choi et al., &lt;em&gt;Nat. Neurosci.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some extra Sox9 seems to give the aging astrocytes a new lease on life, the researchers found. The Sox9 protein has &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7759/cureus.36129"&gt;previously been found&lt;/a&gt; elevated in Alzheimer's brains, which may indicate the brain's attempt to ramp up waste removal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers tried an opposite experiment, too, genetically engineering mice to remove Sox9. In these animals, the astrocytes showed signs of reduced health, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-may-now-know-why-alzheimers-erases-memories-of-our-loved-ones"&gt;memory recall worsened&lt;/a&gt;, and more amyloid-beta clumps stacked up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"An important point of our experimental design is that we worked with mouse models of Alzheimer's disease that had already developed cognitive impairment, such as memory deficits, and had amyloid plaques in the brain," &lt;a href="https://www.bcm.edu/news/brain-stars-hold-the-power-to-preserve-cognitive-function-in-model-of-alzheimers-disease"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Choi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We believe these models are more relevant to what we see in many patients with Alzheimer's disease symptoms than other models in which these types of experiments are conducted before the plaques form."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists are now tackling the challenge of Alzheimer's disease from numerous different angles, including treatments that &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/supplement-for-high-blood-pressure-clears-signs-of-alzheimers-in-mice"&gt;target amyloid-beta plaques&lt;/a&gt;. However, not all of these &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-of-our-biggest-hopes-for-alzheimers-treatment-doesnt-seem-to-work"&gt;treatments work&lt;/a&gt;, emphasizing the complexity of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are multiple ways to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-simple-new-compound-reverses-alzheimers-symptoms-in-rats"&gt;clear out amyloid-beta clumps&lt;/a&gt; or stop them from forming, but we're still not sure if these protein aggregations are causing Alzheimer's or just a result of the disease. All of these factors need to be weighed up by researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, each new study gets us closer to understanding how this disease progresses – and how, eventually, it might be stopped. Although these latest tests were carried out in mice rather than humans, there's good reason to believe scientists may have discovered a crucial new route to tackling the manifestations of Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Most current treatments focus on neurons or try to prevent the formation of amyloid plaques," &lt;a href="https://www.bcm.edu/news/brain-stars-hold-the-power-to-preserve-cognitive-function-in-model-of-alzheimers-disease"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neuroscientist Benjamin Deneen. "This study suggests that enhancing astrocytes' natural ability to clean up could be just as important."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41593-025-02115-w"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 21:03:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNOEE2S2RlSVR4MVQxck9JWDNGdzVYWWxaTFNoVWlnaHZya1VrWkVDNm1lQVU3RXBYLXRFNTdtaEtWNDRXc2xXRFpCclZTUEFJYUE2RkhmXzVUY3FPclpHOGxsdUxmSllHR3FLT19TZHdUdDdtWHFsSU1HOU9VQzhQX185N09CeDdmbV9UWVptVXUzcmpXdWcyYWZ3YS1UQQ</guid></item><item><title>美国食品和药物管理局将提高疫苗接种门槛，指责新冠肺炎疫苗导致10名儿童死亡-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/11/29/nx-s1-5624998/fda-vaccines-covid-children-safety</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-99815" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Food and Drug Administration officials say they are going to scrutinize vaccines more stringently.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    JHVEPhoto/iStock Editorial/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        JHVEPhoto/iStock Editorial/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;The Food and Drug Administration intends to get tougher on vaccine approvals, as top officials raised concerns about the risk of COVID vaccines for children.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Speaking on Fox News Saturday morning, &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/about-fda/fda-organization/martin-makary" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;FDA Commissioner Marty Makary&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; said the agency would no longer "rubber-stamp new products that don't work," claiming it made a "mockery of science."&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;Makary's comments came the day after FDA's top vaccine regulator, &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/about-fda/fda-organization/vinay-prasad" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Vinay Prasad&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, told his team the agency would change its annual flu vaccine framework, update vaccine labels to be "honest," and make other changes to how it reviews vaccines, according to contents of an internal email reviewed by NPR and &lt;a href="https://x.com/AliRogin/status/1994567973030535301?s=20" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;reported on first&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; by a &lt;em&gt;PBS News Hour&lt;/em&gt; correspondent and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/29/fda-vaccine-approval-child-covid-deaths/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;later by&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;The Washington Post.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Prasad wrote that the FDA would also no longer authorize vaccines for pregnant women without stricter requirements. And for pneumonia vaccines, manufacturers will have to prove they reduce disease rather than show they generate antibodies. He also raised questions about giving multiple vaccines at the same time, which is standard practice.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The changes could make it much more difficult and expensive for vaccines to get approved, further limiting the availability of vaccines, which are considered among the safest and most effective tools for protecting people against infectious diseases.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;While all vaccines carry some risks, most public health experts argue the current process for vetting vaccines before marketing has long assured that the benefits of vaccines outweigh their risks. Studies required after vaccines are approved and surveillance systems, including the &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/vaccines-blood-biologics/report-problem-center-biologics-evaluation-research/vaccine-adverse-events" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Vaccine Adverse Event Reporting System&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (VAERS), also flag potential safety issues once vaccines are in use.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;FDA says an analysis links COVID shots to some deaths&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Makary said on Fox News that 10 children had died from the COVID shot during the Biden administration, but did not offer specifics about how the FDA came to that conclusion. &lt;a href="https://usafacts.org/visualizations/covid-vaccine-tracker-states/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Millions of children&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; have received the vaccine.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Officials with the Department of Health and Human Services and Food and Drug Administration didn't immediately respond to requests for comment on the COVID analysis and changes to vaccine review standards.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;According to the FDA email from Prasad, he told the agency's biostatistics and pharmacovigilance team to analyze 96 reported deaths from 2021 to 2024, and they determined 10 children died "after and because of" the COVID vaccine. But Prasad said the true number was likely higher.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Dr. Paul Offit, who &lt;a href="https://www.chop.edu/doctors/offit-paul-a" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;directs the Vaccine Education Center at the Children's Hospital of Philadelphia&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, said in a text message that Prasad has not shared the evidence that these vaccines killed 10 children.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Because he doesn't provide any evidence, he is asking us to trust him on an important issue," Office said. "All this will do is scare people unnecessarily. At the very least, he should provide all the evidence he has so that experts in the field can review it and decide whether he has enough data to prove his point."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Dr. Jesse Goodman, &lt;a href="https://gufaculty360.georgetown.edu/s/contact/00336000014TNITAA4/jesse-l-goodman" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;a professor at Georgetown University&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; who held Prasad's job at FDA from 2003 until 2009, said in an email that the FDA's Center for Biologics Evaluation and Research, which oversees vaccine approval, has been "recognized globally as a gold standard regulator." Goodman defended "immunologic endpoints like antibody levels" for the accelerated approval of pneumonia and influenza vaccines. He said science supports their use and they are confirmed with studies after approval: "These approaches have helped provide children and adults with timely access to safe and effective vaccines, saving many lives."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://directory.sph.umn.edu/bio/sph-a-z/michael-osterholm" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Michael Osterholm&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, an epidemiologist at the University of Minnesota, reviewed the email from Prasad and challenged his statement that "COVID-19 was never highly lethal for children." Osterholm also questioned the FDA's latest analysis of adverse event reports attributing the 10 deaths to COVID vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Prasad's email is filled with factual mistakes and misrepresents both the severity of COVID in children (1597 deaths in 2020-2022) and how the US responded to the first signals of possible vaccine-associated pediatric deaths in May 2021," Osterholm wrote in an email to NPR.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"While Prasad's email notes 10 such deaths, these cases have never been presented for review by the medical and public health communities or published in the medical literature," Osterholm continued. "Given the record of this Administration to misrepresent scientific data regarding vaccines, until these cases have been reviewed by an expert third party, like the National Academy of Science[s], we can not accept the fact they are vaccine-associated deaths."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Surveillance system collects vaccines reports&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The FDA makes public data from the VAERS surveillance system co-sponsored by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. But &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/vaccines-blood-biologics/vaccine-adverse-events/vaccine-adverse-event-reporting-system-vaers-database-information" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;FDA cautions&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, "it is important to note that for any reported event, no cause and effect relationship has been established." In his email, Prasad wrote that "with case reports, causality is typically assessed on a subjective scale. In this scale ranging from certain to unlikely -- certain, possible/likely, and probable are broadly considered as related to the product."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Makary said on Fox News that when the COVID shot was first rolled out, it was "amazing" for people at high risk of coming down with severe disease, but things have changed. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Back in 2020, we saw a reduction in the severity of illness and lives saved, but now recommending that a 6-year-old girl get another 70 million COVID shots – one each year for the rest of her life – is not based on science. And so we're not going to just rubber stamp approvals without seeing some scientific evidence."&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;The claim is the latest move by Trump administration health officials questioning the safety and effectiveness of vaccines and how the government has regulated them. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has long questioned vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The FDA &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/08/27/nx-s1-5515503/fda-covid-vaccines-restricted" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;restricted eligibility&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for the updated COVID vaccines in August after announcing the agency planned to &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/05/20/nx-s1-5405013/fda-covid-vaccine-limits" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;require more evidence &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;about the shots' safety and effectiveness going forward.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;CDC committee will meet to review vaccine policies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The FDA email on vaccine policy comes just before the CDC convenes a crucial &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/meetings/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;two-day meeting&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of that agency's influential Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices on Dec. 4-5. The committee is in the process of conducting a major review of how children are inoculated against dangerous infectious diseases such as measles, mumps, rubella, polio and hepatitis B.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Many public health experts are concerned the committee will upend the childhood vaccination schedule. It could move to delay the timing of some inoculations, space out vaccinations and call for the reformulation of some vaccines. Taken together, the moves could result in fewer children getting protected and the resurgence of once-vanquished diseases.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Asked about Makary and Prasad's claims that the COVID vaccine caused deaths among 10 children, Moderna, whose COVID vaccine is approved for children as young as 6 months old, pointed to a &lt;a href="https://investors.modernatx.com/statement-on-the-safety-of-spikevax" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;statement it made in September&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The company says that multiple published, peer-reviewed studies from a variety of sources show its shot is safe and that it is "not aware of any deaths in the last year or pertinent new information from prior years."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Moderna says it monitors its vaccine's safety along with regulators in more than 90 countries. "With more than one billion doses distributed globally, these systems — including in national health systems across Europe, the United Kingdom, Canada, Australia, and the U.S. — have not reported any new or undisclosed safety concerns in children or in pregnant women."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Pfizer did not immediately respond to requests for comment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 19:49:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxOU3dVRndQSU1xTUZDTFdKSWhMV2RHQlJNdDJsQWhheUN0eXJjTHp4aXN1RENNQWU3bWE4N0JaUTdEMC1Ldmk1SmNQQ29MVUQxWVI0Y0VKSUpaV1dNanNTNGZmRVNDT1BWYVk0eklJRURubGFUTFk1RXUxXy1lVEF0NV9zZDVHNFpRazB2SDFvYkxELWVxV2JVRjdxNHd0RUpGSkNyUjB6WUhndw</guid></item><item><title>与慢性大麻使用有关的新健康问题--而且很难治疗--《纽约邮报》</title><link>https://nypost.com/2025/11/29/health/new-health-concern-linked-to-chronic-cannabis-use/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;For some chronic cannabis users, a case of the munchies is the least of their problems.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Over the past decade, ERs have seen a surge in regular tokers showing up with sudden, stomach-churning attacks that leave them doubled over in pain. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The worst part? Many sufferers experience these episodes three or four times a year, often leaving both patients and providers scratching their heads.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Chronic cannabis users are increasingly facing a temporarily debilitating health concern. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Seventyfour – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;What is CHS?&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The culprit is cannabis hyperemesis syndrome (CHS), a gut-wrenching disorder that triggers relentless nausea, abdominal pain and severe vomiting that can strike four or five times an hour, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/21665-cannabis-hyperemesis-syndrome" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Symptoms usually appear within 24 hours of cannabis use and can last for days. The episodes are so brutal that ER staff have coined a term for them: “&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6690288/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;scromiting&lt;/a&gt;” — a chilling mashup of screaming and vomiting.&lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Tough to treat&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Despite its growing prevalence, many doctors are still unfamiliar with the syndrome, which was only recently defined, making it hard to distinguish from medical issues like food poisoning or the stomach flu.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“A person often will have multiple [emergency department] visits until it is correctly recognized, costing thousands of dollars each time,” &lt;a href="https://adai.uw.edu/staff_members/bia-carlini/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Dr. Beatriz Carlini&lt;/a&gt;, a research associate professor at the University of Washington (UW) School of Medicine who studies adverse health effects of cannabis use, said in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251126095029.htm" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a statement&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Cannabis hyperemesis syndrome patients often present with the combination of screaming and loud vomiting, which has led to the term “scromiting.” &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Monkey Business – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But even after a diagnosis, CHS can be difficult to treat.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There are currently no FDA-approved therapies, and standard anti-nausea medications often don’t work, according to &lt;a href="https://em.uw.edu/people/faculty/christopher-buresh" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Dr. Chris Buresh&lt;/a&gt;, an emergency medicine specialist with UW Medicine and Seattle Children’s Hospital. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That sometimes forces clinicians to try second- and third-line options, including &lt;a href="https://www.annemergmed.com/article/S0196-0644(20)30666-1/abstract" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Haldol&lt;/a&gt;, a medication more commonly used for psychotic episodes.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Some patients find limited relief by rubbing &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7718060/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;capsaicin cream&lt;/a&gt; on their stomachs, which creates a warming sensation that can temporarily ease discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Hot baths and showers also often help curb symptoms, with many patients driven to bathe for hours each day to soothe their pain.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“That’s something that can clinch the diagnosis for me, when someone says they’re better with a hot shower,” Buresh said. “Patients describe going through all the hot water in their house.”  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Recovery challenges&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Even after symptoms subside, long-term recovery can be tricky. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Because the syndrome strikes intermittently, some cannabis users assume a recent episode was unrelated and continue using — only to become severely ill again, according to UW. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For those who accept the diagnosis and try to quit, addiction often makes abstinence a major challenge, prolonging the cycle of illness. Carlini said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Stopping cannabis use is currently the only way to fully cure the condition.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;From teens to long-time users&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Scientists don’t know the exact cause of CHS, but the leading theory is that long-term overstimulation of receptors in the endocannabinoid system may disrupt the body’s natural control of nausea and vomiting, per the Cleveland Clinic. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;CHS can be tough to spot, often blending in with far more common gastrointestinal illnesses. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Mdv Edwards – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Why it affects some cannabis users but not others remains a mystery.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We don’t know if it’s related to the greater general availability of cannabis or the higher THC potency of some products or something else,” Buresh said.  &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It seems like there’s a threshold when people can become vulnerable to this condition, and that threshold is different for everyone,” he added. “Even using in small amounts can make these people start throwing up.” &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://emed.smhs.gwu.edu/news/painful-syndrome-sending-cannabis-users-er-are-you-risk" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;study published earlier this year&lt;/a&gt; by researchers at George Washington University surveyed 1,052 people with CHS in an effort to better understand risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They found that starting cannabis use earlier in life was linked to a higher likelihood of future ER visits for hyperemesis symptoms. Daily use and prolonged consumption were also common, with 44% reporting regular use for more than five years before the syndrome appeared. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But CHS isn’t just an adult problem. &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2836403" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research shows&lt;/a&gt; that emergency department visits among adolescents in the US have jumped more than 10-fold from 2016 to 2023.  &lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Notably, while overall rates were higher in states with legal recreational cannabis, the fastest year-over-year increases in the number of adolescent CHS cases at hospitals occurred in states where casual cannabis use is still illegal.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Gaining attention&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;On Oct. 1, the World Health Organization formally recognized cannabis hyperemesis syndrome, adding an official diagnosis code to its manual. The CDC has also incorporated the new code into US diagnostic systems.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Experts say the update offers several benefits, including giving researchers a clearer picture of how often CHS occurs. Having the code appear in a patient’s medical record also helps providers spot repeat episodes during future visits.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“A new code for cannabis hyperemesis syndrome will supply important hard evidence on cannabis-adverse events, which physicians tell us is a growing problem,” Carlini said. &lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 19:46:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQRi1uakpYWW9tY3Y3d1Z0Q2NnMU1VaVZiWTIwd1h5YUpJakZqanZZVFZEZUhSM2I0cHd6UXFZUkNaYTlDOXQ1SWV1VTltS3gyYTRNQzBaelZYU3ZOUjQzc2luOXR6YlJTbUNPUDNjSDNBbjIzOGljQm1ZbWpScFI3TkkyZ21uaEEzUnhYOWxVRXY</guid></item><item><title>FDA官员在没有提供数据的情况下，声称COVID-19疫苗与儿科死亡之间存在联系- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/food-drug-administration-covid-19-vaccines-pediatric-deaths/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Dr. Vinay Prasad, the director of the Food and Drug Administration's vaccine division, sent a memo to staff that linked children's deaths to the COVID-19 vaccine, but did not provide data to back the claim. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The memo said that a review "found that at least 10 children have died after and because of receiving COVID-19 vaccination," according to multiple sources familiar with the email. The memo was first reported by the New York Times.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prasad suggested that the deaths were related to myocarditis, or the inflammation of the heart muscle. Prasad did not share any data used in the review, including the children's ages, whether they had existing health conditions, or how the FDA determined there was a link between their death and the vaccine. The findings were not published in a peer-reviewed medical journal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Myocarditis has been linked to the COVID-19 vaccine, but &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/10.1056/NEJMoa2110475" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;studies have largely confirmed&lt;/a&gt; that the risk of the condition is significantly higher after a coronavirus infection, &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-vaccines-myocarditis-heart-damage-infection-children/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;pediatric cardiologists told CBS News in 2023&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The prognosis following myocarditis due to the vaccine is also better than from infection, &lt;a href="https://www.jacc.org/doi/full/10.1016/j.jacc.2022.09.049" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;studies show&lt;/a&gt;. COVID-19 infection is also linked to other &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/long-covid-what-scientists-now-know/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;long-term complications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk of myocarditis appears to be higher when vaccine doses are given closer together, as was the case when the vaccines first hit the market. Now, most people receive each dose of the vaccine about a year apart. If someone receives the primary series before age 5, the risk virtually disappears. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pfizer and Moderna COVID-19 vaccines &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/fda-covid-vaccine-mrna-heart-side-effects-warning-label/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;carry warnings about the risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of myocarditis or pericarditis, a condition where the membrane surrounding the heart becomes inflamed. The warnings were expanded in April 2025 to apply to males aged 16 to 25. The rate of myocarditis and pericarditis was around 8 cases per million doses for children and adults under 65 years old after use of that season's vaccines, the FDA said at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;COVID-19 vaccines, developed during the first Trump administration, have become a target of the second. Top FDA officials selected by the administration under Health and Human Services Secretary &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rfk-jr-vaccine-safety-aluminum-ingredients/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; overrode career staff to limit the approvals of COVID-19 shots from Novavax and Moderna, according to records released by the FDA. A &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/tag/centers-for-disease-control-and-prevention/" rel="nofollow" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; official said in June that she was &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cdc-official-overseeing-covid-19-vaccine-recommendations-resigns/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;resigning from her role&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; overseeing updates to the agency's COVID-19 vaccine recommendations, following &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rfk-jr-covid-vaccines-cdc-children-pregnant-women/" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;an order&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; from Kennedy that forced an update to the agency's guidance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/kids-flu-covid-shots-fall-2025-vaccine-guidance-shifts/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Changing COVID-19 vaccination guidance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has caused confusion for many. The CDC's vaccine advisory committee, known as the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, or ACIP, &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cdc-acip-recap-measles-mmrv-covid-vaccines/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;voted in September&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to change recommendations for the shot. All members of the committee have been picked by Kennedy, himself a vaccine skeptic. &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rfk-jr-cdc-vaccine-advisory-panel-names/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Several of the panel members&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; have criticized the COVID-19 vaccine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The updated CDC guidance recommends people make individual, informed decisions about COVID-19 vaccination, but did not specifically recommend the shots. The &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/covid-19-shot-recommendations-american-academy-of-pediatrics-cdc/" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;American Academy of Pediatrics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; said it was "strongly recommending" shots for children between 6 months and 2 years old, while the &lt;a href="https://www.idsociety.org/ID-topics/infectious-disease/covid-19/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Infectious Diseases Society of America&lt;/a&gt; recommended the vaccine for everyone six months and older. State governments have also banded together, forming the &lt;a href="https://www.cdph.ca.gov/Programs/CID/DCDC/CDPH%20Document%20Library/Immunization/IMM-1481.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;West Coast Health Alliance&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/about/press/pr2025/announce-northeast-public-health-collaborative.page" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Northeast Public Health Collaborative&lt;/a&gt;, to issue recommendations that differ from the CDC guidance. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/video/what-parents-need-to-know-as-vaccination-rates-for-kids-continue-to-decline/" rel="nofollow" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Dr. Céline Gounder&lt;/a&gt;, CBS News medical contributor and editor-at-large for public health at KFF Health News, told CBS News in August that there's "a lot of noise out there" when it comes to vaccines, but advises parents to "stick the course" and talk to your doctor about making sure children get all their necessary vaccinations, including the initial COVID vaccination series. &lt;/p&gt;

    

                    
        
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 18:41:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxQbmIzcmlTZnhtMkExRUpiS1h2YTdJamw3NU1lVzFwNHpmalJScjZUZWpBLTlhX2wzZUVWU2k2clUtNW8ycnBaVWZMTll2c2NsbVJ5SWpzdm1NNWZ0c0FVZlpoNkMzSG1GeVo1ZHMtWW5wQzlVSmR2Y2Q3bzBNYTcwY2ZhT1poT1VtLU81cW9WdmRtc0XSAZgBQVVfeXFMTklFWmhVdXRVQWJRLVlqbmJFS0RSTFZwNHJjaFBxeFNTMWlyb3FmMWQ5cFJVNDhXVF9wLV94aXFWcHYwSkFEX1NmREM1SzlVMFpmWG4xX2hZU2lNdDRqeGtwbkQ4Vl9pSmp5YVlhSEd6UHpDZVRUU2xpdlZmMVl2TnlkbGNMZ3ZPSHlJcXlzQk50eWtSc21HS2Y</guid></item><item><title>FDA声称新冠疫苗造成10名儿童死亡，并发誓要制定新的疫苗规则- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/fda-covid-vaccines-children-deaths-rcna246437</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2d35c5" class="body-graf"&gt;The director of the Food and Drug Administration’s vaccine division told agency staff in a memo that an internal review found that at least 10 children died “after and because of receiving” the Covid vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6d091b" class="body-graf"&gt;The 3,000-word memo, obtained by NBC News, was written by Dr. Vinay Prasad, director of the FDA’s Center for Biologics Evaluation and Research. In it, Prasad claims that agency staff determined that “no fewer than 10” of 96 child deaths reported to the Vaccine Adverse Event Reporting System, or VAERS, between 2021 and 2024 were “related” to Covid vaccination. He said the true numbers could be higher, accusing the agency of ignoring the safety concerns for years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f73a77" class="body-graf"&gt;The memo, sent Friday, did not include the children’s ages or medical histories, timelines or documentation for the deaths he references and does not identify the manufacturer of the vaccine. The FDA’s findings have not been published in a peer-reviewed journal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-c40629" class="body-heading"&gt;Experts push back&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-707cd0" class="body-graf"&gt;Experts who reviewed the memo say it is misusing information from VAERS, an unverified reporting system that allows anyone, including doctors, patients and caregivers, to submit entries  about adverse events they believe are linked to vaccines. The system’s &lt;a href="https://vaers.hhs.gov/" target="_blank"&gt;own website&lt;/a&gt; warns that submissions can contain inaccurate, incomplete or biased information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-925f0d" class="body-graf"&gt;“This is sort of science by press release,” said Dr. Paul Offit, a pediatrician and the director of the Vaccine Education Center at the Children’s Hospital of Philadelphia, calling the memo “irresponsible” and “dangerous.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3a5066" class="body-graf"&gt;“This is a profound revelation,” Prasad wrote in the memo. “For the first time, the U.S. FDA will acknowledge that COVID-19 vaccines have killed American children.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e946e8" class="body-graf"&gt;Prasad suggests that the child deaths were tied to myocarditis, an inflammation of the heart muscle, but doesn’t include evidence to support the claim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1c1d2b" class="body-graf"&gt;The FDA directed all media inquiries to the Department of Health and Human Services. An HHS spokesperson did not immediately respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-be31a9" class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Peter Marks, the FDA’s former vaccine chief who was ousted by Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. earlier this year, said the agency is misusing the database and the claims are right out of what he calls the “anti-vaccine playbook.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b49966" class="body-graf"&gt;The FDA uses the database to look for early “signals” — patterns that might suggest a possible safety issue, Marks told NBC News. It was one of the tools the agency used to identify a rare blood clotting condition linked to Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson’s Covid vaccine, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c4551e" class="body-graf"&gt;The mRNA Covid vaccines, from Pfizer and Moderna, have also been linked to a small but increased risk of myocarditis in young men. Most cases &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/myocarditis-covid-vaccine-teens-study-rcna60118" target="_blank"&gt;have been found to be mild&lt;/a&gt; and resolve within a few days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e18af0" class="body-graf"&gt;Marks said the FDA is not reviewing new safety reports but instead re-examining older ones and appears to be classifying some of them as vaccine-related. He added that Covid infection is also associated with myocarditis — and is often more severe than cases seen after vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4519ab" class="body-graf"&gt;“This memo conveys a very troubling mixture of misrepresentation and lies,” Marks said. “The climate within the agency is incredibly toxic right now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-a55299" class="body-heading"&gt;Proposed changes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7c12e2" class="body-graf"&gt;The memo uses highly ideological language, repeatedly characterizing Covid vaccine requirements for schools and employers as “coercive,” calling past agency decisions “dishonest,” and arguing that vaccine regulation “may have harmed more children than we saved.” At one point, Prasad instructs staff who disagree with his conclusions to resign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fee3fd" class="body-graf"&gt;He outlined a series of proposed changes to how the FDA evaluates vaccines. He said the agency would revisit how annual flu shots are evaluated, calling the current process an “evidence-based catastrophe of low quality evidence.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-21292b" class="body-graf"&gt;He also said pneumonia vaccine makers “will have to show their products reduce pneumonia (at least in the post-market setting), and not merely generate antibody titers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-293c74" class="body-graf"&gt;He also claimed the Biden administration dismissed early safety concerns, and criticized former Centers for Disease Control and Prevention Director Rochelle Walensky for what he described as “dishonest and manipulative” public comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3cb084" class="body-graf"&gt;The memo comes ahead of a two-day CDC vaccine advisory committee meeting next week, when officials are &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/agendas/draft-posted-2025-11-14-508.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;scheduled to discuss the childhood vaccine schedule&lt;/a&gt; and the hepatitis B shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4ebbee" class="body-graf"&gt;Earlier this year, the FDA and CDC limited who is eligible to get a Covid vaccine this fall and winter, focusing on people 65 and older and those with medical conditions that put them at increased risk of severe illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fd593d" class="body-graf"&gt;Kennedy, an anti-vaccine activist, has &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/kennedy-draws-misinformation-playbook-touting-inhaled-steroid-treat-me-rcna200085"&gt;downplayed the benefits of vaccines&lt;/a&gt; and has singled out vaccines made with mRNA as particularly dangerous, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/covid-vaccine-kids-pregnant-women-cdc-recommendation-rfk-jr-rcna207312"&gt;calling the mRNA Covid vaccine&lt;/a&gt; “the deadliest vaccine ever made.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-2f462f" class="body-graf"&gt;In September, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/09/04/health/video/the-lead-marty-makary-health-rfk-jr-hhs-congress-hearing-jake-tapper"&gt;FDA Commissioner Marty Makary told CNN&lt;/a&gt; that the agency was looking into the deaths of healthy children from the Covid shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-6146b4" class="body-graf"&gt;Extensive research has found that the Covid vaccines are safe for children and protect against severe illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a4053b" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9871947/" target="_blank"&gt;2023 analysis in JAMA Pediatrics&lt;/a&gt; reviewed 17 studies covering more than 10 million children ages 5 to 11 who got Pfizer’s or Moderna’s Covid vaccines. Vaccinated kids had a lower risk of infection and hospitalization compared to those who weren’t vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-653035" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;A 2024 study in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-024-47745-z" target="_blank"&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/a&gt; also found no increased risk of serious adverse events in young kids after Covid vaccination. It did identify a small increased risk of myocarditis in teen boys after the first two days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 18:30:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPbVJ4LXBZbW5zc2dWOUhLZFdvcUNFZXpsR3pNYnFudVc5VUlRMXVRWWg4ZGxteElsY25yNFZDY0Y2MUVLTndCMDA3MGN5c04yXzYydkowWjE1amMwRFhraWtKNV90RE9jbW5ybXhqLVQzanNnUGFmalEtcjNzQjFlY0c2ZkhjdXhVcHByVXp1VU9fUdIBVkFVX3lxTE9DckRjU0JNcFZDNUc3aXk4WkJuQnEtdHpJOEQtYWRyQW1Sa1V5M0tCVndrdm0wZXh4ZnpsTGN4blM1NTh2cF9UZ2RoTFV5QlgzZF9aR1VB</guid></item><item><title>对逆转小鼠阿尔茨海默氏症迹象的旧药感兴趣的科学家-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/scientists-intrigued-alzheimers-drug-mice</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="article-featured-image-figure"&gt;
			
			
	&lt;p class="article-featured-image-caption-container"&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="article-featured-image-caption"&gt;
			Illustration by Tag Hartman-Simkins / Futurism. Source: Getty Images
 		&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	
	
	
	
	&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;The next new treatment for Alzheimer’s disease may be an already-existing drug, according to a team of researchers in Japan.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;In a series of experiments, administering an oral dose of an amino acid called arginine, which is already prescribed to treat high blood pressure, was able to suppress the buildup of a protein associated with Alzheimer’s in mice, the scientists report in a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S019701862500155X?via%3Dihub" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Neurochemistry International&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Our study demonstrates that arginine can suppress amyloid-beta aggregation both in vitro and in vivo,” study coauthor Yoshitaka Nagai, neuroscientist at Kindai University, said in a &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1106825" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; about the work. “What makes this finding exciting is that arginine is already known to be clinically safe and inexpensive, making it a highly promising candidate for repositioning as a therapeutic option for Alzheimer’s disease.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Scientists still don’t understand the underlying cause of Alzheimer’s disease, but amyloid-beta proteins figure somewhere in the question. Though they’re a part of normal brain function, they’re sticky and can clump together to form “plaques” in the brain. These plaques are considered a hallmark of Alzheimer’s, though not all patients with the disease are found to have them.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;According to the researchers’ findings, the arginine can help flush these plaques and break them apart. They demonstrated this by feeding mice with amyloid-beta buildup in their brains drinking water and food infused with small doses of the drug.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Along with breaking up the buildup, they also found that the mice which were administered arginine showed improved behavior and cognitive performance, suggesting that the drug helped reverse some of the disease’s harmful effects. This was assessed by analyzing how the mice navigated an elevated Y-shaped maze, noting how far the mice traveled and how many times it entered the maze’s “open arms,” a test of a healthy mice’s natural instinct to avoid open spaces and enter enclosed ones.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Human clinical trials are needed to bear out the medical potential, but the researchers are optimistic.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Given its excellent safety profile and low cost, arginine could be rapidly translated to clinical trials for Alzheimer’s and potentially other related disorders,” Nagai said in the statement.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Other recent studies have explored promising avenues for treating Alzheimer’s. A team of scientists in China said they were able to almost instantly reverse the disease’s progression &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/nanoparticle-treatment-reverses-alzheimers-mice"&gt;using nanoparticles&lt;/a&gt; injected in their brains that cleared the plaques and led to cognitive improvements. Another team in Japan &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/scientists-reverse-alzheimers-synapse-damage-mice"&gt;used synthetic peptides&lt;/a&gt; to reverse progression in early stages of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Still, amyloid-beta’s function in the brain in general remains a mystery, and so the jury’s still out on whether targeting them is a meaningful way of treating, let alone curing, the tragic disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on Alzheimer’s:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/lab-mice-microplastics-dementia"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Lab Mice Exposed to Microplastics Show Signs of Dementia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxOS3FwaG5MM015UlZ2Y2xFdGNhMGg5SXkyZHF1eE5TVGN5eV9XcVE0dEZnS1dFYWNncXhvQ1ROQWRNZzZuZm5HVjliUjVRdWYwbkZGVjlYT0w4MmVxaFp5S1dkazFINmJKdnF0eDlDdUU5cy1CcmFoWmtkY240UGRqN0dfdXo</guid></item><item><title>人类可能天生就具有预先配置的大脑，可以帮助我们了解世界- Earth.com</title><link>https://www.earth.com/news/humans-born-with-preconfigured-brains-neural-circuits-that-help-us-understand/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a fascinating new study, scientists used pieces of human brain tissue to demonstrate that neural circuits produce electrical patterns very early in the development process, even before senses are active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These experiments at the University of California, Santa Cruz (&lt;a href="https://www.ucsc.edu/"&gt;UCSC&lt;/a&gt;) and other labs suggest that the brain comes with built-in timing rules for thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers tracked signals in organoids – lab grown pieces of human brain tissue – and in slices of newborn mouse cortex that never received sensory input.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across these preparations, neurons lit up in repeating ordered patterns, hinting that the brain carries an internal script for making sense of the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-early-brain-circuit-activity"&gt;Early brain circuit activity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the center of this project is Tal Sharf, an assistant professor of biomolecular engineering at UCSC. His research focuses on how the brain’s neural circuits assemble themselves before sensory experience shapes them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neuroscientists have known for years that brain activity in adults is not just random noise – it follows structured sequences when animals move, remember, or rest quietly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Classic &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nature09633" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;work&lt;/a&gt; in rodents showed that hippocampal cells can “preplay” paths an animal will walk, suggesting activity patterns exist before experiences arrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those repeating chains are called neuronal firing sequences (&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/time-cells-in-the-brain-are-key-to-complex-learning/"&gt;NFS&lt;/a&gt;), which are ordered bursts of nerve cell spikes over very short periods of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are thought to be units the brain uses to send information from one place to another and to stitch events in time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have argued over whether these sequences appear only after months of sensory input.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sharf and his collaborators set out to test if any are present before a brain has had the chance to sense the outside world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-growing-mini-brains"&gt;Growing mini brains&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To tackle that question, the group turned to organoids that can mimic parts of the human cortex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41420-023-01523-w" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;review&lt;/a&gt; described how these brain cultures capture early developmental stages and are used to study autism and Alzheimer disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-022-32115-4" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;experiments&lt;/a&gt; from Sharf and colleagues showed that brain organoids form circuits where neurons connect, synchronize, and react to drugs that shift activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those findings suggested that these models are not just static tissue samples but active networks that can learn and change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1934590919303376" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found that cortical organoids gradually develop complex oscillatory waves that resemble patterns seen in preterm infant brain recordings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together with the new work, these results strengthen the idea that organoid networks follow internally guided programs as they mature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In experiments, the team grew organoids from human stem cells and placed slices of tissue onto &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/brain-computer-interface-bci-reads-your-innermost-thoughts-and-translates-them-into-text/"&gt;microelectrode arrays&lt;/a&gt;, which are flat chips with many recording sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those arrays let the researchers separate signals from hundreds of neurons at once and follow how each cell fired over minutes of spontaneous activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-early-brain-circuit-sequences"&gt;Early brain circuit sequences&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When they looked at these recordings, the scientists saw that bursts of activity swept through organoids in ordered steps, rather than as random flashes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each burst followed a specific schedule, with some neurons firing early and others firing late, forming sequences that match a built in wiring plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within those patterns, the analysis revealed a fraction of cells that fired on every burst in a fixed order, creating backbone for the sequence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many other cells participated sometimes or at varying times, adding flexibility around that backbone so the network could explore combinations without losing its rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The timing of these sequences resembled patterns measured in adult cortex, where spontaneous events outline the range of sensory responses a circuit can produce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These cells are clearly interacting with each other and forming circuits that self-assemble before we can experience anything from the outside world,” said Sharf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That isolation from outside input means the ordered firing reflects sequence rules encoded in the brain circuit network itself not carved by experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This idea fits with a view in developmental neuroscience that some circuits start with scaffolds which later get tuned by senses and by learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-from-lab-to-newborn-mice"&gt;From lab to newborn mice&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To see if patterns arise in brain tissue, the researchers recorded from slices of the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/mice-capable-empathy/"&gt;somatosensory cortex&lt;/a&gt; in mice, which is tissue that processes touch signals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These mice were at an age when most senses besides smell are still developing, so their cortices had received only limited outside input.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In those slices, &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/our-decisions-are-shaped-by-optimistic-and-pessimistic-neurons/"&gt;neurons&lt;/a&gt; fired in recurring bursts that unfolded in the same order, with a backbone of cells leading the wave and others joining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That parallel between organoids and living tissue strengthens the case that the underlying sequence rules are built into the way these circuits grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In flat cultures of cortical neurons, the cells produced bursts of activity but lacked the ordered sequences that appeared in organoids and slices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That contrast suggests that having a three-dimensional layout with diverse cell types is important for letting backbone sequences form and persist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similar timing motifs in lab grown human tissue and early mouse cortex argue that sequence-based organization is a general feature of mammalian brains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It supports the idea that evolution has shaped the brain’s neural circuits so they can assemble maps of time, even before an individual encounters the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-implications-of-preconfigured-brains"&gt;Implications of preconfigured brains&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because these mini-brains develop from patient or healthy stem cells, researchers can compare how sequences unfold in organoids from people with different conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a disorder changes when backbone cells fire, or how cells join a sequence, those changes could expose assembly problems before symptoms appear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organoid-based models let scientists probe disorders, including microcephaly and epilepsy, giving access to stages of brain growth that cannot be studied directly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding precise measurements of early-firing sequences to that toolkit could help explain why some conditions disturb perception, movement, or cognition from the start.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These recording platforms can track how sequences change after a drug or gene edit, letting researchers search for treatments that restore normal timing patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That approach could be especially valuable for disorders where current medicines blunt symptoms, but don’t correct the underlying wiring problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taken together, the organoid recordings, neonatal mouse slices, and flat culture comparisons point to a brain that starts life with preconfigured firing rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Understanding those rules could clarify how infants rapidly learn, and could open paths to treating disorders while the brain is still assembling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41593-025-02111-0" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 18:03:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxPZloyY3NPN0plS2R5d1VEZ08wRVY0Ujh5NXU2ei0tV1F0U2ZkaUl6SjJaNHBGWkZ0WEJtZ0hUMGxOU1Z5NHU5YVAxR1NGTUFDenp2Njh3dGhCd0xxMmtJdlY1TmZuVWtyOE5uVm5QRDNfNW8yWlpUSFdfaWVmYThrakpDV3hsLXZETEEzSmh1TEJxN085clN0S0xMMDRsWkcyQUxMMF9hODc</guid></item><item><title>您可能不会以这种方式烹饪土豆-但您应该- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/how-to-make-melting-potatoes-11853047</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Melting potatoes are crispy on the outside and tender on the inside.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;High oven heat and flavorful broth create restaurant-quality results at home.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Simple to make, melting potatoes elevate any weeknight meal.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Buttery Yukon Golds, fluffy Idaho russets, picturesque red- and blue-skinned beauties … potatoes are not just pretty and delicious, they also pack a surprising nutritional punch, containing a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290053/8-foods-with-more-potassium-than-a-banana/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;good amount of potassium&lt;/a&gt;, vitamin C, fiber, a small amount of protein and a handful of antioxidants, among other nutrients.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Originally domesticated in the Andes and brought to Europe in the 1500s, ‘taters are popular worldwide, showing up in meals from places as far flung as India, Finland and Peru. Plus, potatoes keep well, can be found in pretty much any food store and are fairly easy to grow in a home garden. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Because potatoes are so beloved—the USDA estimates that Americans consume an average of 50 pounds per year—most home cooks have &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/highly-rated-potato-side-dishes-11839320" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;wonderful potato dishes&lt;/a&gt; in their repertoires.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; As a youngster, I learned to make tangy &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/248189/buttermilk-mashed-potatoes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;buttermilk mashed potatoes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/8077643/roasted-garlic-butter-potatoes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;roasted potatoes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/252910/classic-potato-salad/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;classic potato salad&lt;/a&gt;, and all of them were hits. After all, when people are explaining that they’re selective eaters, they often describe themselves as loving “meat and potatoes.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-why-you-should-try-melting-potatoes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Why You Should Try Melting Potatoes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When I got older, I started incorporating more chef-y techniques into my cooking, and that’s when I discovered the glory of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/279036/melting-potatoes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;melting potatoes&lt;/a&gt;, or fondant potatoes. Roasted at high heat and then bathed in flavorful broth, the resulting potato pieces are crispy on the outside and beautifully tender in the middle. Adding herbs to the mix, and throwing in some smashed garlic, makes them even more delicious. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The best part is that melting potatoes are so easy to make. Once you have slices prepped, all you need to do is babysit them while they cook, flip them once and then pour in the broth. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-make-melting-potatoes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Make Melting Potatoes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You’ll begin by &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/do-you-really-need-to-preheat-your-oven-8744075" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;preheating your oven to 500℉&lt;/a&gt;. It’s pretty common for home cooks to use 350℉ for the majority of their cooking tasks, and this is one way that restaurant chefs set themselves apart. In professional kitchens, cooks vary cooking temperatures widely to meet specific goals. In this case, we’re aiming to get a gorgeous browned exterior on our potato slices, and to cook them quickly, which leads us to use an amped-up oven temp. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As the oven heats up, you’ll toss the potatoes with a mixture of olive oil, butter and seasonings, including fresh herbs, salt and pepper. Doing this in a bowl ensures that you can mix the slices around and get all of the sides nice and coated. Then, arrange the potato pieces in a single layer in a metal baking dish—glass isn’t safe to use at higher temperatures—and pop them into the oven.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Now’s the time to work on other dinner projects, or simply hang out and do whatever else you want! You’ll cook the potatoes for 15 minutes, flip them with a spatula and then give them another 15 minutes. When you pull out the potatoes halfway through, look at how they’re cooking. If they look uneven, rotate the pan before putting it back into the oven. If they look like they’re getting too dark in spots, perhaps your oven is running a little hot? If that’s the case, you could knock the heat down to 475℉.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; When 30 minutes is up, carefully pour the broth into the pan and add the smashed garlic. Pop the ‘taters back into the oven, and continue roasting until the potatoes are tender throughout when you stick a fork into them, and the majority of the broth is absorbed. These are nicest served while piping hot. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-fun-variations"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Fun Variations &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The truth is, when I make this dish, I skip peeling the potatoes. Not only does it save me some time but it also results in a more nutritious finished product. Plus, I like the way the skins taste when they’re crispy and bathed in herby broth. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Once you’re comfortable with the “high heat plus liquid” methodology, you can start playing around with different seasonings. Try adding sage, parsley and thyme to the herb mix, and consider using different fats that are safe for higher-heat cooking, including avocado oil, refined sunflower oil or safflower oil. Spices can burn at higher temperatures, so if I want to add smoked paprika or chili powder, I’ll add it toward the end of the cooking time or sprinkle it on just before serving. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Another way to change up the flavor is to mix a zingy, acidic liquid in with the broth. A small splash of vinegar, wine or citrus juice will brighten up the end result remarkably, as in &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/281569/lemon-rosemary-melting-potatoes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lemon-Rosemary Melting Potatoes&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Sprinkling on a bit of cheese for the final few minutes of roasting, like we do when making &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/280315/garlic-parmesan-melting-potatoes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Garlic-Parmesan Melting Potatoes&lt;/a&gt;, is another excellent move. &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/french-onion-melting-potatoes-11844097" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;French Onion Melting Potatoes&lt;/a&gt;, with rich beef broth and Gruyère cheese, are even more decadent. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-to-serve-with-melting-potatoes"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What to Serve with Melting Potatoes &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Melting potatoes are so delicious that your other accompanying dishes can be fairly simple. While the potatoes are in the oven, I might whip up a stovetop seafood dish, such as &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/275030/seared-scallops-with-white-bean-ragu-charred-lemon/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Seared Scallops with White Bean Ragu &amp;amp; Charred Lemon&lt;/a&gt;, which sounds fancy but takes only 25 minutes, or &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/279114/spice-seared-salmon-with-greek-style-green-beans/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Spice Seared Salmon with Greek-Style Green Beans&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-bottom-line"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; The Bottom Line &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; By using high heat to roast the potatoes and then adding liquid for the last few minutes of cooking, you’ll end up with slices that are browned and crispy but nicely cooked all the way through. The broth, which will pick up all of the lovely herbs from the pan and become infused with the flavor of garlic, turns into a sauce as liquid is absorbed by the potatoes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Overall, melting potatoes are a perfect fusion of home cooking simplicity and restaurant kitchen technique, which yields an extraordinarily delicious product quickly, with just a handful of common ingredients, and using only a single bowl and pan.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE1xYVRVWDBoRWFYQWNvcWp4Z1NhbnVuOFBKMXExQk81cDE2azBaTWJRWGoyb0VWZjNPbnhBdGpCNWZ3eElma0hiRmhYOGtwdmsyVWlUcmgtcTdhemc5NEFsZmFwbU1kVHdNZi1nMGpzbmZ1QQ</guid></item><item><title>我从小就与贪食症和厌食症作斗争。现在，在46岁的时候，我终于看到了自己的本来面目--《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/diet/nutrition/my-decades-long-battle-against-bulimia-and-anorexia/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;Many people with severe bulimia end up with dental decay but luckily, somehow my teeth are OK and there’s no lasting damage to my body. I have issues with alcohol too and have been in and out of rehab for many years. My worst alcohol binge was after my father died – I just couldn’t cope with the agony of losing someone I loved so much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over a period of four days, I lost control and drank 17 bottles of wine. For some reason, maybe to shock myself into getting better, I even photographed all the bottles I drank. I was in self-destruct mode and ended up being hospitalised with liver poisoning. The nurses were so worried, explaining that I’d nearly killed myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve never attempted suicide and I wasn’t trying to die – I just feel emotions so deeply, I find it hard to manage them. I know I’ll never go back to that dark place again, as something has shifted within me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;The agony of grief&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;After my father died, I agreed that a filmmaker could follow me in the studio for a year. It ended up being very painful and triggering, but ultimately cathartic. The director, Shafin Basheer, was a lovely, gentle guy and we became good friends. The film, &lt;em&gt;Life with Emotions&lt;/em&gt;, was about my father having Parkinson’s, but it also followed me through my grief. It won awards and helped raise money for the charity Parkinson’s UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During filming, my bulimia got dramatically worse, but it also forced me to look at myself and face my demons. It has always been a kind of &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/2022/03/12/time-dispel-stigma-surrounds-addiction/"&gt;dysfunctional coping strategy for my emotions, as all addictions are&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking back now, I’m horrified that my bulimia made me 4st overweight. I look so unhappy and unhealthy in the film. I’m 6ft 4in and my natural weight is 16st 7lb, but I weighed nearly 20st.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watching it at the launch recently made me cry. It was so emotional because I was intensely focused on making a sculpture of my father throughout the film. It was a powerful way of saying goodbye, but I also found it very hard to physically let go of the sculpture.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 16:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNT2g2SEo4SGNrY0pKY0FRMDN5S0JackUzSi1pekhNQng1NHhqNzdwZUNHUkFMZHpsbjZOSzNQZVdDYVBLbHoydFBQUjdvZzU2ekF4ZGgxVXhuVU5nX3d4YXA3TXZwV3c3RjQtTW85dGVNb2FZaXh2TnJDenh5Smh3QUQ5MnZoVUQ3Z3UtTG1WbEdSRVpnTkFfanpSenAtYjBaZmQzV2w0YnY4UlRnT3BN</guid></item><item><title>古巴的健康危机-《哈瓦那时报》</title><link>https://havanatimes.org/diaries/safie-m-gonzalez/the-health-crisis-in-cuba/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="cm-entry-summary"&gt;
	
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-medium"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.47_58c935af-442x600.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-238869" srcset="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.47_58c935af-442x600.jpg 442w, https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.47_58c935af-589x800.jpg 589w, https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.47_58c935af.jpg 736w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 442px) 100vw, 442px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Micro-landfill in Centro Havana, one of the main causes of arbovirus.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p class="has-medium-font-size"&gt;&lt;a href="https://havanatimes.org/category/diaries/safie.m.gonzalez/"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;By Safie M. Gonzalez&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;HAVANA TIMES – In every corner of the island, daily life unfolds under an alert triggered by the buzz of the mosquito — no longer just a nuisance, but a constant reminder of a threat that has gained strength. The spread of Chikungunya, along with Dengue, Oropouche, and Zika, has exposed deep flaws in the country’s health infrastructure and in the State’s ability to respond, revealing a crisis that extends far beyond the presence of the mosquito.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-medium is-resized"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.48_c1cdd40b-450x600.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-238873" srcset="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.48_c1cdd40b-450x600.jpg 450w, https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.48_c1cdd40b-600x800.jpg 600w, https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.48_c1cdd40b.jpg 720w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 450px) 100vw, 450px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Inflamación causada por el virus&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p class="has-medium-font-size"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pain With a Name: Arbovirosis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Chikungunya, a word in the Kimakonde language meaning “to bend over in pain,” is not a passing discomfort. Those infected describe a burning sensation that travels through bones and joints, immobilizing them. The Pan American Health Organization warns that many patients develop chronic joint pain that lasts months or even years. In a country with an aging population and deteriorated nutrition, the aftereffects become an almost unbearable burden.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-medium is-resized"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.48_1e7c7c14-517x600.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-238870" srcset="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.48_1e7c7c14-517x600.jpg 517w, https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.48_1e7c7c14-689x800.jpg 689w, https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.48_1e7c7c14.jpg 720w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 517px) 100vw, 517px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Fumigation is the main response to the epidemic.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p class="has-medium-font-size"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Failure of Fumigation: Fuel That Evaporates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Fumigation, presented as the government’s main tool, has become a meaningless exercise. The fuel assigned to it is very often diverted to the black market, leaving brigades that fumigate irregularly and with diluted products. It is a symbolic, not effective, defense — something that satisfies a statistic but protects no one.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-medium is-resized"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.47_e67f4aa6-600x338.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-238871" srcset="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.47_e67f4aa6-600x338.jpg 600w, https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.08.47_e67f4aa6.jpg 736w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Medicines are in great shortage at the state pharmacies.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p class="has-medium-font-size"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Systemic Breeding Grounds: The Great Lie of Individual Responsibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The official campaign insists: “Cover your tank, turn over your bucket…” But shifting the blame onto citizens is a strategy designed to hide state responsibility. The real massive breeding grounds are structural. First, micro-dumps — mountains of garbage that remain uncollected for weeks. Second, leaks from broken pipes create permanent pools of water that are perfect for mosquito reproduction.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;A bucket can produce hundreds of larvae. A micro-dump, by contrast, millions. Yet the individual is still indirectly blamed under the pretext of raising awareness — a way to avoid acknowledging the real and most powerful cause of the generation and expansion of this health crisis, disguising the State’s inability to maintain basic services.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;All of this is accompanied by uncertain diagnoses: in Cuba, the necessary tests to identify the type of arbovirus are not done due to a lack of reagents. Every diagnosis is clinical — an approximation that hides the true scope of the epidemic. In parallel, medicines are found only on the black market: steroids, IV fluids, painkillers, etc., have disappeared from state pharmacies. Their prices in the informal market are unaffordable for the vast majority. Another undeniable factor worsening the health situation is the accelerated loss of professionals, which has left technical and human gaps that the system can no longer fill.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-medium is-resized"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" loading="lazy" src="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.10.13_7c2e922e-600x450.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-238872" srcset="https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.10.13_7c2e922e-600x450.jpg 600w, https://havanatimes.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/WhatsApp-Image-2025-11-28-at-13.10.13_7c2e922e.jpg 736w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 600px) 100vw, 600px"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p class="has-medium-font-size"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bureaucracy Above Pain&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Going to the doctor does not guarantee treatment; it only guarantees a work certificate. Bureaucracy demands paperwork even when no relief can be offered. People with high fevers stand in line to justify an absence from work.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Official reports are scarce, incomplete, and late. Most sick people never appear in the statistics. People prefer to endure the illness at home, self-medicating. A parallel epidemic has emerged — one the State does not acknowledge, but which lives and hurts in every Cuban household.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The arbovirus crisis in Cuba reflects a deeper deterioration: structural failures, mismanagement, and the abandonment of basic functions. While the State urges people to cover tanks and turn over buckets, the population faces alone an epidemic that is, in reality, the visible consequence of disastrous state management.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://havanatimes.org/category/diaries/safie.m.gonzalez/"&gt;Read more from the diary of Safie M. González here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
	
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Havana Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 15:37:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQVlphbGlZVVowd1JYNnRFMUJSNDBZUTdKMWtBLUZRMXVtaE9FNnlhaWhhbXNzNkpWazg0MUVfdDBtWG5lVXdjZzFueE5mdUVUZTFnZWJJdG9FTzM0VzRmNDBlR0dqc1pLOTItczJ6TnlmWW8xXy1PR3lNQk5ucDVTTw</guid></item><item><title>据《纽约时报》报道，美国FDA备忘录将10名儿童死亡与新冠疫苗联系起来-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-fda-memo-links-10-child-deaths-covid-vaccines-nyt-reports-2025-11-29/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 15:26:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxNUVpYakRuZldFeDVUbFY0Nm5zY1piM1RPV1c1NGNnd2RsY3lsbG1GSGlVTWJyNGhVeFdjYWY0ZkZrLUVxaUVvQWl3RzhGMzFzcXJHcDNrSjMxWUFXLXFTdVpxc2ZwbF9QUjJoSktPWXVHMThPLWh6b3FlNjRxRzJjUzBrV3VjdjJyZ0FTUTlBUmVLVFM0NFBfTXpaZUZkSURXYWZNOE1UY1BlZEptQllHZVpYX3JIRVpxWHp4RkV5NG9hLXhPM0pQdTZYUEQ</guid></item><item><title>免疫学家分享了9种缓慢衰老和更强免疫力的补充剂-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/immunologist-shares-9-supplements-for-slow-ageing-and-stronger-immunity/articleshow/125659001.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ageing may be inevitable, but the process can be made significantly smoother with the right nutritional support. While lifestyle, sleep and stress remain central pillars of healthy ageing, certain supplements can give the body what modern diets often lack. Dr Jenna Macciochi, a UK-based immunologist, recently shared in an Instagram post that a targeted supplement routine can strengthen immune resilience and support healthier, slower ageing. Her nine-part regimen focuses on boosting energy, improving gut balance and calming inflammation, all of which become increasingly important as people move through 40s and 50s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;9 supplements that can slow ageing and boost energy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;CoQ10: The energy catalyst&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;CoQ10 plays a central role in mitochondrial function, which powers every cell in the body. Levels naturally decline with age, reducing energy and increasing oxidative stress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Why it helps: It supports heart health, reduces fatigue and improves cellular energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to take it: Most adults use 100–200 mg daily, preferably in a softgel with oil for better absorption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to include it: Take it with a meal containing healthy fats such as avocado, nuts or olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Omega-3 and 7: Healthy fats for healthy cells&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Omega-3 fatty acids reduce inflammation, support brain function and improve heart health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Omega-7 helps maintain skin and mucosal barrier health — something that weakens with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Why it helps: These oils improve cell membrane flexibility, boost immune signalling and support overall metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to take it: Fish oil, algae oil for vegetarians, or supplements combining omega-3 and omega-7.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to include it: Complement supplements with fatty fish like salmon or with flaxseed, chia and walnuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Vitamin D and K: The essential duo&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin D supports immunity, mood, muscle strength and bone density. Vitamin K2 ensures that calcium absorbed through vitamin D is deposited in the bones, not soft tissues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Why it helps: Prevents bone loss, supports immune balance and improves inflammatory responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to take it: Look for vitamin D3 paired with K2 (MK-7).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to include it: Spend regular time in sunlight, eat fortified foods and take a daily D3 + K2 capsule or spray.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Creatine and taurine: Power and recovery&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Creatine boosts strength, muscle mass and cognitive performance by helping replenish ATP, the body’s quick energy source. Taurine hydrates cells, stabilises mitochondria and supports recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Why it helps: Great for preserving muscle as you age and improving mental clarity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to take it: Creatine monohydrate (3–5 g daily) and taurine (500–1000 mg).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to include it: Mix creatine into water, smoothies or coffee; taurine works best taken in capsules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Magnesium: The all-round regulator&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Magnesium supports over 300 biochemical reactions, including muscle relaxation, sleep, nerve function and energy production. Many adults are unknowingly deficient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Why it helps: Improves sleep, reduces stress, eases muscle cramps and supports heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to take it: Magnesium glycinate for sleep and stress, citrate for digestion and malate for energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to include it: Add leafy greens, pumpkin seeds, almonds and whole grains to your diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Targeted gut support&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ageing weakens the gut barrier and reduces microbial diversity, affecting immunity and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Why it helps: A stronger gut means better nutrient absorption, stable mood and reduced inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to take it: Look for prebiotics, postbiotics or specific gut-support formulas focused on barrier integrity rather than generic probiotics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to include it: Eat fermented foods like yoghurt, kefir, sauerkraut and fibre-rich vegetables.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="77"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="78"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Spermidine: A longevity molecule&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spermidine triggers autophagy, the body’s natural process of clearing damaged cells and regenerating new ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Why it helps: Supports cellular repair, brain health and longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to take it: Typically in supplement capsules derived from wheat germ or plant extracts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to include it: Food sources include wheat germ, mushrooms, soybeans and aged cheese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Quercetin: Anti-inflammatory support&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Quercetin is a plant antioxidant that reduces inflammation, supports blood vessels and aids immune function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Why it helps: Helps reduce oxidative stress, supports metabolic health and may improve allergy symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to take it: Usually taken as a capsule (250–500 mg). Works even better when paired with vitamin C.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to include it: Add onions, apples, berries and capers to your meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="97"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="98"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fisetin: Clearing old cells&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="99"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fisetin helps remove senescent cells, which accumulate with age and contribute to chronic inflammation and fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="101"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Why it helps: Supports healthier ageing, better recovery and improved metabolic function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="104"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to take it: Often available in 100–200 mg capsules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="106"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; How to include it: Naturally found in strawberries, apples, persimmons and cucumbers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="108"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Dr Macciochi reminds us, supplements are not magic fixes, but they can help fill the gaps created by modern living and the natural shifts that come with age. Paired with good sleep, movement and balanced eating, these nine additions can support a more resilient immune system and a steadier, stronger body through your 40s and 50s. For many people, it’s about giving the body the quiet, consistent support it needs to age well from the inside out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="112"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="114"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 14:24:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAJBVV95cUxPcWdibVF6RlBzQlotaUVnaHZlanJMV3NoYU9KNVJZRzFzVXh6WHpTb0p0NWNmQ0NMTnNlN1dTNGFobnpVZmtVYmVNa1BxVWNVYUt4THJ0YlNqcS1lVHZOWWdxT2hnb1JaSVdGTzdpWkN3TnhDSUxfaE5VOUFkY1loZ0FhM1BnYXdYVUNKMU82b05IcG5FOThFS1daQ2R3OHhSRDZXTlZBWHpod2FUeDBWR1oxNUswTFdXMU9YUHhYTTBvWUtyVWVYYTE1cGxyQUg3YktqeHlLOUZlQUREMDhobEpSSG5ELUxsbkFvQXRYU1U0WmhUZGxLWU5DWFZBX1pf</guid></item><item><title>危机时期的公共卫生领袖Walter Dowdle去世，享年94岁--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/29/us/walter-dowdle-dead.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 14:17:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE4xdG5UTlZjSU42TE5uVDVKMWJjMTBXZjd0OURFMnljLXA2Vll5U216OW5fQUxybUlidElWRjlKLTBrRHQ0NHFYeWZicTczdDJCbU5CRGpIV052Vkk5bDNQd1FGcWViVVZaWlFlZFNB</guid></item><item><title>人民药店：在我的医生开处方之前，我经历了10年的更年期地狱- OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2025/11/peoples-pharmacy-i-went-through-10-years-of-menopause-hell-before-my-physician-prescribed-this.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BWVOY24CQBDELDXQ6NXPISPPEE"&gt;Q. I went through a long, arduous menopause, more than 10 years of pure hell. The killers weren’t the chills, night sweats or insomnia, though inadequate sleep does make you a little wonky. It was the major depression that almost did me in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RSQOVWSOIJAJJFRF7IXFZEBLVM"&gt;I finally consulted a physician who was a specialist in bioidentical hormone replacement. She did very thorough testing and balanced my female hormone levels. She also added a tiny dose of testosterone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Y4BFG4IW7BAEJJK7YD2Q7ZM77Y"&gt;The results were nothing short of miraculous. I came out of the fog of depression almost overnight. That was after a decade of suffering. I had energy to exercise and dance again. And I could sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KQVMONYA4JFPZFHJTS6VW2ZXDQ"&gt;Balancing out my hormones plus adding a dash of testosterone may have saved my sanity, if not my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="COYEVY5WDFFIBBKZN7CIK2374U"&gt;A. Thank you for sharing such a compelling story. The Food and Drug Administration recently announced that it would be removing the black box safety warnings on hormone therapy. FDA Commissioner Dr. Marty Makary agrees with you. He has pointed out that many women experience debilitating symptoms during menopause, including severe depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="B2DOKOIGV5B3HFI6BIZW46PIYA"&gt;The current discussion of hormone replacement therapy rarely mentions testosterone, although women also make this “male” hormone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KDGNOPTE7VECTPBRJZNNMUOFAQ"&gt;A study in the British Journal of Psychiatry (June 16, 2025) found that hormone therapy, including testosterone, helped ease depression in menopausal women. A comprehensive review of the medical literature in the journal Cureus (Aug. 28, 2024) also concluded that testosterone can be helpful, especially for easing vaginal dryness and improving sexual desire and satisfaction. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SOVMSS6W6JEQ3JQSZVRX5423TQ"&gt;Q. I am on rosuvastatin to lower my cholesterol. Of the several side effects I am experiencing, constipation is the showstopper. I take magnesium and a stool softener plus laxatives just to poop every two to three days. Do you have any suggestions to help control constipation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="O7L4J26XUVASTPMXMJQ5SXRB3M"&gt;A. Constipation can be a side effect of many medications, including statins like rosuvastatin (Crestor). A different cholesterol-lowering drug might be less likely to cause this complication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="I77ARYTTT5DBHJZQIKS6TBRNSQ"&gt;You might also want to consider taking the soluble fiber psyllium (Metamucil). Not only does it help with regularity, but it can also lower cholesterol modestly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VT3WZ4LAUVFZJAFI7DLKAP4IUU"&gt;You can learn more about medications that cause constipation and many ways to relieve this problem in our “eGuide to Overcoming Digestive Disorders.” This online resource can be found under the Health eGuides tab at www.PeoplesPharmacy.com. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV6MCHOH2VEWXPLJQLBNMTAT4M"&gt;&lt;i&gt;In their column, Joe and Teresa Graedon answer letters from readers. Write to them in care of King Features, 628 Virginia Drive, Orlando, FL 32803, or email them via their website: www.PeoplesPharmacy.com. Their newest book is “Top Screwups Doctors Make and How to Avoid Them.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2AFBVV95cUxQaTYxOGM3Wk1XTlBYcVpLMHExQzg1WlFDWnpiX2sybUNyRnNFZUlQSW12TzE2YlRzTlFqZ1JFeVMwMHc2a0VwVEZ5QUlGRzRjMXE5QU1ISFFaX3g0S0tiZmx6N1Z3ZVZMaTdTaGd6ZVVVMXJVT3BwRDJkdklHU0NTUkowTVB1d3lMVTlISE1KVW9ZQndiamdsZEJTQzZvX1F4alNWUVZKc2dJdklHUGwtMlpNYmFhOW5VWWpnRmpkMFJIWFJtU1hVdXdsaklwNVppa3hGM1NvaljSAewBQVVfeXFMTjh3WkRMcUN1QjlVTEhBLXdyS3gxT0J3cUVISVloN21vaWZrUXZHeE1KS05uSVNla0lQM3ZZVk8zVGNIUDJrLXdqd3FWdGlUa1BnNlc0X3VFVlpjTUVGeXpjdDhsTmVneEc2R0pjYWlDRTlDRG9la1hUVjRnOV9KdnNxNFRJSG1tQjktQ3Z6TEx0NlkzdHUwbzNfYU9ZSU9DSXEzcFlpYmFPUkxUM2NIOG5yNjFOU0NROEJuNENuNjhuNE0yTmJyc2ZYbEQtMy1NV0xqQy1hdE9wcWlaSVZLM0gwQy1iRTJOYlJjS2I</guid></item><item><title>北欧饮食习惯可能是长寿、健康生活的秘诀- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/nordic-eating-habits-may-hold-the-secret-to-longer-healthier-lives/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:49:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxPbk94ZDhtLVBOQi13V213OHVGbkFYZU0zWGhsMzZKWHEzeWNVQWZudEIwamJWSk52OHRNY3BJd2hkTGNIMmdjNUNaQXFIdHE5bTBmRkgtRFVMbFVFSVQzcUpTT1FsS25UTG5FRjRweVJWbWtJYmtFdG94eDNXM2U5b3BYTkJ0TUduOFREY2haUHZSb2RQYklz</guid></item><item><title>对于注册官Craig Olive及其家人来说，阿尔茨海默氏症临近家庭- JoCo报告</title><link>https://jocoreport.com/for-registrar-craig-olive-and-his-family-alzheimers-hits-close-to-home/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content is-layout-flow"&gt;
			
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;November is Alzheimer’s Awareness Month&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://jocoreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Craig-Olive-Pearl-Thompson-Brown-Olive-cp.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-200137" srcset="https://jocoreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Craig-Olive-Pearl-Thompson-Brown-Olive-cp.jpg 630w, https://jocoreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Craig-Olive-Pearl-Thompson-Brown-Olive-cp-276x300.jpg 276w, https://jocoreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Craig-Olive-Pearl-Thompson-Brown-Olive-cp-138x150.jpg 138w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 630px) 100vw, 630px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Register of Deeds Craig Olive and his mother, Pearl Thompson Brown Olive. Contributed Photo&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;JOHNSTON COUNTY – For Johnston County Registrar of Deeds Craig Olive and his blended family, Alzheimer’s disease is personal. He and his kin have seen the disease ravage parents, siblings, grandparents, aunts and uncles.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Olive lost his mother, Pearl Thompson Brown Olive, to Alzheimer’s in 2007.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“She helped raise 15 children altogether — stepchildren and her own,” he recalls in an interview from his office in the Johnston County Courthouse.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But Pearl was more than his mom.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“At age 45, she went back to school and got her nursing degree at what was then Johnston Technical College,” Olive says. “She then worked 16 years as a nurse at WakeMed.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We’ve got a scholarship in her name at the college,” a proud Olive adds. “And they even named a room after her.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But in her early 70s, Alzheimer’s began robbing him of the mother and woman he knew. She did and said inexplicable things, Olive says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“She put utensils in the trashcan,” he recalls. “She walked out into the median of Highway 70. She’d say she had to go pick my brother up from work, something she hadn’t had to do in years.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;His mother had been a regular at what was then the Clayton Senior Center, now the Clayton Center for Active Aging. “But we had to stop that,” Olive says, explaining that his mother became too much for staff to handle. “Mama was wandering around, even going into the men’s bathroom by mistake.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Olive became his mother’s caregiver, but he had help. “My mother was going to an adult day care program over here at First Baptist Church and then at Divine Destiny, another adult day care,” he says. “That was a big help for me.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But then his mother suffered a brain bleed in a fall, and Olive had to keep her at home. “She was never like she had been before,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;After his mother’s fall, Olive turned to in-home care for help, and he sang the praises of those caregivers, including Martha Godwin. “She’s like family,” he says all these years later. “She was a jewel, and Camille Hunter too.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For those who can afford it, Olive recommends in-home care. “I have nothing against nursing homes,” he says. “I just wish they had more staff members.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For caregivers, Olive recommends self-care. “You need to allow time for yourself,” he says, “because it can take a toll. You’re under stress, worrying all the time.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Caregivers can find themselves sacrificing things that gave them joy, adds Olive, who most recently found himself caring for a brother who died earlier this year of kidney disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I love the beach, and I haven’t been to the beach in four years because of being a caregiver,” he says. “You need to get away from the whole situation and give yourself time to do things,” Olive says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And by all means, take advantage of the resources available, he says. “It’s a long, lonely, hard road,” Olive says of Alzheimer’s caregiving.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For help and advice, he turned to his mother’s doctors, Community &amp;amp; Senior Services of Johnston County, the state’s Division of Aging, the Johnston County Department of Social Services and the N.C. Alzheimer’s Association.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“It made the journey a lot easier,” Olive says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A daughter’s story&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br&gt;Early on, Melanie Nunn and her siblings thought their mother, Brenda Ann Brown Dixon, was suffering from hearing loss.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image aligncenter size-full"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://jocoreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Brenda-Ann-Brown-cp.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-200138" srcset="https://jocoreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Brenda-Ann-Brown-cp.jpg 580w, https://jocoreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Brenda-Ann-Brown-cp-244x300.jpg 244w, https://jocoreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/11/Brenda-Ann-Brown-cp-122x150.jpg 122w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 580px) 100vw, 580px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Craig Olive’s sister, Brenda Ann Brown Dixon. Contributed Photo&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Conversations over the telephone became different and shorter than usual,” recalls Nunn, niece of Johnston County Registrar of Deeds Craig Olive. “We even pursued getting her hearing aids, but they didn’t help.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;But the family was also aware that a far worse diagnosis was possible. “We knew fairly early that mom had the possibility of developing dementia as I talked her into getting an APO-E blood test,” Nunn says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The test determines a person’s genetic risk for Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Her result came back as a 3/4,” Nunn says. “This meant mom was most likely going to develop dementia.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And her mom’s doctor confirmed an early diagnosis of mild cognitive impairment.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I’m thankful for the blood test and knowing early that mom had a high probability of developing dementia,” Nunn says. “This allowed us to prepare as much as we could and to really cherish our time together while she still had some clarity of mind.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Because the diagnosis was early, her mom was able to remain at home, where Nunn’s dad was her main caregiver.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“Since I lived close by, I gave dad breaks a few times a week for a few hours,” Nunn says. “I would wash and style mom’s hair and make sure she got a good bath and her hygiene was taken care of.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Her mom found it hard to decide which outfit to wear each day. “So we went through her closet and paired outfits — tops with pants were hung together — and narrowed her choices to five,” Nunn says. “This helped her and my dad immensely.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Her father needed more help than he admitted. “He didn’t want us to worry,” Nunn says. “Mom had always done the laundry, cooking, house cleaning, etc. He really tried, but meals became pickups from restaurants.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As the disease progressed, her mother changed. “Mom started having bathroom accidents and asking repetitive questions,” Nunn says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Her personality changed too. “She was initially an introvert but became more of an extrovert who spoke her mind in love,” says Nunn, who also changed. “I became a fierce protector and advocate for my mom.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And when her father died in 2020, Nunn became her mother’s chief caregiver. “Mom came to live with my family and I for 16 months, until she needed more care than I could give her,” she says. “I wasn’t able to care for her full time, care for two kids at home, homeschool them and be a full-time wife.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Putting her mom in a skilled nursing home was hard but necessary, Nunn says. “I experienced so much guilt but knew that placing her in a facility where she would have access to therapy would be helpful,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In a real sense, the daughter became the mother in terms of care. “But the respect I had for her as my mom never dwindled,” Nunn says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“During her time with dementia, the Lord taught me so much through her,” she adds. “Mom handled the declines that came with dementia with such grace.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Still, the woman and mother she knew slipped away. “I truly missed opportunities to have meaningful conversations with my mom,” Nunn says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;As she cared for her mom amid her decline, Nunn found comfort in daily walks — “a great way to relieve stress,” she says — and in her faith. “I talked to God and read the Bible daily,” Nunn says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I knew I needed his strength and I couldn’t be all that mom needed me to be without him.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nunn also took part in online grief counseling. “I started this after my dad passed away and I began caring for mom,” she says. “I had godly friends from my church who prayed for me, listened to me and helped me care for mom to give me a break.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nunn is grateful too for the support she received from her husband and children. “My husband treated and loved my mom like his own,” she says. “He also took over household chores so I could spend time with mom. He was my eyes and kept me accountable to eat well, continue to exercise and seek out help when I needed it.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Caring for someone with Alzheimer’s is a labor of love, Nunn says. “It’s hard and emotional, but so worth it,” she says. “Cherish every day.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nunn has this advice for caregivers of dementia sufferers. “Make life as normal as possible for them because change is hard for someone with dementia,” she says. “Hug them and express your love to them. They can still hear and feel.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In the nursing home, Nunn decorated her mom’s room much like her room back home.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“I took her to get her nails done, kept her dressed in the best clothes — if you look good, you feel good — took her out to get ice cream, pushed her in her wheel chair outside every day to get her into the sunshine and took her to church almost every week,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At church, her mother was much like her old self, Nunn says. “Taking my mom to church gave me back my mom for a few hours each week,” she says. “She could enter the church confused, but when the worship music started and the preacher preached, it was like the Holy Spirit made the confusion dissipate and mom was present. It was so cool to watch.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;For anyone starting the caregiver journey, Nunn has plenty of advice. “Ask for help early on,” she says. “Take pictures with your loved one as much as possible, record their voice in videos, have your loved one write letters to their children, grandchildren, friends before they are unable to express themselves.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Though dementia eventually claimed her mother’s memory, Nunn says she never forgot her husband, Don Dixon, and her Savior, Jesus Christ. “She talked about dad frequently and told others about her love for Jesus,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;And that’s how she hopes people will remember her mom. “She loved Jesus and trusted him completely, even in this diagnosis,” Nunn says. “And she loved her family.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Story by County of Johnston &lt;br&gt;Republished with permission &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class="wp-block-group has-border-color is-layout-flow wp-block-group-is-layout-flow"&gt;
	
	&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-alpha-channel-opacity is-style-wide"&gt;
	

	
	&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading has-text-align-center"&gt;Discover more from JoCo Report&lt;/h3&gt;
	

	
	&lt;p class="has-text-align-center"&gt;Subscribe to get the latest posts sent to your email.&lt;/p&gt;
	

	
	
	
&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>JoCo Report</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:43:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxObTVuSTY2Tm5xZFhDb3V5eEYxbHk5RENlVjM1T2pSVkpHaHRyX18wdXNoaEVaUEV2anNIcE1LVDZVNGRtZDh5VG5hYnp6WlNnb1VfS3hxMlZNRTB6VHlnODc3SWlyMnpfMy1idXBxd21IS2V3dG56U1ZHem1MTUlfNktscHkwT3NQUktXRnllYTNHV1p5a1lGVW93</guid></item><item><title>可能有助于减缓大脑衰老的5种令人惊讶的活动-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/5-surprising-activities-that-might-help-slow-brain-ageing/articleshow/125658393.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aging shows up in the body long before we notice it in the mind. But the brain ages quietly, slowly, sometimes without any obvious sign until memory slips or focus blurs. Scientists have spent years trying to understand whether lifestyle choices can actually shape this timeline, whether everyday activities can nudge the brain toward resilience instead of decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in Nature Communications in October suggests the answer might lie in something surprisingly simple: creativity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;7 Daily habits to follow every night for a sharper brain&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers found that certain activities were linked to brains that looked younger than a person’s actual age. What stood out was how accessible these activities are; they’re not limited to artists or prodigies, but to anyone willing to immerse themselves in something imaginative. As study author Agustín Ibáñez, director of the Latin American Brain Health Institute at Universidad Adolfo Ibáñez, put it, “This is not just a solution for the da Vincis of the world. Anyone can benefit from having a creative hobby, not just geniuses or professional artists.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking about the modern pressures people live under, he added, “We are living in a world full of stress, uncertainty and despair. Creating a little bubble through art or music can have a positive impact on your brain health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What the study found&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team analyzed brain imaging data from 1,467 healthy participants, including tango dancers, musicians, visual artists and strategy video game players. To measure how fast or slow the brain was aging, they used computational “brain clocks” that estimate biological brain age versus chronological age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Accelerated aging, where the brain appears older than the person, is often seen in people with psychiatric or neurological conditions. But this study looked at the opposite: what activities are linked to delayed brain aging?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;All four creative and cognitively demanding pursuits studied showed strong association with younger-looking brains. People with higher skill levels or years of practice had even stronger results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even beginners weren’t left out. In one experiment, researchers trained 24 people to play StarCraft II, a strategic video game, for 30 hours over several weeks. A control group trained on Hearthstone, a more rigid, rule-based game. After the training period, only the StarCraft II group showed slower brain aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the basis of the study, these are few activities that were most strongly associated with delayed brain aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dancing&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The strongest effect in the study came from highly skilled tango dancers, whose brains appeared, on average, seven years younger than their chronological age. Dance activates motor skills, rhythm, coordination, social connection and fast decision-making, creating a deep cognitive workout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Playing music&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Musicians also showed younger biological brain age. Whether it’s learning a new instrument or returning to an old one, the combination of melody, memory, timing and emotional processing seems to strengthen brain networks over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Visual art&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Painting, drawing or any form of visual creation was linked to delayed brain aging. It’s not about talent; it’s about a process that keeps cognitive pathways active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Strategy video games&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Games like StarCraft II, which require planning, creativity and rapid problem-solving, were associated with younger-looking brains, even after just 30 hours of training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Attending performances and exhibitions&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Passive engagement matters too. Going to concerts, plays or museums for a few hours a week was associated with better memory and slower cognitive decline, according to Sonke’s 2022 study of older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7gFBVV95cUxOZTk1cFMyeE9vSmE3T0dIdlNUNjNLQUdYOXpPUFA5RHNIZWFpNl81ejk5a0NmX3dJb0s5MVRPRnI4aTFQQU1ILVNtclFhWktxZFpOQkt5Y2c2NXdDXzhNTWFEd0ZIb1BSMEtOejd4YmRHSlJ3N1lGNmQydk02ZFdyS1JWNk8yTHFWOHFXVV9reVlpWEZOUzNCRWQ2VXBGRFdtc2draDhKa090QTJWOVFDRFA4clBkYnBkTm1ESmp5WVRFZXdwa3dRMXJDNndfMmlQWnZOZUo1bWpGdkI0blB0cEVIVmdMVllWREpfdkxR0gHzAUFVX3lxTFBMV0gxc3p3Q0J0WGJ4YjBGZXQwTy1BZDlibXc2NlBVMEJrN3J0N2pZNjNyY1RTXzJxYVY1MEFJSTNNRjMzVEdBLXQ5UUhORmhFaHJhYVBZNFY4LWhhR2hQdFlrWVdEODNjZ0JCUXZDYzM2TFJUM0xISE05SlB4UGpqUm5jWTBqcU4waGZrdV93d3IxZ3dBNWVENXd4eGE5dWNEX3hhUElZRm5jUE1NS0JqM1NVUkRPblA5RG9DQ2Zoc2hkdjlqWWpSc0RZSzRuNjJJQ3QxLWFaYW5TOG5WZ3kyeVdDVmxFenZnLXBZQ3JMWEtUTQ</guid></item><item><title>您家中已有的5种阿育吠陀头发生长的日常成分-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/beauty/5-ayurvedic-everyday-ingredients-for-hair-growth-you-already-have-at-home/photostory/125656434.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly every Indian household has a hibiscus plant with blooming red and white hibiscus flowers. Well, these beautiful flowers are a beloved Ayurvedic herb and are known for their deep-conditioning, hair-strengthening, and scalp-nourishing powers. Brimming with amino acids, vitamins, and flavonoids, hibiscus boosts hair growth, reduces hair fall, enhances hair shine, and also prevents premature greying. You can apply hibiscus-infused oil, create a homemade natural hair mask, opt for a hibiscus hair rinse, and eventually witness the change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Image Credits: Pinterest)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5wFBVV95cUxNckRPTWtER0U1ZVNpZVUtbTE2RHc0cnJpdUNuVkdZd1UwTUxpal9HM2wtWHgtVU9wWEFmSmJ5SHUzdXZNSHhSbUJEY0Uza202MDlVUmhtUXdDYnNOeVNtTWowYXl6MGYxV0ZRNG95aVlXaDFBbmFwTXkyTXp5YThuZnZ6c3JycGhnMkJRdTJkczhJcnAzNlJHV3NDWS1sM3pHWnNPOUNUX0pHWTZRQklKSFNvazA2c0J1OHlSRnR5OEdlMVpzalpUMXR3b1pWWFoyT2JHVnhHSWFzOG1CYnVHLTBTODNZRVHSAe8BQVVfeXFMTXhwLTMyY2VqSVcwaDF2MGl0SF9iY3EtcFFBSWtBMXMyNHN1eEhLcldsYUtwNHNreUJLYWdtU1BoaEVlbWd5YXRVTzU4b0ZQOGp3aFBYdEdfUS1pZ3UtT2RPOTVvTUpVb2x3N2tMVVZ4TGdBVXJHYjZfQk1KekZnVTJGdHZZVU81LTQxS2x1aFRhbWxpcFRiUFVLMGN0SWFXOERlUklkb0prSVBCZDJVd2pXMk5qQ1B3OW9GUTdFSXNpRWhrQjlfYmwwRGl1X2NxcnFVT1N2YVFIdHRIckE4WnFXUDV4NmlSY3ZwZ3RQUms</guid></item><item><title>新型鼻用纳米滴剂根除小鼠脑肿瘤- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/new-nasal-nanodrops-eradicate-brain-tumors-in-mice/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:14:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOVUlSdW5Eb0MwMEJaNTVvelJLQ3VpQ2d2YkVvckZZMDBHSm41OEVoRnlfTWVadUVkUk5Nb0xqR05OOXFENkJMSFp3b2RFbnFyeXRxTnI4aXVsdDhISjd5dkJ4UXlvdTF6RlpoMkMyRUdjMUp1ZnBZYkRiZVR0VGxiNC1B</guid></item><item><title>可以预防慢性疾病或某些癌症的常用疫苗-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/29/vaccines-chronic-disease-prevent-cancer/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TFYSXEN7PREOLB6PJK53VDEBSA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Vaccines don’t just shield you from specific infectious diseases or help make symptoms less severe if you get sick but can also prevent common chronic illnesses, including some cancers, according to public health experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:01:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOOUhMQ3ozcXhYNmtzNTJzMk5yR3FpNENiakpzaUQ4M3NlV2xIdjUtdTV3ZUVtckMtSkhaUGZ5Vld5dE1fcmlTWmlWanBVa2dQN21FSTJPQ1kzZlA4dXp6d3JFVGEyeWxpU05IRXpXZHZCenZmVnBBYjgyejV0cnZnSm9fWERZYnM2TUpRYmZQTHNxTW8</guid></item><item><title>一位蹒跚学步的孩子在妈妈注意到令人担忧的症状后，只活了3年。他证明每个人都错了。- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/pediatric-cancer-acute-lymphoblastic-leukemia-miami-florida/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Meghan Jenkins had her hands full with her toddler, Malachi. He was energetic and inquisitive, eager to explore the world around him. He loved anything to do with the Miami Dolphins and played constantly with dinosaurs and monster trucks. He was settling in at day care while Jenkins returned to work after taking a year off. Life was busy, but happy.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In March 2021, Jenkins noticed Malachi was tired and lethargic. He also had a lingering cough. One day, he threw up. When Jenkins changed his diaper, she found black stool. Immediately concerned, she and Malachi went straight to the emergency room. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things moved quickly then, Jenkins said. Malachi was "connected to all these cords." Someone said he might need a blood transfusion. Hours passed with no answers. Jenkins grew more scared by the minute. Finally, Malachi was admitted to the pediatric intensive care unit, where doctors performed a bone marrow biopsy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, a doctor sat Jenkins down for the diagnosis: Acute lymphoblastic leukemia. She was told her little boy's life expectancy could be just two and a half to three more years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In that moment, you question God. You ask him 'Why did this happen?'" Jenkins said. "I was so lost. This was my only child. I was young still, going through life, trying to figure things out. And then I had a big hit." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/8f57571e-88d7-4cf9-a986-4d075d46f2c8/thumbnail/620x729/4af9606f2eea33ed8f49be90c37f083f/img-6456.jpg#" alt="img-6456.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/8f57571e-88d7-4cf9-a986-4d075d46f2c8/thumbnail/620x729/4af9606f2eea33ed8f49be90c37f083f/img-6456.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/8f57571e-88d7-4cf9-a986-4d075d46f2c8/thumbnail/1240x1458/397c6931ab72f641a2a7b0c3c51f5a6e/img-6456.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Meghan Jenkins' son Malachi in the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Meghan Jenkins

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;h2&gt;What is acute lymphoblastic leukemia? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Acute lymphoblastic leukemia, or ALL, is a rare cancer that starts in the bone marrow, &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/acute-lymphocytic-leukemia/about/what-is-all.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the American Cancer Society's website&lt;/a&gt;. Only about 6,100 new cases of ALL are diagnosed a year, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/acute-lymphocytic-leukemia/about/key-statistics.html#:~:text=About%206%2C100%20new%20cases%20of,males%20and%20680%20in%20females)" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;, with children under the age of 5 having the highest risk of developing the disease. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ALL is a fast-growing cancer that results in the body producing immature white blood cells. Malachi's white blood cell count was more than 10 times higher than it should be. The white blood cells were crowding out healthy cells, weakening his immune system and making it impossible for his body to fight off infections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ALL can quickly spread throughout the body and affect the lymph nodes, liver, spleen and other organs, as well as the central nervous system. Because the cancer grows so quickly, immediate treatment is key. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Malachi was already "quite sick" when he was diagnosed, said Dr. Julio Barredo, the director of pediatric cancer programs at Sylvester Comprehensive Cancer Center. She started Malachi on chemotherapy immediately. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Treating acute lymphoblastic leukemia  &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the first month of treatment, Malachi was hospitalized. The first weeks of chemotherapy are intense, so staying in the hospital is often safer, said pediatric hematologist Dr. Aditi Dhir. Malachi had side effects including nausea and fatigue. He regressed in his potty training. Jenkins needed to wear gloves to hold him because of his compromised immune system. The toddler milestones she'd expected to celebrate were nowhere to be seen. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"There were days I didn't even think I was going to go on, but I had to," Jenkins said. "It was stressful. It was depressing, constantly being in there." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/ad82a3c5-f794-43c3-b95e-53e29226a2dc/thumbnail/620x753/0300d9a2ea38db1d3cd92cc98554c275/img-6457.jpg#" alt="img-6457.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/ad82a3c5-f794-43c3-b95e-53e29226a2dc/thumbnail/620x753/0300d9a2ea38db1d3cd92cc98554c275/img-6457.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/ad82a3c5-f794-43c3-b95e-53e29226a2dc/thumbnail/1240x1506/faab9c83d9084d03335d06171c1aa2ba/img-6457.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Meghan Jenkins' son Malachi in the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Meghan Jenkins

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Still, the chemotherapy was clearly helping Malachi, Dhir said. She recalled seeing him run around the PICU within a week of starting treatment. Barredo said that Malachi handled the chemotherapy "as well as anybody could have handled it given the circumstances." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the first month, Malachi continued chemotherapy at home. He took eight medications a day, Jenkins said, and spent several days a week in the hospital. Next came the "maintenance" phase, Barredo said. During this time, Malachi remained on oral medication and only needed to go to the hospital every few weeks, Dhir explained. The maintenance phase lasted for two years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, in August 2023, "the storm blew over," Jenkins said. Malachi was able to ring the bell that signified the completion of cancer treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"You can't tell he ever had leukemia" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, Malachi is a "very loving" 7-year-old who excels in school, takes gifted classes and regularly appears on the honor roll, Jenkins said. He still cheers for the Dolphins and plays with dinosaurs and trucks. He's become a big reader and loves to share fun facts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, he is in remission. With acute lymphoblastic leukemia, the highest risk of relapse is within the first year of completing therapy, Barredo said. Malachi passed that milestone with flying colors. There's "some risk" of relapse in the second year, Barredo said, but Malachi and Jenkins marked that in August without incident. After two years, it "is quite unusual" for an ALL patient to relapse, Barredo said. Malachi has outperformed his initial prognosis, and the success of his treatment means "his life expectancy is like that of any other kid his age." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/bde9f6ce-6354-48a5-8efd-82b720c8e6c1/thumbnail/620x752/96d4f22a30d2cc9cfa7ec01ec7020722/img-6455.jpg#" alt="img-6455.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/bde9f6ce-6354-48a5-8efd-82b720c8e6c1/thumbnail/620x752/96d4f22a30d2cc9cfa7ec01ec7020722/img-6455.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/11/06/bde9f6ce-6354-48a5-8efd-82b720c8e6c1/thumbnail/1240x1504/698da72e39b33eac5c26da0251590f69/img-6455.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Meghan Jenkins' son Malachi after completing cancer treatment.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Meghan Jenkins

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;"You look at him, you can't tell he ever had leukemia," Barredo said. "For all practical purposes, he is pretty much cured at this point in time. ... He'll be able to do whatever he wants to do." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Malachi's immune system remains compromised, Jenkins said, but she hopes to build it up so can have a normal childhood going forward. The family is looking forward to "finally blossoming" after the years of treatment and trauma. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This whole process was very hard. It's still hard. I have moments sometimes where I'm in shock, like I don't believe we went through this or this even happened," Jenkins said. "But there is a brighter situation. Every situation doesn't have this outcome. But there are brighter outcomes. There are happier days than just being in the hospital and being sad." &lt;/p&gt;

    

                    
        
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 13:00:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOOVlsdHdLa0lTdklOOENKaEtaNzhvMG5JMHBvM2U2UE9qTG1IU2lXNHByMnE2MFV4OExHWW11NWpDUkdMMzg2Tk14SWctb0xRUV8zZjJRbkZZcW82ZnNKaG9FUGM1TUpuZjh3b2hMWkhxVjhTdFNqeldnc01NUDV5Y04wMGdtYlc4aHMxaGZqQmFkODTSAZgBQVVfeXFMT19ucmEwQjBZNE9FYlBwMW5HdEU3cWtTbnZ1c3U1M0xENExaU3lFWnUwWWprTEJraXd5MXZ2b09pSjgzcTBXcGJxLTNXWmptU0w4SXZPV0hwcklLZmJlam1nTThMa1d1dGZQTzFuUE9MMy03ZW95cjlYZ3NsdEE4SU9UWmdEa2dCTEcxbkZzUW1CWjFtR1ZHeG0</guid></item><item><title>当疾病颠覆退休计划时-华尔街日报</title><link>https://www.wsj.com/lifestyle/when-illness-upends-retirement-plans-b2ecfe81</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Wall Street Journal</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 12:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQVk9PWnpjdzZkWnJtc2hBV0dRZE9CSzBCcVlRSWNadVdVbTlNUkliWjZoa0lvejJLbldpcUFNMFgzbU9XRTJrX2hBMWJxSWV6ZlotUWhKTDh5OElkTnNjVUZzMENQQ3NLQmRWQmwtZjlpTXV5ZlpLQmZPOVA3Wko3aA</guid></item><item><title>您的排便时间表对您的整体健康有很大影响，研究表明- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/your-poop-schedule-says-a-lot-about-your-overall-health-study-shows</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;"How often do you poop?" might sound like a very personal question, but your answer could reveal quite a lot about your overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in July 2024 investigated how often 1,425 people went number two, and compared those stats to their demographic, genetic, and health data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The healthiest participants reported pooping once or twice a day – a 'Goldilocks zone' of bowel movement frequency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pooping too often or too rarely were both associated with different underlying health issues, the team led by researchers at the Institute for Systems Biology (ISB) found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/something-in-your-poop-may-predict-an-imminent-death?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Something in Your Poop May Predict an Imminent Death&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This study shows how bowel movement frequency can influence all body systems, and how aberrant bowel movement frequency may be an important risk factor in the development of chronic diseases," &lt;a href="https://isbscience.org/news/health/timing-is-everything-isb-study-finds-link-between-bowel-movement-frequency-and-overall-health/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; ISB microbiologist Sean Gibbons, the corresponding author of the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These insights could inform strategies for managing bowel movement frequency, even in healthy populations, to optimize health and wellness."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below for a summary:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study investigated the bathroom habits of people who were "generally healthy" – that is, with no history of kidney or gut issues like &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-7-common-daily-habits-could-be-damaging-your-kidneys"&gt;kidney disease&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/researchers-have-sussed-out-a-driving-mechanism-behind-irritable-bowel-syndrome"&gt;irritable bowel syndrome&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/blood-tests-can-reveal-crohns-disease-8-years-before-diagnosis"&gt;Crohn's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants self-reported how often they dropped the kids off at the pool, and the researchers organized them into four categories: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-constipation-could-be-having-a-serious-impact-on-your-heart"&gt;constipation&lt;/a&gt; for those reporting one or two bowel movements per week; low-normal for three to six movements per week; high-normal for one to three movements per day; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/severe-diarrhea-cases-surging-across-uk-and-scientists-dont-know-why"&gt;diarrhea&lt;/a&gt; for four or more watery stools per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also analyzed patients' blood metabolites and chemistry, their genetics, and the gut microbes present in their stool samples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_132891" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-132891" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1-642x578.jpg" alt="A graphic depicting the studied variables" class="size-medium wp-image-132891" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1-642x578.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1-461x415.jpg 461w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1-600x540.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1.jpg 765w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-132891" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Participants provided samples of blood plasma and stool, in addition to filling out extensive diet, health, and lifestyle questionnaires. (&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell-reports-medicine/fulltext/S2666-3791(24)00360-4"&gt;Johnson-Martínez et al., &lt;em&gt;Cell Reports&lt;/em&gt;, 2024&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team looked for possible associations between bowel movement frequency and these health markers, as well as other factors like their age and sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, those who reported less frequent bowel movements tended to be women, younger, and with a lower &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/bmi-is-an-awful-predictor-of-early-death-weve-had-a-better-option-for-decades"&gt;body mass index&lt;/a&gt; (BMI). But even accounting for these factors, people with constipation or diarrhea showed clear links to underlying health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bacteria usually found in the upper gastrointestinal tract were more common in stool samples from participants with diarrhea. Their blood samples, meanwhile, showed biomarkers associated with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/vicious-cycle-revealed-how-alcohol-helps-gut-bacteria-attack-your-liver"&gt;liver damage&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144992" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144992" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/LiverHumanAnatomy642.jpg" alt="Anatomical diagram of upper body with liver highlighted" class="size-full wp-image-144992" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/LiverHumanAnatomy642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/LiverHumanAnatomy642-295x415.jpg 295w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/LiverHumanAnatomy642-600x844.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144992" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The liver usually recycles bile acid to dissolve and absorb dietary fats. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADAyYOC5_Y/"&gt;Eraxion/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stool samples from people with less frequent bowel movements had higher levels of bacteria associated with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/mnfr.201100542"&gt;protein fermentation&lt;/a&gt;. This is &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-well-is-your-gut-working-theres-a-grossly-simple-way-to-check"&gt;a known hazard from constipation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If stool sticks around too long in the gut, microbes use up all of the available dietary fiber, which they ferment into &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/eating-fiber-could-protect-you-from-infections-heres-why"&gt;beneficial short-chain fatty acids&lt;/a&gt;," &lt;a href="https://isbscience.org/news/health/timing-is-everything-isb-study-finds-link-between-bowel-movement-frequency-and-overall-health/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Johannes Johnson-Martinez, a bioengineer at ISB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"After that, the ecosystem switches to fermentation of proteins, which produces several toxins that can make their way into the bloodstream."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sure enough, some of these byproducts were found in these patients' blood samples. Particularly enriched was a metabolite called indoxyl-sulfate, a known product of protein fermentation that can damage the kidneys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team suggests the finding is potential evidence of a causal link between bowel movement frequency and overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is some hope that people can change their habits and, as a result, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/yo-yo-dieting-may-trigger-long-lasting-changes-in-gut-bacteria"&gt;their health&lt;/a&gt;. Recent research suggests your gut microbiome can shift a lot faster than you might think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For instance, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/lifting-weights-could-change-your-gut-microbiome-within-weeks"&gt;a 2025 study from Germany&lt;/a&gt;, yet to undergo  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/science-peer-review" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73086" data-postid="182074" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;peer review&lt;/a&gt;, tracked inactive adults who began resistance training twice or three times a week. Those who gained the most strength showed changes in the makeup of their gut bacteria in just eight weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These kinds of changes might help some people move out of the constipation or diarrhea categories and into a healthier bowel-movement range.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those in the Goldilocks zone of pooping reported eating more fiber, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/first-of-its-kind-study-lists-health-benefits-of-drinking-more-water-each-day"&gt;drinking more water&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pooping-before-you-exercise-has-an-incredible-effect-on-performance"&gt;exercising more often&lt;/a&gt;. Their stool samples also showed high levels of bacteria associated with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/particular-gut-bacteria-could-help-you-fight-cancer"&gt;fermenting fiber&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_144950" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-144950" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PlantBasedDietFood642.png" alt="Food on a table with hands grabbing it" class="size-full wp-image-144950" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PlantBasedDietFood642.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PlantBasedDietFood642-533x415.png 533w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PlantBasedDietFood642-600x467.png 600w" sizes="auto, (max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-144950" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A more plant-dominant diet can have health benefits. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAExZ_P9JfI/"&gt;Prostock-studio/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-guts-methane-making-microbes-could-secretly-turn-fiber-into-extra-calories"&gt;A clinical trial published in 2025 by US researchers&lt;/a&gt; found that people with a lot of methane-producing microbes in their guts are especially efficient at turning dietary fiber into short-chain fatty acids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This suggests that both the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/eating-30-plants-a-week-a-healthier-diet-or-just-a-gimmick"&gt;amount of fiber&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-contain-a-variety-of-microbiomes-heres-a-look-at-a-few-of-the-most-important"&gt;specific mix of microbes&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-strange-world-of-organisms-lives-inside-you-but-not-like-you-think"&gt;an individual's gut&lt;/a&gt; are important, which explains why two people eating the same diet can experience &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/bacteria-inside-you-may-explain-why-weight-piles-on-after-dieting"&gt;different health outcomes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/heres-how-to-avoid-food-poisoning-this-thanksgiving"&gt;Here's How to Avoid Food Poisoning This Thanksgiving&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, everybody's found themselves at one extreme or the other at some point in their lives, after catching a stomach bug or eating &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cheese-may-actually-fuel-nightmares-surprising-study-confirms"&gt;too much cheese&lt;/a&gt;. But this study was looking at people's everyday routine, and reveals how our own version of 'normal' could &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-identify-specific-bacteria-linked-to-multiple-sclerosis"&gt;hint at health issues&lt;/a&gt; we weren't aware of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in the journal &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.xcrm.2024.101646"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in July 2025.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 12:01:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOc3N6U2ZidV91RzRPaHlXc3VTWDJwV2FFQVpDM0laYjFPcGZOTXNsVC1UaXJ2MlZ6NWN0VG11NEdybUhWUHVJcGkyVW9KeTRxOWZFRG5wbG1JUjA5UHJTYW9UeHhSSXJCdFlsNGN0QUFkamFYaGJVX0ZIREUtUWxoWnR6UG5saWo1NUlSN1dnTG83Qmo2Qk1qWU1vQTU</guid></item><item><title>新泽西州的临床试验为无法治愈的癌症患者提供了新的生活机会- NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/11/clinical-trial-in-nj-gives-patients-with-incurable-cancer-a-new-chance-at-life.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K4ZQ72M5RJCHRJ4ZGKJJKRLG5I"&gt;Cancer came crashing into Maria Pascale’s life like a high-speed car — literally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PMNZYY2SAZCXNC5VH44HTZFX3M"&gt;During a CT scan after a traumatic car accident in February 2018, Pascale was dealt another blow when doctors noticed a mass in her neck, in between the esophagus and thyroid gland. A biopsy later confirmed it was squamous cell carcinoma, snaking around her vocal cords.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RKFTTKGP6RC2RNMJ6DUHZNVTMU"&gt;“I was really nervous,” said Pascale, who lives in Philadelphia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IR53NBG7NZE63IEQA4YE37TVZY"&gt;Over the next seven years, she tried all of the conventional treatment options, but the cancer kept returning. Pascale assumed she would be sick forever. That is, until a new treatment developed at Rutgers Cancer Institute, New Jersey’s only National Cancer Institute-designated Comprehensive Cancer Center, and RWJBarnabas Health changed her life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HRDMZMBKQ5C3JC4INUIGMOSQYI"&gt;“I didn’t know if I was going to be alive. And now I have 14 months of being strong,” said Pascale, who has been in remission since September 2024. “I’m doing more exercise, I go to karate. Now I can do things.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XTZGBMZF45CMHJHNXLMZ5PIKGY"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Losing hope and finding it again&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="T437CPYNJ5B3RMZ6X2OZ6C5BYE"&gt;The cancer diagnosis caught Pascale by surprise. She didn’t notice any symptoms. She also didn’t match the standard profile for head and neck cancer, which is twice as common among men and often diagnosed in people over age 50. Pascale, now 50, was diagnosed at 43 years old. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TZZMUJYVIRDGBHYVQ2DPCXNJS4"&gt;Head and neck cancer impacts thousands of people each year in the United States. In 2025, an estimated 72,680 people in the U.S. will receive a diagnosis of cancer of the oral cavity, pharynx, or larynx, the major types of head and neck cancer, according to the &lt;a href="https://seer.cancer.gov/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;National Cancer Institute&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6NN5BC2X25G2XP5HSSIYKHGOWQ"&gt;Alcohol and tobacco use are two of the most important risk factors for head and neck cancers. However, a large portion of new head and neck diagnoses are being driven by cancer-causing types of human papillomavirus, or HPV, according to an &lt;a href="https://www.facs.org/for-medical-professionals/news-publications/news-and-articles/bulletin/2025/october-2025-volume-110-issue-9/rising-incidence-of-head-and-neck-cancer-drives-treatment-advances/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.facs.org/for-medical-professionals/news-publications/news-and-articles/bulletin/2025/october-2025-volume-110-issue-9/rising-incidence-of-head-and-neck-cancer-drives-treatment-advances/"&gt;Oct. 30 article&lt;/a&gt; in the &lt;i&gt;Bulletin of the American College of Surgeons&lt;/i&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K7M5HZXI2BFNJA7HJ75DNN3DFI"&gt;Pascale was diagnosed with a type of HPV-related head and neck cancer. Within months of her diagnosis, Pascale underwent three surgeries to remove the cancerous mass in her neck, cut out parts of her tonsils and the back of her tongue, and take out her lymph nodes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CVVS4M3E5JDKBEDKMKGI2L5IUQ"&gt;“The surgeries were really painful, especially the second one. My sister is strong, but that one was bad,” said Maria Durante, Pascale’s sister. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XAJ2LVIS6FBTJPWYUBS3U6DNZU"&gt;The surgeries were brutal, but they seemed effective at removing the cancer. Then, one day in 2021, Pascale began to have difficulty swallowing. It felt like food getting stuck in her throat. A CT scan revealed a mass around her esophagus. This time, Pascale said, she underwent chemotherapy and radiation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RJXTB2F6ERF5HAAUWVFVXYG2UE"&gt;Two years later, she learned the cancer had metastasized to the lungs. More chemotherapy followed, but it was less effective at shrinking her tumors. Then, at the start of 2024, Pascale developed an allergic reaction to her chemotherapy treatment. She felt defeated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7XDH3OUFDNGC3LSMT2YDTP3XBU"&gt;“I didn’t have any hope because all of the traditional treatments, they were not working for me,” said Pascale. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EJR3TRIFH5HZXMFS4VFLDLR7XY"&gt;That’s when her oncologist at Thomas Jefferson University Hospital mentioned a clinical trial at Rutgers Cancer Institute and RWJBarnabas Health that was using cellular therapy to treat advanced HPV-related cancers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XJNESOWNH5GVXBCVY2PCHZTPUU"&gt;Cellular therapy has generated a lot of excitement in recent years, especially &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/06/a-revolutionary-drug-made-in-nj-is-giving-cancer-patients-years-of-their-lives-back.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/06/a-revolutionary-drug-made-in-nj-is-giving-cancer-patients-years-of-their-lives-back.html"&gt;CAR T-cell therapy&lt;/a&gt;, which has proven to be successful in treating certain blood cancers. The therapy takes a patient’s cells and genetically engineers them to target and attack the cancer cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DEYSIMYG6JF5XKL23WKOAHESAQ"&gt;Dr. Christian Hinrichs, who leads the cell therapy program at Rutgers Cancer Institute, has been working for years on a similar treatment for other types of cancer. He developed a one-time cellular therapy for patients with metastatic HPV-associated cancers and the clinical trial has yielded promising results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="article__image"&gt;&lt;div class="article__image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="low" loading="lazy" decoding="async" alt="Maria Pascale Rutgers Cancer Institute" class="article__image-content" src="https://www.nj.com/resizer/v2/AVIXP77NDVDX5BUPC4KHNF27E4.jpg?auth=f7a3be84bf348cdb75f99dbae2edf659ad68ebc4ed28496bb61d6a44aa328455&amp;amp;width=1280&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90" srcset="https://www.nj.com/resizer/v2/AVIXP77NDVDX5BUPC4KHNF27E4.jpg?auth=f7a3be84bf348cdb75f99dbae2edf659ad68ebc4ed28496bb61d6a44aa328455&amp;amp;width=500&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90 500w, https://www.nj.com/resizer/v2/AVIXP77NDVDX5BUPC4KHNF27E4.jpg?auth=f7a3be84bf348cdb75f99dbae2edf659ad68ebc4ed28496bb61d6a44aa328455&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90 800w, https://www.nj.com/resizer/v2/AVIXP77NDVDX5BUPC4KHNF27E4.jpg?auth=f7a3be84bf348cdb75f99dbae2edf659ad68ebc4ed28496bb61d6a44aa328455&amp;amp;width=1280&amp;amp;smart=true&amp;amp;quality=90 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 500px) 100vw, (max-width: 800px) 80vw, 60vw"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="article__image-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="article__mm-image-caption-text"&gt;Dr. Christian S. Hinrichs with his patient Maria Pascale, right, and her sister Maria Durante, left, at Rutgers Cancer Institute.&lt;span class="article__mm-image-credit"&gt;Rutgers Cancer Institute&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="J432SLFYL5EDFJS2X5JLKZGEEY"&gt;When Pascale got the treatment at Rutgers Cancer Institute in July 2024, she said that at first, “it was really painful.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="USRTHRXOHZEYFAEHG6AAVCYSNI"&gt;“I felt like I had pneumonia, it was horrible, but it was the cells working. That’s how I took it — I’m feeling this way because the cells are working and killed the cancer," said Pascale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5N3AHKMU3RESLG7HAIMAI5SKG4"&gt;Six out of 10 patients treated so far, including Pascale, have achieved substantial tumor shrinkage, according to the &lt;a href="https://cinj.org/landmark-data-shows-long-term-complete-responses-t-cell-therapies" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://cinj.org/landmark-data-shows-long-term-complete-responses-t-cell-therapies"&gt;findings&lt;/a&gt; presented at the Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer Annual Meeting on Nov. 5–9. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BGESJKIARVE6BE62OBYGAG2ULI"&gt;“At an individual level it’s life-changing for these patients who’ve had their cancers go away,” said Hinrichs, co-director of the Duncan and Nancy MacMillan Cancer Immunology and Metabolism Center of Excellence at Rutgers Cancer Institute and chief of the Section of Cancer Immunotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EJBXRLHAFNA57NO24GVANQPZ7M"&gt;On a broader level, he added, the study offers hope that cellular therapy can be applied for the treatment of other cancers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="INOKWB3A75HBNLX35KALRPXSZM"&gt;“It shows that this type of treatment approach with the one-time engineered T-cell therapy can cause complete responses in epithelial cancers, in these common cancers. And although we’re starting with HPV, it’s a foundation to build from,” said Hinrichs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VGOSA3PM3VCXHJBKZ7EKP6DR7M"&gt;Now living in remission, Pascale encourages other cancer patients to never give up trying new treatment options. Just when she was feeling weary, the clinical trial came around. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AYBSVHYBWJGXFOBF247JUTDUXA"&gt;“It’s painful. It’s hard. But you have to be strong and try,” said Pascale. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:XJ3YCBPTGZHX3E2YD7NNSYNLD4" data-fusion-component="XJ3YCBPTGZHX3E2YD7NNSYNLD4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:XJ3YCBPTGZHX3E2YD7NNSYNLD4" data-fusion-component="XJ3YCBPTGZHX3E2YD7NNSYNLD4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxOX2xOZVdoVDkzbGVBNjRJUG1LdW9faGJGYndaUkdNaFdjZm5ENllwTHRjSHNjNE1aY2lRVU9zQzFTSFA3VnUyaldkWHFSWU1qV3BrMUlmWFl2MFVObTFQcjd1UXo1eGNZNWxjbmFhWnFoa0Y1WElZMU5hcjNsSVBzUThQal9pbUhaeXFkcFZnakNJUXdGZU9ELUFEYklGb1F0NE9YZ19kUHFOeUxjRVlCVHptQXRnWlNHTjBpONIB0AFBVV95cUxOaTJFSWRoN0JjdmQzOXowZEZjdGFXUXpjQXhPSm9qMFgwckJNLWY4UjlKamNCNTFrbHp2eTZYZGVvRGswUjRTd0RfdzF0NjMxWHVLZk5CNmZhWWR4YzZGRTBhM2ZJNW1WNGVCa2RCdC05UGhrZGVwdTY0bE01YkpZa0lwQVQyTXZCVjBNcGlCeWZQdE82VnZWRzRkQldxX2NhZTRTMUFHQ01pYXRiYW9vRHprRTd5ckV6MEFocUNfSXhaU0Z6b3VveWFEWkw3Um94</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现，美国最受欢迎的与肥胖有关的食用油-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/americas-favourite-cooking-oil-soyabean-oil-linked-to-obesity/articleshow/125654722.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s the cooking oil Americans reach for every single day, often without a second thought. In fact, it is a staple in processed foods. A cooking oil commonly consumed in the United States could be fuelling the obesity crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A recent experiment conducted at UC Riverside found that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="linkinghub.elsevier.com/retrieve/pii/S0022227525001956" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;America’s favourite cooking oil is linked to obesity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. The findings of the research are published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Journal of Lipid Research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;5 Oils that should be consumed raw for potential health benefits&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;keyword id="920592" type="General" weightage="100" keywordseo="soybean-oil" source="Orion"&gt;Soybean oil&lt;/keyword&gt; linked to obesity&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The researchers found that soybean oil, which is widely consumed by Americans, significantly contributes to obesity, at least in mice. The researchers also explored the metabolic pathway behind weight gain in mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; During the experiment, the researchers found that most mice on a high-fat diet rich in soybean oil gained significant weight. However, this oil had no impact on genetically engineered mice. Instead, they produced a slightly different form of a liver protein that influences hundreds of genes linked to fat metabolism. This protein also changes how the body processes linoleic acid, a major component of soybean oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; “This may be the first step toward understanding why some people gain weight more easily than others on a diet high in soybean oil,” corresponding author Sonia Deol, a UCR biomedical scientist, said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The researchers noted that both versions of the liver protein HNF4α exist in humans; however, the alternative form is produced only under certain conditions, such as chronic illness or metabolic stress from fasting or alcoholic fatty liver. This variation, along with differences in age, sex, medications, and genetics, may help explain why some people gain weight, and others don’t, while consuming soybean oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; This new experiment builds on previous work by UCR researchers &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0132672" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;linking soybean oil to weight gain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. “We’ve known since our 2015 study that soybean oil is more obesogenic than coconut oil. But now we have the clearest evidence yet that it’s not the oil itself, or even linoleic acid. It’s what the fat turns into inside the body,” Frances Sladek, a UCR professor of cell biology, said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The linoleic acid in soybean oil is converted into molecules called oxylipins. Excessive consumption leads to increased amounts of oxylipins, which are linked with inflammation and fat accumulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Is soybean oil the villain?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Soybean oil is widely consumed in the US. In fact, a 2011 study published in the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;American Journal of Clinical Nutrition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that there has been a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002916523022700?via%3Dihub" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;five-fold increase in soybean oil consumption&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; in the past century, from about 2% of total calories to nearly 10%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Though soybeans are excellent sources of plant-based protein and their oil contains no cholesterol, excessive consumption of linoleic acid may cause more harm than good. As soybean oil is a staple in ultra-processed foods, it may be fuelling chronic metabolic conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The researchers also found that despite the lack of cholesterol in soybean oil, its consumption is still associated with higher cholesterol levels in mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; “Soybean oil isn’t inherently evil. But the quantities in which we consume it are triggering pathways our bodies didn’t evolve to handle,” Sladek said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; “It took 100 years from the first observed link between chewing tobacco and cancer to get warning labels on cigarettes. We hope it won’t take that long for society to recognise the link between excessive soybean oil consumption and negative health effects,” Sladek added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi8wFBVV95cUxNMmJNcDJhTk90cmZvUm9HX1QtWVpvV3kwRzM4eDdvNWVMVFN2eTIxMThwRmFhTm9MNUJrNUZIUzgzUXU0YmdTYWc5SElhamI3ZWNNVDJ3WlFfbmNHa0hWSzJPTzc1d0R6SmpSYmxZc1dfd0MxaUw4OFVXZHpmcDhnTEdpV19rTTM2ZWlYbDZubHF2Tlhta2lTWWRIVVl3dHowbjFobzdVdkU2RlJxc1E2WFJ2cThCYTlOVU5abENLbk5QcTNKWUhOMVFacFhCdDNNMDZtYmRnZ2ZzTFBVM3RFQXB6QW4yS3oxR04tcEQzdXNCUmc</guid></item><item><title>高空气污染可能会使运动益处减少一半–研究- Hacker News</title><link>https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=46086624</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hacker News</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 11:24:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWEFVX3lxTFBaX09FSzEyZmgwbXVBek1kWnJHYnFSWlphRE5rMVFvcU1VclRTS09YNzFRWHpUeXp1cGZHN0tMT0VWNTJuVGFNTXdMM3pUQkh3OE1ldHN2RnM</guid></item><item><title>女性心胸外科医生，解锁男性堡垒-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/11/29/health/women-surgeons.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 10:00:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTE42bFpNREJZazBYM2xrdGg4X2hXbmdXSUZMS0N1bWE3X2F3RXo1ZTk4aklfV2R1Sy16cHhoUmd3M3JpVWlka21SUHZZeldzLUxoZWVjZTNUYnlFYmZnUlE1QW1uUDl6WnpXallxb3h3</guid></item><item><title>FDA将实施严格的新疫苗要求，声称儿童因新冠肺炎疫苗而死亡--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/11/29/fda-vaccine-approval-child-covid-deaths/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TE4N3MB7V50Q96K75C6X9RAKVC" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The nation’s top vaccine regulator on Friday laid out a stricter approach for&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;federal vaccine approvals, citing his team’s conclusion that coronavirus vaccines had contributed to the deaths of at least 10 children, according to an internal Food and Drug Administration email obtained by The Washington Post.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 09:36:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNUHBRWnVxSHA4bW54SVEyUzdPQzFwWEFnZG9Dd2xmeGxOTkczWThSUzF2UzhrTlRmYXRpRzJXbVk5WVZUTW43WUROWFl3YXNwOGRtaHFscTUwQWFNUXhDS3dqQXZReEViOG1vbFo4NVBnN2Yxbmo2dFBnOHBJYzUzRS1BMW53bTJUaHpyU1JBWEFjM00</guid></item><item><title>I-90检查站标志CWD合规性- Coeur d 'Alene Press</title><link>https://cdapress.com/news/2025/nov/29/i-90-checkpoint-flags-cwd-compliance/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-body font-weight-normal fr-view" id="storycontent"&gt;
	
		
		

			
				
			

			
				
				
				
	                                &lt;p&gt;Staff from Idaho Fish and Game’s Panhandle Regional Office operated a check station Nov. 16 along Interstate 90 near Fourth of July Pass. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The purpose of the station was to monitor hunter compliance with Idaho’s wildlife laws and to evaluate whether big game harvested out of state or from an Idaho chronic wasting disease management zone was being transported in accordance with CWD regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like many other states, Idaho prohibits transporting or importing the spine or brain tissue of deer, elk and moose harvested in states where CWD has been detected. Nearly all of Idaho’s neighboring states — and most states nationwide — are currently CWD-positive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the recent check station represents only a brief snapshot in time, Fish and Game staff observed that compliance with CWD-related transport rules was very low. Chronic wasting disease is a fatal neurological disease that poses a significant risk to Idaho’s big game herds, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hunters who pursue big game outside Idaho and plan to bring any parts into or through the state are encouraged to review Idaho’s legal transport requirements by visiting the CWD webpage on the Idaho Fish and Game website. Hunters who pursue big game within Idaho’s CWD management zones should also take time to understand the zone-specific rules and requirements before heading into the field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Idaho law authorizes Fish and Game to operate check stations to enforce wildlife regulations and collect biological data that supports wildlife management. All hunters, anglers and trappers — with or without game — are required to stop when encountering an official Fish and Game check station.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;— Idaho Department of Fish and Game&lt;/p&gt;
				
			
		
	

&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Coeur d'Alene Press</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 09:04:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxQUURfemgyZFNhdmh2NmdNTExHa2c2cldhLUNLdi1veHVHaUtWUW43b0pBc3dNbHlvWDlvQ0FodWFpZi1BUHNoVWpERm1qMU9KT1RNOVUySmJYOG9XRkFueEk2OEpJRlBYTkJKSW1QNTB3UlZ2ZEVaYy15X2NtSXJYQg</guid></item><item><title>加尔各答心脏病专家解释为什么您的心脏可能“跳动太慢” ；分享5个心动过缓的警告信号|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/kolkata-cardiologist-explains-why-your-heart-may-be-beating-too-slowly-shares-5-warning-signs-of-bradycardia-101764403095193.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/kolkata-cardiologist-explains-why-your-heart-may-be-beating-too-slowly-shares-5-warning-signs-of-bradycardia-101764403095193.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Heart rhythms and pace give critical insights into &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiovascular-health-to-metabolic-disorders-know-what-recent-human-trials-reveal-about-garlic-s-therapeutic-potential-101763796258603.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="cardiovascular health"&gt;cardiovascular health&lt;/a&gt;. The rhythms of your heartbeat can reveal a lot, even warn you about your conditions. Just like how irregular &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/caffeine-may-prevent-irregular-heartbeats-in-people-with-atrial-fibrillation-new-study-claims-101763467185496.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="heartbeats"&gt;heartbeats&lt;/a&gt; indicate conditions like arrhythmia. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Just like irregular heartbeats can indicate arrhythmia, a slow heartbeat is not always normal either; it could be a sign of a concerning condition called bradycardia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/29/550x309/5913_1764403502197_1764403514878.jpg" alt="Slow heartbeats can be an issue that requires medical attention immediately. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Slow heartbeats can be an issue that requires medical attention immediately. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/29/550x309/5913_1764403502197_1764403514878.jpg" alt="Slow heartbeats can be an issue that requires medical attention immediately. (Picture credit: Freepik)" title="Slow heartbeats can be an issue that requires medical attention immediately. (Picture credit: Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Slow heartbeats can be an issue that requires medical attention immediately. (Picture credit: Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/eating-these-foods-could-reduce-your-risk-of-heart-disease-irregular-heartbeat-heart-failure-potassium-rich-diet-101756626887815.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Are you at risk of heart disease? Study reveals eating these foods could reduce your risk of irregular heartbeat"&gt;Are you at risk of heart disease? Study reveals eating these foods could reduce your risk of irregular heartbeat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;To better understand the warning signs, HT Lifestyle reached out to Dr Dilip Kumar, senior interventional cardiologist and device specialist, Manipal Hospital at EM Bypass in Kolkata.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Explaining what bradycardia is, Dr Dilip Kumar said, “It is a condition where your heart consistently beats slower than 60 beats per minute (bpm).” &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;As per the cardiologist, this is alarming because it means your heart might not be pumping oxygen-rich blood enough to your body, impacting energy and overall health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Kumar further elaborated that when the heart's electrical system, which controls its rhythm, does not work properly, the heart can beat too slowly. While a slow heartbeat can be normal for athletes, for others it may signal an underlying health problem that needs attention.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Who should be careful?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A slow heartbeat can happen to anyone; some people need to be particularly cautious. Dr Kumar, "Certain groups are at higher risk, including older adults, individuals with existing heart conditions, diabetes, or kidney disease, and those taking certain medications.” &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;So if you fall into any of the mentioned groups, monitoring your heart rate and consulting a doctor regularly would help to detect bradycardia and prevent complications such as dizziness, fatigue, or fainting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Can it be prevented?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, can this be prevented? &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;As per the cardiologist, not all causes of a slow heartbeat can be avoided, but you can lower your risk by taking care of your heart.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He added, "&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;While not all causes are preventable, maintaining a heart-healthy lifestyle through regular exercise, a balanced diet, stress management, and routine medical check-ups can significantly reduce your risk and support overall heart health.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 warning signs which indicates that indicate your slow heartbeat could be bradycardia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/06/09/original/dizzyy_1749461325665.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Dizziness is one of the symptoms of bradycardia.(Picture credit: Shutterstock)" title="Dizziness is one of the symptoms of bradycardia.(Picture credit: Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dizziness is one of the symptoms of bradycardia.(Picture credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Kumar listed these 5 signs which may mean you have bradycardia and require a doctor visit:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Persistent fatigue and weakness:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; Feeling drained, even after rest, can signal that your heart isn't delivering enough oxygen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dizziness or light-headedness:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; Insufficient blood flow to the brain due to a slow heart rate can cause these sensations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fainting or near-fainting spells:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; A sudden, significant drop in heart rate can lead to loss of consciousness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Shortness of breath, especially during activity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; Your heart struggles to meet oxygen demands, causing breathlessness with minimal exertion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chest pain or discomfort:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; This can indicate your heart muscle isn't receiving enough oxygen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 08:57:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAJBVV95cUxQbG9xMUNjRTctVjVuVnI4U2pFSWVYWWNNQWlRT3lQS1RRQnRrbnJYN3dORERnQmhPeUxCSVVQaFlGSmZmU0VFU293QVotOWlCWENNTkJ5UEx3TExEa0phb1BwWWdIa1B6aVNPaVVZdVVLM281Vk5PWGZYOXFVQmlSQy1Hd2RHRnJZa1o1cDdWd2lyYnM0MlJkdUhWcGU5R3dOTXhOT1VxSXdLUjhSRFNQU2ZTcFZJdUM3dTBzOGQ2aWs5TFNhLURtdnR2VE1EQVlXZ3J2REM0ZUZEdHBNM204eXR6dEJzc3NjQzFXUnQxbnBsa293M2hwb1VFVVVyS1h4RmtEM2ZFVm3SAY4CQVVfeXFMUEJmNlQ0cDFoNnpEdTNmcGsxUVFuME1jeVlBVXFaOEYycUtqZTdIbWpYNFlNNUhWc3Q3Nk55Z0RfeVJnREU1X3BmSGtzbXZLeGFCS2VzVmlYZDVVNGhKT3JZQzU3blZWOHRhZU12Y3hySWtYLU9kQWs1OW1LakMtRGZ0dUN0UUNyR21RUkc5QzBkczZPSmw4QWhVQmNPMTRTTkpXRm5HdjNPNlN2SmdNNVdGeXNfSkpKNU5JQmZJNW5fS3p3UFBGTEdFNjJ6RWtvTk5wN2ZrWTljZnFIdUlNRUhYX2tvQ002cnFRTTNER0p1TWVmaWxhUmFzRHRYbk00ZzVDckJFZExhOHlOMWJ3</guid></item><item><title>冷冻面包如何使面包对血糖控制和肠道健康更健康-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/how-freezing-your-bread-makes-it-healthier-for-blood-sugar-control-and-gut-health/articleshow/125642357.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bread sits at the centre of many winter meals, yet few people realise that the way it is stored can subtly shape its nutritional behaviour. For many households, freezing bread is simply a practical step to reduce waste during colder months when groceries last longer and consumption patterns shift. Recent discussions among clinicians and nutrition researchers have highlighted that freezing may also influence how the body processes carbohydrates. In a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/reel/DRkiUK4DRh5/?utm_source=ig_web_copy_link&amp;amp;igsh=NTc4MTIwNjQ2YQ==" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;popular reel, Dr Kunal Sood explained&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; that freezing alters the structure of starch in ways that change how the digestive system responds to it. This has prompted renewed interest in understanding whether a basic habit like freezing bread can support healthier metabolic patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Hidden health &lt;keyword id="31113739" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="benefits-of-freezing-bread" source="Orion"&gt;benefits of freezing bread&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Kunal Sood describes the process clearly, saying, “Freezing your bread doesn’t just keep it from going stale, it can actually make it a little healthier. Here’s how. When bread is frozen and then defrosted, some of the starches go through a process called retrogradation. That’s when part of the starch structure reorganises and turns into what’s known as resistant starch.” Resistant starch behaves differently from the rapidly digested starches found in freshly baked bread. In his words, “Resistant starch acts more like fibre than sugar. Your body digests it more slowly, which leads to steadier blood sugar levels and less of a spike after eating.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Five Effective Ways to Detoxify Your Gut Health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This explanation aligns with findings from a controlled trial &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.jpcmed.com/article_178948.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;published in Journal of Preventative and Complementary Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, which examined how freezing and reheating white bread affected the glycaemic response of healthy individuals. The researchers reported that freezing and then defrosting reduced post meal blood glucose spikes by up to 30 percent compared with fresh bread. As Dr Sood states, “One study even found that freezing and then defrosting white bread reduced post meal blood sugar spikes by up to 30 percent, compared to eating it fresh.” These effects offer a foundation for understanding the key benefits, which include better digestion and metabolic balance, antioxidant protection and immunity support, a more stable blood sugar response, improved gut microbiome function and higher natural energy levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;The key health effects linked to freezing bread:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supports digestion&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Boosts immunity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stabilizes blood sugar&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improves &lt;keyword id="2049757" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="gut-health" source="Orion"&gt;gut health&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Supports better daily energy&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Better digestion and metabolic balance through resistant starch formation&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When bread is exposed to freezing temperatures, the starch molecules gradually reorganise into a form that the body breaks down more slowly. This change means the digestive tract expends less effort managing sudden glucose surges, which often strain metabolic pathways during colder seasons when heavier meals are common. The presence of resistant starch encourages a steadier digestive rhythm, allowing nutrients to be absorbed at a smoother pace. Many individuals find that foods containing resistant starch contribute to prolonged satiety and more consistent digestive comfort, particularly when eaten during winter months when fluctuations in eating patterns tend to be more pronounced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Antioxidant protection and immunity boost influenced by slower digestion&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slower carbohydrate digestion affects how antioxidants and micronutrients are released and absorbed. Winter diets often rely on preserved, reheated or starchy foods, which sometimes offer limited micronutrient density. Bread that has undergone freezing and retrogradation releases its sugars at a slower rate, which helps maintain more balanced cellular activity. This supports the immune system indirectly, because stable metabolic conditions improve the body’s capacity to regulate inflammation and oxidative stress. Although bread is not a primary antioxidant source, its altered digestibility helps regulate processes that protect immune cells from excessive metabolic strain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. More stable blood sugar response supported by clinical findings&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A central benefit, articulated by both Dr Sood and the referenced study, is the measurable reduction in post meal blood glucose spikes. The shift toward resistant starch means the carbohydrate behaves more like dietary fibre, resulting in a gradual rise in glucose rather than a rapid surge. This is particularly relevant in winter, when many people rely on toast or warm sandwiches as quick energy sources. A gentler glycaemic response helps support concentration, appetite control and overall metabolic stability throughout the day. As Dr Sood adds, “If you toast it after freezing, the effect becomes even stronger,” suggesting that reheating may amplify this stabilising influence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. Improved gut microbiome function through increased resistant starch intake&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Resistant starch plays a recognised role in feeding beneficial gut bacteria, which rely on fermentable fibres to produce short chain fatty acids. These compounds support colon health, enhance nutrient absorption and contribute to balanced immune responses. Dr Sood highlights this when he says, “That slower digestion helps not just for glucose control but also supports gut health since resistant starch feeds the beneficial bacteria in your colon.” During winter, when digestive sluggishness and irregular meal timing are common, foods that nourish the microbiome can help maintain smoother digestive behaviour and improve overall wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. Higher natural energy levels linked to steadier carbohydrate release&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Energy fluctuations in cold weather often reflect inconsistent glucose patterns influenced by refined carbohydrates. Freezing bread adjusts the structure of its starch in a way that creates a more gradual energy supply. Instead of a quick burst followed by fatigue, the body receives a sustained release that supports alertness and endurance throughout daily activities. This makes frozen then toasted bread a practical winter staple for individuals who rely on predictable energy, whether for work, study or exercise in colder conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a healthcare professional before making any changes to your diet, medication, or lifestyle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/what-eating-soaked-raisins-daily-can-do-for-your-bones-digestion-and-immunity-this-winter/articleshow/125642189.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;What eating soaked raisins daily can do for your bones, digestion, and immunity this winter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 07:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9wFBVV95cUxNSDdCZHdPN0dNb3ZjUTFwTS1ydDVIUUZTeFpVaGJ6TEx2WnpkWTZnenJReDVjMTBBRHJNLS1WTDA1V1BnUzc5aEttWjJ6eGNEWDlEM29qN0NEa0lpS3RvTi1ZR0xvZkF6X1RKa1VkTE5Mb0Jib1MyeEowN1gzd3FfQ2N3aXloLUVHQUllVU5rb3dlNmgwQ1hvODVPQlBuR09VRFhrcTFWRE1lUjEzNG1hQmt2NnZBTWRMWlBSUWZqcTVPMHN5b2xBME5oZDNvQ2RKUzNTNy1DNF9tM1dCbG1jMnlnX0MwcXBpVkJtS2ZFM3NIcE12UVJV0gH8AUFVX3lxTE41dHJ0b0EyU016RWVaenYwNHBVb09NcGhnS1dOYU04WEZBOGhQSUxwNTZmNl81a0dCbXBQWHo4TEpDVklFTFhVclV1RjNnbVNEY0RjWUczdWVzQVAzZXI0WVB0VWZ5bkJQLWVPYmpwM0tNa3d0cHJ0dnlrZnRZRTAtVTlWWUFqaTItWC11RWNFT2dtVDVvQ3BYSDktZWgxSEU3OG9zUUFKYzZVYjhtaF94WVJ1N1Z6MlY4S1JMNkZ0NGVxcW1WWmxiM0wxSy02Z3VaQ1VMZ210NzFlaVdFY2o4U1pqdUg2aWpVSmVEQ2FDRk9Pc2p6MUVWM3RZcg</guid></item><item><title>这个冬天，每天吃葡萄干对你的骨骼、消化和免疫力有什么好处-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/what-eating-soaked-raisins-daily-can-do-for-your-bones-digestion-and-immunity-this-winter/articleshow/125642189.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;During winter, maintaining balanced nutrition is particularly relevant due to colder temperatures, reduced sunlight exposure, and shifts in daily activity. Traditional practices in many households encourage consuming soaked raisins, or kishmish, on a daily basis, a habit increasingly supported by modern nutritional science. Soaked raisins are rich in fibre, essential minerals, antioxidants, and natural sugars, making them a compact source of nutrients that can support energy levels, digestive function, and immune resilience. By integrating these nutrient-dense dried fruits into daily meals, individuals can address seasonal nutritional gaps, promote cardiovascular and bone health, and provide their bodies with steady energy throughout the colder months. Scientific understanding now validates these traditional practices and explains the physiological benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Benefits of &lt;keyword id="22030834" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="eating-soaked-raisins" source="Orion"&gt;eating soaked raisins&lt;/keyword&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientific research &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31878160/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;published in Nutrients&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; indicates that consuming soaked raisins regularly offers multiple advantages during the colder months. Raisins are an abundant source of dietary fibre and bioactive compounds, which aid digestion and contribute to moderating blood glucose levels. They also contain key minerals such as iron, calcium, and boron, which are important for oxygen transport, bone density, and joint health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Additionally, the phenolic compounds present in raisins function as antioxidants, helping reduce oxidative stress and support immune function. Regular intake has also been linked to favourable cardiovascular outcomes, including improved lipid profiles and reduced blood pressure. These combined properties make soaked raisins particularly valuable as a winter dietary inclusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Health benefits of Raisins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Eating soaked raisins helps:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Aid digestion and metabolism&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support bone strength and blood health&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support &lt;keyword id="48619" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="immunity" source="Orion"&gt;immunity&lt;/keyword&gt; with antioxidants&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stabilize &lt;keyword id="76262" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="blood-sugar" source="Orion"&gt;blood sugar&lt;/keyword&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Digestive and metabolic balance&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the primary benefits of raisins is their high dietary fibre content, which promotes healthy bowel function and supports overall digestive regularity. Soaked raisins, which absorb water during preparation, become softer and easier to digest, allowing nutrients to be absorbed more efficiently. The soluble fibre and natural sugars in raisins provide a steady release of energy, avoiding sharp post-meal spikes in blood glucose that are commonly associated with refined or processed snacks. Scientific studies demonstrate that raisins have a low-to-moderate glycaemic index, which can help maintain metabolic stability throughout the day. During winter, when individuals may consume heavier meals and engage in less physical activity, this property of raisins becomes particularly advantageous, supporting both digestive comfort and sustained energy levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Mineral content for bone and circulatory support&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raisins are rich in minerals that are crucial for maintaining health during winter. Iron, for example, is essential for the production of haemoglobin and the transport of oxygen in the blood, helping to sustain energy and reduce fatigue that may be exacerbated by colder weather and reduced activity. Calcium and boron are important for bone health, with boron facilitating calcium absorption and utilisation, particularly during months when vitamin D synthesis from sunlight is limited. Consuming soaked raisins regularly provides a natural source of these minerals, supporting bone density, joint function, and overall circulatory health. Additionally, the iron content in raisins contributes to maintaining haemoglobin levels, which in turn supports cardiovascular performance, energy metabolism, and general wellbeing during periods of reduced outdoor exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Antioxidants for immunity and oxidative stress&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Raisins contain phenolic and polyphenolic compounds that act as antioxidants, helping the body neutralise free radicals and reduce oxidative stress. Winter conditions, including lower sunlight, cold stress, and higher exposure to seasonal pathogens, can increase oxidative stress and challenge immune function. The antioxidants present in raisins support cellular defence mechanisms, helping to maintain tissue integrity and reduce the impact of oxidative damage. These compounds also contribute to cardiovascular protection by preserving vascular health and promoting favourable lipid profiles. By incorporating soaked raisins into the daily diet, individuals provide their bodies with a natural source of antioxidants that support immunity, reduce inflammation, and contribute to overall physiological resilience during the colder months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. Cardiovascular wellness and glycaemic control&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular consumption of raisins has been associated with improvements in cardiovascular and metabolic health. Clinical trials indicate that consuming raisins before meals can reduce postprandial glucose levels compared with calorie-matched processed snacks. Observational studies further suggest that regular raisin intake may lower systolic blood pressure and improve low-density lipoprotein cholesterol levels. These cardiovascular and metabolic benefits are particularly relevant in winter, when sedentary habits, heavier meals, and seasonal changes in activity can increase the risk of elevated blood pressure or impaired glucose regulation. Incorporating soaked raisins into daily routines provides a simple, natural means to support heart health, maintain steady blood glucose levels, and contribute to overall metabolic stability during the colder season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How to consume soaked raisins&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For maximum benefit, raisins should be soaked in water for several hours or overnight, which softens their texture and improves digestibility. A recommended portion of 80–90 grams, roughly half a cup, delivers concentrated nutrients without excessive caloric intake. Soaked raisins can be eaten directly in the morning, added to breakfast cereals, yogurt, or smoothies, or incorporated into baked dishes and winter recipes. Regular inclusion in a balanced diet, alongside vegetables, whole grains, and protein, ensures that their fibre, minerals, antioxidants, and natural sugars complement overall nutritional intake. By consuming soaked raisins consistently, individuals can support digestion, cardiovascular health, immune function, and energy balance throughout the winter months in a convenient and practical manner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: This article is for informational purposes only and should not be considered medical advice. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/how-everyday-foods-like-tea-and-coffee-can-protect-your-heart-from-damage-caused-by-prolonged-sitting/articleshow/125633069.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;How everyday foods like tea and coffee can protect your heart from damage caused by prolonged sitting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 06:40:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggJBVV95cUxPYTNrNk5ET2lad1FPX3BJNXl6MWV0dkl6cG9Id1ZYLXgyXzg1WFVRUHRZRllFRVh3MmJDd0NnMmwtX1JzNERiZm14ZWJMNlN6STNJdkhLUC1uYlRWQ25jVElkRUQ2bmE3a3NoMFp2bW1KVkQ1YXBTdmhPc2ZKaEhQaXdWMFNNUGpVUjBlOE54TDVsa09uWjhMQ0sxbGxuNDlLREpCN0RBcmp0cW4wWWgtMWNhLXdKc0RsT2hCYWhmdUItYW9uVFFyMVFRWkdkNlRJbnoxQXFkNWJKdUtDemI4YzRKZnI1MDB0dHJxcm5Mb3Ewd18ydVpPOTloenFVZFl2U3c</guid></item><item><title>糖尿病前期可能在前2年最容易可逆-今日医学新闻</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/prediabetes-may-be-most-easily-reversible-in-the-first-2-years</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-7j3c6j"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/Prediabetes-Diabetes-Monitoring-Woman-Kitchen-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/Prediabetes-Diabetes-Monitoring-Woman-Kitchen-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/Prediabetes-Diabetes-Monitoring-Woman-Kitchen-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="eager" src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/Prediabetes-Diabetes-Monitoring-Woman-Kitchen-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="Indian woman with glucose monitor seen from the back in the kitchen" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Fprediabetes-may-be-most-easily-reversible-in-the-first-2-years&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F11%2FPrediabetes-Diabetes-Monitoring-Woman-Kitchen-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Prediabetes%3A%20To%20easily%20reverse%20it%2C%20act%20in%20the%20first%202%20years" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/11/Prediabetes-Diabetes-Monitoring-Woman-Kitchen-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-1nzy6lj css-whkgel"&gt;Acting fast on prediabetes may be the best way to stop it progressing into type 2 diabetes. Image credit: Fly View Productions/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Type 2 diabetes, which occurs when the body stops responding to insulin, the hormone that controls blood glucose levels, is becoming increasingly common.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Before type 2 diabetes develops, many people have blood glucose levels that are higher than normal, a condition called prediabetes that is usually symptom-free.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now, an Indian study has found that if people take steps to combat prediabetes within 2 years of diagnosis, they can prevent it progressing to type 2 diabetes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diabetes, a condition in which the body cannot control blood glucose levels, is a leading cause of death and disability worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2021, &lt;hl-trusted-source source="The Lancet" rationale="Highly respected journal,Expert written journal,Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/article/S0140-6736(23)01301-6/fulltext" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;529 million people&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; had diabetes, and the number is forecast to rise to 1.31 billion by 2050. Of these, some 96% have &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/317462" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, a condition that is often linked to &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/type-2-diabetes-prevention" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;lifestyle factors&lt;/a&gt;, such as poor diet, overweight and obesity, or lack of exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now, an Indian study, published in &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s40200-025-01790-7" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;The Journal of Diabetes &amp;amp; Metabolic Disorders&lt;/a&gt;, has found that if people take steps to control their prediabetes within 2 years of diagnosis, they have a good chance of preventing it progressing to type 2 diabetes.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://thelagom.co.uk/meet-the-team/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Jack Ogden&lt;/a&gt;, MBChB, BSc, LLM, IBLM, MRCGP, a primary care physician with a specialization in diabetes, from The Lagom Clinic, Bristol, United Kingdom, who was not involved in this research, commented to &lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt; that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The study employs a well-constructed retrospective cohort using 10 years of electronic medical record data from a closed urban population. The use of multi-state modeling is robust, with transitions aligning well with other cohort studies. However, there are some limitations to consider, such as reliance on opportunistic testing, potential selection bias, and limited generalizability due to the specific population studied. This study was only in a small area of India with its own culture and food preferences, making its less generalizable to many other people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, a few people are diagnosed following symptoms that may include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;increased appetite&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;unexplained weight loss/weight gain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;high body mass index (BMI)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;weakness&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;fatigue&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;sweating&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;blurred vision&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;slow healing cuts or bruises&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;recurrent skin infections/gum bleeding.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Because prediabetes is usually symptom-free, Ogden advised that “it’s crucial to focus on risk factors like being overweight, having a family history of diabetes, or conditions such as &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/150109" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;hypertension&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;“&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Testing is generally recommended from the age of 35, or earlier for individuals with these risk factors. For higher-risk populations, such as South Asians, earlier testing from around age 25 may be appropriate,” he told &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most, the condition will be detected by a blood glucose test — the &lt;hl-trusted-source source="PubMed Central" rationale="Highly respected database from the National Institutes of Health"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK549816/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;hemoglobin A1c, or HbA1c test&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;. This simple blood test shows average blood glucose levels over the preceding 3 months, with the results given as a percentage, as follows:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;normal blood sugar — below 5.7%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;prediabetes — between 5.7 and 6.4%&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;type 2 diabetes — above 6.4%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Type 2 diabetes is far more common in people who have had prediabetes than in those who have normal blood glucose levels, so lifestyle changes that reverse prediabetes are key to preventing it progressing to the more serious condition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Preventing progression to type 2 diabetes requires prompt lifestyle modifications. Aiming for 5-10% weight loss, engaging in at least 150 minutes of physical activity per week, and focusing on a diet rich in whole grains, vegetables, and lean proteins can be impactful. Addressing lifestyle factors such as sleep quality, stress management, and smoking cessation is also vital.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;– Jack Ogden, MBChB, BSc, LLM, IBLM, MRCGP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10420389/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt; have shown that several lifestyle interventions are effective in reversing prediabetes in adults. These include: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;hl-trusted-source source="National Institute of Diabetes and Digestive and Kidney Diseases" rationale="Governmental authority"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/diabetes/overview/what-is-diabetes/prediabetes-insulin-resistance" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; — keeping to a healthy weight (BMI of less than 25) or, if overweight, losing 5-7% of your body weight&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;increasing your physical activity — &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/150-minutes-of-exercise-per-week-could-help-reverse-prediabetes" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;one study&lt;/a&gt; found that just 150 minutes of exercise a week could bring blood glucose back to healthy levels&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;following a healthy diet, such as the &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/324221" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Mediterranean&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/dash-diet-for-hypertension-may-also-prevent-diabetes-complications" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;DASH&lt;/a&gt; diet, which focuses on complex, fiber-rich carbohydrates and healthy unsaturated fats, while restricting sugars, processed foods, and saturated fats&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;getting adequate sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Nutrition (whole foods, balanced intake, moderated caloric load), mindful movement, and lifestyle stewardship aren’t just wellness buzzwords but proven intervention tools,” advised &lt;a href="https://events.diabetes.org/b/sp/barbara-eichorst-1072" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Barbara Eichorst&lt;/a&gt;, MS, RD, CDCES, vice president of health care programs at the American Diabetes Association, likewise not involved in the recent study.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This study is not alone in suggesting that lifestyle modifications can be very effective, as Eichorst emphasized:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Results from the landmark &lt;hl-trusted-source source="National Institute of Diabetes and Digestive and Kidney Diseases" rationale="Governmental authority"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/about-niddk/research-areas/diabetes/diabetes-prevention-program-dpp" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Diabetes Prevention Program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; show that individuals at high risk for type 2 diabetes who engaged in a structured lifestyle-change program like modest weight loss (about 7% of body weight) plus about 150 minutes per week of physical activity, reduced their risk of developing type 2 diabetes by 58% over three years, compared with placebo.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What’s more,” she added, “these benefits endure. Long-term follow-up demonstrated that the lifestyle intervention continued to delay onset of diabetes and reduced long-term incidence over 10 to 15 years.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“These findings powerfully affirm that through intentional, consistent choices around nutrition, physical activity, and weight management, many people with prediabetes can significantly delay progression to type 2 diabetes,” said Eichorst.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longer a person has had prediabetes, the harder it is to reverse it, so Ogden advised that taking steps as soon as prediabetes is diagnosed is key.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“The study emphasizes the importance of timely action, particularly within the first 2-3 years of a prediabetes diagnosis, as this period is the most effective window for reversal,” he pointed out.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It also underscores that, despite healthcare accessibility, approximately 30% of individuals with prediabetes progress to diabetes within a decade, whereas up to 60% revert in the early stages. This highlights the potential for targeted, early interventions to yield significant benefits,” added Ogden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 06:22:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPUjhCdjVlTmtKVTcyWFF1OGN1d21HQW1RMW9BdFMxUXZZN3VBOWRuaGRfWXdOQzhXZHVoZ19qMHlpTld3eGpnYzlYNmtCSTczTUlUSnhCZlZoNW9LR3FBTVdodkJNaVQxS0NxaWllTGlHY0lXUzRtY2w3LVU3VFFYeVVKV0paNDhkQkozeGlYakgxZUxnTUc3amhBVTI4OXVZcFdhRlVzcw</guid></item><item><title>本地和地区艾滋病毒感染病例呈上升趋势- Stabroek News</title><link>https://www.stabroeknews.com/2025/11/29/news/guyana/hiv-cases-locally-regionally-on-the-rise/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="post-825113" class="post-825113 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail category-guyana tag-featured"&gt;&lt;div class="article-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;-Health Minister urges persons to get tested&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="in-content-ad"&gt;
  
&lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-client="ca-pub-3287926565830325" data-ad-slot="2321168057"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the rise in HIV cases, Minister of Health, Dr Frank Anthony, yesterday appealed to persons to know their HIV status by accessing his ministry’s free at-home HIV self-testing kits, as he announced that Guyana last year reported 449 new cases and the Caribbean some 15,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the Caribbean 340,000 are living with HIV and over the last year we would have had about 15,000 new infections. In the past year here in Guyana, we would have diagnosed at least 449 new infections,” Dr. Anthony said as the Ministry of Health yesterday launched planned activities for the month of December with World AIDS Day globally recognised on December 1.  The Human Immunodeficiency Virus (HIV) can result in Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome (AIDS) and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="in-content-ad mbo"&gt;
  &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle betweencontentmbo" data-ad-client="ca-pub-3287926565830325" data-ad-slot="2321168057"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Minister of Health emphasised that many of the new cases were preventable if persons would access the information and “understand how to prevent these infections.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;nav class="next-article"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.stabroeknews.com/2025/11/29/news/guyana/president-to-launch-five-year-blueprint-for-rapid-economic-expansion/" rel="prev"&gt;&lt;svg class="scroll-icon" aria-hidden="true" data-prefix="fa" data-icon="angle-double-right" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 448 512" data-fa-i2svg&gt;&lt;path fill="currentColor" d="M224.3 273l-136 136c-9.4 9.4-24.6 9.4-33.9 0l-22.6-22.6c-9.4-9.4-9.4-24.6 0-33.9l96.4-96.4-96.4-96.4c-9.4-9.4-9.4-24.6 0-33.9L54.3 103c9.4-9.4 24.6-9.4 33.9 0l136 136c9.5 9.4 9.5 24.6.1 34zm192-34l-136-136c-9.4-9.4-24.6-9.4-33.9 0l-22.6 22.6c-9.4 9.4-9.4 24.6 0 33.9l96.4 96.4-96.4 96.4c-9.4 9.4-9.4 24.6 0 33.9l22.6 22.6c9.4 9.4 24.6 9.4 33.9 0l136-136c9.4-9.2 9.4-24.4 0-33.8z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/nav&gt;&lt;footer&gt;&lt;div class="subscribe-box"&gt;&lt;div class="subscribe-box-details"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlock 1 week of unlimited access for just $5, or pick our top plan for only 30¢ a day! Enjoy fewer ads, full ePaper access, and our iOS &amp;amp; Android apps as a subscriber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Stabroek News</author><pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 06:13:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxOMFdsME9iemdzaXVRRjJUQU8xdE0tN2p6d1JRLUlhMDc2cmU5VTItRmhQd215cUxveDMxaFEzZ01sZlJVX0RFY1hUMGlreXdGZndkQmwtYjREUDlZN01iYmlDR1RnSHBndE1oNE5DT01qS2FBWU0zZU5GSjBzSFFoWk1OZkl6Tl82RnYxXzFxTmppLTR4TGZwUg</guid></item></channel></rss>