<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>一种甜美的水果，还可以控制血糖水平。研究声称它降低了糖尿病患者的风险-《经济时报》</title><link>https://m.economictimes.com/magazines/panache/a-fruit-that-is-sweet-and-can-also-control-blood-sugar-levels-study-claims-it-lowers-diabetics-risk/articleshow/124570023.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-brcount="26" class="artText"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may sound surprising, but research suggests that eating mangoes—a fruit known for its natural sweetness—can actually help manage &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/blood-sugar-levels" target="_blank"&gt;blood sugar levels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. A study conducted by researchers at &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/george-mason-university" target="_blank"&gt;George Mason University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; revealed that individuals who consumed mango daily had better blood sugar control and reduced body fat compared to those who opted for low-sugar snacks. The study’s findings, published in Foods in August 2025 under the title “Daily Mango Intake Improves Glycemic and Body Composition Outcomes in Adults with Prediabetes: A Randomized Controlled Study,” emphasize that the nutritional context of sugar within whole foods plays a more crucial role than the sugar content alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The Science Behind Mango’s Benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an interview with&lt;/p&gt;&lt;em&gt; Science Daily&lt;/em&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Raedeh Basiri, Assistant Professor in George Mason’s Department of Nutrition and Food Studies, explained that it’s not simply about how much sugar food contains, but about the overall nutritional makeup. Mangoes, for instance, offer a unique balance—while they contain natural sugars, these are accompanied by fiber, antioxidants, and essential vitamins. This combination helps slow sugar absorption, keeping blood glucose levels stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-newpos-mgid="mgid_124570023" id="div-mgid-mid-newpos-124570023"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p id="E_3" class="etoro"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, foods that contain added sugars—such as processed cereals or packaged low-sugar snacks—lack this natural balance and can actually heighten the risk of developing diabetes. The fiber in mangoes supports digestion and promotes satiety, helping control appetite and preventing overeating, which further aids weight management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Glycemic Index and Safe Consumption Tips&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mangoes fall within a moderate range on the glycemic index (GI), scoring between 51 and 56, a range comparable to orange juice. According to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a ref="dofollow" data-ga-onclick="Inarticle articleshow link click#Magazines#href" href="/topic/american-diabetes-association" target="_blank"&gt;American Diabetes Association&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; (ADA), this places mangoes in the low-to-medium GI category, making them suitable for moderate consumption. The ADA recommends choosing fruits that are fresh, frozen, or canned without added sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-mid-vdoai="vdoai_124570023" id="div-vdoai-mid-124570023"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A typical serving of fruit should provide around 15 grams of carbohydrates, which roughly equals two-thirds of a cup of mango. The ADA also notes that fresh fruit tends to be more satisfying than dried varieties, as the portion size of dried fruit is smaller and can lead to excessive intake of sugars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID_INTL_300" data-loc="100" id="div-gpt-ad-858478126-1-124570023" class="country_specAD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="2" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124570023" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="5" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124570023" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-size="[[300, 250], [600, 250], [600, 300]]" data-adsslot="/7176/Economictimes/ET_News/ET_News_ROS/ET_News_ROS_MID1_INTL_300" data-loc="3" id="div-gpt-ad-858478132-1-124570023" class="country_specAD2nd"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Additional Health Perks&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond controlling blood sugar, mangoes may also improve cholesterol levels. A study published in the British Journal of Nutrition in 2011 observed that mice fed a high-fat diet supplemented with freeze-dried mango exhibited lower body fat, reduced cholesterol, and improved glucose levels compared to those treated with lipid- or sugar-lowering drugs like fenofibrate and rosiglitazone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research underscores that incorporating whole fruits like mangoes into one’s diet not only satisfies sweet cravings naturally but also supports metabolic health, making this tropical fruit a surprisingly smart choice for balanced living.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h3&gt;Signs Of High Blood Sugar&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As per a Cleveland Clinic report, early signs of high blood sugar, also known as hyperglycemia, often appear gradually and may include excessive thirst or hunger, frequent urination, headaches, and blurred vision. These symptoms occur as the body struggles to manage rising glucose levels. If left unchecked for a longer period, chronic hyperglycemia can lead to more serious issues such as persistent fatigue, unexplained weight loss, recurring vaginal yeast or skin infections, and slow-healing cuts or sores. Recognizing these warning signals early is crucial, as timely lifestyle changes and medical intervention can help prevent severe complications like nerve damage or diabetes-related disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;meta content="cms.article3" name="cmsei-article3"&gt;&lt;div class="inSideInd"&gt;&lt;div data-ga-action="Preference Banner InArticle Widget" data-ga-impression="Preference Banner InArticle Widget#Impressions | Preference Banner | Articleshow#url" class="Pbanner"&gt;&lt;div class="Pbannertext"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add &lt;/p&gt;&lt;img alt="ET Logo" src="https://img.etimg.com/photo/123467569.cms"&gt;&lt;p&gt; as a Reliable and Trusted News Source&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Economic Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 16:15:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAJBVV95cUxQNkQzYUE3YktFWHNVSHpSYzZrVWtrY083WWthSEhacWprS20wR01OUjc2ZlpVSFRnWUdVbVRhZEpPNER1LWFlWEtRNFVZU3RPR2g2dkJWRi1QNlNDNHpTY3o0MGItYTF6N2pZOEl6UWlDMV8tOWNTaHdjSS1qTF9ZX2cwUXhoaklrQ1NlSkZzQkpwSWVVT1lLNS1adjlrUnpGSTZndzNoM1RqOEdmUndQSU84VkJKQ0JYaTlZVkhpT3dVdnBVd2NUYkwtZmJNbGJFU2F2V1VCdmw5TGxaTHlvNVA3TU01NERjdGpzbm50eVB3VEREM1pnN3pTc2xDMkVm0gGGAkFVX3lxTE1odjBmSW9fMUk2YlJXLWdHM3ZSb2lZY2tMeXh3N01VMk9IMHBJVFYtQUtmWm9xOHpSN2czQUxtTDI0eUh4aVB4Qm5yVVd6bkhCcFJLb0NHWG93Q25LUmdSd3NnQ1k3cUp5MFZTaFZseWlDVGk4YXYyT3VuUmZwcVFmV2ktUEM4aHBtS2pQZmxjTTFuZXhoNE5wRnk2OGRvSVNjTnZ0VUgwMlFIOGxWRjVPYmNieU9HTTBGaTJsOFE5QnhLbm9IZktpSFZkUV9UVWFMR0NaSUw1RnFqOXVEaUU2alJPZlVRVkVPTUc1c2YtNjZmSDRCUG5CemdVTEh2QVBRUnJRWlE</guid></item><item><title>当助听器还不够时--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/18/health/cochlear-implants-older-people.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:29:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNMDZ0U2dXYTN0MXdWanVzT2RGek8wOXYzaDk0TmlqYldvWkZ2NUhmdERxZmNHXzVXSUpOR05WLWhINjEyeU9lN0xWWVVZLVd1N2JIUHZVRUdIQXNYRldrQzdTRkU0YUt2eU9ISFdsYkNNRmNWeW9VazBLRmFMVzhtVFVBMA</guid></item><item><title>意见：世界更年期日将犹他州更年期护理差距置于聚光灯下-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/opinion-world-menopause-day-puts-140000477.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Oct. 18 is designated as World Menopause Day by the &lt;a href="https://www.imsociety.org/education/world-menopause-day-2025/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:International Menopause Society;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;International Menopause Society&lt;/a&gt;. The purpose of the day is to raise awareness of menopause and the support options available for improving health and well-being. So it’s the right moment to examine how the U.S. and Utah perform on menopause care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Fewer than 5% of American women use hormone replacement therapy (HRT), according to &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama-health-forum/fullarticle/2823976" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:JAMA;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;JAMA&lt;/a&gt;, to help manage symptoms they experience during the menopause transition. Compare that with an HRT usage rate closer to 15% in the U.K. and Australia, where prescribing is steadily rising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;American health care practitioners are not well prepared: only &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinicproceedings.org/article/S0025-6196(18)30701-8/abstract" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:6.8%;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;6.8%&lt;/a&gt; of family medicine, internal medicine and obstetrics and gynecology residents reported feeling adequately prepared to manage women experiencing menopause transition symptoms, according to a 2019 Mayo Clinic survey. Six years later, that has undoubtedly risen with the increasing general awareness of menopause, but it’s still shockingly low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Utahns face some additional challenges. The state does fairly well on the ratio of obstetricians and gynecologists (OB-GYNs) to women, ranking &lt;a href="https://www.beckersphysicianleadership.com/physician-workforce/womens-health-providers-by-state-2023/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:18th;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;18th&lt;/a&gt; in the country. However, as a state with one of the highest birth rates, Utah OB-GYNs are busy with maternal care rather than menopause care. While women often think to turn first to their OB-GYNs for help with menopause, they might not be the best equipped. Primary care physicians (PCPs) can provide menopause care, but Utah has one of the &lt;a href="https://www.beckershospitalreview.com/rankings-and-ratings/states-ranked-by-total-primary-care-physicians-in-2024/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:worst ratios of PCPs to residents;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;worst ratios of PCPs to residents&lt;/a&gt; in the entire United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Medication options are also more limited in the U.S. There are no approved testosterone treatments for menopausal women despite the fact that in appropriate dosages, testosterone can increase energy, improve sexual function, and preserve muscle mass and bone health. American doctors only prescribe testosterone to women “off label,” whereas Australia offers a cream approved specifically for postmenopausal women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;The shadow of old data&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So why is the U.S. so different in our approach to menopause care?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Much of the hesitation originates with a Women’s Health Initiative study published in 2002. The data from that study was &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10758198/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:presented in black-and-white terms that overstated risks;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;presented in black-and-white terms that overstated risks&lt;/a&gt;. But those headlines stuck, and two decades later, many women are still paying the price. It takes &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3241518/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:17 years;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;17 years&lt;/a&gt; on average for medical research updates to translate into day-to-day medical practice. This is far too long for women to wait for effective and appropriate menopause care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Despite the need to close the gap between current medical practice and new research, the U.S. still lacks adequate medical training around menopause. Only &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2023-08-survey-menopause-residency.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:31.3%;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;31.3%&lt;/a&gt; of obstetrics and gynecology residency program directors report they have any type of menopause curriculum as part of their residents’ training. For most, this curriculum consists of one to two lectures per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;The human cost of delay&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When menopause symptoms go untreated, the costs are high. Sleep suffers. Cognitive function declines. Emotional well-being takes a hit. Productivity at work drops. And over time, without hormone replacement intervention, health risks can mount — most specifically, increases in osteoporosis, cardiovascular disease and the likelihood of Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So better menopause care isn’t just a women’s health issue. It’s a public health issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Moving forward&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While we don’t know everything about hormones, in large part because of a significant gap in research on women’s health specifically, the overwhelming consensus today is that &lt;a href="https://www.bcrf.org/about-breast-cancer/hrt-breast-cancer-risk/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HRT is both safe for most women;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;HRT is both safe for most women&lt;/a&gt; and the most effective solution to treat menopause-related symptoms. And it should be readily available. This requires better education for health care providers, more specialized and holistic care, and less stigma. It also means giving women space to track their own symptoms, understand what’s changing and decide what “forward” looks like for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;That’s why I founded &lt;a href="http://inflexxionhealth.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Inflexxion Health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Inflexxion Health&lt;/a&gt; — so that together, we can ensure that women in Utah no longer have to wait for the care they deserve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This &lt;a href="https://www.imsociety.org/education/world-menopause-day-2025/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:World Menopause Day;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;World Menopause Day&lt;/a&gt;, awareness must translate into action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOM2NtUWVXUjlobnRmamxSQ1lkZE5LNXZhMExkVmdJa3NUQ3U5LWlpTjVwRzgtSjZOdlJFRFl5NjZNS09GY3h3cVpFUUttN1dVR3dwZV8wcTBsZXk4M3gzNGh0bHhqTElGWjRIUDRiMHJHUnhnbFJoY3FnTEctVXpxQXA4MF9oNHZSUU5j</guid></item><item><title>我们是否生活在一个愚蠢的黄金时代？ -卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2025/oct/18/are-we-living-in-a-golden-age-of-stupidity-technology</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;tep into the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) Media Lab in Cambridge, US, and the future feels a little closer. Glass cabinets display prototypes of weird and wonderful creations, from tiny desktop robots to a surrealist sculpture created by an AI model prompted to design a tea set made from body parts. In the lobby, an AI waste-sorting assistant named Oscar can tell you where to put your used coffee cup. Five floors up, research scientist Nataliya Kosmyna has been working on wearable brain-computer interfaces she hopes will one day enable people who cannot speak, due to neurodegenerative diseases such as amyotrophic lateral sclerosis, to communicate using their minds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Kosmyna spends a lot of her time reading and analysing people’s brain states. Another project she is working on is a wearable device – one prototype looks like a pair of glasses – that can tell when someone is getting confused or losing focus. Around two years ago, she began receiving out-of-the blue emails from strangers who reported that they had started using large language models such as ChatGPT and felt their brain had changed as a result. Their memories didn’t seem as good – was that even possible, they asked her? Kosmyna herself had been struck by how quickly people had already begun to rely on generative AI. She noticed colleagues using ChatGPT at work, and the applications she received from researchers hoping to join her team started to look different. Their emails were longer and more formal and, sometimes, when she interviewed candidates on Zoom, she noticed they kept pausing before responding and looking off to the side – were they getting AI to help them, she wondered, shocked. And if they were using AI, how much did they even understand of the answers they were giving?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;With some MIT colleagues, Kosmyna set up an experiment that used an electroencephalogram to monitor people’s brain activity while they wrote essays, either with no digital assistance, or with the help of an internet search engine, or ChatGPT. She found that the more external help participants had, the lower their level of brain connectivity, so those who used ChatGPT to write showed significantly less activity in the brain networks associated with cognitive processing, attention and creativity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In other words, whatever the people using ChatGPT felt was going on inside their brains, the scans showed there wasn’t much happening up there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The study’s participants, who were all enrolled at MIT or nearby universities, were asked, right after they had handed in their work, if they could recall what they had written. “Barely anyone in the ChatGPT group could give a quote,” Kosmyna says. “That was concerning, because you just wrote it and you do not remember anything.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Kosmyna is 35, trendily dressed in a blue shirt dress and a big, multicoloured necklace, and she speaks faster than most people can think. As she observes, writing an essay requires skills that are important in our wider lives: the ability to synthesise information, consider competing perspectives and construct an argument. You use these skills in everyday conversations. “How are you going to deal with that? Are you going to be, like, ‘Err … can I just check my phone?’” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The experiment was small (54 participants) and has not yet been peer reviewed. In June, however, Kosmyna posted it online, thinking other researchers might find it interesting, and then she went about her day, unaware that she had just created an international media frenzy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Alongside the journalist requests, she received more than 4,000 emails from around the world, many from stressed-out teachers who feel their students aren’t learning properly because they are using ChatGPT to do their homework. They worry AI is creating a generation who can produce passable work but don’t have any usable knowledge or understanding of the material.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The fundamental issue, Kosmyna says, is that as soon as a technology becomes available that makes our lives easier, we’re evolutionarily primed to use it. “Our brains love shortcuts, it’s in our nature. But your brain needs friction to learn. It needs to have a challenge.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If brains need friction but also instinctively avoid it, it’s interesting that the promise of technology has been to create a “frictionless” user experience, to ensure that, provided we slide from app to app or screen to screen, we will meet no resistance. The frictionless user experience is why we unthinkingly offload ever more information and work to our digital devices; it’s why internet rabbit holes are so easy to fall down and so hard to climb out of; it’s why generative AI has already integrated itself so completely into most people’s lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;We know, from our collective experience, that once you become accustomed to the hyperefficient cybersphere, the friction-filled real world feels harder to deal with. So you avoid phone calls, use self-checkouts, order everything from an app; you reach for your phone to do the maths sum you could do in your head, to check a fact before you have to dredge it up from memory, to input your destination on Google maps and travel from A to B on autopilot. Maybe you &lt;a href="https://www.arts.gov/stories/blog/2024/federal-data-reading-pleasure-all-signs-show-slump#:~:text=Last%20fall,%20the%20NEA%20reported,54.6%20percent%20ten%20years%20earlier." data-link-name="in body link"&gt;stop reading books&lt;/a&gt; because maintaining that kind of focus feels like friction; maybe you dream of owning a self-driving car. Is this the dawn of what the writer and education expert Daisy Christodoulou calls a “&lt;a href="https://substack.nomoremarking.com/p/are-we-living-in-a-stupidogenic-society" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;stupidogenic society&lt;/a&gt;”, a parallel to an &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/may/20/young-people-obesity-2030-report" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;obesogenic society&lt;/a&gt;, in which it is easy to become stupid because machines can think for you?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;AI companies are determined to push their products on to the public before we fully understand the psychological and cognitive costs&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Human intelligence is too broad and varied to be reduced to words such as “stupid”, but there are worrying signs that all this digital convenience is costing us dearly. Across the economically developed countries of the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD), Pisa scores, which measure 15-year-olds’ reading, maths and science, &lt;a href="https://archive.ph/0S5wK#selection-3313.60-3313.87" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;tended to peak around 2012&lt;/a&gt;. While over the 20th century IQ scores increased globally, perhaps due to improved access to education and better nutrition, in many developed countries they appear to have been declining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Falling test and IQ scores are the subject of hot debate. What is harder to dispute is that, with every technological advance, we deepen our dependence on digital devices and find it harder to work or remember or think or, frankly, function without them. “It’s only software developers and drug dealers who call people users,” Kosmyna mutters at one point, frustrated at AI companies’ determination to push their products on to the public before we fully understand the psychological and cognitive costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the ever-expanding, frictionless online world, you are first and foremost a user: passive, dependent. In the dawning era of AI-generated misinformation and deepfakes, how will we maintain the scepticism and intellectual independence we’ll need? By the time we agree that our minds are no longer our own, that we simply cannot think clearly without tech assistance, how much of us will be left to resist?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;tart telling people that you’re worried about what intelligent machines are doing to our brains and there’s a risk that, in the not-too-distant future, everyone will laugh at what a fuddy-duddy you were. Socrates worried that writing would weaken people’s memories and encourage only superficial understanding: not wisdom but “the conceit of wisdom” – an argument that is strikingly similar to many critiques of AI. What happened instead was that writing and the technological advances that followed – the printing press, mass media, the internet era – meant that ever more people had access to ever more information. More people could develop great ideas, and they could share those ideas more easily, and this made us cleverer and more innovative, as individuals and as communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After all, writing didn’t only change how we access and retain information; it changed how we think. A person can achieve more complex tasks with a notebook and paper to hand than without: most people can’t work out 53,683 divided by 7 in their head but could have a stab at doing long division on paper. I couldn’t have dictated this piece, but writing helped me organise and clarify my thoughts. As humans, we’re very good at what experts call “cognitive offloading”, namely using our physical environment to reduce our mental load, and this in turn helps us achieve more complex cognitive tasks. Imagine how much harder it would be to function each day without a calendar or phone reminders, or without Google to remember everything for you. In the best case scenario, intelligent people working in partnership with intelligent machines will achieve new intellectual feats and solve tricky problems: we’re already seeing, for instance, how AI can help scientists discover &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-024-03434-4" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;new drugs faster&lt;/a&gt; and doctors detect &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/research/infrastructure/artificial-intelligence" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;cancer earlier and more efficiently&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The complication is, if technology is truly making us cleverer – turning us into efficient, information-processing machines – why do we spend so much time feeling dumb?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Last year, “brain rot” was named Oxford University Press’s word of the year, a term that captures both the specific feeling of mindlessness that descends when we spend too much time scrolling through rubbish online and the corrosive, aggressively dumb content itself, the nonsense memes and AI garble. When we hold our phones we have, in theory, most of the world’s accumulated knowledge at our fingertips, so why do we spend so much time dragging our eyeballs over dreck?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;One issue is that our digital devices have not been designed to help us think more efficiently and clearly; almost everything we encounter online has been designed to capture and monetise our attention. Each time you reach for your phone with the intention of completing a simple, discrete, potentially self-improving task, such as checking the news, your primitive hunter-gatherer brain confronts a multibillion-pound tech industry devoted to throwing you off course and holding your attention, no matter what. To extend Christodoulou ’s metaphor, in the same way that one feature of an obesogenic society are food deserts – whole neighbourhoods in which you cannot buy a healthy meal – large parts of the internet are information deserts, in which the only available brain food is junk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Digital multitasking gives you a false sense of being on top of things without ever getting to the bottom of anything&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the late 90s the tech consultant Linda Stone, who was working as a professor at New York University, noticed that her students were using technology very differently from her colleagues at Microsoft, where she also worked. While her Microsoft colleagues were disciplined about working on two screens – one for emails, perhaps, and another for Word, or a spreadsheet – her students seemed to be trying to do 20 things at once. She coined the term “continuous partial attention” to describe the stressful, involuntarily state we often find ourselves in when we’re trying to toggle between several cognitively demanding activities, such as responding to emails while on a Zoom call. When I first heard the term I realised that I, like most people I know, live most of my life in a state of continuous partial attention, whether I’m guiltily checking my phone when I’m supposed to be playing with my kids, or incessantly sidetracked by texts and emails when I’m trying to write, or trying to relax while watching Netflix and simultaneously doing an online food shop, still wondering why I feel as chilled-out as an over-microwaved dinner. Digital multitasking makes us feel productive, but this is often illusory. “You have a false sense of being on top of things without ever getting to the bottom of anything,” Stone tells me. It also makes you feel permanently on edge: one study she conducted found that 80% of people experience “screen apnea” when checking their emails: they become so caught up in the endless notifications that they forget to breathe properly. “Your fight or flight system becomes up-regulated, because you’re constantly trying to stay on top of things,” she says, and this hypervigilance has cognitive costs: it makes us more forgetful, worse at making decisions and less attentive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="#EmailSignup-skip-link-23" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;skip past newsletter promotion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;aside aria-label="newsletter promotion" class="dcr-av5vqf"&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-10et71f"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-1sbse14"&gt;Sign up to &lt;span&gt;Inside Saturday&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-1xjndtj"&gt;The only way to get a look behind the scenes of the Saturday magazine. Sign up to get the inside story from our top writers as well as all the must-read articles and columns, delivered to your inbox every weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SecureSignup" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"newsletterId":"inside-saturday","successDescription":"The only way to get a look behind the scenes of the Saturday magazine. Sign up to get the inside story from our top writers as well as all the must-read articles and columns, delivered to your inbox every weekend."}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1eusqlu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Notice: &lt;/strong&gt;Newsletters may contain information about charities, online ads, and content funded by outside parties. If you do not have an account, we will create a guest account for you on &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;theguardian.com&lt;/a&gt; to send you this newsletter. You can complete full registration at any time. For more information about how we use your data see our &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com/help/privacy-policy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. We use Google reCaptcha to protect our website and the Google &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/privacy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/terms" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt; apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p id="EmailSignup-skip-link-23" tabindex="0" aria-label="after newsletter promotion" role="note" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;after newsletter promotion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="5997b8a7-9bff-443f-9fc0-3a2b91779d13" data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.ImageBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;figcaption data-spacefinder-role="inline" class="dcr-fd61eq"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1inf02i"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 18 13"&gt;&lt;path d="M18 3.5v8l-1.5 1.5h-15l-1.5-1.5v-8l1.5-1.5h3.5l2-2h4l2 2h3.5l1.5 1.5zm-9 7.5c1.9 0 3.5-1.6 3.5-3.5s-1.6-3.5-3.5-3.5-3.5 1.6-3.5 3.5 1.6 3.5 3.5 3.5z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Illustration: Justin Metz/The Guardian&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Continuous partial attention helps explain both brain rot as a mental state – because what is it if not cognitive overwhelm, the point at which you stop resisting the onslaught of digital distraction and allow your brain to rest in the internet’s warm, murky shallows? – and the existence of the online slop itself. After all, what matters to tech companies financially is not that you want to be reading what you’re reading, or that you love what you listen to or what you’re looking at, only that you are unwilling or unable to pull yourself away. This is why streaming services such as Netflix crank out bland, formulaic films that are euphemistically labelled “casual viewing” and are literally designed for viewers &lt;a href="https://www.nplusonemag.com/issue-49/essays/casual-viewing/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;who aren’t really watching&lt;/a&gt;, and Spotify playlists are filled with &lt;a href="https://harpers.org/archive/2025/01/the-ghosts-in-the-machine-liz-pelly-spotify-musicians/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;generic stock music&lt;/a&gt; by fake artists, to provide background music, “Chill Out” or “Party” vibes, for listeners who aren’t really listening. In short, the modern internet doesn’t necessarily make you an idiot, but it definitely primes you to act like one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;t is into this climate that generative AI arrived, with an entirely novel offer. Until recently you could only outsource remembering and some data processing to technology; now you can outsource thinking itself. Given that we spend most of our lives feeling overstimulated and frazzled, it’s little wonder that so many have jumped at the chance to let a computer do more things we would have once done for ourselves– such as write work reports or emails, or plan a holiday. As we transition from the internet era to the AI era, what we’re consuming is not only ever more low-value, ultra-processed information, but more information that is essentially predigested, delivered in a way that is designed to bypass important human functions, such as assessing, filtering and summarising information, or actually considering a problem rather than finessing the first solution presented to us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Michael Gerlich, head of the Centre for Strategic Corporate Foresight and Sustainability at SBS Swiss Business School, began studying the impact of generative AI on critical thinking because he noticed the quality of classroom discussions decline. Sometimes he’d set his students a group exercise, and rather than talk to one another they continued to sit in silence, consulting their laptops. He spoke to other lecturers, who had noticed something similar. Gerlich recently conducted a study, involving 666 people of various ages, and found those who used AI more frequently &lt;a href="https://download.ssrn.com/2025/1/4/5082524.pdf?response-content-disposition=inline&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Security-Token=IQoJb3JpZ2luX2VjEKT%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2F%2FwEaCXVzLWVhc3QtMSJIMEYCIQCmRbALQalkGRB3jehFvi8nWZYpU%2BYsnAEPxO%2BoBB3wfQIhANrBGQfOPSK1dN8whuYILYNDsxhGw%2Bwlhc2H60tAdzgIKr0FCB0QBBoMMzA4NDc1MzAxMjU3IgzIZwV6noZaCGBCVVgqmgX8DsiB0tO6Adb6CtCDPG%2BnQuA6DxEy0Z2ot1NJ2g2bvGSRRq45nuWOo55d55Pz5bq%2F2M5wU2wtGpw5wlb6CD9YvJ5RgiQGq3YyIkesQhcbzGWlfVuSdjgcbsDcWtTaLR1%2FCalN8Qv2qhaW%2FrHHuHpjQyYMVXjtb2IPyLmswLY2CPhkWGTiqPlpkCubG2OmeQkyPABjnsk4wPNsu1YQF8bRjglekBXqg3n6osewqzYFUTnkMjtzN%2Ff4LnScCLPqmUZujjlUMxR3lwy8TfqsgVGYJ7hnrrOJ4TSmwp%2FlUXMADWyKGsTl6M1m%2Fjjk725o2M7FQF1QVC%2BWdr4cbvYt07ZydSFlMsGOAD8BoK98ngz7AZx92KjzmEqXkNewaMMlLeKCxUj63VkBBBBbCqPm3HnjU9IX1DQccbCyyT1oBWJXx6fE%2FZHR87Ch3W37DlLrvpoATKzuFIcj6uVsw1y4SS3C9sbdadKKuIQmJq5UpJI%2FL8n%2Fhl2wEPI8INq%2BIF0AMJzea5sajvfxqKEwTpcCI%2BB1eBLhq7%2FcCcTOFTgKG2xCHSgQw0yyYvUYKiOg4WLpSLzTP%2B%2B2QYaSAo3DQ69YfTW4E%2Fyfub5uv%2BimLRlJY3GtSJI4%2F%2B202Poiky3aW8nRQcLqoCWs7dtmnQeAr6vGsV2LEd2uwdRQYXve7A7%2B1WtkcCrskewpY30QvFeJzVH4OXJXtdxDPWUzblSI8g4FeWb8fgWqyEwLwh6miJ1jWclzK2rsA8a5jr5i4noPlcyqDEMFy49K709tHkYqUxT8SQt1ksox35sTMMqGs8ANPHU8WvnLZ2tsPGwR15V98q9XG6X7U6f9zki0jOUys0%2BGUQ4TPKCBlMC%2BeQ0n6VmMvvPHUQRj5dJJLfeo4M4w3dOMxgY6sAEBzWuQ5bMH%2FMBg3a1NXRNmFhsyMCvI%2FoOPTxuCMwut7ECx2YbOwEm1S4gm2wJnBcCP8Qd31iHo5fUdO4dC%2BbB8jPxyh%2Fb5fpLJgHhiWmgZurM4ql8KNWP2jH9NLdxv%2BZi9x8MfXGMnTTYL43ceUvMzKQY8J%2FvxFvIAi2kT0CLsJUl%2FkPk723vqh%2FWIZrVfOn0A%2FBLIta2wTijg3itrnZYER8X%2BBSrcMHw8cAtHblhuxA%3D%3D&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Date=20250911T204332Z&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Expires=300&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Credential=ASIAUPUUPRWEWUPPMNLX%2F20250911%2Fus-east-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&amp;amp;amp;X-Amz-Signature=dda7f43bea1f7f00507c51a611aa025ba9386abe173968804683fc1892469502&amp;amp;amp;abstractId=5082524" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;scored lower on critical thinking&lt;/a&gt;. (As he notes, to date his work only provides evidence for a correlation between the two: it’s possible that people with lower critical thinking abilities are more likely to trust AI, for example.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;Are schools equipped to produce creative thinkers – or is the education system going to churn out mindless, AI-essay writing drones?&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Like many researchers, Gerlich believes that, used in the right way, AI can make us cleverer and more creative – but the way most people use it produces bland, unimaginative, factually questionable work. One concern is the so-called “anchoring effect”. If you post a question to generative AI, the answer it gives you sets your brain on a certain mental path and makes you less likely to consider alternative approaches. “I always use the example: imagine a candle. Now, AI can help you improve the candle. It will be the brightest ever, burn the longest, be very cheap and amazing looking, but it will never develop to the lightbulb,” he says. To get from the candle to a lightbulb you need a human who is good at critical thinking, someone who might take a chaotic, unstructured, unpredictable approach to problem solving. When, as has happened in many workplaces, companies roll out tools such as the chatbot Copilot without offering decent AI training, they risk producing teams of passable candle-makers in a world that demands high-efficiency lightbulbs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is also the bigger issue that adults who use AI as a shortcut have at least benefited from going through the education system in the years before it was possible to get a computer to write your homework for you. One &lt;a href="https://www.hepi.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/HEPI-Kortext-Student-Generative-AI-Survey-2025.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recent British survey&lt;/a&gt; found that &lt;a href="https://www.hepi.ac.uk/wp-content/uploads/2025/02/HEPI-Kortext-Student-Generative-AI-Survey-2025.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;92% of university students&lt;/a&gt; use AI, and about 20% have used AI to write all or part of an assignment for them. Under these circumstances, how much are they learning? Are schools and universities still equipped to produce creative, original thinkers who will build better, more intelligent societies – or is the education system going to churn out mindless, gullible, AI essay-writing drones?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="dcr-z9ge1j"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;ome years ago, Matt Miles, a psychology teacher at a high school in Virginia in the US, was sent on a training programme on tech in schools. The teachers were shown a video in which a schoolgirl is caught checking her phone during lessons. In the video, she looks up and says, “You think I’m just on TikTok or playing games. I’m actually in a research room talking to a water researcher from Botswana for a project.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s laughable. You show it to the kids and they all laugh, right?” Miles says. Alarmed at the disconnect between how policymakers view tech in education and what teachers were seeing in the classroom, in 2017 Miles and his colleague Joe Clement, who teaches economics and government at the same school, published &lt;a href="https://screenschooled.com/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Screen Schooled&lt;/a&gt;, a book that argued that technology overuse is making kids dumber. In the years since, smartphones have been banned from their classrooms, but students still work from their laptops. “We had one kid tell us, and I think it was pretty insightful, ‘If you see me on my phone, there’s a 0% chance I’m doing something productive. If you see me on my laptop, there’s a 50% chance,’” Miles says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-gu-name="pullquote" class="dcr-nyoej5"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 22 14" class="dcr-scql1j"&gt;&lt;path d="M5.255 0h4.75c-.572 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941H0C.792 9.104 2.44 4.53 5.255 0Zm11.061 0H21c-.506 4.53-1.077 8.972-1.297 13.941h-8.686c.902-4.837 2.485-9.411 5.3-13.941Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;blockquote class="dcr-zzndwp"&gt;In essence what is happening with these technologies is we’re experimenting on children&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Until the pandemic, many teachers were “rightly sceptical” about the benefits of introducing more technology into the classroom, Faith Boninger, a researcher at the University of Colorado, observes, but when lockdowns forced schools to go online, a new normal was created, and ed tech platforms such as Google Workspace for Education, Kahoot! and Zearn became ubiquitous. With the spread of generative AI came new promises that it could revolutionise education and usher in an era of personalised student learning, while also reducing the workload for teachers. But almost all the research that has found benefits to introducing tech in classrooms is funded by the ed-tech industry, and most large-scale independent research has found that screen time gets in the way of achievement. A global OECD study found, for instance, that the more students use tech in schools, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/business-34174796" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the worse their results&lt;/a&gt;. “There is simply no independent evidence at scale for the effectiveness of these tools … in essence what is happening with these technologies is we’re experimenting on children,” says Wayne Holmes, a professor of critical studies of artificial intelligence and education at University College London. “Most sensible people would not go into a bar and meet somebody who says, ‘Hey, I’ve got this new drug. It’s really good for you’ – and just use it. Generally, we expect our medicines to be rigorously tested, we expect them to be prescribed to us by professionals. But suddenly when we’re talking about ed tech, which apparently is very beneficial for children’s developing brains, we don’t need to do that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;What worries Miles and Clement is not only that their students are permanently distracted by their devices, but that they will not develop critical thinking skills and deep knowledge when quick answers are only a click away. Where once Clement would ask his class a question such as, “Where do you think the US ranks in terms of GDP per capita?” and guide his students as they puzzled over the solution, now someone will have Googled the answer before he’s even finished his question. They know students use ChatGPT constantly and get annoyed if they aren’t provided with a digital copy of their assignment, because then they must type rather than copy and paste the relevant questions into an AI assistant or the Google search bar. “Being able to Google something and providing the right answer isn’t knowledge,” Clement says. “And having knowledge is incredibly important so that when you hear something that’s questionable or maybe fake, you think, ‘Wait a minute, that contradicts all the knowledge I have that says otherwise, right?’ It’s no wonder there’s a bunch of idiots walking about who think that the Earth is flat. Like, if you read a flat Earth blog, you think, ‘Ah, that makes a lot of sense’ because you don’t have any understanding or knowledge.” The internet is already awash with conspiracy and misinformation, something that will only become worse as AI hallucinates and produces plausible fakes, and he worries that young people are poorly equipped to navigate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;During the pandemic, Miles says, he found his young son weeping over his school-issued tablet. His son was doing an online maths program and he had been tasked with making six using the fewest number of one, three and five tokens. He kept suggesting using two threes, and the computer kept telling him he was wrong. Miles tried one and five, which the computer accepted. “That’s kind of the nightmare you get with a non-human AI, right?” Miles observes: students often approach topics in unanticipated and interesting ways, but machines struggle to cope with idiosyncrasy. Listening to his story, however, I was struck by a different kind of nightmare. Maybe the dawn of the new golden era of stupidity doesn’t begin when we submit to super-intelligent machines; it starts when we hand over power to dumb ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 13:21:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOaTlPNEh0NjJmNGVtcDUyWEJhbVZSazk1MGpMbXpFc25PTl9vZ1VBdk11a09yRnlyZXMxTEYyMmtWM1hhNEpseDRvcFNHbk5Za2lFdWh3emZyLVl4dm1rNTg5cjBJcElRMEZCaU12ZUJOQWdtcFdKWXlsakthNkJRa3E5cWpKbENXaTI0R2hpNUpTcXROTHZIb09UWlBtb1plUUtJaVVFYw</guid></item><item><title>男性大脑比女性大脑收缩得更快，研究结果- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/male-brains-shrink-faster-than-female-brains-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;New evidence has found that male brains really may shrink faster than female brains with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among 4,726 participants with healthy cognition, brain scans have revealed "modest yet systematic sex differences" in how neurological tissue wastes away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The human brain &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/archneur.60.7.989"&gt;naturally shrinks&lt;/a&gt; as we get older, and those who die with  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="177626" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease have brains that &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/alzheimers-causes-and-risk-factors/what-happens-brain-alzheimers-disease"&gt;show drastic volume losses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women are diagnosed with Alzheimer's at &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41591-025-03564-3"&gt;twice the rate of men&lt;/a&gt;, but surprisingly little is known about how a person's sex impacts their brain volume as they age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it turns out, the female brain may actually lose &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grey_matter"&gt;gray&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/White_matter"&gt;white matter&lt;/a&gt; at a slower rate than the male brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/men-and-women-may-respond-differently-to-latest-alzheimers-drugs"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Men And Women May Respond Differently to Latest Alzheimer's Drugs&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If women's brains declined more, that could have helped explain their higher Alzheimer's prevalence," co-author Anne Ravndal, a neuroscientist at the University of Oslo in Norway, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03353-5"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;Nature&lt;/em&gt; journalist Rachel Fieldhous&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ravndal and an international team of researchers pulled together more than 12,000 brain scans, collected over the years from participants aged 17 to 95. Each individual had at least two brain MRIs, with an average interval of about 3 years between them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After controlling for sex-based differences in brain size, the team found that men showed a decline in a greater number of brain regions, including many parts of the cortex, in older age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, women showed a decline in fewer regions, and the thickness of their cortex was less altered with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest that there are real sex differences in the biology of aging, but the results should be interpreted with caution, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2510486122"&gt;the authors note&lt;/a&gt;, as far more research is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177643" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177643" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-642x495.png" alt="Age Differences Between Sexes" class="size-medium wp-image-177643" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-642x495.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-875x675.png 875w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-768x593.png 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-1536x1185.png 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging-600x463.png 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/SexDifferencesAging.png 1542w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177643" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Differences between male and female participants in the study. (Ravndal et al., &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2510486122"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;PNAS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite extensive investigation into the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/biomedgerontology/article/77/11/2177/6529714"&gt;biology of the aging brain&lt;/a&gt;, there remains an &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/grave-consequences-scientists-warn-of-extreme-bias-in-brain-aging-research"&gt;&lt;span&gt;extreme sex bias&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in the field. &lt;span&gt;In 2019, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-022-29903-3"&gt;only 5 percent&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; of published studies in neuroscience or psychiatry considered the influence of sex.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neurobiolaging.2021.06.002"&gt;Inconsistent findings abound&lt;/a&gt;. Today, it remains unclear whether men and women differ in the extent or speed of brain decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some studies show steeper declines in gray and white matter &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neurobiolaging.2019.05.020"&gt;among men&lt;/a&gt;, while others show steeper declines &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0114478"&gt;among women&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new research, led by researchers at the University of Oslo in Norway, sought to clear up the picture. Between the sexes, researchers found sex-based differences in total brain volume, subcortical brain volume, cortical thickness, and surface area, among dozens of other measurements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What these losses mean for cognitive function requires further research. Scientists are only just starting to understand how brain shape is &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-signal-of-future-dementia-may-be-hidden-in-the-shape-of-your-brain"&gt;linked to disease&lt;/a&gt;, and some studies &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-new-alzheimers-drug-shrinks-the-brain-scientists-say-thats-the-point"&gt;suggest that shrinkage&lt;/a&gt; can sometimes be helpful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The location of volume loss can certainly give important clues. &lt;span&gt;Surprisingly, Ravndal and colleagues found no difference in volume changes to the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hippocampus"&gt;hippocampus &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;– a neural hub for memory and learning closely involved in dementia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Only in older age did women in the study begin to show a faster decline in the hippocampus, once their relative life expectancy was taken into account. But this may simply be a delay in aging: a product of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/it-s-not-just-humans-females-outlive-males-in-other-mammals-too"&gt;women living longer&lt;/a&gt; than men and not necessarily a sign that explains their dementia risk. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the authors compared men and women who were predicted to live the same amount, some of the brain decline between the sexes balanced out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_launch"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Launch" class="alignnone wp-image-177073 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teasing apart the impact of sex on the brain from other genetic and environmental forces is tricky business, made all the more challenging by a lack of longitudinal research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A 2023 review argued that the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/grave-consequences-scientists-warn-of-extreme-bias-in-brain-aging-research"&gt;continued scientific bias&lt;/a&gt; in brain aging studies has "grave consequences" for wellbeing and places a "disproportionate burden" on female health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research on the aging female brain is long overdue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The study was published in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2510486122"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;PNAS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:01:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQcGZVMThQbDJ3MndZbC1OOGF1a3pjTjlNdjItc0pabjRoUzE3RFN6OHRMbkFjWGJQSFVnVmJSQ3hPUlNBYlVYTEFMQnpHMVdPT3J5LXJBOFJ0VFBRNl85UlExZllKRW9hZHR6enZKMVNGWkpnQkE2V1YzNm1ZcTNwUldORm9fVllYVFBOdXBR</guid></item><item><title>27岁的女性在几乎无视警告标志后被诊断出患有乳腺癌： “难以置信” - CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-young-diagnosis-awareness-mammogram-cleveland-clinic-nyu-langone/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Marissa Coreno was embracing a new life in 2021. She had just moved out of her parents' house and was spending more time in the gym. She liked her job at a hospital in Ohio. Everything seemed to be going great — until she found a lump in her armpit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coreno wasn't particularly concerned at first. She was 27 and had no family history of cancer. But her colleagues thought she shouldn't ignore it. An ultrasound found "questionable characteristics." That was followed by a &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/mammograms-breast-cancer-screening-questions-experts/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;mammogram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, then a biopsy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three days later, Coreno was diagnosed with Stage II breast cancer that had spread to her lymph nodes. She said she felt like her world had been turned upside down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was devastating. It took a while to process. I knew it was positive, and I knew I had breast cancer but in my head, it was like 'No way,'" Coreno said. "You hear about these cases and you see them on TV but it was hard to believe that this was now my life." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/e80eb04b-f0bb-470d-8914-830308f6c4d0/thumbnail/620x1083/1e10ef47ea5bd67855064539af41fbb5/img-3258-1.jpg#" alt="img-3258-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/e80eb04b-f0bb-470d-8914-830308f6c4d0/thumbnail/620x1083/1e10ef47ea5bd67855064539af41fbb5/img-3258-1.jpg 1x, https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/e80eb04b-f0bb-470d-8914-830308f6c4d0/thumbnail/1240x2166/fc8e571500e321be0ca889608d7cb97b/img-3258-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa Coreno.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Marissa Coreno

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;An increase in young diagnoses &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breast cancer is the leading cause of cancer death in U.S. women aged 20 to 49, and the incidence rate of &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/elissa-kalver-her2-positive-metastatic-breast-cancer-memorial-sloan-kettering-ucla/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;breast cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in women under 50 has risen faster than in women over 50, &lt;a href="https://www.bcrf.org/about-breast-cancer/breast-cancer-young-women/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Breast Cancer Research Foundation&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I've been a physician for over 25 years. When I first started practicing, we saw women in their 40s and now we're seeing the late 20s and early 30s more commonly," said Dr. Mary Gemignani, the director of the Women's Early Onset Cancer Program and chief of the Division of Breast Surgery at NYU Langone, who was not involved in Coreno's care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, breast cancer diagnoses in women as young as Coreno are rare. The &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/content/dam/cancer-org/research/cancer-facts-and-statistics/breast-cancer-facts-and-figures/2024/breast-cancer-facts-and-figures-2024.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt; estimates that only about 1 in 1,344 women will develop breast cancer in their 20s. Younger patients are unlikely to have &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/doctor-explains-why-mammograms-should-start-at-age-40/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;regular screenings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, Gemignani said, since most women &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-awareness-month-early-screening-diagnosis-northwestern-university/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;do not receive mammograms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; until they are 40. Younger women also tend to have "more aggressive" tumors or be diagnosed with rarer disease subtypes, Gemignani said. There is no &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/breast-cancer-increase-reasons/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;proven reason&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for the increase, she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gemignani said younger women tend to have unique needs, including fertility concerns, which make it important for them and their doctors to develop a personalized &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/olivia-munn-breast-cancer-story-test-inside-edition-correspondent-alison-hall/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;treatment plan&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Coreno said she found few research studies that looked at outcomes for her age group but spoke candidly with Dr. Baidehi Maiti, a medical oncologist at the Cleveland Clinic, about her best options. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Being so young and not having a lot of research or studies or proof out there, every option I had along the way, I chose the most," Coreno said. "I was very protective." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Connection amid "exhausting" chemotherapy &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coreno's treatment started with four months of "exhausting" chemotherapy to stop her cancer from spreading any further. Her mom moved in to help take care of her, while her dad drove her to every appointment. Coreno said she lost her hair and could barely leave the house. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Going from such an active life — I was in my prime, I was working out on the regular, I was so proud of what I had accomplished — to not even having enough energy to get off the couch was hard," Coreno said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/6c02dcc8-578c-419d-a183-10ae09cd5fce/thumbnail/620x827/ef2da15e6d32eca1dcda715bc6ae4bd0/img-7118-original-1.jpg#" alt="img-7118-original-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/6c02dcc8-578c-419d-a183-10ae09cd5fce/thumbnail/620x827/ef2da15e6d32eca1dcda715bc6ae4bd0/img-7118-original-1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/6c02dcc8-578c-419d-a183-10ae09cd5fce/thumbnail/1240x1654/31fe0a9641c11cfb7ff0c9fea8e1bf18/img-7118-original-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa Coreno in the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Marissa Coreno

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was one bright spot: One night, Coreno decided to "eat (her) feelings" and ordered Crumbl cookies. She posted a picture of the delivery on Instagram. She received a message about the sweet treat from Anthony, a former classmate. The two struck up a conversation and "just never stopped talking." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It was so nice to talk to somebody, have somebody listen to me, have a new friend that I could confide in," Coreno said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, the two went on a date. Coreno dreaded leaving the house and was self-conscious about wearing a wig but enjoyed herself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He didn't even mention the wig. We just had a great time," Coreno said. "It just felt so natural." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/81029970-bc2d-47dd-979d-8ff56533ca82/thumbnail/620x1091/17885e8123520e4ed4a66eee032b2fcf/img-7993-original-1.jpg#" alt="img-7993-original-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/81029970-bc2d-47dd-979d-8ff56533ca82/thumbnail/620x1091/17885e8123520e4ed4a66eee032b2fcf/img-7993-original-1.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/81029970-bc2d-47dd-979d-8ff56533ca82/thumbnail/1240x2182/d20a17e220b7e223a015b54190b6d0d7/img-7993-original-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa Coreno in the hospital.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Marissa Coreno

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After chemotherapy, Coreno underwent a &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/olivia-munn-breast-cancer-diagnosed/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;double mastectomy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, followed by a reconstruction surgery and 25 days of radiation therapy, Maiti said. Coreno started hormone therapy in March 2022 and will continue it until 2032. She also has regular scans. The treatment stops her body from creating estrogen to limit the chance of the cancer returning. Coreno is currently cancer-free, Maiti said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"She has not let cancer define her life," Maiti said. "She's thriving as a breast cancer survivor and living her life to the fullest." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"Life is beautiful" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hormone therapy sent Coreno into menopause at 28. Working out is harder now, she said, and she grapples with hot flashes and has trouble sleeping. It has taken years for her to get used to the new normal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I thought this would be the easy part," Coreno, now 31, said. "After treatment was over is when what I went through hit me the most." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the difficult adjustment, her relationship with Anthony turned more serious. They were married in August 2024 and spent their honeymoon in Italy. Over the summer, they celebrated their anniversary in Cancún, Mexico. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/9f2509a7-36d8-43fa-8400-40bc443f912c/thumbnail/620x930/1f9d7fe7bb145ef1422456b8630af7bb/coreno1517-original-1.jpg#" alt="coreno1517-original-1.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/9f2509a7-36d8-43fa-8400-40bc443f912c/thumbnail/620x930/1f9d7fe7bb145ef1422456b8630af7bb/coreno1517-original-1.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/10/15/9f2509a7-36d8-43fa-8400-40bc443f912c/thumbnail/1240x1860/0b4c7ac0649ac996d953bda3a74cbb91/coreno1517-original-1.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Marissa and Anthony Coreno on their wedding day. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Arlee Reust/Azkalynn Photography

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Coreno also hopes that sharing her story encourages others to investigate any warning signs they experience. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I just want everyone to realize that it seems like it will never be you, it seems like it's always going to be someone else, it seems like it's going to be a person on the TV, but it can happen to you," Coreno said. "If you feel uncertain about anything, you need to speak up and get checked out. If, for some reason, you don't get the best news, there is light at the end of the tunnel. It might not seem like it. It might seem like it's a very long tunnel. But life is beautiful afterwards." &lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/section&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxNMEtPM1lxU2Y4bHE0VmtLc2RtMXlkZ3JNVjlKVXJiRlRscjB6eTNxNW9JZm5fdFBwZUJGZmFlaE16aVFpUDI5MjdJU2o4UVhLbERhVmp6ampzNkNjbkJ3RVFBcU5vbE9sRE5WVktKQWtBUTJHRmdyQ2VRVXZKUXIyVDdsdkdRWk9EcFp3R1NLa3I1MGJtTHNQQ00tdktLWllDRzBtWUFjUkxNU1Nn0gGyAUFVX3lxTFBhaVlLMDFpLVQtbGJpaHM2bHVocmFnQkhxcHBlWXBYUGVSdjlfSG9Sbi03UE1FNDNGRlpnSV95R1hpaU5CbjJjN21oVXhmSzdxeHRDeW16ck5MREhTZ2J2UXRCUTM4S2xsNzd4clNGWFVFTnNnV2FqWFhIdWc1emRoZDZCRDc2d2VhWXJSdDhfb21kZTA1ZE1SQU1mMGIwZWZTYkFRQzFsS19CVGg0dnBPRGc</guid></item><item><title>强壮、稳定脚踝的9项运动-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/18/well/move/ankle-mobility-exercises.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 09:00:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFBCby1WZDBZSjk0c1l2bTYwaWFmaE1udjJfOHF0ei1ZX09VZzZRbGU4NlZXcEdYejBGSnpic243Y3FMZ2Z5dU95dDEwRHpiRnBNbFZaQnhseTBBTzJZN0tuSF8zYWR1b2Y5X2tzSDVheXZfUjJwN2dJby1NY1hyVzg</guid></item><item><title>“我以为我疯了，但那是更年期” - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c6208d6mr71o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;'I thought I was losing my mind - so I quit my job'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Lynette Horsburgh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;North West&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/21fc/live/22c9c760-a829-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/21fc/live/22c9c760-a829-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/21fc/live/22c9c760-a829-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/21fc/live/22c9c760-a829-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/21fc/live/22c9c760-a829-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/21fc/live/22c9c760-a829-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/21fc/live/22c9c760-a829-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/21fc/live/22c9c760-a829-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Leonie Painter Leonie Painter sitting in a stationary car wearing a seat belt. She has auburn hair and is wearing sunglasses on her head and a grey sleeveless top. She is smiling." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Leonie Painter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;The menopause hub set up by Leonie Painter is described as a "lifeline" by women who go there&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A woman has described how she quit her job after she thought she was "losing her mind" while she was suffering loneliness, anxiety and confusion which turned out to be symptoms of menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Leonie Painter from Moston in Manchester said she did not know why she felt that way and did not think she could talk to others about it when the symptoms began to develop after the Covid pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The 50-year-old said: "It was only after learning what was causing it that I began to feel better, but it's taken a long time to get to this point."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Following her experience, she started a group for women going through menopause that has come to be described as a "lifeline" by those who attend. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The sessions started in September 2024 at the Harpurhey Neighbourhood Centre, and were originally set up as a 12-session menopause group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Painter said the aim was to break the stigma around menopause by giving women a space to talk and discuss subjects such as "brain fog" with others who understand, to increase their knowledge of perimenopause and menopause, and bust myths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It has proved so successful it is now a weekly community group funded by the Winning Hearts and Minds initiative under Manchester City Council and Jigsaw Housing which provides targeted community-based funding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Painter said her experiences meant she knew how important it was to break the stigma around menopause and empower women by giving them a safe space to talk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She said the hub's message was "menopause doesn't mean your life is ending, it's a new chapter".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/be73/live/72459160-a82a-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/be73/live/72459160-a82a-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/be73/live/72459160-a82a-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/be73/live/72459160-a82a-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/be73/live/72459160-a82a-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/be73/live/72459160-a82a-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/be73/live/72459160-a82a-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/be73/live/72459160-a82a-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="North Manchester menopause hub A group of 12 women at the Menopause Hub holding up certificates after completing menopause champion training. They are all smiling." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;North Manchester menopause hub&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;A number of women have qualified as menopause champions in the group and can now help others navigate the menopause&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Liza Davies, from Collyhurst, Manchester, said the hub has been a "lifeline" for her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She suffered the most challenging period of her life from September 2024, and said she felt like taking her own life "most days" as well as being "agitated and angry but could not understand why". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The 46-year-old said: "I was overwhelmed, confused, and felt like I was losing my mind. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The physical symptoms were relentless, and the emotional toll was even harder to explain."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It truly saved me," she said, adding it enabled her to not only manage her symptoms but move "from surviving to thriving". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Liza said the hub "offered clarity, compassion, and connection when I needed it most".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She said "I found a community that understood me, resources that empowered me, and support that made me feel less alone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Liza said: "I am not 100% there yet but I have come a long way. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I have started to rebuild my life and with time, patience and the support of Leonie and the group I will get there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Liza has trained as a "menopause champion", supporting others "going through this journey" and helping "break the silence around menopause". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It creates a space where people feel seen, heard, and validated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It truly saved me and now I'm committed to helping it save others," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0660/live/ace71930-a828-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0660/live/ace71930-a828-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0660/live/ace71930-a828-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0660/live/ace71930-a828-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0660/live/ace71930-a828-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0660/live/ace71930-a828-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0660/live/ace71930-a828-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0660/live/ace71930-a828-11f0-9f09-57500e5dbf06.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Deena Banister Deena Banister with short grey hair and brown eyes wearing brown glasses and a brown top. She is smiling.  " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Deena Banister&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Deena Banister said the difference in her well-being since joining the group less than a year ago has been astounding&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Deena Banister, from New Moston, Manchester, joined the hub - which offers expert talks covering everything from symptoms and HRT, to bone health, lifestyle and mindfulness - almost a year ago when her GP suggested it after struggling with severe symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The 60-year-old said the "difference for me has been astounding".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I left my job because I thought I had serious health issues linked to menopause symptoms," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My confidence had taken a knock and unknowingly I was suffering depression and high anxiety."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She said the group has given her "vital information and support" and connections with mental health and physical health practitioners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I have received the correct medication for my menopause and mental health issues, I have joined a small gym run by the hub leader and I'm now investing in myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"My strength and confidence have been boosted and my understanding of what is happening to my body and mind has improved dramatically."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She has also become a "menopause champion" and passes on what she has learned to others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Deena said: "The hub is so important because it gives correct, up-to-date information, establishes important links with medical and mental health services, and improves the lives of women."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The NHS Greater Manchester Integrated Care is hoping the menopause hub model will now extend across Manchester and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 06:23:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5ZM3Y4UV9yazRramsyVUFnNEhESTA2UHduUDljTW9yU054UVFRTjkyLVNQN0hWeGVIS05YaGhaXzJkLW9hSUt0aml1d3JaVDMwY29uN0VjWlYyQdIBX0FVX3lxTE1fVlY3dGY4VjQ0UzFoUFJLcGdyaDVFUTNfdE9GUU9KbWVKZnUwS2RrUldaYm55bHQteVROaE9qdVYteEVFV3RETnMwQlBkVk1RdVZyNE5ueXYzUS1QVGFZ</guid></item><item><title>Essex MUM （英国广播公司）表示，肠癌体征并不总是适合勾选列表</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/ce8z03kg546o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Bowel cancer signs do not always fit a tick list, says mum&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/998a/live/2eb25e70-aa81-11f0-9334-19f2cf191969.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/998a/live/2eb25e70-aa81-11f0-9334-19f2cf191969.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/998a/live/2eb25e70-aa81-11f0-9334-19f2cf191969.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/998a/live/2eb25e70-aa81-11f0-9334-19f2cf191969.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/998a/live/2eb25e70-aa81-11f0-9334-19f2cf191969.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/998a/live/2eb25e70-aa81-11f0-9334-19f2cf191969.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/998a/live/2eb25e70-aa81-11f0-9334-19f2cf191969.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/998a/live/2eb25e70-aa81-11f0-9334-19f2cf191969.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Paul Seager A smiling woman with shoulder length brown hair looks to camera. She is holding up a ginger coloured spaniel dog alongside her. She is stood in front of a green hedge. " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Paul Seager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Laura Seager is urging people to be aware of all possible bowel cancer symptoms&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A mum diagnosed with stage three bowel cancer has urged people to be aware of its lesser-known symptoms after her early diagnosis helped her chances of recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Laura Seager, 42, first called her GP after noticing she still felt like she needed to go to the toilet after she had a bowel movement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The mum-of-two from Langham, near Colchester, was diagnosed with cancer earlier this year and had a 3cm (1.2in) tumour removed ahead of starting chemotherapy treatment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Don't assume you will have a tick list of all the symptoms as everyone is different," she said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Seager, who works for a social housing company, first had stomach pains last Christmas, which she described as "annoying and in the background". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She initially thought the problems were being caused by her diet, so she tried making changes but the "on-and-off" pains continued. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a430/live/bef21600-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a430/live/bef21600-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a430/live/bef21600-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a430/live/bef21600-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a430/live/bef21600-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a430/live/bef21600-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a430/live/bef21600-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a430/live/bef21600-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Paul Seager A woman with brown hair, tied back in a ponytail, sits with her chin on her folded hands. She is looking across a pub and has numerous charm bracelets on her right wrist. She is sat in a pub with another woman who has her arms crossed. " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Paul Seager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Ms Seager is walking 44 miles (71km) for Cancer Research in October and is hoping to educate others about symptoms&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In July she noticed her bowel habits had changed - including an increased frequency of needing to go to the toilet, as well as feeling tired - so she made an appointment with her GP. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"After I had been to the toilet - it felt, every time, like I had not finished - they call it an 'incomplete evacuation'," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She did not, however, spot any blood in her stools, &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/bowel-cancer-info/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;which is one of the better&lt;/a&gt;-known symptoms of the illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;According to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.cancerresearchuk.org/about-cancer/bowel-cancer/symptoms" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;Cancer Research UK&lt;/a&gt;, symptoms of the disease to be aware of include bleeding from the back passage or blood in poo; changes in bowel habits, losing weight, tiredness and breathlessness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A faecal immunochemical test - designed to detect small amounts of blood - showed Ms Seager had highly elevated levels so she was placed on to the NHS's two-week cancer pathway. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a1ce/live/d5ee2e20-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a1ce/live/d5ee2e20-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a1ce/live/d5ee2e20-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a1ce/live/d5ee2e20-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a1ce/live/d5ee2e20-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a1ce/live/d5ee2e20-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a1ce/live/d5ee2e20-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a1ce/live/d5ee2e20-a9b0-11f0-97ec-91b89bd10dfa.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Contributed Nine people are lined up outside a pub. They are all looking to the camera and smiling. They are stood on a gravelly area and have trainers or walking boots on. There is a cream coloured building behind them to the right. " class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Contributed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Friends and family have been joining Ms Seager on her charity walks throughout October&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She feared cancer was a likely possibility after a colonoscopy could not be completed because a tumour was in the way and a stage three bowel cancer diagnosis was confirmed following a CT scan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Seager then underwent a five-hour operation to remove the 3cm cancerous tumour. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She added that she was thankful to her GP who "did not rule anything out" at the initial appointment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If I had not gone to the GP, then by Christmas this year I think my prognosis would be so much worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"People know their own body - so don't assume you will have a tick list of all the symptoms as everyone is different and certainly don't expect you will see blood in the toilet," she said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Seager's surgeon at Colchester Hospital has told her she now has a "really good prognosis" and that she will be cancer-free after a course of chemotherapy to "mop up" any cancerous cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The mum-of-two is now trying to raise awareness of the symptoms of the cancer in the hope she can save lives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She was inspired by the campaigning efforts of "Bowelbabe" Dame Deborah James who died from the illness in June 2022 when she was 40 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/0a52/live/a1832f40-a9b1-11f0-a923-ff705558ae00.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/0a52/live/a1832f40-a9b1-11f0-a923-ff705558ae00.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0a52/live/a1832f40-a9b1-11f0-a923-ff705558ae00.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/0a52/live/a1832f40-a9b1-11f0-a923-ff705558ae00.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/0a52/live/a1832f40-a9b1-11f0-a923-ff705558ae00.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/0a52/live/a1832f40-a9b1-11f0-a923-ff705558ae00.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/0a52/live/a1832f40-a9b1-11f0-a923-ff705558ae00.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/0a52/live/a1832f40-a9b1-11f0-a923-ff705558ae00.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt='PA Media "Bowelbabe" Dame Deborah James smiles to camera. She looks happy and has bobbed brunette hair which is sitting on her shoulders. She is stood in front of a garden wall and fence on a bright sunny day. She is wearing a fundraising vest. ' class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;"Bowelbabe" Dame Deborah James who died in June 2022, aged 40&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Seager and her husband Paul, 56, are fundraising for the Bowelbabe Fund for Cancer Research UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;After setting a modest target of £250 the family has been shocked by the generosity of people's donations and have already raised more than £6,000. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Seager&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.cancerresearchuk.org/get-involved/find-an-event/bowelbabe-walk-44-miles-challenge" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt; is walking 44 miles (71km) throughout October&lt;/a&gt; to help to continue to raise awareness of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I am trying to walk at least a mile each day, depending on how I am feeling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I've got a good little team who are walking with me and it's something for me to focus on rather than feeling sorry for myself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I really admired Dame Deborah and had followed her even before her diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I have tried to be as positive as possible and get people talking about it like she did. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Bowel cancer and toilet habits are still one of the taboo subjects that people don't want to talk about and that still needs to change," she added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:21:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5MVlA1ZmFTMms0QzZMcmRFVUtkcVdNa0Z4ZldPU3JlNlVvblUzSzNZQjdhTTFMOE5hZTRvNmdCSU9hWF9RQWVWS2l0bzZVZU53YmFSdEkxeV9EUdIBX0FVX3lxTE04NnF1ZDA1TkN2UWw5cTh3VVNLS3JReFBSUTVlVFpCc1pDWF9PMFhkUHpkNUNoVEJSU2gtbVEwVFpyWEloYlBmU0gxbklJckhJVjBiU01RdUVyMUFPaDZB</guid></item><item><title>营养师推荐的改善胆固醇的7种最佳冷冻蔬菜- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/best-frozen-vegetables-for-better-cholesterol-11828506</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;High cholesterol is common, with about 10% of U.S. adults having the condition.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Foods high in soluble fiber, like these frozen veggies, may help reduce cholesterol levels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stock up on frozen edamame, broccoli, cauliflower, Brussels sprouts and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; High cholesterol affects about 10% of U.S. adults; having it puts you at a higher risk of developing heart disease and stroke.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; When it comes to managing high cholesterol, small dietary changes can help. Eating enough vegetables not only helps reduce high cholesterol but may even prevent the condition. While many people believe that fresh veggies are healthiest, frozen veggies with no added ingredients can be just as nutritious. Plus, they tend to be budget-friendly and have a much longer shelf life.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;We spoke with registered dietitians and dove into the latest research to share the seven best frozen vegetables for lower cholesterol.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-edamame"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 1. Edamame &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8049006/health-benefits-of-edamame/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Edamame&lt;/a&gt; (aka young soybeans) is a good source of a key nutrient for cholesterol: soluble fiber. “Although fiber never enters the bloodstream, soluble fiber binds to bile in the digestive tract and carries it out of the body. The liver then uses cholesterol to create new bile, thus lowering blood cholesterol levels,” explains &lt;a href="https://feedyourintention.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Stephanie Dunne, M.S., RDN, IFNCP&lt;/a&gt;, an integrative registered dietitian nutritionist. Just 1 cup of frozen edamame contains 8 grams of fiber and 18 grams of plant-based protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Edamame is also a source of isoflavones, compounds in soy products that may help lower cholesterol levels.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You can find frozen edamame in the pod or shelled. “I always keep a bag of frozen edamame on hand to toss in salads, stir-fries and soups,” says &lt;a href="https://www.lauramali.com/laura-ali-registered-dietitian-nutritionist/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Laura M. Ali, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;, a culinary nutritionist and registered dietitian.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-green-peas"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 2. Green Peas &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Green peas have 7 grams of cholesterol-lowering fiber per cup.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Plus, they’re another &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/291111/the-10-best-vegan-protein-sources/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;plant-based source of protein&lt;/a&gt;, with 8 grams of protein per cup.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Higher intake of plant-based proteins has been shown to be helpful with cholesterol as they are often lower in saturated fats,” says &lt;a href="https://www.thedietitiandish.com/about-me" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Patricia Kolesa, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and nutrition educator. In other words, replacing some animal proteins—like beef, sausage, bacon and deli meat—with peas can help lower your total saturated fat intake. Consuming too much saturated fat is associated with high levels of LDL cholesterol, which is the harmful type of cholesterol.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Kolesa recommends tossing frozen green peas into pasta dishes, casseroles, stir-fries and soups or serving them as a side dish. If you’re looking for ideas, try a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/249993/pea-soup/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Pea Soup&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/249652/skillet-tuna-noodle-casserole/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Skillet Tuna Noodle Casserole&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3-spinach"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 3. Spinach &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Frozen &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/spinach-benefits-11703396" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;spinach&lt;/a&gt; is jam-packed with fiber, vitamins, minerals and antioxidants to promote heart health. “Spinach is high in insoluble fiber and can help reduce LDL cholesterol levels. As a plant-based source of iron and protein, it’s also a great source of calcium, vitamin C and various antioxidants to help you stay healthy,” says &lt;a href="https://thepolishdietitian.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Daria Zajac, RD, LDN&lt;/a&gt;, a dietitian specializing in diabetes. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This leafy green is also high in antioxidants, particularly one of them. “Spinach is rich in a compound called lutein, an antioxidant known to help reduce inflammation. Research suggests that lutein may help cholesterol oxidation, which may help prevent cholesterol from sticking to artery walls,” says &lt;a href="https://www.vandanasheth.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Vandana Sheth, RDN, CDCES, FAND&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian nutritionist and plant-based and diabetes expert.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Studies suggest that eating more dark leafy greens like spinach is linked with lower rates of cardiovascular disease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Zajac recommends adding spinach to stews, soups or your morning eggs. It also goes great in your &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7899857/spinach-smoothie/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;morning smoothie&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-cauliflower"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 4. Cauliflower &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/is-cauliflower-good-for-you-8608382" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Cauliflower&lt;/a&gt; is another frozen veggie worth stocking up on. &lt;a href="https://heidimcindoord.com/#about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Heidi McIndoo, M.S., RD&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian focusing on budget-friendly nutrition, recommends it for its heart-healthy fiber and lack of saturated fat. Each cup of frozen cauliflower has 3 grams of fiber—about 10% of the Daily Value.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “It's delicious roasted with just a little olive oil and kosher salt, or fancy it up with a drizzle of Buffalo sauce before popping into the oven," says McIndoo. "You can also puree it after steaming it to turn it into a perfect substitute for some or all of the cream in cream-based soups and sauces like potato soup or fettuccini Alfredo.” If you like McIndoo’s suggestion, you'll want to try our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7870653/roasted-buffalo-cauliflower/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Roasted Buffalo Cauliflower&lt;/a&gt; version. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-broccoli"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 5. Broccoli &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Like the other veggies on this list, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/broccoli-benefits-8653215" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;broccoli is rich in fiber and micronutrients&lt;/a&gt;. What makes it stand out is its glucosinolate content, particularly sulforaphane. This is a phytochemical found almost exclusively in cruciferous veggies like broccoli, cauliflower and Brussels sprouts. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Research suggests that sulforaphane may help reduce oxidative stress and inflammation, both key factors that support heart health,” says Sheth.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One small study found that eating about 1 cup of broccoli per day improved HDL cholesterol—the beneficial type of cholesterol—by 7.6% in female participants. In male participants, it reduced their total cholesterol by 10%.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/8028966/frozen-broccoli-recipes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;bag of frozen broccoli can be used in anything&lt;/a&gt; from ramen noodles to mac and cheese to casseroles and more.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-6-brussels-sprouts"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 6. Brussels Sprouts &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Each cup of Brussels sprouts has 2 grams of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7962360/what-is-the-difference-between-insoluble-and-soluble-fiber-according-to-a-dietitian/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;soluble fiber&lt;/a&gt;, the kind that’s especially helpful for lowering cholesterol.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/brussels-sprouts-health-benefits-8650195" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Brussels sprouts&lt;/a&gt; are also rich in antioxidants and phytochemicals that could provide more cholesterol-related benefits.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Brussels sprouts contain plant compounds, including kaempferol, which has both antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties. Kaempferol has been linked to promoting heart health and lowering cholesterol levels,” says Sheth.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Roasting them is one of the best ways to enjoy them. Browse through some Brussels sprouts recipes to spark inspiration.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-7-mushrooms"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 7. Mushrooms &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These earthy veggies are easy to toss into pasta dishes, add to pizza or sauté on their own. Plus, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/9583/5-amazing-health-benefits-of-mushrooms/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;mushrooms have unique benefits&lt;/a&gt; when it comes to cholesterol.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Mushrooms contain beta-glucans, a type of soluble fiber known to help reduce cholesterol by binding to cholesterol-rich bile acids and removing them from the body,” says &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/author/lauren-manaker/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lauren Manaker, M.S., RDN, LD&lt;/a&gt;, a registered dietitian and nutrition writer. “Some studies suggest that certain varieties, like shiitake mushrooms, contain compounds that can further enhance cholesterol metabolism and promote heart health."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Other varieties shown to benefit cholesterol include enoki mushrooms, reishi mushrooms and portobello mushrooms.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-strategies-to-improve-cholesterol"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Strategies to Improve Cholesterol &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Besides adding these frozen veggies to your diet, there are a few other ways to improve cholesterol:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Incorporate Regular Physical Activity.&lt;/strong&gt; Ideally, aim for at least 150 minutes of moderate-intensity aerobic activity or 75 minutes of vigorous-intensity aerobic activity per week.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; But informal movement also counts, so try &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-to-add-movement-limited-time-11772724" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;moving more throughout the day&lt;/a&gt;. This involves being intentional with looking for opportunities to move more—like taking the stairs instead of the elevator, incorporating movement breaks every hour—especially if you sit most of the day—and using a stand-up desk and walking pad.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be Mindful of Your Saturated Fat Intake.&lt;/strong&gt; This type of fat, found in foods like red and processed meats, baked goods, butter and full-fat dairy, can increase cholesterol levels if eaten excessively. &lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; However, a healthcare provider may recommend less if you have heart disease or high cholesterol, so make sure to check in with them. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limit Your Alcohol Consumption.&lt;/strong&gt; Drinking too much alcohol can raise cholesterol, so be mindful of your total alcohol intake. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention suggests that women shouldn’t have more than one drink per day and men shouldn’t exceed two drinks daily—though some experts advise limiting it to less than these amounts.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; To &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-stop-drinking-alcohol-8773934" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;cut back on alcohol&lt;/a&gt;, try a tasty mocktail, such as &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7883572/elderberry-elixir-mocktail/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;Elderberry Elixir Mocktail&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7919850/moscow-mule-mocktail/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;Moscow Mule Mocktail&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/no-added-sugar-sangria-mocktail-11769655" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;No-Added-Sugar Sangria Mocktail&lt;/a&gt; (trust us, you won't miss the alcohol!).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Plain frozen veggies are just as nutritious as fresh ones (plain being ones without added ingredients and sauces). Plus, they tend to cost less and don’t go bad after a few days, so stock up on frozen veggies. If you’re managing high cholesterol, we invite you to make room for these seven especially. They’re full of fiber, antioxidants and plant compounds that can help lower cholesterol and protect heart health. Plus, they go well in everything from smoothies to casseroles to pasta dishes and more.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNZzhHOWFCQmRsNW9xNUptSm1WVHdkblhheENVTDdpbXVwMmIwYnNZY3VZTGhrX2ZVSzc3elo5SXRPNWVvZ3VQdGhtT1hYd01UMUlRV1BQb085ZWtSRVIwNDIzaW5SSGl3cGNlX1NjNXFTX2R2M3JUNEEtbmtkWl8xdks4elBXbWRw</guid></item><item><title>专家揭示如何随着年龄的增长保持大脑敏锐- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/an-expert-reveals-how-to-keep-your-brain-sharp-as-you-age</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Is it an achievable goal to remain mentally sharp while aging, or is it a pipe dream?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's entirely possible if you cultivate habits throughout your life that are beneficial to brain function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a researcher in cognitive neuroscience and the neuropsychology of aging processes, I aim to shed light on the ways we can maintain good cognitive health while aging in light of recent scientific advances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The importance of cognitive reserve&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most effective strategies research has identified is developing and maintaining good cognitive reserve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive reserve refers to the brain's ability to resist the effects of aging or neurodegenerative diseases without resulting in significant functional decline. This concept is now central to approaches for preventing cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its report &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(24)01296-0/abstract"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dementia prevention, intervention, and care&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, updated in 2024, the &lt;em&gt;Lancet&lt;/em&gt; highlighted the fact that 45 per cent of dementia cases could be prevented or delayed by addressing 14 modifiable risk factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These factors include physical inactivity,  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depression" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73097" data-postid="177929" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt; and social isolation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But one of the earliest and most significant factors is having a low level of education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Beyond education&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Education has long been considered the main indicator of &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1017/S1355617702813248"&gt;cognitive reserve&lt;/a&gt;. It reflects prolonged exposure to intellectually stimulating activities that promote the development of effective brain networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this view is now considered incomplete. Cognitive reserve is not fixed in childhood or adulthood: &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jalz.2018.07.219"&gt;it can be built, maintained and even amplified throughout life&lt;/a&gt; through different experiences including learning, rich social interactions and cognitively stimulating leisure activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Specific examples of these activities include playing a musical instrument or complex board games such as chess, or participating in volunteer activities that require planning and problem-solving skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Understanding cognitive reserve&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientific research offers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1684/nrp.2016.0394"&gt;several complementary models&lt;/a&gt; for understanding the mechanisms of cognitive reserve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some focus on the structure of the brain itself, suggesting that characteristics such as the number of neurons influence the brain's tolerance to damage. This is the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1037/0894-4105.7.3.273"&gt;brain reserve model&lt;/a&gt;, which is based on the idea that some people are born with a greater number of neurons, enabling them to cope better with aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others argue that active lifestyles can slow down the effects of brain aging by strengthening biological resilience — for example, the brain's ability to remain intact and functional as it ages, showing few visible signs of deterioration despite age. This is the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.tics.2012.04.005"&gt;brain maintenance model&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A third set of models emphasizes the functional flexibility of the brain, which allows it to mobilize its resources differently or recruit alternative neural networks to compensate for age-related losses. This is known as the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neuropsychologia.2009.03.004"&gt;cognitive reserve model&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These different models are part of a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jalz.2018.07.219"&gt;common conceptual framework&lt;/a&gt; that distinguishes between brain reserve, brain maintenance and cognitive reserve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each model is based on a specific idea, but they are complementary and supported by empirical data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cognitive reserve model remains the most widely studied, particularly because of its link to modifiable factors such as level of education and regular participation in cognitively stimulating activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177976" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177976" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/ElderWomenPlayingChess-e1760653217648.jpg" alt="Older women playing chess" class="wp-image-177976 size-full" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177976" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Choosing leisure activities that require brain power can help us maintain cognitive health well into old age. (&lt;a href="https://unsplash.com/photos/a-group-of-women-playing-chess-2c4gG2nVwjc"&gt;Pierre Cazenave-Kaufman/Unsplash)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Cognitive reserve is dynamic&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This clarification helps to harmonize research and effectively guide prevention strategies. Above all, it reminds us that far from being a fixed entity, cognitive reserve evolves due to interactions with experience and learning, and can therefore be strengthened throughout life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_launch"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Launch" class="alignnone wp-image-177073 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Launch.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent work supports this dynamic view. &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0197458022002251?via%3Dihub"&gt;A team of Québec researchers, of which I am a member&lt;/a&gt;, has shown that structured learning of memory strategies, including the method of loci (associating each piece of information with a familiar place) or mental visualization (transforming information into images to better retain it), can induce significant changes in brain activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A combination of increases and decreases in activation, including variations in the level of activity in different areas of the brain, was observed in different brain regions during the phases of learning and recalling information. This observation reflects the fact that the use of memory strategies allows for greater functional flexibility in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results also showed that in more educated individuals, certain regions are activated in a more targeted manner during learning and recall, suggesting that their brains use more effective strategies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other research has also highlighted the role of education in brain structure and function. A study I conducted with colleagues &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s11682-016-9621-7"&gt;highlighted an association between years of schooling, volume of grey matter and brain activation in the context of memory&lt;/a&gt;. Another study in which I participated showed &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.neurobiolaging.2022.02.001"&gt;greater flexibility of activation according to task complexity in more educated individuals&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this research confirms that cognitive reserve can be developed with experience and modulated by cognitive training at any age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Stimulating your brain while having fun&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the same vein, the Engage study by the &lt;a href="https://ccna-ccnv.ca"&gt;Canadian Consortium on Aging and Neurodegeneration&lt;/a&gt; aims to study the behavioral and neurophysiological effects of cognitively stimulating leisure activities in older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This hybrid intervention combines formal cognitive training (memorization strategies, attention) with structured leisure activities such as learning music, a second language or video games.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It offers an ecological model — in other words, an approach that is close to real-life conditions, enjoyable and motivating and conducive to sustained engagement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By demonstrating that these natural interventions produce effects comparable to those of traditional cognitive training program, which often consist of repetitive exercises done on a computer or on paper to work on functions such as memory or concentration, Engage could transform approaches to preventing age-related cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Learning another language&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my neuropsychology of aging laboratory (&lt;a href="http://www.uqtr.ca/neuropsychologieduvieillissement"&gt;NeuroÂge&lt;/a&gt;) at the University of Québec at Trois-Rivières (UQTR), we are conducting a complementary project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In collaboration with professors Paul John, from the Department of Modern Languages and Translation, and Simon Rigoulot, from the Department of Psychology, we are exploring the effects of learning English as a second language on cognition and brain activity in older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using a protocol that integrates classes, tutoring and cognitive and electroencephalography measurements, this project aims to document the cognitive and neural benefits of meaningful, motivating and accessible learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preliminary results are promising and support the idea that intellectual engagement, even when started later in life, can generate measurable benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maintaining good cognitive health at any age requires a combination of accessible, motivating and stimulating interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive reserve, far from being fixed, is built up throughout life. Advances in research now offer us concrete tools for healthy aging, particularly when it comes to cognitive health.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/266451/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/benjamin-boller-2327896"&gt;Benjamin Boller&lt;/a&gt;, Professeur agrégé en neuropsychologie, &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/universite-du-quebec-a-trois-rivieres-uqtr-1713"&gt;Université du Québec à Trois-Rivières (UQTR)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/how-to-maintain-good-cognitive-health-at-any-age-266451"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 01:01:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxPSzRJVjR5TzVIeFNPejFWT19QbVNDWS1vbWIydjJ0ZUZXNUUtTkVTUndYMFZLOFdmeWJHazJMeDRMMkthT0pDSHlOZlE1UFpKZnZJRTh2RGxmdHBtRkxiOENPR3hmQWRscUFKRHZQUWI5Z1hQY3RNT0RIeHdUOGo1VGh3Z3JibW1EbnZhNDFvQQ</guid></item><item><title>在马里恩县废水中检测到麻疹，州警告- OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/10/measles-detected-in-marion-county-wastewater-state-warns.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FIY7DM4XOZHBBGV6Q53RIJMDHA"&gt;Traces of the &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/whos-immune-to-measles-what-if-you-dont-know-if-youre-vaccinated-what-you-need-to-know.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/whos-immune-to-measles-what-if-you-dont-know-if-youre-vaccinated-what-you-need-to-know.html"&gt;measles virus&lt;/a&gt; were found in a wastewater sample collected earlier this month from a Marion County treatment facility, state health officials announced Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XSFVFPCYU5GQPH6GGBNVKFAXAI"&gt;The virus was detected during &lt;a href="https://flashalert.net/id/OregonHealthAuthority/184460" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://flashalert.net/id/OregonHealthAuthority/184460"&gt;routine wastewater sampling&lt;/a&gt; on Oct. 6, according to the Oregon Health Authority. The detection suggests that at least one person had measles in the area, health officials said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7D62V2Z2K5FSPG4PW63FHL2AU4"&gt;A single positive water sample “does not show whether there is ongoing risk to the community” and that it’s possible that a person with measles was just traveling in the area, health officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KQN57TW2CRG33D5T6M5P4M26UE"&gt;Dr. Howard Chiou, medical director for communicable disease and immunizations at the Oregon Health Authority, said wastewater surveillance works “like a ping on a radar.” It can pick up low levels of a virus moving through a community or signal the start of a larger outbreak, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OM37JET3XVHG3LUTXXMYSYLYHQ"&gt;Chiou said this early warning helps health care providers prepare and remind patients to protect themselves by staying up to date on their measles vaccinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KIMY6DOQJFD7LDWECIUBV743XM"&gt;While most Oregonians have been vaccinated, health officials said the virus poses a serious risk to those who are not, especially pregnant people, infants under 1 year old and those with weakened immune systems. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D4USQMHBKVHRPKHJXYQ3FVYLSA"&gt;Measles is a respiratory disease that spreads through the air when an infected person coughs or sneezes. The virus can linger in the air for up to two hours after an infected person leaves an area. It’s notoriously contagious — &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/index.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;nine out of 10 unvaccinated people&lt;/a&gt; near someone with measles can become infected, according to the federal Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RQIOAX4PY5EPRIRQTWRXA3U7DM"&gt;Measles typically starts with symptoms such as fever, cough, runny nose and red, watery eyes. A few days later, a characteristic red rash breaks out, usually starting on the face and spreading downward. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="R3BJ7WHIIFAZREE6TFDX2BWFCQ"&gt;The disease can also lead to serious complications, including pneumonia, brain swelling and, in rare cases, death. According to the CDC, there have been &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;three confirmed measles-related deaths&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EWZG4IPV3ZA4NOZLTZTQVJGVLU"&gt;Oregon health officials have &lt;a href="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2025/06/oregon-confirms-first-measles-case-of-2025-linked-to-international-travel.html"&gt;confirmed only one case of measles&lt;/a&gt; so far this year — an unvaccinated adult from Multnomah County who tested positive in June after returning from an overseas trip. Last year, the state recorded 31 confirmed cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BNHZAIS2YFC7PHQ3CZVLTFAIGQ"&gt;Across the U.S., the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;CDC has confirmed&lt;/a&gt; 1,573 measles this year. That’s already more than four times the number of confirmed cases last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3TP6XR5Z6ZBDZJU3RWRJXZSTLA"&gt;Most cases are linked to outbreaks — defined as three or more connected infections — and nearly 90% of the people who got sick were either unvaccinated or didn’t know their vaccination status. So far, there have been 44 measles outbreaks in 41 states this year, according to the CDC’s latest data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 23:50:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxOU29oazB4aTRuSFl5N29aaFhKSXZ0YkJxU3dHOHBmcVhQY2YyR01wUE9HUllJUV9NdV9EZVhCaG9JM0swQmNZZW9mX19oWE1XWHNsbk5KdnVQVnZyaEVSZHNtYm11SW9YUGZpNmpDcjAxSDREZXYtQ0hkWGlfNG1NSkNhcl83OFF6RUw3cnhGQTJxWWVlcnVHUFVmTU1vbzhJTE5WN1NR0gG6AUFVX3lxTE5BM1A0dGxaRjVhSnVxZUFFQ0JSaTU4emFCZVJqWUF5bUhtRFY4RTRkaE56Vm5rN1FGTjVVQTFlbEdLUHdiVzZmUHJxa1AtOWZLM1VlcG12QXVkdEhYV015MGpsc0Jvcy1tcVk0MldFZWEtUVpiZ3FTYTBfR2tsVlJhV3BFZXpKMTdFRklsSktzUHU4Ykc4d2hKbXVXU2E1TGVsYUVMaVJYbmtTc0N1NFRSLXN4WHRrWGRKdw</guid></item><item><title>芬太尼：美国如何摆脱毒品致死疫情-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cm2e471159vo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;'It's scary to think I could have died': How Americans are coming back from fentanyl addiction &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/eb8c/live/49e57ff0-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/eb8c/live/49e57ff0-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/eb8c/live/49e57ff0-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/eb8c/live/49e57ff0-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/eb8c/live/49e57ff0-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/eb8c/live/49e57ff0-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/eb8c/live/49e57ff0-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/eb8c/live/49e57ff0-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Tim Mansel Kayla smiles for the camera" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Tim Mansel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Kayla says she became "instantly addicted" to fentanyl as a teenager&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Kayla first tried fentanyl as a troubled 18-year-old, growing up in the US state of North Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I felt like literally amazing.  The voices in my head just completely went silent. I got instantly addicted," she remembers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The little blue pills Kayla became hooked on were probably made in Mexico, and then smuggled across the border to the US - a deadly trade President Donald Trump is trying to crack down on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But drug cartels aren't pharmacists. So, Kayla never knew how much fentanyl was in the pill she was taking. Would there be enough of the synthetic opioid to kill her?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's scary to think about that," Kayla says, reflecting on how she could have overdosed and died at any moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In 2023, there were over 110,000 drug-related deaths in the US. The march of fentanyl, which is 50 times more potent than heroin, seemed unstoppable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But then came a staggering turnaround. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In 2024, the number of fatal overdoses across the US fell by around 25%. That's nearly 30,000 fewer deaths – dozens of lives saved every day. Kayla's state, North Carolina, is at the forefront of that trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 cnKFtO"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Why fatal overdoses have fallen so sharply&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;One of the explanations is a commitment to harm reduction. This means promoting policies that prioritise drug users' health and wellbeing rather than criminalising people - a recognition that in an era of fentanyl, drug-taking too often ends with death by overdose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In North Carolina, where Kayla still lives, and where overdose fatalities are currently down by an impressive 35%, harm reduction strategies are well-developed.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Kayla no longer takes street drugs. And she's a client of an innovative law enforcement assisted diversion (LEAD) programme in Fayetteville. It's a partnership between the town's police and the North Carolina Harm Reduction Coalition. Together, they work to divert substance users away from crime, and get them on the road to recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/8d23/live/69247650-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/8d23/live/69247650-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/8d23/live/69247650-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/8d23/live/69247650-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/8d23/live/69247650-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/8d23/live/69247650-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/8d23/live/69247650-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/8d23/live/69247650-a915-11f0-b5e8-25b94b51d777.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Tim Mansel Ly Jamaal Littlejohn poses in front of a police car" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Tim Mansel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Lt Jamaal Littlejohn watched his own sister deal with substance use disorder&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"If someone's stealing from a grocery store, we run their criminal history. And often we see that the crimes they're committing appear to fund the addiction they have," says Lt Jamaal Littlejohn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;This might make them a candidate for the LEAD programme, meaning they can get support to tackle their addiction, and can start thinking about secure housing and employment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The proponents of LEAD say it isn't about being soft on crime. Drug dealers still go to prison in Fayetteville. "But if we can get people the services they need, it gives law enforcement more time to deal with bigger crimes," argues Lt Littlejohn, who watched his own sister struggle with a substance use disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Kayla has blossomed. She's such a long way now from the days when she used prostitution to fund her fentanyl habit. As part of the LEAD process, her criminal record has been wiped. She recently graduated as a certified nurse assistant, and is now working in a residential home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It's like the best thing ever. This is the longest time I've been clean," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Critical to Kayla's recovery has been treatment. She's been taking methadone for nearly a year when she tells her story to the BBC. "It's keeping me from going back," she believes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Methadone and buprenorphine are medications used to treat opioid use disorder.  They stem cravings and stop painful withdrawal. Nationwide, treatment has played a role in puncturing the overdose fatality statistics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In North Carolina, it's been a game-changer: more than 30,000 people were enrolled in a programme in 2024, with numbers climbing in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'You're still playing Russian roulette, but your odds improve'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/9846/live/0c239ac0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/9846/live/0c239ac0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9846/live/0c239ac0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/9846/live/0c239ac0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/9846/live/0c239ac0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/9846/live/0c239ac0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/9846/live/0c239ac0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9846/live/0c239ac0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Tim Mansel A worker sits behind a reception window at a clinic. Printed notices adorn the surrounding wall" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Tim Mansel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;This Morse Clinic experiences its busiest time soon after 05:30&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At 09:00 at one of the Morse Clinics in the state capital of Raleigh, two or three people wait their turn in reception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The busiest time is 5.30am to 7am, so before work," says Dr Eric Morse, an addiction psychiatrist running nine clinics offering medication assisted treatment (MAT) in North Carolina. "Most of our folks are working - once they're sober, they show up to work on time every day."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The clinic runs a finely-tuned operation. After patients check in, they're called to a dosing window to receive their prescription. They're in and out in minutes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;They'll randomly be drug tested for illicit narcotics. Dr Morse says around half his patients are still testing positive for opioids bought on the street, but he doesn't see this as failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Maybe you're using once a week and you're used to using three times a day… You're still playing Russian roulette with fentanyl but you've taken a whole bunch of bullets out of the chamber, so your survival rate goes up significantly," says Dr Morse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;This is harm reduction.  So rather than be expelled from the treatment programme, patients who get a positive drug test are given extra support and counselling.  Dr Morse says 80-90% will eventually stop using street drugs altogether.  And in time, many will taper off their medication too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;The abstinence debate&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 geRyoc"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/2876/live/9b086a40-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/2876/live/9b086a40-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2876/live/9b086a40-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/2876/live/9b086a40-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/2876/live/9b086a40-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/2876/live/9b086a40-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/2876/live/9b086a40-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/2876/live/9b086a40-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Tim Mansel Mark Pless speaks to the BBC" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Tim Mansel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Not everyone thinks this is the right approach.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mark Pless is a Republican who sits in North Carolina's state House of Representatives, and used to be a full-time paramedic. He points out that illegal drug-taking starts with a choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt; And he doesn't believe in harm reduction. In particular he's against treating opioid use disorder with medications like methadone or buprenorphine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"You're replacing an addictive product with another addictive product," he says. "If you have to take it in order to stay clean, it's still addictive. We've got to figure out how to get people to where they can do better – we can't leave them on drugs forever."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;He favours abstinence treatment programmes, when drug users go "cold turkey".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But there's pushback from health professionals in North Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I believe there are multiple paths to recovery," says Dr Morse. "I'm not pooh-poohing abstinence-based treatment - except when you look at the medical evidence."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Dr Morse references &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://news.yale.edu/2023/12/19/treating-opioid-disorder-without-meds-more-harmful-no-treatment-all" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;a Yale University study from 2023&lt;/a&gt; analysing the risk of death for opioid users in a treatment programme compared to people not in treatment.  The study suggested that someone in abstinence treatment was as likely - or more more likely - to have a fatal overdose as a person who wasn't in treatment and was continuing to use street opioids like fentanyl.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Treatment aside, another drug is helping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Naloxone is widely available, and used as a nasal spray it reverses the effect of an opioid overdose, helping someone breathe again. In North Carolina in 2024, it was administered more than 16,000 times. That's potentially 16,000 lives saved – and these are only the overdose reversals that have been reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"This is as close to a miracle drug as we can ever imagine," says Dr Nabarun Dasgupta, a scientist specialising in street drugs at the University of North Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/017c/live/d96d02a0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/017c/live/d96d02a0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/017c/live/d96d02a0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/017c/live/d96d02a0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/017c/live/d96d02a0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/017c/live/d96d02a0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/017c/live/d96d02a0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/017c/live/d96d02a0-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Tim Mansel Dr Nabarun Dasgupta" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Tim Mansel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Dr Nabarun Dasgupta hails the benefits of naloxone&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Many users of narcotics like cocaine, methamphetamine and heroin want to know that what they're taking won't kill them. Some people use test-strips to check for fentanyl, because they know it's been implicated in so many fatal overdoses.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But the strips don't identify all potentially harmful substances. Dr Dasgupta runs a national drugs-testing laboratory. Users send him a tiny bit of their drug supply via local non-profit organisations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We've analysed close to 14,000 samples from 43 states over the last three years," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;A generational shift&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Testing drugs for potentially dangerous additives is an additional weapon in the harm reduction armoury. Dr Dasgupta believes another reason for decreasing overdose fatalities in the US is that young people are avoiding opioids like fentanyl.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We see a demographic shift. Generation Z are dying of overdose much less frequently than their parents or their grandparents' generations were at the same age," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Dr Dasgupta isn't entirely surprised 20-somethings are steering clear of opioids. A shocking four out of 10 American adults know someone whose life has been ended by an overdose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It was this epidemic of death, set in train in the 1990s by prescription opioids, that motivated North Carolina's former attorney general - now the state governor - to move against powerful corporations benefitting from so many Americans' dark spiral down into addiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Josh Stein picked up the phone to his counterparts in other states, and took a leading role in co-ordinating legal action against opioid manufacturers, distributors and retailers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/6b25/live/fd5d7320-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/6b25/live/fd5d7320-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6b25/live/fd5d7320-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/6b25/live/fd5d7320-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/6b25/live/fd5d7320-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/6b25/live/fd5d7320-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/6b25/live/fd5d7320-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/6b25/live/fd5d7320-a916-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Tim Mansel Josh Stein speaks to the BBC" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Tim Mansel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;North Carolina Governor Josh Stein took a leading role in co-ordinating legal action against opioid manufacturers&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"There was a Republican attorney general in Tennessee, I'm Democrat in North Carolina… But we're all caring about our people and we're all willing to fight for them," Stein reflects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The upshot, after years of intense negotiations, was an Opioid Settlement totalling some $60bn (£45bn). This is money that huge companies have agreed to pay to US states, to be used for the "abatement of the opioid epidemic". North Carolina's share is around $1.5bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It has to be spent in four ways – drug prevention, treatment, recovery, or harm reduction. I think it's transformative," says Governor Stein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Meanwhile, funding from the national government is uncertain. The cuts to Medicaid included in President Trump's One Big, Beautiful Bill Act could have a tremendous impact on this area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In the Morse Clinics in Raleigh, 70% of patients depend on Medicaid. If they lose health insurance, will they end treatment and become more vulnerable to death by overdose? Although North Carolina's drug fatality statistics look optimistic, thousands of people are still dying - and the state's black, indigenous and non-white populations haven't experienced the same rates of decrease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;And there remain other states that have witnessed a stubbornly slower rate of decrease in lethal overdoses - including Nevada and Arizona.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/9bae/live/3b76aaa0-a917-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/9bae/live/3b76aaa0-a917-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9bae/live/3b76aaa0-a917-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/9bae/live/3b76aaa0-a917-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/9bae/live/3b76aaa0-a917-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/9bae/live/3b76aaa0-a917-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/9bae/live/3b76aaa0-a917-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9bae/live/3b76aaa0-a917-11f0-85e5-b7e4f930730c.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Tim Mansel Charlton Roberson speaks to the BBC" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Tim Mansel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Kayla credits Charlton Roberson, her mentor at North Carolina Harm Reduction Coalition, with being instrumental in her recovery&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;No one is complacent. Least of all Kayla.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In the grip of fentanyl for three long years, she never overdosed herself, but she did have to save her friends. Kayla's parents didn't know what to do with her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"They kind of gave up on me - they thought I was gonna be dead," she remembers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Kayla credits Charlton Roberson, her harm reduction mentor, as being instrumental in her recovery.  Her aim now is to taper off methadone and become medication- and drug-free. She also wants to find a job in a hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I feel more alive than I ever did when I was using fentanyl," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;i id="if-you've-been-affected-by-the-issues-in-this-story,-help-and-support-is-available-via" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;If you've been affected by the issues in this story, help and support is available via &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/actionline/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;&lt;i id="the-bbc-action-line" class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;the BBC Action Line&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="." class="sc-d16436d-0 gbdkAi"&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 23:42:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9nSFk5OVBacTlSZjhnVnR0Wm5GczZRSGUxMTlpWEwtMnNPRFE3dHZSZGhFWURON2l0SWl3blR4NmJLMDVYZTNnWGR6VkJ1SnEzMXJvR1lrZm4yUdIBX0FVX3lxTE5tRm9TV3BlSWFNejVpWDZGVjJkdV9HRWtCZjRRQ3NwMjF5dml4TExZd1A3OG5kVzBVTVlFaXhvcEFCYTA0QjFoNW1yVW92ZERyYW85UEtKZzc5NXo4cnpj</guid></item><item><title>麻疹暴露在国家“重大复苏”期间在西雅图机场得到确认- KOMO</title><link>https://komonews.com/news/local/measles-case-detected-at-seattle-airport-unrelated-to-other-local-cases-king-county-national-resurgence</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText-module_storyText__FWhP"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;SEATTLE — &lt;/span&gt;A new confirmed measles case in a traveler who passed through Seattle-Tacoma International Airport on Monday is not connected to any previous local measles cases, &lt;a href="https://doh.wa.gov/you-and-your-family/illness-and-disease-z/measles/measles-cases-washington-state-2025" target="_blank" title="https://doh.wa.gov/you-and-your-family/illness-and-disease-z/measles/measles-cases-washington-state-2025" class="themeColorForLinks"&gt;Public Health  Seattle &amp;amp; King County officials said Friday. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The infected person was at the airport before getting a diagnosis, was unvaccinated, and is a resident of Arizona, an area with an active measles outbreak, health officials confirmed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virus can linger in the air for up to two hours after an infected person leaves, according to King County health officials. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those exposed at the airport on Oct. 13 may develop symptoms between Oct. 20 and Nov. 3  , health officials said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have now been 12 cases of measles statewide this year, according to Public Health – Seattle &amp;amp; King County.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;READ MORE: &lt;a href="https://komonews.com/news/local/measles-virus-king-county-rash-vaccine-seattle-public-health-mumps-rubella-booster-bellevue-fire-station-childrens-hospital#" target="_blank" title="https://komonews.com/news/local/measles-virus-king-county-rash-vaccine-seattle-public-health-mumps-rubella-booster-bellevue-fire-station-childrens-hospital#" class="themeColorForLinks"&gt;2 more confirmed measles cases reported in King County &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The county has responded to three other measles cases this year among people who traveled through King County but are not Washington state residents, officials said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sandra J. Valenciano, Health Officer for Public Health – Seattle &amp;amp; King County, highlighted a national resurgence: "In the U.S., we are experiencing a significant measles resurgence. Nationally, there have been over 1,500 cases reported so far this year—five times more cases than last year." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The measles vaccine, she noted, is highly effective, providing about 97% protection with two doses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles is highly contagious, spreading through the air via coughs or sneezes, and can lead to severe complications. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public Health advises those at high risk, including young children, adults over 20, pregnant individuals, and those with weakened immune systems, to contact healthcare providers if exposed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The MMR vaccine remains the best preventive measure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KOMO</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 23:35:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxPS2J2bXEzZE1qamYxLVk3VDVtek5ELWtGTDdVUFNDRHcwS3JOVy11UWZubDNTV2diaEVWbXRPb0NjRTZjbXhIT0lOM25FTk0zU1hSS1NOYXRBQjhNemxiMW0ycVVDWmo4WjJHNERpbGhvV2NPb1A5UklHM3pGYnFPV2xJLUUteWNpQTEyVDJTWHhNbDdQY21QdmYzQnBjdEJjckRmTlV6UXh2ZVFpY0F0Wm42enVuWTViWkFnZlZqUzlrd2pTQTBqSTlOX05SdGZs</guid></item><item><title>官员在检测到异常位置的入侵生物后发出警告： “这是第一次已知的检测” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/officials-issue-warning-detecting-invasive-223000643.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Officials in Canyon County, Idaho, found a single Aedes aegypti mosquito in August 2025, the first time anyone has spotted this illness-spreading insect in the state, &lt;a href="https://idahonews.com/news/local/invasive-mosquito-species-detected-in-idaho-for-the-first-time" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:CBS2 News;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;CBS2 News&lt;/a&gt; reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What happened?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The Canyon County Mosquito Abatement District collected the specimen on Aug. 11 as part of standard tracking efforts. Scientists examined the insect's DNA on Sept. 17 and verified its identity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"This is the first known detection of Ae. aegypti in the State of Idaho," Jim Lunders, the district's director, said, per CBS2 News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;After the discovery, workers set up traps and monitoring equipment around the area. The search hasn't produced any more Aedes aegypti mosquitoes, but officials will keep checking the area into 2026.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;This mosquito type breeds in artificial water holders and targets humans as its primary food source.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why are invasive mosquitoes concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The arrival of invasive mosquito species &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/explore-critical-climate-issues/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:threatens local ecosystems;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;threatens local ecosystems&lt;/a&gt; by pushing out native insects that compete for the same resources. When non-native species move into new territory, they can disrupt food chains and spread diseases to which local populations have no resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Maintaining native species' safety helps balance natural systems. Native insects support local bird populations, preserve plant diversity, and help control pest numbers naturally. When invasive species take over, these benefits disappear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;For people, the Aedes aegypti mosquito poses direct health risks. According to the European Centre for Disease Prevention and Control, this species &lt;a href="https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/disease-vectors/facts/mosquito-factsheets/aedes-aegypti" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:carries diseases;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;carries diseases&lt;/a&gt; like dengue fever, Zika virus, and yellow fever. The mosquito bites during the day, making it harder to avoid than mosquitoes that only come out at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about invasive mosquitoes?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Local mosquito control teams are monitoring the situation closely. The Canyon County district has asked residents to check their properties for pooled water and drain it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;If you own a home, drain containers like plant saucers, decorative fountains, and rain-blocked drains. Tiny amounts of pooled water create places for reproduction. These insects deposit eggs in amounts no bigger than a bottle cap holds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Wear insect repellent when spending time outside during the day. Long sleeves and pants add another layer of defense. Check that screens on windows and doors fit snugly without damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Contact your local mosquito control office if you notice mosquitoes biting during daylight hours. &lt;a href="https://guide.thecooldown.com/actions/take-local-action/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Quick reports;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Quick reports&lt;/a&gt; allow authorities to map potential breeding zones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?rece7g7qwyRapsTHD" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxNR0h4dWsxR2hqbXphMFotcTJ2NVRRUmtlMVIxczVBQXM2QlZYX3RvU1U0b2NuQUVtMFJHNGN4dmJsNmFzcUFRNENQa1dfdGVBaThkVERhbGxnbnhMZXJYZENxSEdiTWlmelV3ZGtieVh5d01JX3BFd2ozSTFkcGppWkhVQnRZTExId09CTUROT2dIVjl6NFJXMg</guid></item><item><title>西雅图塔科马机场报告的麻疹暴露- KIRO 7 News Seattle</title><link>https://www.kiro7.com/news/local/measles-exposure-reported-sea-tac-airport/DF65HLH6QRD73FOMZU64XHCXKU/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;SEATAC, Wash.  — Public Health - Seattle &amp;amp; King County issued a public warning of a confirmed measles case from an adult at the Seattle-Tacoma International Airport this week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;The case was reported on Oct. 13. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;“If you are not immune to measles or don’t know your vaccination status, and were at the airport on October 13th, please visit our &lt;a href="https://kingcounty.gov/en/dept/dph/health-safety/disease-illness/measles#toc-Locations-of-potential-exposuresdelivery.com/CL0/https:*2F*2Fkingcounty.gov*2Fen*2Fdept*2Fdph*2Fhealth-safety*2Fdisease-illness*2Fmeasles*23toc-Locations-of-potential-exposures/1/01000199f439e1da-2f6ab628-6e90-48b4-8605-ca18dc697491-000000/3L4-Xiagez3suoGo7TEwCl3S2oN-An_E2UzLm23TOoI=427__;JSUlJSUlJSUl!!F8-Dj6fVkZI!duovKmwShLx1aYCYVQ_I1hHSnnxHssa6ZwRJ8g_4wYBIgLRuLG22DMGZQjgL1zbC6FVwqmwt7YS1T5R8PhEoTE4aGWj7FzsiJJQ$" target="_self" rel="" title="https://kingcounty.gov/en/dept/dph/health-safety/disease-illness/measles#toc-Locations-of-potential-exposuresdelivery.com/CL0/https:*2F*2Fkingcounty.gov*2Fen*2Fdept*2Fdph*2Fhealth-safety*2Fdisease-illness*2Fmeasles*23toc-Locations-of-potential-exposures/1/01000199f439e1da-2f6ab628-6e90-48b4-8605-ca18dc697491-000000/3L4-Xiagez3suoGo7TEwCl3S2oN-An_E2UzLm23TOoI=427__;JSUlJSUlJSUl!!F8-Dj6fVkZI!duovKmwShLx1aYCYVQ_I1hHSnnxHssa6ZwRJ8g_4wYBIgLRuLG22DMGZQjgL1zbC6FVwqmwt7YS1T5R8PhEoTE4aGWj7FzsiJJQ$"&gt;measles website&lt;/a&gt; for specific information about potential areas of exposure within the airport," the health department said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;This case is not connected to any previous local measles cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;It’s unclear if the infected person was a local or was traveling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;The infected person was at Seattle-Tacoma International Airport before being diagnosed with measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://kingcounty.gov/en/dept/dph/health-safety/disease-illness/measles#toc-Locations-of-potential-exposures" target="_self" rel="" title="https://kingcounty.gov/en/dept/dph/health-safety/disease-illness/measles#toc-Locations-of-potential-exposures"&gt;See where the person was in the airport here. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;The times include the estimated period when the individual was at the location and two hours after. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;The measles virus can remain in the air for up to two hours after someone infected with measles leaves the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;People with measles can spread the disease before they know they are infected and before any rash appears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;If you were at the locations during the times listed above and are not immune to measles, the most likely time you would become sick would be between October 20, 2025 and November 3, 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;About measles from the DOH&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;Measles is a highly contagious and potentially severe disease that causes fever, rash, cough, runny nose, and red, watery eyes. If one person has it, up to 9 out of 10 people nearby will become infected if they are not protected. It mainly spreads through the air after a person with measles coughs or sneezes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;Measles symptoms begin 7 to 21 days after exposure. Measles is contagious from about 4 days before the rash appears through 4 days after the rash appears. People can spread measles before they have the characteristic measles rash. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph"&gt;Measles is preventable with the safe and highly effective measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccine. Two doses of the MMR vaccine are about 97% effective at preventing measles and that protection is long lasting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gdrPeS body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KIRO 7 News Seattle</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:29:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxNRWlnMWdzRjhXZmVPZzZQWVpxNXZqbU54b2pPbzdqNC10NXhYQ3VSWlk4czRDYXBsc1ZaVnNQcmVaRDBSbmc3VWQyYjlKMnJWSngzT1J3U3EyMlZqaURvcnhNdzJJWGt5d3IyNGp3UEtoSnhRdHBRQ2tyb3FBZkU4SzdTeWd0cHo2RkhsZGl1ZWIxUElpTXNjZWwwUnJrMW5aQmJMS9IBuAFBVV95cUxQNUNVOWpIcWtxcGtrWmdKWjFURkZDTXFZWGwxVHRZcEozb19hRjlCSGdEbHJaVzNmb3VsTFJiQ1BHWFVqQWF4T19Fa3FiWVYzRVBVRkJOU29JTE15LUxCeVdFR2trUHVrX0JaQTVTNm1WbXQzbG85bUVQc1VucDNhdWdmM2RnTnAxR285SXJ1bU9Tb1QwMWNkS0toSzBuOVBXSHFIZVJfTlVnc3AzcnZWVEVzc1htNEg1</guid></item><item><title>阴道疾病治疗更新：男性也应接受治疗- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2025/10/vaginal-condition-treatment-update-men-should-get-treated-too/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
                      
                      
          &lt;p&gt;For some cases of bacterial vaginosis, treatment should include a package deal, doctors now say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The American College of Obstetricians &amp;amp; Gynecologists (ACOG) &lt;a href="https://www.acog.org/news/news-releases/2025/10/acog-recommends-concurrent-sexual-partner-treatment-recurrent-bacterial-vaginosis-first-time"&gt;updated its clinical guidance&lt;/a&gt; Friday to fit with &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/abs/10.1056/NEJMoa2405404"&gt;recent data&lt;/a&gt; indicating that treatment for recurring bacterial vaginosis (BV) in women is significantly more effective &lt;em&gt;if&lt;/em&gt; their male partners are also treated at the same time—with both an oral antibiotic and an antibiotic cream directly onto the potentially offending member.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Partner therapy offers us another avenue for hopefully preventing recurrence and helping people feel better faster,” Christopher Zahn, chief of clinical practice and health equity and quality at ACOG, said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BV is a common condition affecting nearly 30 percent of women worldwide. Still, it’s potentially stigmatizing and embarrassing, with symptoms including itching, burning, a concerning fishy smell, and vaginal discharge that can be green or gray. With symptoms like this, BV is often described as an infection—but it’s actually not. BV is an imbalance in the normal bacterial communities that inhabit the vagina—a situation called dysbiosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This imbalance can be especially difficult to correct; of the women who suffer with BV, up to 66 percent will end up having the condition recur after treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BV symptoms are “incredibly uncomfortable and disrupt people’s daily lives,” Zahn said, and that discomfort “becomes compounded by frustration when this condition comes back repeatedly.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Firm recommendation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Studies in recent years have started to expose the reasons behind recurrence. Though again, BV is an imbalance, it has the profile of a sexually transmitted infection, with links to new sexual partners and similar incubation periods. Going further, microbial communities of penises can silently harbor the bacterial species linked to BV, and penile microbial communities can be predictive of BV risk in partners.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                      &lt;p class="ars-interlude-container in-content-interlude mx-auto max-w-xl"&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:02:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxNUHlsUHFTWC1uYlNhQzVkNDBfU0xQT3NjOEhUbW9TdllZSkZEMFpfWGxFMmgwN2NTNlNmalpJd1hCLTlsSWVqNWhRMEptdk5ySXFNenRBZ040SF9Nb1p4R3E3b0sxdUkzeDkzNzcxYTZDM0JmRlU0d3JrRVM5TXZYY0dfbzlIUjFCdHlDVUtyZldma0x5T2lLTlNMUzk1WnhZLWJB</guid></item><item><title>Galleri测试： 50种癌症的血液测试结果令人兴奋- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c205g21n1zzo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Exciting results from blood test for 50 cancers &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-c4820dd1-0 cYDsPh"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-c4820dd1-11 bxdaHR"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-c4820dd1-5 iYeVyy"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-c4820dd1-7 dbQBRo"&gt;Fergus Walsh&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="undefined-role-location" class="sc-c4820dd1-8 evcqcz"&gt;Medical editor&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251015-170100-8e96f025b0-web-2.31.4-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f714/live/07276060-aba5-11f0-bba9-81f28efa2a1e.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f714/live/07276060-aba5-11f0-bba9-81f28efa2a1e.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f714/live/07276060-aba5-11f0-bba9-81f28efa2a1e.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f714/live/07276060-aba5-11f0-bba9-81f28efa2a1e.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f714/live/07276060-aba5-11f0-bba9-81f28efa2a1e.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f714/live/07276060-aba5-11f0-bba9-81f28efa2a1e.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f714/live/07276060-aba5-11f0-bba9-81f28efa2a1e.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f714/live/07276060-aba5-11f0-bba9-81f28efa2a1e.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A woman puts a piece of cotton wool onto her arm after giving blood. In the foreground of the picture, a healthcare professional holds two samples of blood in a gloved hand." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A blood test for more than 50 types of cancer could help speed up diagnosis according to a new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Results of a trial in north America show that the test was able to identify a wide range of cancers, of which three quarters don't have any form of screening programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;More than half the cancers were detected at an early stage, where they are easier to treat and potentially curable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The Galleri test, made by American pharmaceutical firm Grail, can detect fragments of cancerous DNA that have broken off a tumour and are circulating in the blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Impressive results&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The trial followed 25,000 adults from the US and Canada over a year.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Nearly one in a 100 of those tested had a positive result and in 62% of these cancer was later confirmed.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The test correctly ruled out cancer in over 99% of those who tested negative.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;When combined with breast, bowel and cervical screening it increased the number of cancers detected overall seven-fold.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Crucially, three quarters of cancers detected were for those which have no screening programme such as ovarian, liver, stomach bladder and pancreas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The blood test correctly identified the origin of the cancer in 9 out of 10 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;These impressive results suggest the blood test could eventually have a major role to play in diagnosing cancer earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Scientists not involved in the research say more evidence is needed to show whether the blood test reduces deaths from cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The topline results are to be released at the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.esmo.org/" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;European Society for Medical Oncology&lt;/a&gt; congress in Berlin, but the full details have yet to be published in a peer reviewed journal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Much will depend on the results of a three-year trial involving 140,000 NHS patients in England, which will be published next year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The NHS has previously said that if the results are successful, it would extend the tests to a further one million people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The lead researcher, Dr Nima Nabavizadeh, Associate Professor of Radiation Medicine at Oregon Health &amp;amp; Science University said the latest data show that the test could "fundamentally change our approach to cancer screening, helping to detect many types of cancer earlier, when the chance of successful treatment or even cure are the greatest".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But Clare Turnbull, Professor of Translational Cancer Genetics at The Institute of Cancer Research, London, said: "Data from randomised studies, with mortality as an endpoint, will be absolutely essential to establish whether seemingly earlier-stage detection by Galleri translates into benefits in mortality."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Sir Harpal Kumar, President of Biopharma at Grail, told the BBC: "We think these results are very compelling.  The opportunity in front of us is that we can find many more cancers - and many of the more aggressive cancers - at a much earlier stage when we have more effective and potentially curative treatments."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Naser Turabi of Cancer Research UK said: "Further research is needed to avoid overdiagnosing cancers that may not have caused harm. The UK National Screening Committee will play a critical role in reviewing the evidence and determining whether these tests should be adopted by the NHS."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:02:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1ObW5YNUtZT2JqRmh3WjZLLUZZcEdqOGxpQ3ZEZHM0X2owSjdER1R2Vkhwc1NrT3ozaTBpNDNPZ28zd042MGY2SXAzRUlaaF9oeElZZUVhTlVYQdIBX0FVX3lxTE8xdXNTNjNSeW1pbWJGRjdHV1NqWUVYV3BMTVZ4MWdFVERJdC1oeWp2dm1UQUdkSWNYR1ZhUTFWY2JwRFdlSXc4bW9yWTU4aGtmU2c5NGtoSWk1YlFGRDI4</guid></item><item><title>中世纪贝叶挂毯中的阴茎数量惊人-心理线条</title><link>https://www.mentalfloss.com/history/bayeux-tapestry-penis-tally</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content [&amp;amp;_p]:leading-[30px] [&amp;amp;_p]:md:leading-[28px] [&amp;amp;_li]:leading-[30px] [&amp;amp;_li]:md:leading-[28px]" q:key="QW_4"&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-0" class="mt-[18px] md:mt-0 mb-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9q"&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.mentalfloss.com/history/bayeux-tapestry-facts"&gt;Bayeux Tapestry&lt;/a&gt; is one of the most famous pieces of &lt;a href="https://www.mentalfloss.com/section/art"&gt;art&lt;/a&gt; in the world. The 950-year-old, 230-foot chronicle of the Norman Conquest and the Battle of Hastings was embroidered in the years following William the Conqueror’s invasion of England in 1066. It’s both an invaluable historical document and an impressively long-lasting textile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-1" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9t"&gt;Historians have been analyzing and discovering elements of its story for centuries. The idea that King Harold of England was killed by an arrow to the eye originated in the tapestry. A bright star that appeared in the sky a few months after Harold’s coronation—which many saw as a bad omen and portent of doom—also shows up in the tapestry; centuries later, astronomers realized it was Halley’s comet. (Edmund Halley himself wasn’t born until 1656.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-2" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9w"&gt;The Bayeux Tapestry also features a frequent motif: &lt;a href="https://www.mentalfloss.com/article/527234/12-facts-about-penis"&gt;penises&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-3" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9z"&gt;There are a lot more of them in this medieval work, created to decorate a church, than anyone might reasonably expect. And the exact number of them has proven to be a hot topic for debate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-testid="toc-0" class="toc text-primary mt-4 flex flex-col gap-y-2.5 ps-10 list-decimal [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary" q:id="a2"&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-5"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-5"&gt;“Anatomically Fulsome”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-15"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-15"&gt;Coded History&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-5" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="a5"&gt;“Anatomically Fulsome”&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure q:key="9m_2"&gt;&lt;div class="flex items-center gap-4 text-grey font-group-tiny m-3"&gt;&lt;figcaption q:id="af"&gt;The member in question is seen on the figure at center-bottom. | &lt;a href="https://www.wikidata.org/wiki/Q21631145" target="_blank"&gt;Bayeux Tapestry Museum&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Bayeux_Tapestry_Scene_07.png" target="_blank"&gt;Wikimedia Commons&lt;/a&gt; // Public Domain&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-7" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ai"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.history.ox.ac.uk/people/professor-george-garnett" target="_blank"&gt;George Garnett&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of medieval history at St. Hugh’s College, University of Oxford, announced in 2018 that he had tallied up the willies and had a &lt;a href="https://www.historyextra.com/period/medieval/bayeux-tapestry-penis-why-norman-conquest-battle-hastings-william-conqueror/" target="_blank"&gt;total of 93&lt;/a&gt;: Five belonging to people and a fairly staggering 88 to horses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="w-full border-0 my-4 bg-lightGrey h-1" q:key="Xt_0"&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-9" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="an"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You May Also Like:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-11" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="at"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Mental Floss as a&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=mentalfloss.com"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; preferred news source&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="w-full border-0 my-4 bg-lightGrey h-1" q:key="Xt_0"&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-13" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ay"&gt;But there might be one more—and that is the source of the controversy. A 94th penis may be hanging out of the bottom of a man’s tunic, according to Dr. Christopher Monk, a heritage consultant who goes by &lt;a href="https://www.themedievalmonk.com/" target="_blank"&gt;The Medieval Monk&lt;/a&gt;. “I am in no doubt that the appendage is a depiction of male genitalia—the missed penis, shall we say. The detail is surprisingly anatomically fulsome,” he &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/apr/25/bayeux-tapestry-historian-genitalia-dispute" target="_blank"&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; the HistoryExtra podcast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-14" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="b1"&gt;The figure in question is holding two clubs and running along the lower border of the tapestry with, possibly, his junk in plain sight. Garnett, countering Monk’s argument, insists it is a scabbard for a sword. It certainly appears ambiguous to the naked eye. If anything, it looks more like a holster for a pistol, and the end of it also seems to have something of a glow, like &lt;a href="https://www.mentalfloss.com/entertainment/movies/20-things-you-might-not-know-about-et-extra-terrestrial"&gt;E.T.’s finger&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.mentalfloss.com/holidays/christmas/12-very-shiny-facts-about-rudolph-red-nosed-reindeer"&gt;Rudolph’s nose&lt;/a&gt;, which academia has yet to address.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-15" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="b4"&gt;Coded History&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-16" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="b7"&gt;If it is a penis, what does it mean? The nuns who likely created the Bayeux Tapestry put in a huge amount of work, and the bishop who commissioned the piece, the half-brother of William the Conqueror, intended it to be a monumental record of William’s triumph. And male genitals are depicted in art to show power and virility. The largest one on show hangs from William the Conqueror’s horse, and the second-largest appears on the steed of King Harold, perhaps as a show of respect to the late ruler. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-17" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ba"&gt;“Medieval people were not crude, unsophisticated, dim-witted individuals. Quite the opposite,” Garnett said on the podcast. The tapestry’s designers and artisans were obviously educated and seem to be subverting the heroic story of the conquest with visual symbols and allusions, he said: “This is a serious, learned attempt to comment on the conquest, albeit in code.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-18" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="bd"&gt;The meaning of the specific soldier with the maybe-member is harder to pin down. He could be a symbol representing fearlessness or bravery, or the object might be a scabbard, or it could be a simple mistake in the embroidery.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Mental Floss</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 22:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTFAwdHNqTXAxY2JvWTJLTXRvdXFOc1BxdVA5TGtmTzRwdlhnYkRzVEpRN2loZjZ1TTRraTFCcjAzM21SazJVTHV1Zl9RUFdSRDhTY2g1MGFjeVd2ODNIT2RhM1BxcFZhNXE5elpwSmM0NUE</guid></item><item><title>疫情期间北州报告的更多麻疹病例- WYFF新闻4</title><link>https://www.wyff4.com/article/more-measles-cases-reported-upstate/69074676</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						The South Carolina Department of Public Health says there have been three new confirmed cases of measles in Spartanburg County since Tuesday, bringing the total number of cases in the state this year to 19 and the total number of cases in the current outbreak to 15.Health officials say all three cases were among close contacts to known cases who have been quarantining at home, and none were present in any school setting while contagious. Officials say since they were quarantining before they became infectious, no additional exposures have occurred with these new cases.Prisma Health says in order to proactively address the current measles outbreak in South Carolina, the hospital has implemented enhanced masking protocols across all emergency departments to help protect patients, visitors and staff.Masking upon entry: All individuals entering the Emergency Department are required to wear a mask until they have been evaluated at triage.Safety-first approach: These measures are designed to reduce the risk of transmission and ensure a safe environment for everyone during this outbreak.Symptom-based masking: Patients presenting with fever, rash or respiratory symptoms will be asked to continue masking while inside any Prisma Health facility.Parental precautions: Unvaccinated parents accompanying children with fever and rash may also be asked to wear a mask.Dr. Anna Cathryn Burch is a pediatric infectious disease physician and says if you have had two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella vaccine, then you have lifelong immunity. For those who are just getting a vaccine, Burch says it usually takes about two weeks to make antibodies against the measles virus. She also says it's the easiest virus to spread on the planet."The droplets within the virus that somebody might cough up when they're sick with the virus can stay in the air for up to two hours, even after the person who is infected with the measles has left the room," Burch said.  For previous coverage, click here.  
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;SPARTANBURG COUNTY, S.C. —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;The South Carolina Department of Public Health says there have been three new confirmed cases of measles in Spartanburg County since Tuesday, bringing the total number of cases in the state this year to 19 and the total number of cases in the &lt;a href="https://link.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com/ls/click?upn=u001.vYOEavOnxV2T5raErnqLQKw8Ykp82fVrNxeHSHnccISqLItMBQe-2FXDIlfgQjuq6TBLqAOjgyX2lt-2FsMMEwVAWBv6tS4EsDGIRp0QwfraA-2BnVoVg1tjljgYXbV9mCZvejw9JqO20LlO24X0Q-2B0AgrjiZTG-2Ba5AFhOfYZJkg0pR-2FwF-2FneQYcbTKDh1j4y42if06-2FNrFHJhjDG1KsKqEezDdwQXV6LGSqJQdMbkGA8yGQjPR7H8tz5-2F-2B9JrQOh6VrUvAVQo4W3AI5ePly5tzrdG2W65r3msRQXFkuXmiT-2BuISilX-2FsNyJDoNT04U-2B461XhOu0eOws8LuO-2BFwE4mMuaEC7iUBHgTXI6pIN4EN4AMj7GAxiM5Bfvdcmg4E6HS25GnMRR5hn7boE4exbabfTQyhI-2F5AGkUc14cKbycxfECJg8t4adpVG5XPdMQgyYZtaWx9jvDVA0V2XI5AstfqdRO790RNoCNhGepNUxGNpgP3CZEqKK3C4fISRsndJ-2BhTHiqeVikiUsN-2F2HH7vUlh8I2-2BsLNi-2FvFWWRa3-2BVk4Uk8XEKZeMT2NorOVxg-2B-2FOXCVjxTXrG927NAHy7RFBymeXtwLwSS5XOyznfa-2Fo4s5XCCB0PJ8f2FRM-2FAdzXLuI8NHA-2F3s41k3-2BXl0U9K-2FLgv1mWiD4I-2F-2FUd9x6vuZEyCldi053B9ljgw-2BVfn4tUr-2FeiztyPkoBVe7LwZVj6eXhN3CvLS-2FIxHdXVh6NyRo05UOWKsSYDGYjHwhyhdUihXGm0cJxIVJldkE-2BUp2WRKY49D8vtYlQ-3D-3D0Kk3_uG4mCQLB9tukhJpN14mws0ZhzFFBDUdd-2F-2FjqRD3zCPIc6VZItOYVEpPELxBBVI52kOOmJaIcGXtH7I9-2FhWWSgULgs1Xa9kbc-2BoQp-2FBjHt8H57hXzUR6KmHQBwnAC58jz7Sqom7rGh6TJUro-2F51lnuyYdlC1moMR4V0s5NbtAe7LcKHDdWy5oa3EdVHteWv7ifR7UuR7RnsDKEgCl9Ti8XyGw9Mw77ul1pQbSQeiu-2BQU3vOdkQtRjboXaQp80JxRX2QRBE7Ry34ck50HaL169ion9OaYDCSWn-2BYga45kL7iViWiimJ-2BDKhXKeZn80TAkFJf2TbzqvxavR880mxspWlYRpO54sialZFuLre-2BGYMeodNanvkxlCmTNrobaggGO-2B" rel="nofollow"&gt;current outbreak&lt;/a&gt; to 15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials say all three cases were among close contacts to known cases who have been quarantining at home, and none were present in any school setting while contagious. Officials say since they were quarantining before they became infectious, no additional exposures have occurred with these new cases.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Prisma Health says in order to proactively address the current measles outbreak in South Carolina, the hospital has implemented enhanced masking protocols across all emergency departments to help protect patients, visitors and staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Masking upon entry: All individuals entering the Emergency Department are required to wear a mask until they have been evaluated at triage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Safety-first approach: These measures are designed to reduce the risk of transmission and ensure a safe environment for everyone during this outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptom-based masking: Patients presenting with fever, rash or respiratory symptoms will be asked to continue masking while inside any Prisma Health facility.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;Parental precautions: Unvaccinated parents accompanying children with fever and rash may also be asked to wear a mask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Anna Cathryn Burch is a pediatric infectious disease physician and says if you have had two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella vaccine, then you have lifelong immunity. For those who are just getting a vaccine, Burch says it usually takes about two weeks to make antibodies against the measles virus. She also says it's the easiest virus to spread on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The droplets within the virus that somebody might cough up when they're sick with the virus can stay in the air for up to two hours, even after the person who is infected with the measles has left the room," Burch said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For previous coverage, &lt;a href="https://www.wyff4.com/article/south-carolina-measles-outbreak-2025-crunch-fitness/69032262" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WYFF News 4</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 21:43:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE9MQXNkdHk1cjFzV3JOLW1XRnRqX00wQUlxdG5oSzQxMVJWTDZIWENPQzMybUpHQWpSeGVfbzk5QWdnV0FhamJXQlFsang4WEhZaGRpbEdxRHlTYXplT0F0am92SGVNQjQ5TmpzQkM3LVc5UnY4Ym5rTjhPLVAtbEk</guid></item><item><title>日本流感病例每周激增50% - nhk.or.jp</title><link>https://www3.nhk.or.jp/nhkworld/en/news/20251018_03/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="p-article__body"&gt;

      
                    
                  &lt;p&gt;Health authorities in Japan are urging people to take precautions against influenza. They say cases nationwide have surged by about 50 percent in the space of a week.&lt;/p&gt;
        
                    
                  &lt;p&gt;The Japan Institute for Health Security and others say there were 9,074 cases reported by more than 3,000 medical institutions nationwide in the seven days through last Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;
        
                    
                  &lt;p&gt;The average number of patients per institution was 2.36, up 0.8 from a week earlier. The figure rose in 44 of the country's 47 prefectures.&lt;/p&gt;
        
                    
                  &lt;p&gt;The health ministry is calling on people to take precautions such as washing hands and wearing masks, and to consider getting vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>nhk.or.jp</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 21:28:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiYkFVX3lxTFBFVFM4WVFqVkVGZlhENkt1ckUwY2k5dmlndVcxUmlFZlN3d0Y4VFVBWDlUTUYzYUd1S0NqNEMySkRHd21teE9sbkxRUk90RG0tdlNlci1WOFFrMjVieU5uWTNB</guid></item><item><title>激烈的心理锻炼可能能够抵消衰老的影响，研究发现- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/10/17/nx-s1-5573076/intense-mental-exercise-may-be-able-to-offset-the-effects-of-aging-research-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;A new study shows that cognitive training can increase the levels of a key chemical messenger in the brain responsible for decision-making.&lt;/p&gt;   
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="transcript storytext" aria-label="Transcript"&gt;
    &lt;b class="icn-story-transcript-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;b class="icn-story-transcript"&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/b&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARY LOUISE KELLY, HOST: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Scientists have produced the first compelling evidence that mental exercise can cause biological changes in a human brain. NPR's Jon Hamilton reports on a new study showing that intensive cognitive training reversed a process associated with aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;JON HAMILTON, BYLINE: The internet is filled with brain-training programs that promise to improve thinking and memory. But Etienne de Villers-Sidani of McGill University in Canada says it's been hard to know whether they really work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ETIENNE DE VILLERS-SIDANI: They had a positive impact on some cognitive measures, but then the question was, how much is it changing the brain, and how is it changing the brain?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: So De Villers-Sidani and a team of researchers decided to see whether mental exercise could increase levels of a chemical messenger that's closely associated with cognitive performance. It's called acetylcholine. He says levels tend to fall starting in middle age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DE VILLERS-SIDANI: For every decade after the age of 40, 45, you get around 2.5% decline in this neurotransmitter in key brain areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: The decline is much faster in people with Alzheimer's disease. The researchers studied 92 healthy people who were at least 65 years old. De Villers-Sidani says during the 10-week study, half of the participants spent 30 minutes a day doing mental exercises. These came from a science-backed cognitive training program called Brain HQ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DE VILLERS-SIDANI: Which is really targeted at attention and speed of processing, and its characteristic is that it kind of pushes you to the limit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: By asking you to remember more and more in less and less time - other participants spent their time playing video games like Solitaire and Candy Crush. The researchers used a special kind of PET scan to detect changes in acetylcholine levels. De Villers-Sidani says they focused on the anterior cingulate cortex, a brain region that's important for making decisions and detecting errors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DE VILLERS-SIDANI: I was not sure we would find anything, to be honest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: But they did. In people who played video games, acetylcholine levels were unchanged. But De Villers-Sidani says in people who did cognitive training, there was a meaningful increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DE VILLERS-SIDANI: It was about 2.3%, which is not huge, but it's significant considering that you get a 2.5% decrease per decade, normally just with aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: So at least in this brain area, cognitive training appeared to turn back the clock by about 10 years. Acetylcholine levels also increased in other brain areas, including the hippocampus, which plays a key role in memory. The study, funded by the National Institutes of Health, appears in the journal JMIR Serious Games. Michael Hasselmo, a neuroscientist at Boston University, says he was impressed by the result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MICHAEL HASSELMO: It was compelling enough that I looked up the task myself and thought, maybe I need to be doing this task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: Hasselmo has spent much of his career studying acetylcholine, which is a chemical messenger that also modulates the behavior of neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HASSELMO: If you block the neuromodulator function in the brain with a drug such as scopolamine, a person can't even think. You basically go into a delirious state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: Low levels of acetylcholine are a hallmark of Alzheimer's and appear to contribute to the declines in memory and thinking. But Hasselmo says even small increases in this neurotransmitter can noticeably improve cognitive function. He says a cup of coffee boosts levels enough to improve attention and speed up reactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HASSELMO: Changing things by 2.5% could have a pretty profound and notable effect even on a subjective level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAMILTON: Hasselmo says the first Alzheimer's drugs reduce symptoms by increasing acetylcholine. Now, he says, it looks like hardcore brain training can offer a similar benefit. Jon Hamilton, NPR News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(SOUNDBITE OF MUSIC)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="disclaimer"&gt;Copyright © 2025 NPR.  All rights reserved.  Visit our website &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/about-npr/179876898/terms-of-use"&gt;terms of use&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/about-npr/179881519/rights-and-permissions-information"&gt;permissions&lt;/a&gt; pages at &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org"&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/a&gt; for further information.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="disclaimer"&gt;
        Accuracy and availability of NPR transcripts may vary. Transcript text may be revised to correct errors or match updates to audio. Audio on npr.org may be edited after its original broadcast or publication. The authoritative record of NPR’s programming is the audio record.
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 21:03:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxNYXVQR0ZPamU0bWc1UlpRNU0zX0MwbEIta0lobU1RYk5xelo5UHZqUHVGVTc1RVd2U09XQ1puYlV3MWhXdmQ3aXl1emhJTHh6RHZfb05KbG9EMUNwQUpUSjJZcTd3QlB4LUhlMnN5M2NuYjFETWJReVNCQTJlUnhhVlc2ZEVLeWV2a1FteHlCaTZxT3ozN0Z2QWlyWW1FbXg2SVlxQ2lJay1taEg3Mzg0bmpOaWdUU2hXQXpWSUstWkZxc0pt</guid></item><item><title>在阿拉巴马州丢弃的狂犬病疫苗包会伤害您的狗吗？宠物主人需要了解的信息- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/10/will-rabies-vaccine-packets-dropped-in-alabama-hurt-your-dog-what-pet-owners-need-to-know.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3Q4GD3Y3HBCF5I3GJKTFN2HIFU"&gt;As the U.S. Department of Agriculture continues to &lt;a href="https://www.al.com/news/2025/10/planes-helicopters-dropping-bait-packets-with-rabies-vaccine-for-raccoons-across-alabama.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.al.com/news/2025/10/planes-helicopters-dropping-bait-packets-with-rabies-vaccine-for-raccoons-across-alabama.html"&gt;distribute bait packets &lt;/a&gt;containing an oral rabies vaccine across Alabama, some pet owners are concerned about their furry friends eating the bait.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6ZWEZUD3NFHBPHTBTPGTJX2M5U"&gt;One woman in a Vestavia Hills Facebook group posted this week that her 11-month-old puppy found and chewed up over 20 of the packets when she had her outside in the morning. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YYFSLAXNIRAC7FZIDNJ3PCAXKQ"&gt;The owner said that the puppy began foaming at the mouth but was cleared by her vet after being examined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IBHV7HSG2NAYJGEMYH4XB6HV4M"&gt;State Public Health Veterinarian Dr. Dee Jones told AL.com Friday that while 20 is an unusually large amount for an animal to ingest, the packets are generally not harmful to pets if consumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ODTOU2CXENATDFE3AWGZ465VGA"&gt;“I’m not sure how the dog got 20 packets,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WMXJDWI52ZG3TM6TBLXOR73TL4"&gt;“But at some point, yeah, I mean that many packets could be some obstruction problem, you know, even though most of the time they vomit it back up.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZMOK5GW5DBHYZNDGZKRD3LOVRU"&gt;“But that would be an enormous number and that’s certainly not indicative of the normal calls we get,” he continued. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JQWBFWJZRJB63GBGVVAJNEQMAQ"&gt;“Like most of the time it’s two or three or less than five packets.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KOCU3O2MHZAZ3MBMBRIGLLIMJM"&gt;After more than a decade of taking calls for pets who have consumed the packets, Jones said this was the first report he had seen where a dog consumed more than 10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RBFHVPVTQRFNLJ5TPH26Y6VAUQ"&gt;But he asserted that it would likely take more than even 20 of the packets to cause any long-term effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4KVUEN7Y3JGLPHCPGUJ22B2HXY"&gt;“Certainly, there is an attractant on the vaccine on these sachet packets,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LX43IWATJVBLHDKRYTSASR2POI"&gt;“It is fish meal, which can cause some gastrointestinal issues. So, I think you should expect vomiting and diarrhea.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RJGNLPGZV5DA5BUVSVLCS67ATY"&gt;He added, “if it went on for more than 24 hours, I would very much consider taking the pet to the veterinarian to just be on the safe side.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="UFLZKZTYJRGKDBQ4HYYQEDUPDA"&gt;He said that the U.S. has been running these rabies bait drops for roughly 20 years across 17 states, and all research within that time has confirmed that the vaccine is not harmful to domestic pets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VEO4RAMFDBHG3DQRL6XD7ZITD4"&gt;He added that the packets do not cause rabies in animals, nor will they protect an unvaccinated pet against rabies. So, owners should keep their pet on its regular vaccine schedule even if it ingests one of the baits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:U3CI67NYMFHZNCGLQCN7ANB5NY" data-fusion-component="U3CI67NYMFHZNCGLQCN7ANB5NY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:U3CI67NYMFHZNCGLQCN7ANB5NY" data-fusion-component="U3CI67NYMFHZNCGLQCN7ANB5NY"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LDLBLVGFDZAU3C7FN2Z2QWLOIU"&gt;Jones said the state’s federal wildlife partners typically only drop baits in a specific area once a year, and the attractant dissolves over a short period of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="IP6YTDYDHBGHTFM6NKHXA7I5WU"&gt;So, he said pet owners should supervise their pets outside for the next few weeks if they’re worried about ingestion but added that the baits won’t last or be attractive to cats and dogs for very long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZDZCEWYPC5CV7KKVT5F37W6G4E"&gt;While the baits have also proven to be non-harmful to cats, Jones said he had never received a call for a cat ingesting one. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GPPT453BRVBBXJ4OAMG4VOSG64"&gt;If owners are concerned about their pet being exposed to the packets, Jones advised them to call the number listed on the bait and report it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WOWDP5PCSBHIFAT63LH5EMX2WE"&gt;“We are always interested in exposures,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BTJ2A5RTHNA7ZJJ4AZHKWG4FSY"&gt;“If there’s anything beyond the vomiting and diarrhea, we do report that back to wildlife services and onto the vaccine manufacturer and so forth.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 21:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxOQUN0VjEzc1pvc0hDM3pQekxwbmVMQXNqU1pDenlKLS1namlDeDJCMmc3LWdMalFZTXRXRWYtZ1hOM0JsZXdyWGVoMTFiYWlHOEsyUzVXNXNQUXdoR2xaaEVaODI4M0dkNG1WUVFCalZQOVBRSlhPenJieEJDeUcxT3ctblVKZFExRlRfbnE5cW1pQi1Oek45aEpqNkx4NVZwV1pldUR2VUtsajJuRnR3TE50c1k0WE5Cak93VzNHbUZFeWNW0gHYAUFVX3lxTE1xdnFocU5fZ19iSnNiTUpkb2Y2eUJHZmdfTjNRYllDYW92amtwLVllU2tBMGZPaHN2ejZaTE1DeEdoeUE4VkxUZHA5dEdNRnl4WnhYc2cxbUpMemdxczhhUWJoeDlOSVU1SmdIenJaTFZ2WUlZUVBEMER5ZFF3ejdjejJaNWpSUlVqX0hiQVk3anQ0X1BHVUIzektiVnpyMEtNcjZWWjNRUkhOSGhpUVd6RnhRV21XaDRnOHVpY0prUHNlVFctOFRFZWtqUDBDTTZBZVVJMGxBcw</guid></item><item><title>在专家揭示令人信服的健康益处后， “抗衰老”烹饪技巧迅速传播开来- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/anti-aging-cooking-trick-goes-201816537.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A growing body of research suggests that how you &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/food-drink/food/food-prep" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cook your food;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;cook your food&lt;/a&gt; — not just what you eat — may influence health and longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The same high-heat methods that give steak its smoky crust, roast chicken its crispy skin, french fries their golden coating and pastries their browned edges also trigger complex chemical reactions in food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When natural sugars react with proteins at high, dry heat, they create what's known as the Maillard reaction, the process responsible for rich flavors, aromas and deep caramel colors, according to multiple sources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/cocoa-extract-could-slow-aging-process-older-adults-promising-new-study-finds" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cocoa Extract Could Slow Aging Process In Older Adults, 'Promising' New Study Finds;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cocoa Extract Could Slow Aging Process In Older Adults, 'Promising' New Study Finds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the same reaction also produces potentially harmful compounds, including one known as advanced glycation end products (AGEs).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These compounds form naturally in the body and in &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:browned or charred foods.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;browned or charred foods.&lt;/a&gt; They've been shown in studies to be associated with tissue stiffness, inflammation and cellular dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://foxnews.onelink.me/xLDS/mvaj7wvj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Read On The Fox News App;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Read On The Fox News App&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;The smoky crust on a steak comes from a process that can form potentially harmful compounds at high heat.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eating more from very browned foods will add to the collective load of oxidative and inflammatory stress overall," said Ed McCormick, a New Jersey-based food science consultant and CEO of Cape Crystal Brands, which makes natural emulsifiers and thickeners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, AGEs can accumulate in the body and have been &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/geriatric-health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:linked to aging;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;linked to aging&lt;/a&gt;, heart disease and memory decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health/mediterranean-diet-paired-other-lifestyle-changes-slashes-diabetes-risk" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mediterranean Diet Paired With Other Lifestyle Changes Slashes Diabetes Risk;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mediterranean Diet Paired With Other Lifestyle Changes Slashes Diabetes Risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Higher AGE levels have also been associated with diabetes, cardiovascular disease, chronic kidney disease and neurodegenerative disorders &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/nervous-system-health/alzheimers" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:such as Alzheimer's;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;such as Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;, according to observational research from the German Institute of Human Nutrition Potsdam-Rehbruecke and other studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Burning or charring meat at high heat can also create chemicals linked to a &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/health" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:higher cancer risk,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;higher cancer risk,&lt;/a&gt; according to the National Cancer Institute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Simple marinades with lemon, vinegar or herbs can help cut harmful compounds in half.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marbled meats, skin-on poultry, bacon and cheesy toppings are especially prone to AGE formation, McCormick noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cooking methods or sauces that include added sugars — such as glazes or &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/food-drink/recipes/cuisines/bbq" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:barbecue sauce;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;barbecue sauce&lt;/a&gt; — can drive levels even higher, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/5-everyday-foods-drinks-damaging-long-term-health-nutrition-experts" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:5 Everyday Foods And Drinks Silently Damaging Your Long-term Health, Say Nutrition Experts;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5 Everyday Foods And Drinks Silently Damaging Your Long-term Health, Say Nutrition Experts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High-temperature cooking methods such as grilling, broiling, roasting, frying and searing can increase AGE content in food up to 100-fold compared to uncooked versions, according to a 2004 Mount Sinai study that measured AGE content under laboratory conditions. Animal-based foods tend to produce the highest levels, it found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But plenty of cooking methods avoid this process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Water-based cooking methods such as steaming, boiling, poaching and simmering can help preserve nutrients and limit AGE formation, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/health-benefits-of-water-based-cooking_l_68c97d92e4b0bf99dd253b74" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:HuffPost;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;HuffPost&lt;/a&gt; recently reported.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/lifestyle/quizzes" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Test Yourself With Our Latest Lifestyle Quiz&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some social media creators are &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/nutrition-and-fitness/diet-trends" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:promoting the trend,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;promoting the trend,&lt;/a&gt; often claiming benefits such as better hydration, improved cholesterol and anti-aging effects — though these claims haven't been independently verified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent Belgian study published in Cell Reports Medicine found that boiling and steaming the same ingredients under controlled conditions reduced AGE levels by about 50%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;High-heat cooking adds flavor and color, but low-heat methods may better protect nutrients and reduce harmful compounds.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mount Sinai researchers also found that marinating meat in lemon juice or vinegar for one hour before cooking can cut AGE formation roughly in half.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They recommend lower temperatures, &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/food-drink/food/cooking-basics" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:shorter cooking times;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;shorter cooking times&lt;/a&gt; and covered dishes for the best results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here For More Lifestyle Stories&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding antioxidant-rich herbs and spices such as rosemary, thyme, oregano and garlic can further reduce harmful high-heat byproducts in cooked meats and baked foods, according to multiple studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The realistic promise is to lower the inflammatory burden, not &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/health/healthy-living/longevity" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk='slk:reverse the clock,";elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas' class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;reverse the clock,"&lt;/a&gt; McCormick said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Water-based cooking methods like simmering, steaming and poaching may support healthy aging.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;He advises using gentler, moisture-based cooking methods that stay near 212 degrees Fahrenheit to help limit the Maillard reaction, which intensifies once temperatures climb above about 300 degrees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McCormick also recommends using slow cookers or pressure cookers, which add moisture and help prevent excessive browning. When grilling a main dish, he suggests pairing it with moisture-rich sides such as &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/category/food-drink/food/healthy-foods" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:steamed vegetables or braised greens;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;steamed vegetables or braised greens&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/newsletters?cmpid=fnfirstnl" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Click Here To Sign Up For Our Lifestyle Newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For flavor, he recommends leaning on aromatics, acids and umami — ingredients like miso, mushrooms, citrus or vinegar — and, if desired, finishing with a brief sear for texture and color.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Original article source:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.foxnews.com/food-drink/anti-aging-cooking-trick-goes-viral-experts-reveal-compelling-health-benefits" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:'Anti-aging' cooking trick goes viral after experts reveal compelling health benefits;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;'Anti-aging' cooking trick goes viral after experts reveal compelling health benefits&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 20:18:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE9hRnBjVjBTTFpTbUQ2OWhWM0o4bFVoanRCMWRhdzI1emVZOFE2UEF1bTNONFhrZ0hnR2hsd1hyUDEtdG5JMHo0Q3BjLWtMNGE2SUg1ejV1bWtrZ3ZDU016d0tydk1ER0NYdmxiaG5FQU9sQkVna0VYdGRzTXUtQQ</guid></item><item><title>断开连接的大脑可以有意识吗？ -神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/consciousness-epilepsy-sleep-29828/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;A new study reveals that sleep-like slow-wave brain activity can persist for years in surgically disconnected brain hemispheres of awake epilepsy patients. Using EEG recordings, researchers found that the isolated cortex exhibits patterns similar to deep sleep, anesthesia, or vegetative states—suggesting absent or reduced awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These waves, observed years after surgery, raise fundamental questions about whether such neural tissue can maintain any functional or conscious activity. The findings highlight both the resilience of cortical dynamics and the philosophical challenge of defining consciousness in disconnected brain systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Persistent Slow Waves:&lt;/strong&gt; EEG recordings showed lasting sleep-like slow-wave patterns in disconnected hemispheres years after surgery.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduced Awareness:&lt;/strong&gt; The patterns resembled brain activity seen in deep sleep or anesthesia, suggesting limited or absent consciousness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Philosophical Implications:&lt;/strong&gt; The results reignite debate about whether isolated brain tissue can sustain any form of subjective awareness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;PLOS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sleep-like slow-wave patterns persist for years in surgically disconnected neural tissue of awake epilepsy patients, according to a study published October 16&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; in the open-access journal &lt;em&gt;PLOS Biology &lt;/em&gt;by Marcello Massimini from Universita degli Studi di Milano, Italy, and colleagues. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presence of slow waves in the isolated hemisphere impairs consciousness, however, whether they serve any functional or plastic role, remains unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hemispherotomy is a surgical procedure used to treat severe cases of epilepsy in children. The goal of this procedure is to achieve maximal disconnection of the diseased neural tissue, potentially encompassing an entire hemisphere, from the rest of the brain to prevent the spread of seizures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disconnected cortex – the outer layer of neural tissue in the brain – is not surgically removed and has a preserved vascular supply. Because it is isolated from sensory and motor pathways, it cannot be evaluated behaviorally, leaving open the question of whether it retains internal states consistent with some form of awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More broadly, the activity patterns that large portions of the disconnected cortex can sustain in awake humans remain poorly understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To address these questions, Massimini and colleagues used electroencephalography (EEG) to measure activity in the isolated cortex during wakefulness before and up to three years after surgery in 10 pediatric patients, focusing on non-epileptic background activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following surgery, prominent slow waves appeared over the disconnected cortex. This is novel evidence that this pattern can last for months and years after complete cortical disconnection. The persistence of slow waves raises the question of whether they play any functional role or merely reflect a regression to a default mode of cortical activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pronounced broad-band EEG slowing resembled patterns observed in conditions such as deep non-rapid eye movement (NREM) sleep, general anesthesia, and the vegetative state. The findings indicate absent or reduced likelihood of dream-like experiences in the isolated cortex. Overall, the EEG evidence is compatible with a state of absent or reduced awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the authors, any inference about the presence or absence of consciousness, based solely on the brain’s physical properties such as prominent EEG slow waves, should be approached with caution, particularly in neural structures that are not behaviorally accessible. The slowing observed at the scalp level should be further characterized with intracranial recordings in cases in which clinical outcomes require postoperative invasive monitoring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michele A. Colombo says, “This is only the beginning of shedding light on the problem of consciousness in inaccessible systems. During the revision process, we were confronted with different perspectives, revealing the complexity of this problem.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marcello Massimini adds, “This pattern may provide clues to why sleep-like brain activity emerges in patients with brain lesions, and how it relates to their level of awareness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anil K. Seth adds, “This has been an exciting and deeply satisfying scientific journey. It started years ago with philosophical discussions about the possibility of ‘islands of awareness’ in completely isolated neural systems, to, now, this wonderful collaboration which has shed important experimental light on this clinically important issue.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tim Bayne finally states, “The study of consciousness involves many puzzling cases in which it is unclear what to say about the possibility of subjective experience. As a philosopher, it’s been deeply rewarding to explore a new frontier in consciousness science with this wonderful team of scientists and clinicians.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1760729149556"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What did researchers discover about disconnected brain hemispheres?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: They found that surgically isolated brain hemispheres can display persistent, sleep-like slow-wave activity for years after epilepsy surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1760729176070"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Does this mean the disconnected hemisphere is conscious?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: No evidence supports awareness; the EEG patterns resemble unconscious states such as sleep or anesthesia, but the question remains open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1760729192885"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Why is this study important?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;A: It deepens our understanding of brain dynamics after hemispherotomy and challenges scientists to reconsider what brain activity means for consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this consciousness research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#86e4efe9eae9e1fff6f4e3f5f5c6f6eae9f5a8e9f4e1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Claire Turner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://plos.org" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;PLOS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Claire Turner – PLOS&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pbio.3003060" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Hemispherotomy leads to persistent sleep-like slow waves in the isolated cortex of awake humans&lt;/a&gt;” by Marcello Massimini et al. &lt;em&gt;PLOS Biology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hemispherotomy leads to persistent sleep-like slow waves in the isolated cortex of awake humans&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hemispherotomy is a neurosurgical procedure for treating refractory epilepsy, which entails disconnecting a significant portion of the cortex, potentially encompassing an entire hemisphere, from its cortical and subcortical connections. While this intervention prevents the spread of seizures, it raises important questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the complete isolation from sensory-motor pathways, it remains unclear whether the disconnected cortex retains any form of inaccessible awareness. More broadly, the activity patterns that large portions of the deafferented cortex can sustain in awake humans remain poorly understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We address these questions by exploring for the first time the electroencephalographic (EEG) state of the isolated cortex during wakefulness before and after surgery in 10 pediatric patients, focusing on non-epileptic background activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Post-surgery, the isolated cortex exhibited prominent slow oscillations (&amp;lt;2 Hz) and a steeper broad-band spectral decay, reflecting a redistribution of power toward lower frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This broad-band EEG slowing resulted in a marked decrease of the spectral exponent, a validated consciousness marker, reaching values characteristic of deep anesthesia and the vegetative state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When compared with a reference pediatric sample across the sleep–wake cycle, the spectral exponent of the contralateral cortex aligned with wakefulness, whereas that of the isolated cortex was consistent with deep NREM sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings of prominent slow oscillations and broad-band slowing provisionally support inferences of absent or reduced awareness in the isolated cortex. Moreover, the persistence of unihemispheric sleep-like patterns years after surgery provides unique insights into the long-term electrophysiological effects of cortical disconnections in the human brain.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:42:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE14U0kzUE1KR1UtczBCQnppeE9DWVl3T2ZpRkVMN3Z3N0ZyQ3NUVGMzQkEyNS00cHpfenVlM2JiTlRtZmdRUmNoTHhVeDFtWkJ3TXVXQXV6X0pYdTNQVEdCdUhESE00eVk5bWNnY0FyYTNzUQ</guid></item><item><title>宾夕法尼亚州青少年死于细菌性脑膜炎：学区- ABC新闻-突发新闻、最新新闻和视频</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/US/pennsylvania-teen-dies-bacterial-meningitis-school-district/story?id=126613243</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;A Pennsylvania high school student died from bacterial meningitis, according to the local school district.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Ryan Duffy, 18, a senior at Neshaminy High School in Langhorne, contracted Streptococcus Pneumoniae Meningitis last week and was treated in the ICU before dying Tuesday, according to a letter sent to parents by the Neshaminy School District and obtained by ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Neshaminy High School in Langhorne, Pa.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Google Maps Street View&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It is with great sadness that we inform you of the death of a member of our school community, Ryan Duffy, who passed away earlier today, October 14, 2025&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;  Ryan's family has given us permission to share with you that he became suddenly ill late last week and was admitted to the ICU at the hospital," the letter read. "We hold the family in our thoughts and wish them strength in this difficult time. Ryan was diagnosed with Streptococcus Pneumoniae Meningitis."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Duffy's obituary detailed his love for his school and family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Ryan was an amazing young man who will be missed by everyone that he touched. He was a Senior at Neshaminy High School and was excited about going on the Senior Cruise, attending Prom, participating in his fourth gym night and, of course, graduation," &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.jamesobradley.com/obituary/ryan-duffy" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;his obituary reads.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Ryan loved every type of game – electronic and board games – and organized and played them with family and friends all the time," it adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The Neshaminy School District is using enhanced cleaning protocols at Neshaminy High School, but the school said that Duffy's form of meningitis is not typically contagious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It is important to note that this type of meningitis is not usually contagious in a school setting and does not typically spread through casual contact, such as being in the same classroom or cafeteria," the letter continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://nam04.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fpneumococcal%2Fabout%2Findex.html&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CWilliam.M.Mansell%40abc.com%7C8dea84137f034a815b0708de0dacc988%7C56b731a8a2ac4c32bf6b616810e913c6%7C1%7C0%7C638963232914451469%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=h%2FnUsKnCr9D9wDh8yo9WRVOIzli9%2BLJiDTO7f6jAdEg%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;u class=" "&gt;According to the CDC,&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; though this type of meningitis is spread through droplets that are released when you cough, sneeze, or talk, it is not highly contagious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Parents in the community are mourning Duff's death from the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"These old diseases that have been around for years are still affecting people," Eddie Maurer, a parent from Bensalem, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://6abc.com/post/neshaminy-high-school-student-dies-bacterial-meningitis/18020679/" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;told ABC News affiliate ABC 6.&lt;/a&gt; "It just doesn't make sense. It's hard to believe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Bacterial meningitis causes inflammation of the brain's protective lining and spinal cord and can lead to death in a few hours if not treated properly, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/meningitis/about/bacterial-meningitis.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;according to the CDC.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Symptoms include severe headaches, high fevers, excessive vomiting, stiff neck and confusion, according to the CDC, and the best way to inoculate yourself against the disease is through vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Most people recover from bacterial meningitis if managed properly," the CDC page on the infection says, but "those who recover can have permanent disabilities."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;It is not yet known how Duffy contracted the infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;There will be a moment of silence at a football game Friday evening to honor him, according to the Neshaminy School District.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News - Breaking News, Latest News and Videos</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 19:11:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQTXBIZmZGTERlS0pBa0prVlExZVV4UURzQmZaa21rcHYwR29vQVB3MEpSbk0xYXB5emFxN1Vfd3p5YjNpdW9EUmpFUmU0X3JtOXE4UV85ZHJFaEd5RnZhZndjdjRrMjFjN2tYNVVOOXpoeEJlN0FjX1lCaDcya05pNzJZdUJiYkZyZTdfSklmajlaNjNRbXZ5Q3Y0SmRNc3J2NTNFZmdJNNIBrAFBVV95cUxOZ1FBaXFGRTk2OWQwamJFWHliU2JsN2VKUkR2YV8yWkJnVzA3Z0c4czNFV2YtbzR1QkxOU0c1dXpmWFV3b3RFT0pJTFN1ZVBNbmdUVWszeTJvX09DX0wxMk1xMnpSU2ljQi1tNVpycXZZV2Z6M3ctREJIQ2NjdFVtdlhOS1VYS1hyZFozdnR1RWExTXRGWDg0LTBlZTZRMTZjRTVTdGNKVXZCclhf</guid></item><item><title>像大姐姐一样在金毛猎犬周围打猫咪- PetHelpful</title><link>https://pethelpful.com/pet-news/cat-bossing-around-golden-retriever-tiktok</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PetHelpful</author><pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 18:55:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5jdHdGN3ZUWXpYVDU2bUJJeUhKclpVMDBkZ1M2OGNoVzc3dWg5aW1FN19jTjlxb0lna1FFWW0ycDNNRDM4Q3JMUXVvUlBxUjRyeTZCaWU5SEFhUERtWURnRDdlclpXaERoOHVja3Y0RXRKbVpzbGpCcGtGNVk2OWc</guid></item></channel></rss>