<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>为什么同样的感冒病毒会让一些人比其他人更痛苦-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/19/common-cold-virus-variability/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XMMS2EXGLFB4RFDCWN4VPBJRWY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When the common cold rips through a household, it can leave a wildly uneven path of symptoms. The same  cold-causing rhinovirus that produces barely a sniffle in one person can cause a week of stuffy-nose suffering in the next and in others trigger coughing and trouble breathing that can send them to the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:31:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxOV3I4QjJLMjhodUd6cF9IRk1MdWhUR3RQWS1vYnMwR1p4VjQ0c09wRncwTkRySTZuZzRCaUtEU2oxNzlkTEYxLXhTR0lRd2lfdVplZEtzc2V5bzF4MXRPZjRhekhWeTNaZFFVUDZQcWNra2htWmkyODFETE1hNVZmYUsydnNtdw</guid></item><item><title>在压力奥运会中没有金牌–这里是如何开始休息的-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/wellness/2026/jan/19/how-to-start-resting</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-15rw6c2"&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;very new year – after the holiday glut of travel, parties, shopping and baked goods – there can be pressure to do and be more: more active, more productive, more creative, more thrifty. Maybe this will be the year I finally start meal planning or doing morning pages. New year, new me!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But what if the thing we needed more of was to do less? What if this was the year we finally learned to rest?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We all involuntarily participate in the stress Olympics, and are aware that the busiest person wins gold,” says Amelia Nagoski, co-author of &lt;a href="https://www.burnoutbook.net/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Burnout: The Secret to Unlocking the Stress Cycle&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In a culture that glamorizes hard work, sacrifice and the grind, rest is often seen as self-indulgent and lazy, Nagoski says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Not only does this attitude leave us worn out, it’s counterproductive. “Rest is what helps us function at our highest level of capacity,” says Dr &lt;a href="https://www.drdaltonsmith.com/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Saundra Dalton-Smith&lt;/a&gt;, a physician and &lt;a href="https://www.drdaltonsmith.com/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;author&lt;/a&gt; of Sacred Rest. Although many people are accustomed to pushing through feelings of tiredness, doing so generally results in a lower quality of work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;So why not start this year more energized and less depleted? Here’s how to start resting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-rest" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is rest?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Rest is anything that gives you more energy,” says Nagoski.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This doesn’t necessarily mean a cessation of activities, she adds: “Sometimes, it’s just doing different things.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Indeed, the most restorative rest is often more active than passive, argues Alex Soojung-Kim Pang, author of &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/money/2017/jan/22/alex-soojung-kim-pang-interview-rest-why-you-get-more-done-when-you-work-less" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Rest: Why You Get More Done When You Work Less&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“That’s not to say there’s anything wrong with sitting on the couch with a bag of salty snacks in one hand and the TV remote in another,” he says. “But the things that deliver the biggest restorative bang for your buck are things like going for a walk, spending time in nature or exercising.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-the-biggest-obstacles-to-rest" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the biggest obstacles to rest?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If a twisted scientist were to sit down and invent a society designed to de-legitimize rest, it would look a lot like ours, says Pang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We all come with decades of cultural programming that tells us that in order to succeed, we have to spend enormous amounts of time at work,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There is another, more personal obstacle: many people don’t know what kind of rest they need. As we’ll see below, there are many ways to catch a break.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="take-rest-seriously" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take rest seriously&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;So you’re finally open to throwing off the yoke of overwork. But how does one actually incorporate more rest into their lives? If you’ve read this far, that’s a good start. “If you’re asking this question, you’re taking rest seriously,” says Pang. “That’s the first thing you’ve got to do.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="look-at-how-you-work" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Look at how you work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If you are in a job that allows you to have some control over your schedule, Pang suggests combining periods of deep, focused work – 90 minutes to two hours – with breaks of about half an hour. The break could be running errands, going for a walk or having lunch – anything that’s not work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"index":19,"listId":6039,"identityName":"well-actually","description":"Practical advice, expert insights and answers to your questions about how to live a good life","name":"Well Actually","frequency":"Weekly","successDescription":"You are subscribed","theme":"lifestyle","idApiUrl":"https://idapi.theguardian.com","hideNewsletterSignupComponentForSubscribers":true}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;gu-island name="InteractiveBlockComponent" priority="critical" deferuntil="idle" props='{"url":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2023/10/archive-zip/giv-13425WMrLo2pc9VIk/","scriptUrl":"https://interactive.guim.co.uk/embed/iframe-wrapper/0.1/boot.js","alt":"Graphic with three lines of text that say, in bold, ‘Well Actually’, then ‘Read more on living a good life in a complex world,’ then a pinkish-lavender pill-shaped button with white letters that say ‘More from this section’","format":{"design":10,"display":2,"theme":4},"elementId":"220f3eea-5cec-4929-85b5-c137a93f8211","isMainMedia":false}'&gt;&lt;figure id="220f3eea-5cec-4929-85b5-c137a93f8211" class="element element-interactive element--inline element-inline dcr-w422y2" data-alt="Graphic with three lines of text that say, in bold, ‘Well Actually’, then ‘Read more on living a good life in a complex world,’ then a pinkish-lavender pill-shaped button with white letters that say ‘More from this section’" data-testid="interactive-element-Graphic%20with%20three%20lines%20of%20text%20that%20say,%20in%20bold,%20%E2%80%98Well%20Actually%E2%80%99,%20then%20%E2%80%98Read%20more%20on%20living%20a%20good%20life%20in%20a%20complex%20world,%E2%80%99%20then%20a%20pinkish-lavender%20pill-shaped%20button%20with%20white%20letters%20that%20say%20%E2%80%98More%20from%20this%20section%E2%80%99" data-spacefinder-role="inline"&gt;&lt;a data-name="placeholder" href="https://interactive.guim.co.uk/uploader/embed/2023/10/archive-zip/giv-13425WMrLo2pc9VIk/" class="dcr-1eupayo"&gt;Graphic with three lines of text that say, in bold, ‘Well Actually’, then ‘Read more on living a good life in a complex world,’ then a pinkish-lavender pill-shaped button with white letters that say ‘More from this section’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;If your job does not have a predictable schedule, Pang recommends better preserving nights and weekends. He points to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8775585/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; that &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/33424717/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;show&lt;/a&gt; that people who have better boundaries between work and non-work time are more likely to have longer, happier careers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="think-about-what-kind-of-rest-you-need" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Think about what kind of rest you need&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;When she worked in a hospital ICU, Dalton-Smith said she got eight hours of sleep a night, but still felt exhausted most days. Eventually, she realized the rest she needed was emotional, because the amount of energy required to appear calm in the face of horrible situations was leaving her depleted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Drawing on Dalton-Smith’s work, the &lt;a href="https://www.apa.org/topics/mental-health/seven-rest-types" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;American Psychological Association&lt;/a&gt; put together examples of how to practice the seven types of rest:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Physical rest: making sure you get enough sleep; taking naps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Mental rest: journaling; meditating; doing tasks that are not mentally taxing, like puzzles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Emotional rest: talking through feelings and experiences with a friend or therapist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Social rest: setting aside time alone to recharge; making sure you’re spending time with people who don’t leave you feeling drained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Sensory rest: spending time outdoors; taking breaks from screens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Creative rest: engaging in creative hobbies like drawing, reading or dancing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
 &lt;li class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;
  &lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Spiritual rest: connecting to a cause or tradition that feels meaningful to you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 id="enlist-others-for-help" class="dcr-n4qeq9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enlist others for help&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Perhaps the most important and effective way to incorporate more rest into your life is to recruit other people in your efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Nagoski explains that she and her twin sister, sex educator and researcher Emily Nagoski, were inspired to write Burnout together after Amelia ended up in an emergency room with stress-induced illness. “My sister drove two-and-a-half hours to the hospital and fed me a big stack of journal articles about rest and the importance of overcoming burnout,” Nagoski says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Experts agree this kind of care and support – reminding loved ones that their wellbeing is more important than work – is essential to pushing back against a culture of overwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“All these external pressures to sacrifice and give everything you have to give – it’s like a rushing river,” Nagoski says. “If you try to stand against it alone, you’re going to get washed away really fast. But if you surround yourself with people who care about your wellbeing as much as you care about theirs, you can all stand together, and that’s the only way to resist the river.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 17:06:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE81ZW5CRVU1ZUY3RjFHZU9aamJWZ2F1LVJlNGNvWE8ydllyRWJEVVdsd1J0SE1qVkczRmVlUlBZNmNXS2Y1azdUV2NZeGhDWU1XNk90ZjhsR0RHT05vRlFNNm5FVENxdTZVRnZKMExmNi1TaTBTSkhyeg</guid></item><item><title>科学家表示，积极的思考可以提高对疫苗的免疫反应</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2026/jan/19/positive-thinking-could-boost-immune-response-to-vaccines-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Positive thoughts may boost the immune system according to research that points to a connection between the mind and our body’s natural defences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists have found people who used positive thinking to boost activity in the brain’s reward system responded better to vaccination, with their immune systems producing more antibodies than others after having the shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The work does not mean being hopeful can rid people of disease, but hints at the potential for mental strategies to help the immune system fight infections and even attack tumours to keep them at bay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="3f14e39c-182a-44b2-af28-706e8050ea8b" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":3,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Placebos expert Kathryn T Hall: ‘The effect can rival painkillers like ibuprofen or even morphine’","elementId":"3f14e39c-182a-44b2-af28-706e8050ea8b","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/science/2022/oct/08/placebos-expert-kathryn-t-hall-effect-painkillers-interview"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0},"isInStarRatingVariant":false}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s the first demonstration in humans, in what seems to be a causal manner, that if you learn how to recruit your reward system in the brain, the effectiveness of immunisation increases,” said Talma Hendler, a professor of psychiatry and neuroscience at Tel Aviv University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Previous work has shown that positive expectations can benefit patients with some medical problems, as seen in &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/science/2022/oct/08/placebos-expert-kathryn-t-hall-effect-painkillers-interview" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the placebo effect&lt;/a&gt;. And, while animal studies suggest that activating the brain’s reward system can boost immune defences, the picture in humans has been less clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-025-04140-5" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;the study&lt;/a&gt;, healthy volunteers took part in brain training sessions in which they tried different mental strategies to boost activity in particular parts of the brain. They knew how well they were doing thanks to real-time feedback in the form of scores that rose in line with brain activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After four training sessions, the volunteers were given a hepatitis B vaccine. They then gave blood two and four weeks later, which researchers analysed for antibodies against hepatitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The scientists found that people who boosted activity in part of the brain’s reward system called the ventral tegmental area (VTA) had the strongest immune response to the vaccine. Those who boosted it most successfully did so through positive expectations, or imagining good things happening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The effect may prove useful in boosting patients’ immune systems, but larger trials are needed to show if there is any clear medical benefit. Dr Tamar Koren, a co-author, said the team was investigating whether other parts of the immune system were also affected, such as that responsible for inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:10,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:4156,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;morning-briefing&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Our morning email breaks down the key stories of the day, telling you what’s happening and why it matters&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;First Edition&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;We'll send you First Edition every weekday&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;news&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;hideNewsletterSignupComponentForSubscribers&amp;quot;:true}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The approach we tested is intended solely as a complementary tool that may enhance immune responsiveness to vaccination,” said Dr Nitzan Lubianiker, a senior author on the study. “It cannot, and is not meant to, replace vaccines or standard medical care.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Jonathan Kipnis, a professor of pathology and immunology at Washington University in St Louis, agreed. “It is probably too early to draw conclusions about the degree of clinical relevance,” he said. “If such effects were shown to matter clinically in a larger clinical trial, they would most likely complement the established treatments.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Jeremy Howick, a professor of empathic healthcare at the University of Leicester, said the effect was small and cautioned that sick patients in a clinic may respond differently, but he still saw positives. He said: “Given that it’s free for healthcare professionals to say things that can generate positive expectations, without exaggerating, like: ‘We’re going to do our best to take care of you,’ or: ‘I’ve seen this treatment work for people like you,’ this is a pretty robust signal suggesting we should do more of it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxQZzRCSVd5bURqUFVoZEZud01CRm9ORGtIOXd2RFlnTlE3TkRUZGJra01aajMtclR6TFdlNGlUVGs4dFJDWFdjWHVIeTgwRkRtR1BORlV5NXUzLWNkaExZZDlwUVJlb21XWlBWYmxGUU9VLWxvWFRnSGNZQ1M3b00yTXFyMldjQ1lpRUdWNHo1Q2RraEYxU1NLdHVJWXM0V3d5YVR2RmdWalFmWUVXTTRvdGd4aXZuYVpr</guid></item><item><title>尊敬的医生：随着现代医学的进步，为什么人们仍然死于肺炎？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2026/01/dear-doctor-with-all-the-advances-in-modern-medicine-why-are-people-still-dying-of-pneumonia.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6NAZ2HKIXRHUTKUQFNHLTEZ7RI"&gt;DEAR DR. ROACH: Why do people still die of pneumonia? With all the advances that we have seen in modern medicine, losing anyone to this ailment seems like such a waste. Is it a question of pneumonia being difficult to pin down because of the root cause, whether it’s bacterial, viral or fungal? Is it due to a delayed diagnosis and/or delayed treatment? Is it the development of drug-resistant pneumonia strains?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="G6DO64O7IZEETIVSNLVIEZJVLE"&gt;I just don’t get why people still die from pneumonia or “complications” from pneumonia. I’m a 73-year-old stroke and cancer survivor who is in relatively good health. How can I best avoid getting pneumonia myself? -- D.K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZHQ4WOS4NJAXTHTVBQROYRJRC4"&gt;ANSWER: Pneumonia is an infection of the lungs, sometimes called a “lower respiratory tract” infection to distinguish it from an “upper respiratory infection,” like bronchitis. The majority of pneumonias are bacterial or viral, but fungal pneumonia is a rare cause that is usually seen in hospitalized patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WPZZ456ZF5AVDH5MFI4ZJ6YTAY"&gt;You did a very good job of identifying some of the reasons that people still get very sick (and even die) of pneumonia, but an important additional reason is that there are some bacteria that grow very fast and are able to overwhelm the body’s immune system within days. It is often true that late medical attention allows the infection to progress to the point that we still lose patients from pneumonia, even with all that modern medicine can offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FRQ77WNBMVE3LIDLNEN7ZZ4ZAM"&gt;Another reason is that when people are very frail, either because they are very old or have other underlying health conditions, the body’s defenses are weak. Antibiotics can only do so much; doctors still rely on the body to do most of the work by getting rid of the infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6GWHUGX3H5EXLEZLMIAH2IW3OM"&gt;Drug resistance is a big problem, especially inside the hospital. I have seen cases where the bacteria are resistant to all the available antibiotics. There has been a race between the ingenuity of drug developers and bacterial evolution, and our ingenuity has been slowing down lately, with fewer new types of antibiotics being discovered and released. Avoiding unnecessary use of antibiotics helps reduce resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="J5CSI4GIWVGPRCX4K5ONWELSGQ"&gt;The easiest thing a person over 50 can do to avoid pneumonia is get the available vaccines, especially the pneumococcal vaccine (PCV20 or PCV21, called Prevnar). But for a person with health issues in their 70s, you should get the respiratory syncytial virus (RSV) and COVID-19 vaccines. Because influenza damages the lung’s ability to fight off infection, getting pneumonia after the flu is particularly dangerous, so the annual flu vaccine remains important.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YMSPJTDJ7ZARJLROCD3FIDEGS4"&gt;Smoking also damages the lung’s ability to fight off infections, so quitting smoking reduces pneumonia risk. Excess alcohol consumption also predisposes people to pneumonia, so men shouldn’t exceed 2 drinks at a time (1 for women).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XLABEISHJBDEJBPED6SKUDU5DY"&gt;Proper nutrition and good dental health are important for everyone. Diabetics should have their diabetes under good control. Chronic liver, lung, kidney and heart disease all predispose people to infections, so making sure that these are optimally managed reduces the risk further. Both cancer and its treatments can affect the immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="Z2LZKSK7ONB3BP4634ITNP2ZDI"&gt;People who are at risk for pneumonia should know the signs and seek medical care quickly if pneumonia is suspected. Although the classic symptoms of fever, cough, and shortness of breath can occur at any age, older people often have confusion and low fever. The heart rate is often raised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="J2A754WT2NB6TMBTZXN4U2XRAM"&gt;Some symptoms can be subtle: new falls, incontinence, and loss of energy. A significant, unexplained change in overall functioning might signify a serious infection like pneumonia and deserves an evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI" data-fusion-component="CKO4P4ZQQVGLJG2F6XF7ROMKAI"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KVF24K3KTZDAFKOSBLDSBTYRO4"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Dr. Roach regrets that he is unable to answer individual letters, but will incorporate them in the column whenever possible. Readers may email questions to &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu"&gt;&lt;i&gt;ToYourGoodHealth@med.cornell.edu&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; or send mail to 628 Virginia Dr., Orlando, FL 32803.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AUMP2LSRGJBWVFXGMISV4TEA2E"&gt;&lt;i&gt;(c) 2022 North America Syndicate Inc.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="U7EQ3GITRJHTXMWUUBM53ZNYZM"&gt;&lt;i&gt;All Rights Reserved&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1gFBVV95cUxQbS05MlViWUhxaWp1OENRRnlaX2Z0a2FYQjNaWDRMNEd3RWZYZElhZnVHZnQwbkJvNjdvQ3pULURHdENZZjc3MldpMmpsZDYxazNBZ2o2TGtLZ2VraXNQLXprTkYyaS1vOWltb1ZKdEl1V25ScFhOSVBfbnJMYWNSR253WkV2dzBxbG1WVHpibVZBV1hfZWs3SzlNcGpIYWt3cmNURm5ZUEw3THl3VUVncDNucHRtejNIYlNQUlloY2VTckF3aUx5MUhpaTM1Q0w0bmlCTkdR0gHqAUFVX3lxTE9tbVFJOUl0Tm9GWWpkOThEQ0Y5MGJEZlRLQ0tKQWJoT0JHalp1UUZYQVJOc3ZaT3JaZmlCdjhVQnNvZExVUjM3cVZzS3pMMmx2N3FEeDBoUnBZeG9La3BlOFZuU1BReWZyVlVXcGJjTENCb3owY1k3X0RtT0FlZHh1NkVvaWtTQ2k0N1RNNzloTTNlRDFFWjZKaU1lUEU2S0tuVVRuU2pXSDRGcnJuNVJNM1k0VS1yNzk3OGNNMzRRM1NTUnlYWlV3QUgxa2ZURFVTMDlOR1hXcUVvZTdSSkZXRk50S3hKUFExQQ</guid></item><item><title>喝完，咖啡爱好者-一项研究表明，咖啡可以延长您的寿命- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/drinking-coffee-may-add-2-years-to-your-life-11887769</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Research has indicated that drinking coffee may increase health span by two years.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Coffee contains antioxidants that may help protect against chronic conditions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stick with 2-3 cups/day of coffee and limit added sugar or artificial sweeteners.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Coffee sure has made the rounds regarding its health status. Many years ago, it was thought to be a noxious habit.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; More recently, however, evidence is mounting toward its beneficial effects on health. If you’re a coffee drinker, you know one benefit is that &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/why-does-coffee-make-you-poop-8558449" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;it gets things moving in the morning&lt;/a&gt; (buh-bye constipation!). But that’s just the tip of the coffee bean. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Drinking coffee &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8069479/is-coffee-good-for-you/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;has also been linked to&lt;/a&gt; a reduced risk of heart disease and Alzheimer’s disease, and it may help your thyroid work better. You’ve probably also noticed that a cup of joe can make you feel happier and more energetic. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But what about longevity? Could that coffee habit help you live longer? Researchers in Portugal wanted to know, too, so they did a large review of existing studies to see what research to date has shown; here's what they found.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-do-we-know-about-coffee-and-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Do We Know About Coffee and Health? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These researchers combed through studies and meta-analyses that had previously been published and compiled them into this one review. This was a very involved and thorough review—the researchers analyzed data from more than 50 studies done in the Americas, Europe and Asia. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; First, they discussed the aging process and how various bodily systems tend to deteriorate as we age, including how this affects the way we interact within our environment. For example, eyesight and hearing tend to be reduced as we age, which can influence how quickly we age if they’re not tended to. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; They went on to discuss how coffee contains over 2,000 potentially bioactive substances, many of which act like antioxidants. Of course, coffee also contains caffeine. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Researchers then went on to investigate what studies suggest coffee’s influence is on life span, as well as diseases, conditions and health habits that affect life span—like heart disease, cancer, stroke and respiratory diseases. They also looked at coffee’s impact on cognition, depression and sleep. Then to go even further, they examined evidence of coffee’s impact on the body at the cellular level. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-this-review-find"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Did This Review Find? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Ultimately there was one overarching finding. Regular coffee consumption seems to increase not just life span, but also health span (quality of life), by decreasing the incidence of the primary age-associated diseases that contribute to early death. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; They concluded that regularly drinking coffee was associated with preserving muscular, cardiovascular, mental and immune system functions. And it reduces the risk of diseases that commonly affect the elderly, including cardiovascular and respiratory diseases, stroke, some cancers, diabetes, dementia, major depression and frailty. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Regularly drinking coffee may even help you better adapt to stressful situations. And when you can gracefully handle stress—and nix some of your stressors—you reduce your disease risk and may live longer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Bringing all the evidence together, regular coffee drinkers may enjoy an extra two years of life. And it’s not just more years, but years with good health. Because really, what good is a longer life if you don’t also have a good quality of life?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Like most things, more is not necessarily better, and this is true with coffee. The researchers found that the sweet spot tends to be between 2 and 3 cups per day. &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8009784/how-much-caffeine-is-too-much/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;If you overdo it&lt;/a&gt;, you may experience anxiety, sleeplessness, jitteriness and racing heart rate—to name a few. And the health benefits don’t increase with more, and they may even diminish. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There are a few caveats to note. First, most research on coffee has been done on younger people, under age 65. So the researchers could not necessarily transfer some of the findings to older adults. For example, they couldn’t say with any level of certainty that regularly drinking coffee will reduce heart disease risk in healthy 80-year-olds since many of the studies were done on young and middle-aged adults. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Many of the studies were observational, so coffee intake was recorded by participants (like as part of a food diary). This means that researchers depended on participants being honest about their coffee intake—including the amount of coffee they drank and whether the coffee was black or contained cream, sugar, flavor shots, artificial sweeteners, etc.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These researchers note that tea and chocolate have similar bioactive components to coffee, so if you’re not a coffee drinker, don’t feel like you need to start a java habit just for the benefits. We’ve previously reported on other health habits that have also shown an association with living longer—like &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-to-increase-odds-of-living-longer-by-28-per-new-study-8661763" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;replacing sitting time with light physical activity&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Scientists aren’t yet sure what components in coffee are responsible for all these health benefits—the bioactive compounds or the caffeine. It might be a little bit of both, but more research is needed to figure that out. They’re also still trying to figure out through what mechanisms coffee benefits the body. One pathway they’re leaning toward is that &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7962690/does-coffee-cause-inflammation-what-a-dietitian-has-to-say/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;black coffee may reduce inflammation&lt;/a&gt;. And when we have lower inflammation, we have a lower risk of disease.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Until scientists figure it all out, know that your coffee habit might help you enjoy a longer life. Just skip the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7912339/the-best-and-worst-things-to-add-to-your-coffee-according-to-dietitians/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;flavor boosters&lt;/a&gt;—at least most of the time—since we know that too much &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7869775/what-happens-to-your-body-when-you-cut-out-sugar/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;added sugar&lt;/a&gt;, saturated fat and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/are-artificial-sweeteners-bad-for-you-8431961" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;artificial sweeteners&lt;/a&gt; can wreak havoc on health over time. Also, focus on other health habits known to reduce disease risk and potentially add years to your life. This includes eating a varied, balanced diet, engaging in regular physical activity, managing your stressors, getting plenty of quality sleep and spending time with loved ones.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNX0lyNGxGbFNiLS1ON3FFWlJhZDdPa2kySmNSZkNfMEh6UDRWUk5uTnQ4ZXljZENXbmRhTlZWQWRvbW11c2Q1QjEzclNfMGxQWk1nV1hCMUg5emNCVWJyOFBqRE9Ma2F6OWlSaG14RzhMLTZ3MW1KUFFrdHVEVkYxYWFoY1BhU3c</guid></item><item><title>如果您将面包存放在冰箱中，您将获得意想不到的健康益处- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/health-benefits-storing-bread-freezer_l_694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bread may be a simple kitchen staple, but did you know that how you store it can actually impact its health benefits?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe you store yours at room temperature in the pantry or toss it into the refrigerator (&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/storing-bread-refrigerator_n_5630f9dce4b0631799105e56" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="we beg you to stop doing that" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="5630f9dce4b0631799105e56" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;we beg you to stop doing that&lt;/a&gt;, because it only dries it out).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But if you store your bread in the freezer, you may be getting some additional benefits besides long-lasting storage — because freezing bread can also give a meaningful boost to your gut health, blood sugar and digestion, thanks to a natural change in the starches through a process called retrogradation, which forms resistant starch. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Irina Marwan via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Irina Marwan via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Cooling is key to retrogradation, and storage temperature influences how much resistant starch forms.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Science Behind Retrogradation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Starch is a type of carbohydrate found in foods like bread, potatoes and grains, and it absorbs moisture and gelatinizes when cooked with water. At a molecular level, starch is made up of two glucose polymers: amylose and amylopectin. In bread, for instance, registered dietitian &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mycrohnsandcolitisteam.com/writers/683f0deb46c7aa1e0f3349e2" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Avery Zenker" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mycrohnsandcolitisteam.com/writers/683f0deb46c7aa1e0f3349e2" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Avery Zenker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; explains that the heat of baking disrupts the hydrogen bonds that normally keep starch molecules tightly packed in a crystalline structure, allowing amylose and amylopectin to become easier for digestive enzymes to access.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As the bread cools after baking, those starches begin to shift again. “During retrogradation, some of the starch molecules realign and form new crystalline structures that are more difficult for the body to digest and absorb, hence their name, ‘resistant starch,’” Zenker said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The amount of resistant starch that forms in bread can &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6678428/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="range significantly" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6678428/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;range significantly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, depending on factors like the type of wheat, how the bread is processed, the ingredients used and the baking method. “Fresh-baked white bread contains about 0.5 to 1.7% resistant starch by weight. After cooling or freezing and thawing, this might increase to 1 to 3%” said Zenker, as a reference point.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Refrigerating And Freezing Bread Really Does to It&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cooling is key to retrogradation, and storage temperature influences how much resistant starch forms. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bread stored in the fridge actually &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28317765/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="develops more resistant starch" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/28317765/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;develops more resistant starch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; than bread at room temperature or frozen, but the trade-off is that it &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://agris.fao.org/search/en/providers/122535/records/65df4ed90f3e94b9e5d73a52" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="goes stale faster" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://agris.fao.org/search/en/providers/122535/records/65df4ed90f3e94b9e5d73a52" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;goes stale faster&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. While freezing may cause slower formation of resistant starch, it’s typically recommended to preserve its quality.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Storage affects the texture, too. “For refrigeration, the texture ends up being drier as the cooler temperature and circulation of the fridge dehydrates the product unless tightly sealed when cooled,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.chau-time.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Brian Chau" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.chau-time.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Brian Chau&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, principal food scientist at Chau Time. An easy fix is to add a bit of water when reheating, whether you’re toasting it or warming it in the oven or on the stovetop. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freezing, on the other hand, makes bread more rigid. “When thawing frozen foods, the cell structures rupture from the ice formation,” Chau said. “This can further rearrange the starch alignment to create a different and possibly more resistant structure of starches&lt;span&gt; in the food.” While freezing may alter the structure in this way, the total amount of resistant starch formed is generally higher in bread stored in the fridge. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Health Benefits Of Resistant Starch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;These temperature changes affect digestion — fresh bread produces a higher glycemic response than refrigerated or frozen. In fact, &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17426743/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="one study" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17426743/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;one study&lt;/a&gt; found that toasting bread after freezing and defrosting lowered glucose response even further, likely because the freeze–toast–cool cycle creates multiple heat-and-cool phases that favor resistant starch formation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Because resistant starch isn’t absorbed into the bloodstream, it has little effect on blood sugar, making it helpful for people with insulin resistance, including Type 2 diabetes. “Resistant starch slows the absorption of other carbohydrates into the blood,” Zenker explained. “Because less of the carbohydrates in the food are absorbed, the impact on blood sugar is more blunted, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;reducing blood glucose and insulin spikes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. This supports steady energy throughout the day, helps prevent sugar crashes and promotes feelings of fullness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Beyond impacting blood sugar, resistant starch supports gut health, as it reaches the colon intact, where it feeds gut bacteria. “[Gut bacteria] consume resistant starch and release beneficial compounds called short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs) like butyrate,” Zenker said. Butyrate fuels healthy colon cells, reduces inflammation, and even influences brain health via the gut–brain axis. SCFAs also help maintain the intestinal lining, lowering the risk of what’s commonly referred to as “leaky gut.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There’s also emerging evidence that resistant starch may aid feelings of fullness. “Indirectly, resistant starch may impact satiety and blood sugar by increasing GLP-1 production in the gut,” Zenker explained. SCFAs stimulate colon cells to produce GLP-1, a hormone that signals fullness to the brain. This is the same pathway targeted by popular GLP-1 medications such as Ozempic. While boosting GLP-1 naturally may help reduce hunger and cravings, Zenker notes that more research is needed to fully understand the impact of resistant starch on GLP-1 and satiety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Javier Zayas Photography via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Javier Zayas Photography via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Toasting your bread after freezing it can significantly lower glycemic responses.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This Starch Trick Works On More Than Just Bread&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Beyond bread, starchy foods like rice, pasta and potatoes also gain resistant starch when cooked and cooled. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=38395X987171&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;xcust=694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41387-022-00196-1" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="One study" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://go.skimresources.com/?id=38395X987171&amp;amp;xs=1&amp;amp;xcust=694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.nature.com%2Farticles%2Fs41387-022-00196-1" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;One study&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; found that cooled and reheated rice led to a 30% lower rise in blood glucose compared with freshly cooked rice. “It’s important to note that the benefit of resistant starch is small, so moderate portions still matter,” Zenker said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Like bread, storage plays a role in balancing resistant starch formation and texture. “I typically recommend storing foods like potatoes in the fridge for up to three days because freezing can make them unpleasant,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://gutfriendlynutrition.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Sarah Glinski" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://gutfriendlynutrition.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sarah Glinski&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a Canadian registered dietitian specializing in gut health. For rice and pasta, she advises choosing storage based on when you’ll eat them: refrigeration works for up to three days, while freezing is best for longer-term storage — up to three months — before texture starts to suffer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Meaningful Is The Difference?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17426743/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="small 2008 study" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="694962f4e4b099a75cbd9114" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17426743/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;&lt;span&gt;small 2008 study&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; looked at how freezing and toasting white bread affects blood sugar. The study found that compared with fresh, homemade white bread, bread that had been frozen and then thawed (or toasted after freezing and thawing) triggered significantly lower glycemic responses, by up to 39%. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“For people with diabetes or prediabetes, this could help with blood sugar management,” Glinski said. “Many people with these conditions have been advised to avoid carbohydrates, but this is usually unnecessary. Eating foods high in fiber, like resistant starch, can be a way to enjoy carbohydrates without them impacting your blood sugars as much.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How To Pick Bread That Supports Your Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Beyond storage, the key to healthy bread is what’s inside the loaf and how much you eat. “I typically recommend people choose whole wheat bread or sprouted grain bread, which is naturally higher in fiber,” Glinski said. Breads with seeds like chia, flax and sunflower are also good sources, aiming for at least 3 grams per slice. “For healthy blood sugar levels, choose bread with less than 3 grams of sugar per slice, and check the ingredient list for cane sugar, honey, molasses or brown rice syrup,” Glinski added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;For those who need to limit fermentable carbs (FODMAPs), sourdough can be a good option, as it generally has lower FODMAP content and may be gentler on digestion. Ultimately, portion size and what’s in your bread still play a big role in making each slice healthier.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPQlhZdTRNOVNRTXBJZ3huVkpFa21jT2RmRWpmbC1rN0FpUUthaVZyT1dXNGxpOVlzdGVKTkYyY1BLVk5uS3ZLV0N3LTEtRUJCOWtQWkY3NU9ZX2xQRDlBb0FIRnlheWRZcTA5a0xEeXhqVlBscmpyaENKTVpfWW9JSmhYVjhDNXBmMVFrSTNfeGRnRWFaTzJhRkRGRdIBoAFBVV95cUxNeFVvcEE4LWhQTjFSWEJla0ZMel9MUGxXNUdCS3VXaGd1NlZSQXpMaGRlZTNNcXc2MDdoWTNrRnFIVEExRGFiME5SaXJ2TUJYNlFCbThUNGc2MTZfRURiVkpUajhjYkluNEhQSWg3V0NOekFiRk5hN0oyU3c1ZEJleWZBSHNDTjgxQzFCSzliOVFWM0xDMHQ1bDRkNC1OVHhl</guid></item><item><title>1个被低估的技能父母需要开始教他们的儿子- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/boys-anger-goog_l_696a79c0e4b084474f1283d6</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I found out I was having my first boy five years ago, I was elated and excited ... and then worried about anger. There had recently been yet another school shooting, followed by yet another rash of headlines about boys, guns and rage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;I understand the roots of that kind of violence are deeply complex, and that in my own life I am surrounded by loving, empathetic men. But I was also a hormonal soon-to-be first-time mom (who, in hindsight, was probably grappling with a touch of perinatal anxiety). I worried that I would raise an angry young man. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was not alone. Concerns about boys and anger abound, as comedian and writer Michael Ian Black captured in his viral 2018 New York Times opinion piece “&lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/02/21/opinion/boys-violence-shootings-guns.html" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="The Boys Are Not All Right" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696a79c0e4b084474f1283d6" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nytimes.com/2018/02/21/opinion/boys-violence-shootings-guns.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;The Boys Are Not All Right&lt;/a&gt;.” “The man who feels lost but wishes to preserve his fully masculine self has only two choices: withdrawal or rage,” he wrote. The story has more than 2,100 comments. Clearly it struck a chord.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that I know my boys and have spent years watching their beautiful, complex little personalities unfold, those fears I held during my pregnancy seem distant and reductive. &lt;em&gt;Of course&lt;/em&gt; they do not inherently struggle with anger simply because they are boys. And yet they do lash out — sometimes in frustration, sometimes when I ask them to do something they don’t want to. What I want is to help them navigate that anger, so they can experience the feeling, but not be overwhelmed by it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Parents need to give their children the tools to understand their feelings, and it needs to be developed just like developing understanding of other complicated and abstract concepts,” said Steven Meyers, a professor of psychology at Roosevelt University in Chicago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, first and foremost, it helps to understand the basics of what anger is: basically, a response to a perceived threat. The body releases adrenaline (the hormone that plays a key role in the fight-or-flight response) and the heart rate and blood pressure go up. It is absolutely fine — and sometimes really positive — to feel angry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s when that anger is not managed in a healthy way that it can become problematic. So here are some tips for parents to keep in mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2 class="h3-style"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First, understand that there &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; be differences in how boys and girls experience and express anger.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, there is so much nuance when it comes to individuals, emotions — and how they express those emotions. It is not fair, nor accurate, to say that all boys experience anger one way, while all girls experience it another. And research shows it is a myth that boys and men experience anger more than girls and women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet experts say there can be big broad-strokes distinctions parents might want to at least have in mind as they help guide their children through all of this. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Psychologists have a saying that boys externalize and girls internalize. This means that boys are more likely to take their anger and distress and direct it outward, where it can become verbal or physical aggression. On the other hand, girls are more likely to direct their anger and frustrations inward towards themselves, so it can become self-blame or even depression,” Meyers said. “Naturally, this is a simplification, but there are gender differences in the rates of these different disorders between girls and boys, as well as between women and men.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2 class="h3-style"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Help your child learn how to label his feelings.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The first step to stress and anger management is to help your child identify what’s going on, and to empathize with it,” said Kelsey Torgerson Dunn, a social worker who runs a private counseling practice in St. Louis that focuses on anxiety counseling and anger management for children and teens. Young kids don’t always recognize what they’re experiencing. Heck, adults struggle to identify their root feelings a lot of the time. But if you don’t understand what the problem is — in this case, feelings of anger or frustration that might lead a child to act out — you can’t solve the problem. Labeling the feeling is so important. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a younger kid, that might mean explicitly describing their emotions — like, “your body looks like it’s feeling frustrated,” Dunn offered by way of example, or “it seems like you are feeling angry, because I told you ‘no.’” Don’t worry about being presumptuous or getting it wrong. Your kid might turn around and tell you that they’re not actually feeling angry, they’re feeling XYZ thing — and that’s totally fine. You’ve prompted them to identify what is going on internally. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older kids and teens probably won’t respond all that well to those kinds of prompts, but they might still need some help identifying their feelings in the moment. So for them, labeling might sound something more like, “If I were in this situation, I’d probably feel pretty mad. Walk me through what’s going on for you,” Dunn recommended. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“One sentence that I often use when working with boys is that ‘you can feel whatever you want to feel, but you can’t always do whatever you want to do.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__attribution caption-cli"&gt;- Steven Meyers, psychologist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2 class="h3-style"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be soothing.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although parents might react to a child’s anger or outburst by walking away (and strategic ignoring &lt;a href="https://childmind.org/article/managing-problem-behavior-at-home/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="can certainly be one way" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696a79c0e4b084474f1283d6" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://childmind.org/article/managing-problem-behavior-at-home/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;can certainly be one way&lt;/a&gt; to help diffuse tantrums), experts say there is a strong argument to be made for soothing children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Anger can overwhelm young children. They do not necessarily have the ability to calm themselves down so that they become more reasonable,” Meyers said. “There are many ways to soothe and comfort an angry young child, but it may require a shift in the parent’s mindset or focus in the moment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Be patient and calm. Make it clear that you’re not looking to just stifle or deny their anger in the moment — which is especially important with boys, who have historically been taught to bottle up their emotions. The goal is ultimately to help your kids get to a point where they’re able to self-soothe, perhaps by taking deep breaths, walking away or taking a few moments to themselves to calm down. By acting calm and soothing in the moment yourself, you’re modeling compassion for oneself and for others, which is a very good thing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2 class="h3-style"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Provide consequences.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t confuse being soothing with being permissive. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Consequences are needed when anger spills over into aggression, especially as boys get older,” Meyers said. “One sentence that I often use when working with boys is that ‘you can feel whatever you want to feel, but you can’t always do whatever you want to do.’” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consequences can take many different forms, depending on how old your child is, what the specific circumstances are, and what his personality responds to — and, of course, those things can change by the day. But things like brief time-outs or loss of privileges can be powerful tools in teaching boys that there is a difference between emotions and behaviors. Spend a bit of time thinking about the types of consequences you’re comfortable with, so that you’re not blurting out random threats after your child has expressed their anger in a way you’re not comfortable with. Certain strategies work better for some children than others, so you might need to recalibrate and try out a few things. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember, what you’re trying to teach is that it is absolutely OK to feel angry and to express that you are feeling angry. It is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; OK to act out on that anger in an aggressive way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2 class="h3-style"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you’re worried about your child’s anger, ask for help.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Psychologists use the standards of frequency, duration, intensity, and age-appropriateness when they assess whether a behavior is a symptom of a disorder,” said Meyers, so those are criteria parents who are concerned about their son’s anger or aggression should pay attention to. There aren’t hard and fast rules about what’s typical and what’s not, but if your son seems to be struggling with anger on a daily basis, that might be a sign something more serious is going on, Meyers said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dunn said it’s also helpful to consider whether certain behaviors — like aggression — are happening across settings, such as if your child is having similar problems at home &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; at school. That kind of consistency signals that it is less about the particular situation in which they find themselves, and more about their general response to feelings of anger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re concerned, experts say talking to your child’s pediatrician is a good place to start, and checking in with his teachers can also be helpful. It might take some digging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Parents don’t always know what is going on underneath their sons’ anger. There might be stress, or anxiety, or depression,” Dunn said. “It’s important to find out what it might be.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5JbHRaaGlQRm9ocWR1Mkp6M2U0c1FueEFlVUJmRGpuUTRHYmJldElTX05OUjl6LWhWVTJOd1RGUmRDNjhON05BUXkzVm5SMzBtYUNJNGxOaVYwN18tY3pwSlVVdmEzRE1HSmNjQjNvYjZ5NVNUZU5McVpUNzZlQdIBgwFBVV95cUxQaHVYRjJuQjNiVENPWWlFcWtNSmRZdlM2RDdsVXFYU3RnUmYyLUVON0dNMEc4cjVWVFBEQ0ZMY3FlMHU4b2Y4cVZHSUhHcEdwYUpSQ2J1Q2NILUJOZXVMWTJZd3NyZTgtMFhLbEpOTHl1X1lMRFZNUGZUVXRSMDFCMEREQQ</guid></item><item><title>美国是否已消除麻疹？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/19/well/year-anniversary-measles-outbreak-elimination-status.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 10:00:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNZjFVRlhtTlgxNF95SmF4cWdicW9RTFRFR0tBVWZLdDNjMnN3MUxJeHI5SnJQM2VFNG1ZaTBCUUs3RXd1N2tRZVIxd2xwSmd3Qkg2QXlPb2NjT1Q2Z19zdzR5OGNJcFFXa0RKX21GcUZpTFlrXzRXYkVobmo4ZUtwbHBleFN2NlJBSjZnck5meDcxMG9UUjBvaGxEdkxLUQ</guid></item><item><title>AIIMS训练有素的胃肠病学家回答了关于吃鸡蛋的11个问题：鸡蛋有利于减肥还是有利于腹部脂肪？ |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiims-trained-gastroenterologist-answers-11-questions-about-eating-eggs-how-many-eggs-should-you-eat-daily-truth-101768812881398.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt;&lt;p class="content"&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Eggs are not only one of the most popular sources of protein, but also one of the most versatile when it comes to methods of cooking and consumption.&lt;/span&gt; It can fit into any meal, and its compact size and hassle-free experience of eating make it easy to consume multiple servings a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="artImage leadImage"&gt;&lt;figcaption class=""&gt;Eggs are one of the best proteins to have for breakfast, shares Dr Sethi. (Unsplash)&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;Also Read | &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiimstrained-gastroenterologist-answers-12-questions-about-drinking-coffee-effects-on-health-how-much-to-drink-101768542379958.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="AIIMS-trained gastroenterologist answers 12 questions about drinking coffee: Effects on health, how much to drink…"&gt;AIIMS-trained gastroenterologist answers 12 questions about drinking coffee: Effects on health, how much to drink…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;Naturally, questions are bound to arise on how the food affects our health, and whether we are taking it in the most effective manner. Taking to Instagram on January 19, Dr Saurabh Sethi, California-based gastroenterologist trained in AIIMS, Harvard, and Stanford Universities, sought to answer the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Are eggs good for breakfast?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;The answer is a resounding yes, as Dr Sethi considers eggs to be one of the best proteins to have for the first meal of the day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Are eggs good for fatty liver?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eggs are good for &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/canadian-doctor-warns-south-asians-with-fatty-liver-are-making-these-3-mistakes-daily-late-night-eating-endless-cardio-101768807885808.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="fatty liver"&gt;fatty liver&lt;/a&gt;, but only in moderation. Protein in eggs helps reduce sugar intake and supports liver health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Can eggs raise cholesterol?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/can-egg-yolk-cause-a-heart-attack-delhi-based-gastroenterologist-busts-the-myth-101765184107011.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="egg yolk"&gt;egg yolk&lt;/a&gt; is commonly associated with high cholesterol. However, Dr Sethi assures us that for most people, the consumption of eggs does not raise cholesterol levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Are eggs good for losing weight or belly fat?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eating eggs is good for losing weight or &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/soft-vs-hard-belly-fat-fortis-gastroenterologist-explains-which-affects-hormones-insulin-resistance-liver-heart-101768705293470.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="belly fat"&gt;belly fat&lt;/a&gt;, claimed Dr Sethi, stating that the protein in eggs improves fullness and reduces cravings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Can eggs cause blood sugar spikes?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eggs have almost zero carbohydrates and therefore cannot cause the blood sugar level to spike, explained Dr Sethi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. Is it safe to have eggs with coffee or green tea?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eggs can be safely consumed with coffee or green tea, as no harmful interaction has been noted, shared Dr Sethi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7. Can eggs cause bloating?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eggs rarely cause bloating. However, some people are sensitive, and therefore it is better to trust our own gut in this regard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;8. Is it safe to eat raw eggs?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consumption of raw eggs is not recommended as it has the risk of salmonella infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;9. Are raw eggs better absorbed by the body?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sethi debunked the misconception, stating that cooked eggs have better protein absorption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;10. What is the best way to eat eggs?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The healthiest preparations of eggs, according to Dr Sethi, include boiled, poached, scrambled and omelette.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;11. How many eggs can we safely eat in a day?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While there is no magic number, most people do well with one to two whole eggs per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 09:08:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgJBVV95cUxQaVBxUUhMNGxBOFdRMm8tOXdNOFBWbDdyNVlMd3p3UThPZllHejNYdDlBcGVtcVpFc2szREdLNV92YWktWktkQnVsVGh3eTFVdWJucXh4LUdCT3BCTDVRY0FtOFlWcldDc0FXRXpZSU9YbEJKNWZkbUdyQjRGdVo0V0dnSEh0c2RqNVcwc1c0RjlzOHgwZFdabEdXTHg5ZHdtTXJjUzJSUVVaOXpObnlidl9BYmpZQlVVcmZFNXN2dkxESDBrXzlHNkhCaGhZa0FKTHdURW9WWjhzQzg2bldTTFg2U3ZNdEpDdzRaZmUzQnVLc05jY0hVaTd5Um1lTUYxczU4MHN3Zm9sNkg4YXfSAZMCQVVfeXFMUEVaNkdfVnpjeVpUNFpOWFppQkRZZUJlUzFWSV9fWUc0S3pKZEYtXzh1M2JOMFlDWXJRYzJIMW44WUVUVy1yRUl0TDMtUUJlYTJsVnBWdmxmTnpDTVcxZUs5WHp1bG5PNmlucmd6c2J6cmRLd19taWdRaWpKSnI5THNBblVDUEFQaE5GTXhENlJWM0NORl9XR3dGWVNQTGwyZkp0TkVlYkhYZEY0UWlYdjc0VFZHRk82NVpqbVRhZmxyN0hxVjZuaG1rR0ZWdm9EY0M2Vl9TYjdPV1V4WW1lRHV2aXlYMG9aTmRqUTJSOXA5UTVwN0xObXUyOV9rVHpqV3l4aWx3TXRLVmNBU3VzWjVOdGM</guid></item><item><title>Abergele青少年被诊断出对寒冷温度罕见过敏- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c4grjn8e147o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;I'm allergic to cold - anything below 12C and I break out in hives&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a5e1/live/14e532c0-f300-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a5e1/live/14e532c0-f300-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a5e1/live/14e532c0-f300-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a5e1/live/14e532c0-f300-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a5e1/live/14e532c0-f300-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a5e1/live/14e532c0-f300-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a5e1/live/14e532c0-f300-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a5e1/live/14e532c0-f300-11f0-b5f7-49f0357294ff.png.webp" loading="eager" alt="PA Media Amber's face up close with hives all over her cheek. She is wearing a round neck grey top and dark rimmed glasses" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Cold temperatures cause 16-year-old Amber to break out in red, itchy hives&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I just want to be able to do normal things and have a normal life and not have to worry."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A 16-year-old girl from north Wales says she is "always scared" of having an allergic reaction after being diagnosed with a rare condition which sees her experience hives and swelling triggered by cold temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Amber Woodward said it has happened since 2022, whenever the temperature falls below 12C (53F).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She has &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.anaphylaxis.org.uk/understanding-cold-induced-urticaria/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;cold urticaria&lt;/a&gt;, a rare allergy which can cause her to have a reaction to as little as a gust of cool wind in summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The A-level student hopes new antihistamine injections every four weeks will improve her symptoms, which cause her to miss out on plans with friends and leave her feeling self-conscious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Amber, from Abergele, Conwy county, said: "There is no cure and I'm always scared because there's a lot of people [with the condition] who have said that they get &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/anaphylaxis/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;anaphylactic shock&lt;/a&gt;."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She has to wear leggings under her clothes almost all the time and said she often felt as though "everyone is looking" at her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Cold urticaria can be triggered by swimming or other water activities, as well as touching or eating cold foods and drinks, according to Anaphylaxis UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The charity said the underlying cause was unknown and the condition was often difficult to diagnose and manage because symptoms varied widely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/e60d/live/7ac72ba0-f4b0-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/e60d/live/7ac72ba0-f4b0-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e60d/live/7ac72ba0-f4b0-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/e60d/live/7ac72ba0-f4b0-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/e60d/live/7ac72ba0-f4b0-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/e60d/live/7ac72ba0-f4b0-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/e60d/live/7ac72ba0-f4b0-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e60d/live/7ac72ba0-f4b0-11f0-b385-5f48925de19a.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="PA Media A close-up picture of Amber looking at the camera. She has long dark curled hair with blue eyes and dark-rimmed glasses." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Amber feels self-conscious when she breaks out in hives due to cold temperatures&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Amber, who has a part-time job as a waitress, said she was walking back from work the first time she had a breakout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I had bumps and was red all over my face, ears, legs and arms and was itchy," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I thought it might have been the food I'd eaten, so I didn't eat anything at home and I got another rash."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;When the symptoms later returned, she went to her GP who suggested her skin was reacting to pollution and did not prescribe any medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;With Amber having an almost daily reaction, her mum, Dawn, became "very worried".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She always made me wear double layers and she was always scared of what could happen because obviously we didn't know much about it," Amber said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Amber did some research herself and when she came across cold urticaria, she was referred to a dermatologist. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said she was initially shocked by the diagnosis in 2023, because the condition was so rare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"But I was kind of relieved that I had support, I was happy that someone actually believed me," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, Amber's symptoms have not improved with medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She also develops hives and a rash when coming out of water, whether from a swimming pool, the shower, or the sea, regardless of the outside temperature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20260113-125315-2e65791d43-web-2.37.1-4/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/1fdd/live/4e2aff50-f2f7-11f0-9a08-61d9f795eeed.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/1fdd/live/4e2aff50-f2f7-11f0-9a08-61d9f795eeed.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1fdd/live/4e2aff50-f2f7-11f0-9a08-61d9f795eeed.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/1fdd/live/4e2aff50-f2f7-11f0-9a08-61d9f795eeed.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/1fdd/live/4e2aff50-f2f7-11f0-9a08-61d9f795eeed.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/1fdd/live/4e2aff50-f2f7-11f0-9a08-61d9f795eeed.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/1fdd/live/4e2aff50-f2f7-11f0-9a08-61d9f795eeed.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/1fdd/live/4e2aff50-f2f7-11f0-9a08-61d9f795eeed.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="PA Media Overhead view of Amber's thighs and knees covered in hives" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;PA Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Medication has not helped Amber's symptoms and she continues to struggle to manage the condition&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Amber said she often arrived at work and school with redness and hives, and has had to turn down plans with friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"When I go out, I always have a reaction - I walk about 20 minutes to the bus stop and I get a reaction," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"My friends are always out, and they're always inviting me out, and I can't really go out because of it, so I feel left out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We have to plan around where we go. If it's somewhere inside or at someone's house that's fine, but if it's outside, then I can't do it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Amber remains hopeful about the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I'm hoping there's going to be a lot more research going into this and hopefully there's more medication out there for me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I just want to be able to go about my everyday things that other people can do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 06:31:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1BekxKODI0REl6eUMxZ3RmT0VYUlVjWkJsaXhHLWVqbVdISGtqMGc2TThzUnRpM2MxcWxFT1dVREZWUVktdDZFejNxcDlaRXFsaFJLV1dDRWttQdIBX0FVX3lxTE42ZGo4TVp1WFptc0YwdDV2VEZsaWhpeWZKV3lfSEI1RVRrVklGeGl5cVlXdnhoQllCV0lfMUMxQkMyckpmd0FlLWRybFMwc1pDOWdMYXRuWXV3emlvUUF3</guid></item><item><title>橙汁健康吗？营养师解释了如果每天饮用这种剂量的维生素C会发生什么|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/is-orange-juice-healthy-dietitian-explains-what-really-happens-if-you-drink-this-daily-dose-of-vitamin-c-every-day-101768660135558.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt;&lt;p class="content"&gt;&lt;span&gt;A glass of orange juice can feel like the perfect way to start your day with a refreshing burst of flavour. However, the effects of daily use depend heavily on your portion sizes, the quality of the juice, and your overall diet. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;While oranges are a rich source of vitamin C, they are also rich in antioxidants like flavonoids, hesperidin, and carotenoids, which protect your cells from damage and help reduce inflammation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="artImage leadImage"&gt;&lt;figcaption class=""&gt;Is orange juice good for your health? (Freepik)&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Dietitian Deepali Sharma, clinical nutritionist at CK Birla Hospital, tells Health Shots: “Drinking &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/your-body-weight-may-decide-how-orange-juice-works-on-you-study-reveals-gene-level-differences-101765783520684.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="orange juice"&gt;orange juice&lt;/a&gt; daily provides your body with vitamin C, antioxidants, natural sugars, and hydration.&lt;span&gt; In moderate amounts, it can support immunity, skin health, and energy levels. However, because orange juice lacks fibre compared to whole fruit and contains concentrated natural sugars, daily consumption needs to be mindful.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span&gt;As per the nutritionist, the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/web-stories/lifestyle/superfoods-to-the-rescue-14-healthy-foods-rich-in-antioxidants-101737794857699.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="antioxidants"&gt;antioxidants&lt;/a&gt; found in orange juice contain benefits like:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Flavonoids:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;They neutralise the free radicals that can lead to oxidative stress&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;It reduces the chronic inflammation that can lead to heart disease and diabetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Supports immune cell activity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hesperiden&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;It improves the blood circulation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Helps to lower bad cholesterol&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;It supports insulin sensitivity and glucose metabolism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Carotenoids&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;It protect cells from oxidative stress&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;It supports eye health&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is essential for vision and skin health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Benefits of drinking orange juice daily&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here is a breakdown of the positive effects of drinking orange juice daily, explains the dietitian&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boosts immunity:&lt;/strong&gt; Orange juice is rich in vitamin C, which supports immune function and helps the body fight infections.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Improves iron absorption:&lt;/strong&gt; Vitamin C enhances absorption of non-heme iron from plant-based foods, benefiting vegetarians and people prone to anaemia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Provides antioxidants:&lt;/strong&gt; Compounds like flavonoids help reduce oxidative stress and inflammation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Supports heart health: &lt;/strong&gt;In moderation, orange juice may help improve blood vessel function and reduce oxidative damage.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Quick energy source:&lt;/strong&gt; Natural sugars provide an instant energy boost, especially useful in the morning or after physical activity.effects of drinking orange juice daily&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Side effects of drinking orange juice daily&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Orange juice may not always have benefits for every individul. As per the nutritionist, below can be the drawbacks of drinking orange juice every day:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High sugar intake:&lt;/strong&gt; Even unsweetened orange juice contains natural sugars. Excess consumption can contribute to weight gain and blood sugar spikes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Low fibre content:&lt;/strong&gt; Juice lacks the fibre found in whole oranges, which is important for digestion and satiety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May worsen acidity:&lt;/strong&gt; Its acidic nature can trigger acid reflux, heartburn, or stomach discomfort in sensitive individuals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dental issues: &lt;/strong&gt;Frequent intake can erode tooth enamel due to acidity and sugar content if oral hygiene is poor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not ideal for diabetics if blood sugar levels are uncontrolled:&lt;/strong&gt; It can raise post-meal blood glucose levels if consumed in large amounts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;What's the best time to drink orange juice?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The nutritionist suggests it is best to drink orange juice in the morning along with a meal. She says drinking it after food may slow down the process of sugar absorption and reduce acidity-related discomfort.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; Avoid drinking orange juice late at night or on an empty stomach if you have acidity issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;How much orange juice should you drink?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Below is the nutritionist-recommended quantity to drink:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;100–150 ml per day (about half to one small glass)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Choose freshly squeezed juice without added sugar.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Diluting it with water can further reduce sugar load while retaining nutrients.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span&gt;Who should avoid it?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As per the nutritionist,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;People with diabetes or insulin resistance should monitor portion size carefully.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Those with acid reflux, gastritis, or sensitive stomach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Individuals trying to lose weight, if consuming large quantities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;People with dental sensitivity or enamel erosion, unless intake is limited and oral care is maintained&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;span&gt;(Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 05:30:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxOcE9zbTlZS0lzR2dGTmdHRXV1TUFWNlN2UGZuemtyNzBfTzl3ZkJVNzBsRXNtS3J5S2RCWGkwejFSOGsybVZlZDB5QkZxS01aWXl6N3hpSmlWd3dodHdPSXNiWUtwVHVnQkZoV3NFRjc4Y09YaWV5TDVhX0dIaG5CWVpQbEtMRTdacTBTVzY1Q3BET2RIbjFrS0hhOFNuS3RLQk9ueFN0QjVXTU95cV9WdkVpRzN1MUVpM04zOWk0ZE5ROW50czdaV184OFlYT1VCR1c3SzJYMkpjOVZldkJQc0FCSjhYQWU4WlJFOVdMeHQ5MWhvVVBsdXY3ekwwcElyb2tuTFVGZUVQZjlNU3JHTtIBlgJBVV95cUxOR213dzJwLWtNRUxOQy01WFk3Vmg0UWRyV3k3dEdvOXBuam9Cb2IwaG1KbFlSOGF1UFpjb0s0d1M2U0ViQjBYY00wbFFzclVTRzF6NkQzajJ4eFpPWmRZaFpJcXBUM0QzQWhIME9RdkpHYUhvVjZENTAtaVVaWWdZcFBoM3RJaVZQWTVpdzZKY3dvalJ3ZUdOb21jT3g1eEpQRGxiOGxRZkdFcVZIaGhRQzFPWE5JRTVIUEh5NmlkTWFEQk04aFRsTDU5cFNlWUo5TER1RFdzZGhzV19iMWtpWHBrUFZGZDA4UXJudVd1eEF1RmZUM1FDQmlHMVZ6YVA3UWlqZ3VFOWl3ZlllS1dUUXhkMXl6dw</guid></item><item><title>每天看着人们生殖器的专业人士的17个在职自白- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/angelicaamartinez/waxers-obgyns-professionals-confessions-and-secrets</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-23
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="140031392" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;17.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;And finally, "Breast cancer surgeon here. I have seen thousands of breasts. Sometimes in pairs, sometimes not. There is huge variation. If anyone out there thinks you are deformed or ugly, you are not. There is someone out there who loves and celebrates their body — who feels good, and has an active sex life and loving partner — who has a jacked boob job, has nipples pointing in different directions, has uneven or lumpy, ginormous or barely visible breasts, or no breasts at all because it didn’t fit their gender or cancer took them. And they can be happy and healthy in that body they have."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;"If you’re unhappy and you want something about your body to be different, then by all means, feel free to explore that, and don’t feel judged or ashamed to want that. But if you feel like you’re not perfect enough, if that’s keeping you from living your best life, please don’t let it. There are all types of bodies in the world, and there are plenty of people with bodies that aren’t as youthful, or as perky or sensuous as yours, and guess what? They’re doing just fine. There’s no reason for you to get in your head about yours. Confidence in yourself and a sincere desire to have your partner feel wanted and attractive themselves is where success lies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And — at least for me and everyone I work with — we aren’t talking about you or judging you or thinking any one thing about you or your body. We just want to make sure that you’re healthy, you feel heard and respected, that we get our job done, and that we do it safely and correctly to make sure that those tits don’t kill you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1qd1drx/comment/nzolahg/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;amp;utm_term=1&amp;amp;utm_content=share_button" target="_blank"&gt;DrHeatherRichardson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 01:16:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNbDRMOUpCRGVqZkdXbVdpakVLVFNYaWt6MWtXbm13WWpQNjRrN2J4RzR4RWxQbmNTMGxhZ2U3YVhURGJGVE9RN09ncldiZkNPanVYUDZWcnl2QWVZNDA3eTZodjUxMVRqOXFZRXlMUl82TUZJeUJqZ2JVVjgzMlhPcXdGN3BDel9nZHpMT2w5enRwX21aNDA2dUt3</guid></item><item><title>营养师揭示了像Ozempic一样起作用的改变游戏规则的补充剂-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15446727/ozempic-supplements-weight-loss-effects.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A dietitian has revealed the unlikely supplements that may help supercharge the effects of blockbuster &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-e4da46d0-ed67-11f0-9035-67da10d0cb2b"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt; drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taken by one in eight American adults (30 million people) injections like Ozempic and Wegovy have &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15422983/ozempic-reshaping-american-diet-buying-grocery-store.html"&gt;changed the landscape of weight loss&lt;/a&gt;, diet and &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-ccfa0710-eda5-11f0-be85-7d59e2a2da28"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The drugs work by mimicking glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1), a naturally present hormone in the gut that slows digestion, regulates blood sugar and tells the body it's full - which helps control diabetes and weight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because GLP-1 medications slow gastric emptying, those taking them often have to adjust their diets and supplement regimens to avoid potentially debilitating side effects like nausea, constipation, diarrhea and bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In her new book, Your Best Shot: The Personalized System for Optimal Weight Health - GLP-1 Shot or Not, California-based dietitian Ashley Koff revealed the ins and outs of the weight loss shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Speaking to the Daily Mail, Koff, a dietitian for more than 25 years, identified the supplements science suggests may help boost the effects of the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She noted that while tried and true supplements like omega-3s and fiber help aid digestion and satiety, lesser known ones like berberine and Amarasate may enhance the body's natural production of GLP-1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, she cautioned that no supplement can replace a medication for those whose doctors have deemed it necessary for health control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A dietitian has revealed the key supplements to take to maximize the effects of GLP-1 agonists &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There is a lot of misinformation about supplements,' Koff told the Daily Mail. 'There is no "nature's Ozempic," there's no supplement that works exactly like the medications do because [medications] stay working for 24 hours, for seven days a week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There are a couple [supplements] on the market that are helping our bodies have more GLP-1, but nothing that would compare to a medication.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Berberine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Berberine is a yellow plant-derived compound found in herbs like barberry and Oregon grape. Long used in herbal medicine for infections and digestive issues, it is now sold in supplement form for blood sugar, cholesterol and weight control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Costing between $10 and $50 per bottle, berberine is a type of bitter, meaning it stimulates the body's bitter taste receptors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Stimulating these receptors in the gut triggers cells in this area to release more GLP-1, adding on to the benefits of a weight loss shot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If they stimulate the bitter taste receptors, that's going to help our own body's hormones,' Koff said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, berberine has been shown to interact with medications that control blood pressure and cholesterol, so doctors recommend caution if you are taking one of those drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Ashley Koff (pictured) cautioned that while supplements may enhance GLP-1 production, there is no 'nature's Ozempic'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Probiotics&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt; Probiotics are 'good' bacteria naturally found in the gut and in fermented foods such as kimchi, doenjang and kefir.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They have been shown to promote healthy digestion and help the body absorb vital nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Koff specifically pointed to Akkermansia muciniphila, which has been shown to strengthen the intestinal barrier and reduce inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Mucinophilia means it likes mucin, so it goes in and it chews up the mucin and the mucosal layer,' Koff said. 'In doing that, it's going to help to stimulate the production of GLP-1.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Akkermansia muciniphila does not directly come from food, but its growth in the gut and can be boosted by eating foods rich in polyphenols such as berries, green tea and dark chocolate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is also available as a supplement in pill or gummy form, costing anywhere from $20 to $80 per bottle depending on the brand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Glutamine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: Koff's book, which was released on January 6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Koff also recommended glutamine, the most abundant of 20 amino acids in the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the body produces its own, it can also be found in animal products like beef, chicken, fish, eggs, milk, yogurt and cheese, as well as plant-based sources such as legumes, spinach and whole grains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a supplement, bottles with 60 to 180 capsules tend to cost anywhere from $10 to $35. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Glutamine is also available as a powder, with prices ranging from $10 to $40 depending on the size and brand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Similar to berberine, glutamine in food or supplement form triggers intestinal cells to secrete additional GLP-1.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It has also been shown to help strengthen intestinal lining, which helps lower inflammation that could otherwise interfere with GLP-1 signaling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Amarasate &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hailing from New Zealand hops, Amarasate is, much like berberine, a natural bitter extract. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sold as an appetite control supplement, a 90-capsule bottle costs about $70 to $90.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Similar to berberine, Koff explained the supplement stimulates bitter taste receptors that trigger the natural release of GLP-1, promoting feelings of fullness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Koff told the Daily Mail that Amarasate may be particularly useful for people coming off a GLP-1 agonist like Ozempic or Wegovy since it naturally stimulates hormone production with minimal side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Amarasate also works to reduce hunger in as little as 30 minutes, she noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;Your Best Shot: The Personalized System for Optimal Weight Health - GLP-1 Shot or Not is available now through Amazon, Barnes &amp;amp; Noble, HarperCollins Publishers and others. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 20:49:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxONzdrUlpYSDVKbEVaWXF2ckhYZGlHTkFMbnlQeWxlWDhTRjFWNHhheXRZelA1WHlRM1ljZ3E1d3hpZDN1V3ZDUHA4QmNCMW8wa2pSRzFELXBCV004SlpDai1rY2JVLUswc3hqOFlVcXdRbm5LZEF6UjllQThvTm55aTZ6WkI2c0RJTUVQV0FNWEhNbXFCbWdZQ1BfUFc</guid></item><item><title>亨廷顿警告居民在赫克歇尔公园附近发现死鹅-新闻日报</title><link>https://www.newsday.com/long-island/environment/bird-flu-testing-huntington-xxlulg0n</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="continue-reading ContinueReading_continue-reading__uTArZ active ContinueReading_active__SOMMR"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A half-dozen geese found dead in and near Heckscher Park in Huntington this month are being tested for possible avian influenza, according to a post on the&lt;a class="nd-link" href="https://www.facebook.com/photo?fbid=1284350360406443&amp;amp;set=pcb.1284350490406430"&gt; Town of Huntington's Facebook page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The town said official lab results may not be available for as much as a month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="nd-link" href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/livestock-poultry-disease/avian/avian-influenza"&gt;Highly Pathogenic Avian Influenza&lt;/a&gt;, commonly called bird flu, was first identified in New York in 2022. The disease most often infects wild water fowl such as geese and ducks but also can also infect raptors, corvids (ravens and crows) and mammals, according to the state Department of Environmental Conservation. Songbirds do not appear to be very susceptible, the state says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease can be passed to domestic birds such as chicken and even to cattle. Occasionally humans who have had direct contact with an infected animal — usually farmworkers at chicken or diary facilities — can be infected. Severe illness is not common, according to the state Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been no known cases of bird flu in humans in New York, the agency said. "While avian influenza continues to affect wildlife, the risk to humans remain low," state Health Commissioner James McDonald said in a statement earlier this month. "New Yorkers can stay safe by avoiding contact with sick or dead birds and animals and reporting anything unusual."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms include sneezing or nasal discharge, lethargy, neurologic problems such as stargazing or seizures, diarrhea and weakness. The disease generally peaks in the winter months, according to the DEC. There is no treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts advise that people should not touch a dead bird and to keep pets away as well. If it’s necessary to move a bird, wear gloves and a mask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If residents find a dead bird, the town of Huntington asks that they call the town's animal control at 631-754-8722.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Possible avian flu cases can also be reported in the &lt;a class="nd-link" href="https://survey123.arcgis.com/share/dee381c0ee8a4114a83dc1892fc0f7ed"&gt;DEC’s online form&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Newsday</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 20:44:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQbTFLQi1DYzR5alBPLWJNOFRHNVRDS0s5emZLTUlLNHRodC01ZU1YeS1zQmk5eVdlRl9uNTZXRko3UGNnRTctdldNUm83UXFLczd5dldweXctUXlOMXNzUndfdm9FUFp4WTRYSTZHRXRkZHFFM3VrLXhjZTFzaTFFdnBHTkhDVGFxYlBvYg</guid></item><item><title>什么是“代谢健康” ，为什么它很重要？ -《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/what-is-metabolic-health-and-why-does-it-matter/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxQUUIyaS05T2ZrMnJ1TE1FSjZqVGh0ZFJSSngtTS1ENVl2aldjQl9fQkpYMV93NHdOYlBmQnUybU94SXlySmhZTklmY3NzV25TUTRTY3pJYmR6bmhlWFdpaXhKck1RUEtCRE1UM096a2NZRlJMakpjRUtxRWdJNXdZTGNhZmM5SU83dGJzUnN5Q0hvdnps?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;What is ‘metabolic health,’ and why does it matter?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqNggKIjBDQklTSGpvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoRUtEd2k2bC1DdUVCSDJkSFFEWmY3VC1DZ0FQAQ?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&amp;amp;oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View Full Coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQUUIyaS05T2ZrMnJ1TE1FSjZqVGh0ZFJSSngtTS1ENVl2aldjQl9fQkpYMV93NHdOYlBmQnUybU94SXlySmhZTklmY3NzV25TUTRTY3pJYmR6bmhlWFdpaXhKck1RUEtCRE1UM096a2NZRlJMakpjRUtxRWdJNXdZTGNhZmM5SU83dGJzUnN5Q0hvdnps</guid></item></channel></rss>