<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>William H. Foege ，根除天花的关键人物， 89岁去世-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/24/us/william-h-foege-dead.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 02:21:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE5BQjBBWm5QTGRHX0s1Wk9JMGF6NjZDdzN5ZUp1VDBZMl83YnNzcWVTVEI4Zk5OOXktV2VTanVMWmNFZS1LeTRtbDl0MHdOVTE2dFFPR1ctRFNXdnU5cUdVQ1M0M0RGNVdIZTlSVXlZZGg</guid></item><item><title>意想不到的地方，你可以得到黑色素瘤，而不是你的皮肤......它与阳光无关-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15456909/unexpected-spot-skin-cancer-melanoma-eyes.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The signs melanoma, a type of skin &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-74a6f2f0-f7a8-11f0-b093-c11752a910bb"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, are clear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Moles that are either new or changed in appearance are the &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14639039/dermatologist-warning-6-signs-deadly-melanoma-skin-cancer.html"&gt;hallmark of the disease&lt;/a&gt;, which strikes more than 200,000 Americans every year, along with rough patches and color changes in the skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cancerous lesions can pop up anywhere on the skin, but experts warn melanoma may strike an uncommon area for thousands of Americans: the eyes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Melanoma has been known to pop up on eyelids, thin layers of skin that are often exposed to harmful ultraviolet (UV) radiation, which makes them prone to developing lesions. Left unaddressed, these cancers may infiltrate the inner layers of the eye and the brain, making them far less treatable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the cancer can begin in a place even without skin, such as inside the eye, in a form of the disease called ocular melanoma. Of ocular melanomas, there are several subtypes, including uveal melanoma and conjunctival melanoma.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The skin and eyes share the same cells called melanocytes, which produce melanin, the pigment that gives skin, eyes and hair their color. Damage and mutations in these cells lead to melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while melanoma is commonly caused by sun exposure, uveal and conjunctival melanoma are not primarily associated with harmful UV light. Instead, people with lighter eye colors or pre-existing eye conditions like near-sightedness may be at a greater risk.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As melanoma, and skin cancer in general, is on the rise nationwide, eye doctors have urged Americans to keep up with regular eye exams every one to two years to detect potentially cancerous changes, and to be on the lookout for seemingly subtle changes like blurred vision, spots and irritation in or around the eye. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Experts warn melanoma, a type of skin cancer, is not always just on the skin (stock image) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Allison Dashow, pictured above in 2025, was diagnosed with ocular melanoma four years ago at 26 years old&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Jacqueline Bowen, an eye doctor and president of the American Optometric Association, told the Daily Mail: 'Skin cancer involving the eye can appear in several different ways. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Some start in or around the eye itself, while others spread to the eye from elsewhere in the body.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;About 1 million US adults are currently living with melanoma, the deadliest form of skin cancer, and about 212,000 will be diagnosed this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The mortality rate from the disease in the US is about two per 100,000 people, resulting in around 8,000 deaths per year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And melanoma rates have surged over the past 30 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to the American Academy of Dermatology, the rate of melanoma diagnoses in the US doubled from 1982 to 2011, and there was a 31.5 percent increase between 2011 and 2019, the latest figures available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In women over 50, there has been a three percent increase in melanoma rates per year, while men under 50 have seen a one percent dip yearly. Rates among women under 50 and men over 50 have remained stable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Signs of skin cancer range from innocuous to obvious, but experts warn that treating cases early is key to making sure they do not spread or further develop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: Dashow, now 29, after her surgery with a covering over the eye affected by ocular melanoma, which she wore for seven days&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Two forms of melanoma that grow in the eye, subtypes of ocular melanoma, are uveal and conjunctival melanoma. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are usually no symptoms in early stages of ocular melanomas, but as the diseases progress, patients may experience blurry vision, floaters or flashes in their vision and changes in pupil shape. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The exact causes are unclear, but experts believe the disease is more likely in people with lighter eyes and skin colors. The role of UV light in ocular melanomas' development is unknown. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are about 2,000 new cases of ocular melanoma every year, according to the Melanoma Research Foundation (MRF). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Conjunctival melanoma, developing in the conjunctiva (clear tissue over the eye), is exceedingly rare with roughly 130 cases per year in the US and fewer than one in 1 million worldwide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Symptoms include irritation, redness or a sensation of something being stuck in the eye. As it progresses, it may lead to vision loss, blurry vision or a change in pupil size. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Uveal melanoma starts in the eye's middle layer, called the uvea. It is the most common eye cancer. Like the other forms of eye melanoma, the causes are unclear, but it is not thought to be influenced by UV light. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The above graph shows the increase in melanoma cases since 1975. Deaths, however, have decreased slightly&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bowen said: 'It’s important to note that some of the most serious eye cancers, particularly uveal or ocular melanoma, often cause no pain or vision changes in the early and even mid stages. Uveal melanoma is life-threatening because the retina is an extension of the brain, providing a direct pathway for cancer to spread if it goes undetected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This is why annual comprehensive eye exams are essential, even when no symptoms are present. During every exam, doctors of optometry carefully examine the eye using specialized microscopes that can detect very small or early precancerous and cancerous lesions of the eye and surrounding structures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Many eye cancers are found during routine exams before symptoms ever develop, which greatly improves outcomes.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While there are no definitive cures for ocular melanoma, patients can be treated with a specialized laser therapy or plaque brachytherapy. These treatments kill the tumor and while doctors don't declare patients 'cured,' they are considered to be what is called NED, no evidence of disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bowen urged anyone who notices changes in their eyes or vision to visit an eye doctor as soon as possible, especially if symptoms last for several weeks or worsen. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Early detection matters at every age, including in children, where rare but life-threatening eye cancers such as retinoblastoma may only be detected through a comprehensive eye exam,' she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 02:16:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPbFlRMWdldHdzQU52SHdUd0pwOUgzTjd0cmZSZ2VrZkN1VXVVTEtRUlV4TjJ6dEJoZjlHQmw3dEYtZUlDeTM3b1A1bk9EbG9NUmxjdVQ2ckxkeXloZkQxeFZvZW5zRFI4Ylp0dGFiVlFQZ0hwNlhtZGprM0RMdDhkRHV6WjdsZldpZmZ0TjF0WldXRkZFMUVfTmRROFdCQWfSAaQBQVVfeXFMUFFHX1B5OENVcG1ETll4ZVItTF84MGp3QkJTcnhEdlRlT2RWcWpXS25KOVNxUXlpWlBLZ3NINkw2WHBNS2lES0h4b21yQ1Rock9lSFlwMDlaMTBTU3hDQzhuS1RpSjdqRXhUVWkwZUd3Z0tVWno5OFBlSXRfcGs0djJSX2QxWXQ0a2xITExzMFVQMTFrWHZValpETjVTZ1NWUjRmNWY</guid></item><item><title>根据健身专家- EatingWell的说法，在50岁后进行6次平衡锻炼，以提高力量和稳定性</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/balance-exercises-to-boost-strength-and-stability-11891603</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Practice balance exercises at least two to three times per week to improve stability and balance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Start slowly, focus on form and use support as needed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;As your balance improves, try increasing the difficulty or frequency of the exercise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You may recall a time when standing on one foot, walking along a curb or jumping around felt effortless. But as we age, our body changes, and so does our balance. Balance loss is common with age due to natural declines in muscle strength, reaction time, proprioception and spatial awareness. "Balance starts declining for everyone at age 40 and more rapidly after 60 so we need to combat that age-related decline and train our balance to maximize our retention," says &lt;a href="https://ariesphysicaltherapy.com/about-us-best-physical-therapy-fort-lauderdale" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Bill Kelley, D.P.T., ATC, CSCS, Cert. DN&lt;/a&gt;. These changes can make everyday tasks, like climbing stairs, reaching for items on a shelf or walking on uneven surfaces, feel more challenging or even dangerous. Nearly one in three older adults fall each year, with a quarter of those falls resulting in a serious injury such as a hip fracture.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Although balance often declines after age 50, it doesn't have to be a given. Research shows that regular balance exercises can significantly improve stability in older adults.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "Balance exercises should be a vital part of anyone's movement practice as we all age," says &lt;a href="https://hubphysicaltherapy.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Paul Fath, PT, D.P.T., OCS&lt;/a&gt;. "Regularly practicing and performing balance exercises will help to maintain better balance and slow the decline of balance-related events and injuries."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To help you get started, here are six expert-recommended, beginner-friendly balance exercises to safely build strength and stability.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-supported-single-leg-stand"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Supported Single-Leg Stand &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; These single-leg stands are easy to do at home and can transform your balance. "Most balance exercises work by challenging your stability, which trains your body to better sense its position in space. Single-leg stands are especially effective because your base of support is reduced, forcing your brain and muscles to work together to recalibrate your center of gravity," says &lt;a href="https://welltech.com/experts/molly-ruecker" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Molly Ruecker PT, D.P.T., SCS, ATC, CSCS&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "This exercise strengthens stabilizing muscles in the feet, ankles, hips and core, essential for daily movement and balance," she adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stand near a counter, table, wall or sturdy chair for support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Place your hands on your hips or lightly on the support if needed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lift your left foot off the ground, raising your thigh toward parallel to the floor or as high as you can without losing balance. Keep your weight on the other leg and engage your core.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold for 20 to 30 seconds, or as long as you comfortably can.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly lower your left foot and switch to the right leg.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 2 to 3 times per leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Hold the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-exercises-for-aging-11866471" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;single-leg stand without support&lt;/a&gt; or close your eyes for 20 to 30 seconds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-heel-to-toe-walk"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Heel-to-Toe Walk &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Heel-to-toe walks are a game changer for balance. "I stress gait mechanics a lot. How your foot lands, how your toes are placed and how your muscles respond during movement all matter," &lt;a href="https://www.msfitnessstudio.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Melanie Sinclair, CPT, PES, CES&lt;/a&gt; says. "Heel-to-toe walking helps improve how you move forward efficiently, whether you're walking, running, lunging or just moving through daily life."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stand tall and extend your arms out to the sides for balance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Place one foot directly in front of the other so the heel of your front foot touches the toes of your back foot.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continue stepping forward in this way for 5 to 10 steps, aiming to walk in a straight line.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Turn around and walk back to your starting point.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Walk heel-to-toe slowly, pausing briefly on each step to challenge balance and control.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-sit-to-stand"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Sit-to-Stand &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Getting up and down from a chair is a daily activity most people perform many times a day. But as balance changes, this simple movement can become more difficult. "Sit-to-stand is a functional activity that is done throughout the day in self care and in positional changes," shares &lt;a href="https://activecarephysicaltherapy.com/staffs/dr-karena-wu/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Karena Wu, PT, D.P.T., OCS&lt;/a&gt;. "It demonstrates proper loading of weight into the legs to slowly lower or to stand up and good &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/7-day-body-weight-training-plan-for-beginners-11744140" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;hip strength&lt;/a&gt; to stand up fully erect."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Sit on a sturdy chair with your feet flat on the floor and hands resting on your lap.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lean slightly forward, engage your core and push through your heels to stand up fully.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly lower back down to a seated position.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 10 to 15 times, resting as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Tip: Move slowly and deliberately. Standing and lowering slowly helps your muscles engage and improves balance.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Perform slowly from a lower chair or while holding light weights, or progress to traditional squats without a chair.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-supported-hip-hinge"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Supported Hip-Hinge &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Supported hip-hinges test what your balance is like while in motion. "As you hinge at the hips, your center of gravity shifts backwards and forwards, forcing the muscles to constantly adjust to keep you stable," shares Ruecker.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Hip-hinges are also good for balance because they strengthen the core and posterior chain muscles, including the glutes, hamstrings and back, all of which are key muscles for controlling posture and movement. The light support is perfect for those who need an added feeling of safety, allowing them to practice proper form without the fear of failing," she adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stand about one foot away from a wall, back facing it, with feet hip-width apart.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Place your hands on your hips or lightly on the wall for support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hinge at your hips, gently pushing them back while keeping your back straight. Your glutes may lightly touch the wall to guide you.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lower until you feel a gentle stretch in your hamstrings.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly push your hips forward to return to standing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 10 to 15 times.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_56-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Tip: Avoid bending your knees or leaning forward. Focus on hinging at the hips and gently pushing your glutes back.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_57-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_58-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Place your hands on your thighs and slowly slide them down toward your knees or shins. Alternatively, progress to traditional Romanian deadlifts.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_59-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-standing-side-leg-raises"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_60-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Standing Side Leg Raises &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_61-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_62-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Standing side leg raises help with lateral balance. "Standing leg raises improve your balance by shifting your weight onto one leg while the other moves outward, forcing your body to control side-to-side stability," explains Ruecker.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_63-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_64-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "The main working muscles are those on the outside of the standing hip, especially the &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-exercise-for-better-blood-pressure-8619767" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;gluteus medius&lt;/a&gt;, which keep your pelvis level and prevent you from tipping or collapsing inward. At the same time, your core and supporting ankle muscles will make small adjustments to keep your body stacked over the base of support. This trains your body to manage lateral balance and alignment," she adds.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_65-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_66-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_67-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_68-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stand next to a wall, counter or sturdy chair and place a hand on it for support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Shift your weight onto the leg closest to the support.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly lift the other leg out to the side, keeping it straight.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lower the leg back down without fully touching the floor, unless needed for balance.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 10 to 15 times per leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_69-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_70-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Perform side leg raises without support or use a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/stretches-to-do-every-day-to-help-undo-sitting-11849140" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;loop resistance band&lt;/a&gt; just above your knees.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_71-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-step-ups"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_72-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Step-Ups &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="mntl-sc-block_73-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image mntl-sc-block-image--no-theme no-theme figure-landscape figure-high-res"&gt; 
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_74-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Getting up and down the stairs can become a difficult task as we age, but step-ups can help you feel confident going up and down flights. "Step-ups are an important unilateral strength and balance activity that mimics stair climbing and descent," says Wu. "It emphasizes the use of multiple joints and muscles in the leg to step up and down with control and good kinetic alignment."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_75-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_76-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; She adds, "This can help reduce falls if someone trips and lands on a single leg. This is also an important &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7949443/best-strength-training-exercises/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;leg strengthening&lt;/a&gt; and balance exercise that assists in other activities like getting out of a car smoothly and with less effort."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_77-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_78-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Instructions:&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_79-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol id="mntl-sc-block_80-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Use a sturdy step, stair or step box about half a foot (6 inches) high.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand facing the step, holding a railing or placing a hand on a wall for support if needed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Place your left foot on the step and push through your heel to bring your right foot up to meet it.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Step down with your right foot, keeping your left foot on the step.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat 10 to 15 times per leg.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_81-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_82-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Tip: When you push through your heel, you should feel your glutes doing most of the work.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_83-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_84-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Advanced Exercise:&lt;/strong&gt; Use a higher step box or hold a dumbbell in the hand opposite the stepping leg to increase challenge.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_85-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-practice-balance-safely"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_86-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How to Practice Balance Safely &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_87-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To reduce the risk of falls or injury, keep these safety tips in mind:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_88-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_89-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use Support When Needed.&lt;/strong&gt; Keep a wall, sturdy chair or counter nearby to hold onto until you feel stable.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clear Your Space.&lt;/strong&gt; "To reduce the risk of tripping, ensure the area is tidy and free of clutter," says Ruecker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wear Proper Shoes.&lt;/strong&gt; Supportive, &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/podiatrist-approved-non-slip-shoes-11829338" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;non-slip footwear&lt;/a&gt; can prevent slips and improve stability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start Slow.&lt;/strong&gt; Perform exercises at a controlled pace, as rushing increases the risk of losing balance. "Starting simple, listening to your body and slowly increasing the difficulty are also great ways to stay safe while still making progress," shares Ruecker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engage Your Core.&lt;/strong&gt; A strong, engaged core helps support better balance and control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Progress Gradually.&lt;/strong&gt; Increase the difficulty only when you can perform the exercise confidently and safely.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus Your Gaze.&lt;/strong&gt; Looking at a fixed point ahead, such as a picture on the wall, can help improve stability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Seek Professional Help.&lt;/strong&gt; A physical therapist or certified &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-best-exercise-combo-to-lose-visceral-fat-11880936" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;personal trainer&lt;/a&gt; can provide personalized recommendations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_90-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-often-should-you-do-balance-exercises"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_91-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Often Should You Do Balance Exercises? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_92-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Research supports this recommendation, showing that older adults who practice balance training three times per week experience improved stability and a lower risk of falls.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "The best frequency for performing balance exercises is the frequency that you can perform consistently," says Fath. "When included in your regular exercise program, I would suggest at least 2 to 3 days per week."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_93-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_95-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_96-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_97-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Maintaining and improving balance is important at any age, but it becomes especially important after 50. Adding balance exercises to your routine can help strengthen muscles, prevent falls and make everyday movements feel easier. Focus on slow, controlled movements and proper form, and progress to more challenging variations only when you can perform each exercise confidently. For best results, aim to practice balance exercises a few times per week.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 25 Jan 2026 01:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOSWxsdlFHc3Y1cTdBTEM4NVNvejZJZmp0NmF4TlJTVEU0NTVWdmZOMExzQWxuZVNMTVM2eXpHaVdsdVBySnZ0b3FIdUhwTzYyenVVczJzbmR0LWpRZVRlT1l0ajVkTGxNSnpUMGttR09EMEgzdnFsRkxjNEhYblhOT1RSdnpMNEpjWlhpRnNB</guid></item><item><title>猛禽可以缩小30%的大脑。以下是他们如何恢复增长。- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/shrews-can-shrink-their-brains-by-30-heres-how-they-grow-it-back</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;In preparation for winter, the common shrew (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_shrew"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sorex araneus&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-animal-can-shrink-its-brain-and-we-finally-know-how"&gt;shrinks its brain&lt;/a&gt; by 30 percent to conserve precious energy. Then, come spring, the shrew miraculously 'regrows' its shrivelled brain, neurons fully intact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists have now traced the evolutionary origins of this rare adaptation and the genes that likely enable it. While fascinating in its own right, this information may also spark new approaches to understanding and treating &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/just-one-gene-may-be-responsible-for-over-90-of-alzheimers-cases"&gt;human brain degeneration&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-stem-cell-secrets-of-this-tiny-worm-could-help-unlock-human-regeneration"&gt;The Stem Cell Secrets of This Tiny Worm Could Help Unlock Human Regeneration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The unusual adaptation is known as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cub.2021.04.006"&gt;Dehnel's phenomenon&lt;/a&gt;, named for Polish zoologist &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/August_Dehnel"&gt;August Dehnel&lt;/a&gt;, who first described the shrew's remarkable brain-shrinking ability, a method of coping with the seasonal energy shortage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dehnel's phenomenon is rare, but shrews aren't the only practitioners: European moles (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/European_mole"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Talpa europaea&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), common weasels (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Least_weasel"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mustela nivalis&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), and stoats (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Stoat"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mustela erminea&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;) also reduce their brain size with the seasons. These mammals all have fast metabolisms, and they don't hibernate, which may explain why they take such drastic measures to reduce their energy needs when food is short.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ecologist William Thomas, from Stony Brook University in the US, led a study to map the common shrew's entire genome, comparing it to those of other mammals who also exhibit Dehnel's phenomenon to see what genetic tricks they have evolved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study builds on the team's &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-animal-can-shrink-its-brain-and-we-finally-know-how"&gt;previous work&lt;/a&gt;, which looked at seasonal changes in gene expression in two parts of the shrew's brain, and determined which sections of DNA were more active – and therefore possibly involved – during these massive bodily shifts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_189566" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-189566" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-642x428.jpeg" alt="a tiny brown shrew is peeking out of a biologist's 'trap' box, held up to the camera with a blue gloved hand about four times the size of the shrew." class="size-medium wp-image-189566" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-642x428.jpeg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-1012x675.jpeg 1012w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-768x512.jpeg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-1536x1024.jpeg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-2048x1366.jpeg 2048w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/original-1-600x400.jpeg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-189566" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;In 2025, researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cub.2025.08.015"&gt;discovered&lt;/a&gt; that the shrew's seasonal brain shrinkage is caused by water loss, and yet brain cells survive. (&lt;a href="https://www.ab.mpg.de/764426/shrews"&gt;© Christian Ziegler / Max Planck Institute of Animal Behavior&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Putting that data together, the researchers found genes associated with the creation of brain cells were upregulated across multiple species that exhibit Dehnel's phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shrew specifically had amped up expression of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vascular_endothelial_growth_factor_A"&gt;&lt;em&gt;VEGFA&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a gene associated with blood-brain barrier permeability (which may improve nutrient sensing in the brain). Its genome was also enriched with genes associated with DNA repair and longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Water-regulation genes were also active, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cub.2025.08.015"&gt;supporting theories&lt;/a&gt; that shrews achieve reversible loss of brain volume &lt;a href="https://www.mpg.de/25258209/0827-ornr-rare-seasonal-brain-shrinkage-in-shrews-is-driven-by-water-loss-not-cell-death-987453-x"&gt;by losing water&lt;/a&gt;, not net brain cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/castingcall?utm_source=SA_website&amp;amp;utm_medium=article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=casting_call"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg" alt="Audition now for ScienceAlert's Casting Call" class="alignnone wp-image-189354 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-1200x509.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2026/01/Mid-Article-Promos-Casting-Call-1.jpg 1266w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="p1"&gt;The findings point to "a finely tuned system that enables common shrews to reversibly regulate brain shrinkage while avoiding the detrimental effects typically associated with neurodegeneration," the researchers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/molbev/msag006"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cell biologist Aurora Ruiz-Herrera from the Autonomous University of Barcelona &lt;a href="https://www.uab.cat/web/newsroom/news-detail/-1345830290613.html?detid=1345974943963"&gt;adds&lt;/a&gt;: "The role of genes related to energy homeostasis and the blood-brain barrier points to possible biomarkers and therapeutic targets for &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-may-start-at-the-brains-borders-scientists-discover"&gt;neurodegenerative diseases&lt;/a&gt;, always with the necessary caution when extrapolating to humans."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/molbev/msag006"&gt;Molecular Biology and Evolution&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 21:01:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxQZ3lDQUVqYkFSdnFqVlhEY1FQUmVjbGtfRTVzOV9iWGRNUGZjTk51VmRkcnVKWERaRUkwd3FoY2lmUVp6dGJFYk1DMG9NckdfOWpfcnljaHdDMWpqM0l2eHZkcFFIUUVPX1RWeDkyZGlyUXEwb3ZHdHozNU9qTS10Q0hjVnFvRUxRTlhuYUhzWU1IQnpwWEVZWA</guid></item><item><title>在堪萨斯州社区废水中检测到6种高浓度病毒- hayspost.com</title><link>https://hayspost.com/posts/737cea8b-a085-43e3-a2ab-b59cc43b3eea</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="p-4 text-lg text-gray-800 leading-loose"&gt;&lt;figure class="py-8"&gt;&lt;img class="mx-auto w-full sm:w-full md:w-1/2" src="https://media.eaglewebservices.com/public/2022/12/1671049425198.jpg" alt="Image Pixaby"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="text-center italic text-gray-700 text-sm pt-2"&gt;Image Pixaby&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Lawrence sees early flu peak as some health care providers require masking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;By:&lt;a href="https://kansasreflector.com/author/mayasmith/"&gt;Maya Smith&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://kansasreflector.com/2025/02/24/gov-laura-kelly-skeptical-kansas-houses-anti-tenure-legislation-will-reach-her-desk/"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Kansas Reflector&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LAWRENCE — Six viral diseases — including COVID-19, the flu and norovirus — have been found at high concentrations in Lawrence wastewater as Kansas communities face peak flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;COVID-19, influenza A and B, RSV, human metapneumovirus, and norovirus have all been detected at high concentrations in Lawrence &lt;a href="http://bit.ly/4niF8mr" target="_blank"&gt;wastewater&lt;/a&gt; within the last three weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wastewater data indicates trends of illnesses spreading within a community but does not correlate to exact case numbers, with doctors saying it’s normal to see high concentrations of respiratory illness during flu season. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Wastewater data does not measure individual cases, but it provides a reliable picture of how much virus is circulating in a community,” said Veronica White, preparedness and epidemiology coordinator for Lawrence-Douglas County Public Health. “This data captures viral genetic material shed by everyone using the sewer system. One factor that may be contributing to the higher concentrations of respiratory viruses seen in Lawrence’s wastewater is its larger population.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawrence is also seeing an early peak in influenza B compared to the rest of the country. Positive flu tests spiked the last week of 2025, with 32% of total flu tests coming back positive, according to data from the University of Kansas Health System.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some health care providers such as Watkins Health Center at the University of Kansas are requiring masks for all visitors, patients and staff due to a “record surge in respiratory illnesses,” according to a sign at the front door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;White said early rise in the flu doesn’t indicate a more dangerous flu season, but rather earlier circulation of the virus than usual. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Identifying this trend early through wastewater data allows people to take preventive steps, such as getting vaccinated, monitoring symptoms, and staying home when sick,” White said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wastewater data also indicated that a newer strain of COVID, known as the XFG or the Stratus variant, has accounted for 82.5% of positive COVID samples, with concentrations increasing by 25% in the last month. The variant has also been increasing nationally, White said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dana Hawkinson, medical director for Infection Control and Prevention program at University of Kansas Health System, said there are still large populations of people across the state who have not received a flu shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There have been a large number of people ill and circulators too in our communities. But (the flu) still remains at a high level at this point in time,” Hawkinson said. “There have been extremely low numbers of people not getting the vaccine. We know that we can help prevent this and people’s chances of severe illness and death with it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve Stites, chief medical officer at the University of Kansas Health System, said that &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/live/p7chEnUW0EI?si=2KN1bC2byLQI_f0H&amp;amp;t=678" target="_blank"&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt; are incredibly safe and effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hawkinson said flu symptoms include fever, cough, congestion, body aches and a sore throat rather than stomach bug symptoms, with the definitions often getting mixed up during flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wastewater data has also indicated that Salina is seeing medium concentrations of the same illnesses, except for influenza A, which is considered to be at a high concentration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Based on the data, we expect viral activity to continue in both Lawrence and Salina over the next few weeks,” White said. “As we move through flu season, we anticipate seeing elevated influenza activity reflected in the wastewater, especially as the season approaches its typical peak.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical experts continue to advise washing hands, covering coughs and not going into large public spaces when sick to prevent illnesses from spreading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You can still go get the flu vaccine,” Hawkinson said. “It’s still recommended, and you can do it now to protect yourself from infection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>hayspost.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 19:04:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9KN2lSbVhfVkxHa1M5VUVPZnhKVjRwNUczeTg4TGJ6emVtbm9jSVp2QnFNWTRSVlJSWVNSdkpDdUhrN3Z3ZmJtVlhMekFwYVNpTzNzXzdfRmlxeWRjdlBGX0Y2VzBsZnhuR0ZRTE5oODU</guid></item><item><title>我的朋友被吸入了育儿社区最黑暗的群体之一。我受不了她-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2026/01/parenting-advice-friend-baby-vaccination.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="22" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseajw40029cvkkcm75wycu@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is a newsletter bonus question. Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseajw4002acvkk8tjb2xnz@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="52" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksealum000a3b7bywgye87z@published"&gt;My friend, “Angela”, who is in her 30s, is the first of my friends to have a baby. Her circle is small, and so is her fiancé’s. He is new to the state. They decided to try for a baby after just six months of dating, and will be wed this summer.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="59" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksealwz000b3b7bwo2w5sxf@published"&gt;Angela is a hippie, and a victim of abuse at the hands of her father, brother, and past partners. One partner in particular was conspiratorial, and as a result, she has never received a COVID vaccine. In 2022, I was unable to see her before my abortion in the case that I might need surgery—I couldn’t risk contracting COVID.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="41" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksealz6000c3b7blcr322gu@published"&gt;During her pregnancy, we talked about vaccination, and Angela told our friend group she intended on getting the baby vaccinated. She also told us she would get the Tdap shot during her pregnancy, though she never confirmed actually having done so.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseam1g000d3b7bgapsqsxl@published"&gt;Angela is now a stay-at-home mom with a four-month-old baby. I love this baby. I love the title of “auntie.” But Angela is becoming overprotective and delusional. She has no media literacy and is sharing anti-vaccine posts on Facebook. When challenged, she thanks me for my help, but it rings hollow. She talks often about “hating Trump,” but is now parroting a lot of his ideals. I can’t be friends with someone who doesn’t vaccinate their baby! How can I get through to her?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseam68000f3b7bvzjsk7cd@published"&gt;—Vaccinated&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksecyl2000p3b7bwu8lwwt8@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Vaccinated,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="83" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksed31r000u3b7be07orskk@published"&gt;Few things going on here! But the most glaring is that your friend’s baby is &lt;em&gt;four months old, &lt;/em&gt;meaning your friend is just &lt;em&gt;four-months postpartum. &lt;/em&gt;This is a hard, hard time for her—she’s isolated, she’s sleep deprived, her body and hormones are still doing strange things, and she’s got this living creature to take care of. You call her “overprotective and delusional,” but another way to put that might be “suffering from postpartum depression.” (Not a doctor! Just musing here, but like, c’mon.)&lt;/p&gt;

  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="86" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkskwx3q003p3b7bliufjnyr@published"&gt;Right now, the best thing you could do for your friend would be to encourage her to speak to her doctor about how she’s feeling. And the next best thing would be to just be there for her, listen to her, be compassionate, and supportive, and yes, offer one IRL data point of dissent on the vax front (e.g., when she brings it up or posts about it, simply reply: “I’ve read the same stuff you have. And I still believe vaccinations save lives,” or whatever).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksg8olw003g3b7bm4qyhb60@published"&gt;As for “getting through to her” beyond that—good luck. We live in an information hellhole right now. Her media illiteracy and vax hesitancy is the result of societal failure, not her own personal or moral shortcoming. Her baby’s pediatrician will have many opportunities, and some authority, to talk her about vaccines. And there will (likely, probably, definitely, depending on where you live) be many checks in the future that could spur vaccination: daycare registration, school registration, camp registration. This isn’t your problem to solve.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="59" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksl0frn003t3b7b3smdcrrm@published"&gt;But if this is a red line for you, then sure, tell her that and peace out. It sounds like you might be looking for a reason to do that anyway—judgment for your pal is just oozing from your letter, before you even mention vaccines. Your friend could definitely use a friend, but it doesn’t have to be you.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseajw4002ccvkka4ghvgn9@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Logan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmkseajw4002dcvkkaubsb3st@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Classic Prudie

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="122" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkseajw4002ecvkkc88h50gq@published"&gt;I’m a personal assistant to a highly accomplished woman a few years older than me whom I admire and respect a great deal. I’ve worked with her for five years, and we have a close professional relationship. This weekend, we were together late one night when she confided in me how lonely she was; the long hours we work make it difficult for her to maintain a relationship, and she has few friends nearby. Then she told me how good it was to have someone she could confide in and how grateful she was that she could speak to me in confidence. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2016/01/dear-prudence-im-falling-in-love-with-my-boss.html"&gt;She gave me a look that under any other circumstance I would have taken as an invitation to kiss her. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmkseajw5002gcvkk4txv9xbq@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPeExpYmZnN2tiZkZZSVdZdGNkWEZncDIwOW1kN0E1T3BpOG5IQXpsck9ZRkJNaXh2NFBVX1FBWm5hX3VOdWJoOHRBM0pUMDU5eS1qSnFhb0Q2aUg3SjF6VW0tRV9lNDJsSXBLYW9JM0RCNXp1cFIyMXlOWlZEYjZ5WHo1cDU</guid></item><item><title>这种类型的运动在减少老年人体脂肪方面最有效- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/this-type-of-exercise-is-most-effective-at-reducing-body-fat-in-older-adults/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:54:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQY1hmeTFHYWdMVThaaHNBejgwbGt5bW53aFhZVU1NQmNVXzBSOG1qTHNqX3pYMDFfWHVaaGxDLUNlanhjWWhUc1dsdFFxQjlycVZ3UE9aNnZSM2RvMHE3dnJ2S0x1Y3kyalBQSE4xMWk0LWo1a0MwVzRkd29qaHdHUTNDUGNlY25IOGVIWElXWXhEZWFwVzhOU1lEMXNIeEdPWTRyWg</guid></item><item><title>我的粗鲁，爱管闲事的婆婆只是“不得不”走进我们做爱。我们的性生活永远不会是一样的。- Slate</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2026/01/sex-mother-in-law-advice-erectile-dysfunction-treatment-options.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkslb2nz003orzmcfjk3izo0@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkslliz000213b7cqya7d1pl@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="43" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleobt00173b7cu526hkp1@published"&gt;My husband and I went over to his parents’ for the Christmas holiday. His mother has never been particularly respectful of boundaries, but we thought we were safe to go at it at nearly 3 a.m. There’s no way she’d be up, then, right? Wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

    


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="95" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksllz6c00233b7c4l8qdomg@published"&gt;My MIL decided there was something she just HAD to ask us that couldn’t wait until the next day, and she walked in on us. Things were rather awkward in the morning, but I thought it was just one of those dumb things and that would be the end of it. Instead it’s been the end of our sex life, namely the fact that my husband hasn’t been able to get it up since the incident. I’ve tried everything—pussy shaving, sexy lingerie, sucking his dick—nothing works. Both of us are extremely worried and don’t know what to do. Help!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleofp00183b7cd50j256p@published"&gt;—Trying to Raise the Dead&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleoit00193b7clrxkepxb@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Trying to Raise the Dead,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="54" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleoly001a3b7ciz8qjcqf@published"&gt;Please relax. Not a lot of time has passed, and you’ve pinpointed a cause for the E.D. Plenty of people with non-working dicks and their partners write into this column having no idea why it’s happening. You at least have a leg up. It’s not the &lt;em&gt;dick up t&lt;/em&gt;hat you desire, but it’s something.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="190" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleop4001b3b7ckpe56478@published"&gt;Here’s what I would try: Work on eliminating the intrusive thoughts of this incident. This could be accomplished via therapy and/or a meditation practice. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/11/wife-secret-sex-toy-advice-tracking.html"&gt;I went into my practice in a previous column&lt;/a&gt;, so visit that page for tips. I have found that building the meditation muscle gives me the ability to pick and choose what my mind focuses on. It’s not 100 percent (I have not completely eliminated being haunted by disturbing thoughts or images) but I am doing much better than I did before, and I didn’t even know it was possible to not think about things that were bothering me. Your impulse to do whatever you can to help the matter is heartening and logical, but this issue may be above your pay grade. This is especially so if the root of the cause is, as it seems to be, that he feels “caught,” ashamed, like his boundaries were crossed, or like he’s somehow now associating sex with his mom. This is where working with a therapist/coach could really help. Couples counseling could be an option, but this may be something he mostly handles on his own.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="79" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleotl001c3b7curxc3zf7@published"&gt;I would also get your husband some kind of wood-boosting assistance. Physiologically, he may not really need a PDE5 inhibitor like Viagra and/or a cock ring, but just having them can allay the anxiety that comes with and further exacerbates erectile dysfunction. Boner pills tend to be well-tolerated, and while some guys experience side effects (to the point of making the drugs off-putting), I think trying them is worth the small risk here—just to get him over the hump.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="76" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleoxs001d3b7c4suc4f9y@published"&gt;Also, try focusing on sex that doesn’t require his penis to be hard. Maybe that means he focuses on you orally/manually or that you introduce toys. Play in that space for a bit. Allowing him to get comfortable with this kind of contact may take the edge off and he may find himself able to perform. Again, this boner-killing event was fairly recent so giving it some time is also likely going to be useful. Patience!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmksleqjr001i3b7cphfykdj7@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Rich&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmkslivws001v3b7ccilb43mj@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmkslj14l001y3b7cfe5pdf8m@published"&gt;I’m in a polyamorous relationship with my boyfriend. It’s not really my thing, but I agreed to give it a shot because I really like him. We’ve had our ups and downs, but our biggest hangup is that he doesn’t want to give me “veto” power over who he sleeps with. That hasn’t been a problem, really—until now. Recently, he told me he’s very attracted to my friend, and wants to hook up with her. I, um, hate this. For some reason, it’s making me super jealous, but I agreed to a relationship structure where he gets to do what he wants. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2022/10/boyfriend-relationship-rules-friend-sex-advice.html"&gt;What should I do?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmkslb2nz003rrzmc6ai43tch@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQQ3o2SUkyUUl4UHdTeFBaWUtXWG03RWR3M1drQjhsbHNYZEJ2YnJ0MFMzNE1mUmdkR1R3MGtxZ005eGN2aFV5UXFDdEd1NG13RFAzZm43RWRlMDE3bDFBWlQ5ZzlLUGhybzlkUGZ5akVSbl9jVE4xYWhadzRhYWZzUVZ1V2xuYVRjcGUtTlRucDlNVnBFUnZzZDQwM25LeG1aYmM4</guid></item><item><title>非洲顶级卫生官员抨击特朗普政府在非洲进行人体实验的计划-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/health-medicine/vaccines-africa-trump</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="article-featured-image-figure"&gt;
			
			
	&lt;p class="article-featured-image-caption-container"&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="article-featured-image-caption"&gt;
			Illustration by Tag Hartman-Simkins / Futurism. Source: Samuel Corum / Getty Images 		&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/figure&gt;
	
	
	
	
	
	&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;Last week, officials at the Africa Centres for Disease Control and Prevention (Africa CDC) announced that health authorities in Guinea-Bissau had moved to &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/trump-rfk-africa-vaccines"&gt;halt a controversial study&lt;/a&gt; which would have used unvaccinated infants as lab rats. The US Department of Health and Human Services (HHS), however, insisted the trial was still on.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;That wasn’t all US health authorities had to say. In a bizarre outburst, the HHS &lt;a href="https://futurism.com/health-medicine/trump-hhs-africa-cdc"&gt;told &lt;em&gt;Futurism&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that the Africa CDC was a “fake and powerless organization,” and insisted that it was “not a reliable source” for information. During a &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2jhDb-r2jDc" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;press meeting&lt;/a&gt; on Thursday, director-general of the Africa CDC Jean Kaseya hit back.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Let me tell you: we are not an NGO,” Kaseya said defiantly. “We are not a UN organization. We are the convening power in Africa. The mandate [is] given to us by all 55 African heads of state and government.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“People can meet in the US, people can meet in Europe,” Kaseya continued, likely referencing &lt;a href="https://www.rollingstone.com/politics/politics-news/danish-vaccine-study-emails-hhs-rfk-jr-1235498456/" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;leaked emails&lt;/a&gt; between HHS officials and Danish researchers to push the vaccine trial in Guinea-Bissau. “If we are not there, they are wasting their time.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Kaseya also made it clear that no government has the right to impose experiments on the people of Guinea-Bissau.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Africa CDC is respecting and supporting the sovereignty of the country,” the official continued. “It’s not Africa CDC that will say, ‘this clinical trial will take place or not.’ It’s not any other international body that will come to say, ‘this clinical trial will take place or not.’ It’s not a foreign country that will come and say, ‘this one will take place.’ It’s the sovereignty of the country.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Though the HHS evidently thinks it has the power to push dangerous vaccines experiments on African countries, the reality isn’t so simple. According to the &lt;a href="https://africacdc.org/news-item/africa-cdc-guidance-for-any-clinical-trial-to-be-conducted-in-africa/" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;Africa CDC’s guidelines&lt;/a&gt;, any vaccine trial that doesn’t receive a written authorization from the country’s National Medicines Regulatory Authority is illegal. Likewise, it must have approval from the National Ethics Committee, as well as a local institutional review board at each site where the trial is to take place.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;On top of all that, any trial must also have explicit approval from the country’s Ministry of Health — granting officials in Guinea-Bissau the power to functionally veto any experiment the government doesn’t support.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Kaseya emphasized the importance of exercising sovereignty over African public health. “Our vision is not coming from Western countries,” he said. “Our vision is coming from Africa, shaped by African leadership, based on African realities.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;In an &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2026/jan/23/guinea-bissau-hepatitis-b-vaccine-study" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;interview with the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Abdulhammad Babatunde, a doctor and global health researcher in Nigeria, said that it’s “very important to fund research that Africans actually want.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Africans want to solve Africa’s problems, not satisfy the curiosity of the funders,” Babatunde said, referring to the HHS, which announced the &lt;a href="https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2025/12/18/2025-23245/notice-of-award-of-a-single-source-unsolicited-grant-to-fund-university-of-southern-denmark-sdu#page-59125" rel="noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;$1.6 million funding package&lt;/a&gt; for the study in December. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Once up and running, the vaccine trial would have given 7,000 newborn children a vaccine for hepatitis B, while 7,000 more infants in the control group wouldn’t receive the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;As the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt; notes, nearly one in five adults and 11 percent of children in Guinea-Bissau have hepatitis B — which carries a significant risk for debilitating illness and death. In such a health environment, there’s no justification for purposefully leaving infants unvaccinated for any length of time.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“This is not acceptable,” Babatunde told the paper. “To prevent things like the Tuskegee study and others, the control group has to get the standard of care, and the intervention group should get [potentially] better care.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Asked whether the HHS’s comments would affect future collaboration with Africa CDC, Kaseya said he’s putting the strange episode behind him.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“I was briefed that they don’t know anything about any statement against Africa CDC,” he said. “I could tell you about a statement that could be somewhere, made by someone. But officials from HHS just yesterday — senior people — said they don’t know anything about the statement. I trust them, I’ve closed the chapter.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on Africa: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/artificial-intelligence/ai-companion-chatbots-kenya"&gt;AI “Companion Bots” Actually Run by Exploited Kenyans, Worker Claims&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTFBXT1FhSnNmeE1oU1RvMGJmbktBWUJaM3BnOHJ5MkdueG8yV09WcU5YZmlzWXlqcW9MRExuOTF4THdfdmRrNlhRTXhXQ3lSdDJ5SHJzRm9USlU0N3pSQzRuZmRydk5QUzIwYmc</guid></item><item><title>由于官员发出严重警告，印度报告了无法治愈和“潜在流行病”的致命病毒爆发- LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/india-nipah-virus-outbreak-symptoms-deadly-illness-no-cure-who-warning-577116-20260124</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Indian health officials are currently battling to contain an outbreak of a deadly virus which has no vaccine or cure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;There are currently least five confirmed cases of Nipah virus (NiV) in the eastern state of West Bengal, which is the fourth most populous state in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Three nurses, a doctor and a member of &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;health&lt;/a&gt; staff - who all share links to the same private hospital - have been infected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;One of the patients is currently in a 'critical' condition, the West Bengal health department said. Experts are still working to determine how the five people contracted the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;But according &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/global-health/science-and-disease/health-experts-scramble-to-contain-nipah-outbreak-india/"&gt;to&lt;/a&gt; The Telegraph, one of the nurses who was first infected caught Nipah virus while treating a patient with severe respiratory symptoms - who later died before testing could be carried out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Almost 100 people who have been in close contact with the infected have been quarantined and are under observation, state officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"All of them are asymptomatic and tested negative," said Narayan Swaroop Nigam, who is the Principal Secretary of the Health and Family Welfare Department in West Bengal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;The virus is contagious, deadly and has no cure (C. K Thanseer/DeFodi images via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"We will again test them before their 21-day quarantine ends," Nigam added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The World Health Organisation (WHO) classes Nipah virus as a high-risk priority pathogen, meaning it has the potential to cause an 'epidemic'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It has earned itself a spot on the organisation's Research &amp;amp; Development Blueprint &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.who.int/teams/blueprint/nipah-henipaviruses#:~:text=Nipah%20virus%20is%20one%20of,human%20transmission%20have%20been%20documented."&gt;list&lt;/a&gt; of epidemic threats as a result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;With no approved vaccine or cure to remedy the zoonotic illness, the WHO previously &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.who.int/india/home/emergencies/nipah-virus-infection"&gt;warned&lt;/a&gt; that 'urgent' research and development is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;There have been no known cases of Nipah virus reported in the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/uk-news"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt; to date, however, the Health Security Agency (UKHSA) is now intently monitoring the situation in &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/world-news"&gt;India&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;According to the WHO, the illness is transmitted to people from &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/animals"&gt;animals&lt;/a&gt;, although people can also get struck down by it after eating contaminated &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/food-and-drink"&gt;food&lt;/a&gt;. It can then spread directly from person-to-person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Guidance from the UK government also &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.gov.uk/guidance/nipah-virus-epidemiology-outbreaks-and-guidance"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt;: "Close and direct, unprotected contact with infected patients, especially those with respiratory symptoms, has been implicated as a transmission risk."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;A health worker seen wearing protective gear disposes biohazard waste from a Nipah virus isolation centre during an outbreak in India in 2023 (AFP via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Those who have been infected usually begin to experience symptoms which are comparable to the flu or a fever - but it can later trigger fatal brain swelling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Signs of Nipah virus include a temperatures, headaches, myalgia (muscle pain), vomiting and sore throat, as well as dizziness, drowsiness, altered consciousness, and &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/mental-health"&gt;neurological&lt;/a&gt; issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The WHO states: "Some people can also experience atypical pneumonia and severe respiratory problems, including acute respiratory distress."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In severe cases, patients may develop &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/community/encephalitis-lethargica-explained-symptoms-cause-149011-20250803"&gt;encephalitis&lt;/a&gt; - the life-threatening inflammation of the&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;brain - or seizures, which the WHO says can then lead on to 'a coma within 24 to 48 hours'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;According to the WHO, 40 percent to 75 percent of cases of Nipah virus end in fatalities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The virus was first recognised in 1999 during an outbreak among pig farmers in Malaysia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;It is thought to have been transmitted to humans via exposure to secretions from the animals, or unprotected contact with the tissue of a sick pig.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Bats have been blamed for previous outbreaks of Nipah virus in India (Soumyabrata Roy/NurPhoto via Getty Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Nipah was also found in Bangladesh in 2001, and nearly annual outbreaks have occurred in that country since.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Evidence of the virus has also been found in bat species in a number of countries, including Cambodia, Ghana, Indonesia, Madagascar, the Philippines and Thailand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Subsequent outbreaks in India have been attributed to infected fruit bats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;India's Ministry of Health and Family Welfare shared a post on &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/social-media"&gt;social media&lt;/a&gt; encouraging people to 'follow essential precautions to prevent infection'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;People are being urged to wash fruit and vegetables thoroughly, clean their hands with soap and water and to wear protective clothing when in contact with animals, among other advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The government also warned people to avoid eating 'contaminated and half-eaten fruits from trees' as well as raw date palm juice and toddy-like liquid kept in open pots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:54:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxPc0JyUlgwVUx4eG0yUDZuN29mVlBHdU1YSFVDSndGRnktcDFubFlPenRsUWRFcVA2am5xVk5QR3VScXlsSEhyN2NEOG5OaWxEdlc0Q0FWVkI3VVpQVTYySml4ejcyVWwtQ1ZuOU1manV0aVVyMEZqU2hpSnZtYU5ESDY1Vkp6MFdRYW1hV2JVT19sYTJVMUhZYmJmSzFaU0F3WUdJOVBMV0V3UnhhaTZpUXVkclAyaElxMDVzR1czMWs</guid></item><item><title>当您每天服用欧米茄3补充剂时，您的血糖会发生什么？ - Verywell Health</title><link>https://www.verywellhealth.com/omega-3-supplements-and-blood-sugar-11865218</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="health-sc-page_1-0" class="comp health-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content article-content expert-content right-rail__offset lock-journey" data-sc-sticky-offset="60" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[400, 1400, 1400, 1700, 2000, 2200, 2400, 2600, 2800]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="health-sc-block-callout--key-takeaway_1-0" class="comp health-sc-block-callout--key-takeaway health-sc-block-callout-base mntl-sc-block-callout mntl-block theme-key-takeaway theme-key-takeaway" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-callout-heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Key Takeaways&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block-callout-body_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-body mntl-text-block expert-content"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;There is insufficient scientific evidence that daily omega-3 supplementation lowers blood sugar (glucose) levels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;An elevated blood sugar level is a hallmark feature of diabetes, a lifelong condition that is typically managed with a combination of medication, nutrition therapy, and physical activity.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;If you are considering taking an omega-3 supplement, speak with your healthcare provider first to avoid medication interactions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Omega-3 supplements, also called fish oil supplements, contain a type of fat found in shellfish and cold-water fish like salmon, mackerel, and tuna.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Results from scientific studies on whether taking a daily omega-3 supplement impacts blood sugar (glucose) levels are mixed, with emerging evidence leaning towards minimal to no effect.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-omega-3s-inconsistent-effect-on-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Omega-3's Inconsistent Effect on Blood Sugar &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Elevated blood sugar levels due to defects in insulin production or action are characteristic of diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Without careful management, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/type-2-diabetes-complications-5120942" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;diabetes can lead to serious complications&lt;/a&gt; involving the eyes, kidneys, heart, and nerves.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Due to the seriousness and chronicity of diabetes, scientists have launched an extensive and ongoing investigation into the potential role of supplements, like &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/benefits-of-omega-3-11772277" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;omega-3 fatty acids&lt;/a&gt;, in both preventing diabetes and serving as an adjunct to traditional diabetes medications.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Despite substantial scientific investigation, results regarding the effect of omega-3 supplementation on blood sugar levels have been inconsistent.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Specifically, while some studies have found that &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/how-to-choose-omega-3-supplement-11845012" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;omega-3 supplementation&lt;/a&gt; lowers blood sugar levels, others have reported little to no impact.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-do-the-scientific-studies-show"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Do the Scientific Studies Show? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One example of a study reporting conflicting results on the impact of omega-3 on blood sugar is a 2024 study in &lt;em&gt;Current Nutrition Reports. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Basics of the study include the following:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This study&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;reviewed 30 randomized controlled trials involving participants, primarily adults, with one of three forms of diabetes: &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/type-2-diabetes-7371634" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/type-1-diabetes-7971457" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;type 1 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/glucose-tests-in-pregnancy-5115077" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;gestational diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participants received omega-3 supplements of varying types and doses for six weeks to 12 months.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The trial found that some participants experienced a reduction in fasting blood glucose levels with omega-3 supplementation, whereas others showed no change.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Investigators noted that such differences in trial results could be attributable to factors like:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Number of participants in each trial&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trial duration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Participants' age and, specifically, how long they have had diabetes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dosage of the omega-3 supplement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Other examples of studies addressing the uncertain role of daily omega-3 supplementation on blood sugar levels include:&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;A 2022 study reviewed 30 randomized controlled trials involving participants with and without diabetes&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Results revealed that omega-3 supplementation led to a significant reduction in fasting blood sugar levels. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A 2020 study reviewed 12 randomized controlled trials involving just over 800 adults with type 2 diabetes. &lt;strong&gt;Results revealed that&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;omega-3 supplementation did not affect blood sugar levels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A 2019 study reviewed 83 randomized controlled trials involving more than 120,000 individuals with and without diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The average trial period lasted nearly three years. &lt;strong&gt;Results revealed that increasing omega-3 intake, whether through supplements or foods (fish or plants), had minimal to no effect on blood glucose levels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-should-i-take-an-omega-3-supplement"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Should I Take an Omega-3 Supplement? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Overall, there is insufficient evidence to support the claim that omega-3 supplements can improve blood glucose control.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The American Diabetes Association (ADA) does not universally recommend omega-3 supplementation for individuals with diabetes.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Omega-3 supplementation is also not formally recommended for individuals with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/pre-diabetes-4014095" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;prediabetes&lt;/a&gt;, a common health condition marked by high blood sugar levels that are not yet elevated enough to fulfill a diagnosis of diabetes.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; All said, there is some evidence, albeit mixed, that omega-3 supplements may improve cardiovascular health in individuals with diabetes and risk factors for heart disease, like high cholesterol.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Given this potential link, your healthcare provider may recommend omega-3 supplements based on your personal heart disease risk factors.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="health-sc-block-callout--takeaway_1-0" class="comp health-sc-block-callout--takeaway health-sc-block-callout-base mntl-sc-block-callout mntl-block theme-takeaway theme-takeaway" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-callout-heading_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Speak to Your Diabetes Healthcare Provider&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block-callout-body_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-callout-body mntl-text-block expert-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Always consult your healthcare provider before starting an omega-3 supplement to ensure it's safe and appropriate for your care. Omega-3 supplements may interact with certain medications, like blood thinners.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If your provider recommends an omega-3 supplement, side effects are generally mild, with common ones being:&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Unpleasant supplement taste&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bad breath&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gastrointestinal disturbances (e.g., discomfort, nausea, diarrhea, heartburn)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-using-diet-to-improve-blood-sugar-control"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block health-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Using Diet to Improve Blood Sugar Control &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For those with prediabetes or diabetes, the ADA recommends adopting a healthy eating pattern to optimize blood sugar control and prevent diabetes-related complications.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While no single diet suits everyone, the &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/mediterranean-diet-for-beginners-8709362" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt; is a good fit for many. First, check in with your healthcare provider.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The Mediterranean diet is nonrestrictive, offers tasty choices, and has been found to reduce blood sugar levels.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It consists of nutrient-dense foods like fruit, vegetables, and lean protein, as well as foods rich in omega-3s from both animal and plant sources, such as fatty fish, olive oil, and walnuts.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="post-article_1-0" class="comp post-article mntl-block"&gt;
&lt;div id="sources_1-0" class="comp sources mntl-block"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-article-sources_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-sources mntl-expandable-block" data-scroll-offset="70"&gt;&lt;div class="loc expandable-content"&gt;&lt;div id="source-guidelines_1-0" class="comp source-guidelines mntl-text-block"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verywell Health uses only high-quality sources, including peer-reviewed studies, to support the facts within our articles. Read our &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/verywell-editorial-process-4777042"&gt;editorial process&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; to learn more about how we fact-check and keep our content accurate, reliable, and trustworthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-article-sources__citation-sources_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-sources__citation-sources mntl-citation-sources mntl-sources" data-tracking-container="true"&gt; &lt;ol class="mntl-sources__content"&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-5"&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Center for Complementary and Integrative Health. &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/omega3-supplements-what-you-need-to-know" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Omega-3 supplements: what you need to know&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Center for Complementary and Integrative Health. &lt;a href="https://www.nccih.nih.gov/health/providers/digest/type-2-diabetes-and-dietary-supplements-science" class="pseudoStyle" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Type 2 diabetes and dietary supplements: what the science says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-4"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bayram SŞ, Kızıltan G. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s13668-024-00561-9" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;The role of omega- 3 polyunsaturated fatty acids in diabetes mellitus management: a narrative review&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Curr Nutr Rep&lt;/em&gt;. 2024 Sep;13(3):527-551. doi:10.1007/s13668-024-00561-9&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-12"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Delpino FM, Figueiredo LM, da Silva BGC, et al. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/10408398.2021.1875977" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Omega-3 supplementation and diabetes: a systematic review and meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Crit Rev Food Sci Nutr&lt;/em&gt;. 2022;62(16):4435-4448. doi: 10.1080/10408398.2021.1875977&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gao C, Liu Y, Gan Y, et al. &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1186/s12944-020-01214-w" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Effects of fish oil supplementation on glucose control and lipid levels among patients with type 2 diabetes mellitus: a Meta-analysis of randomized controlled trials&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Lipids Health Dis&lt;/em&gt;. 2020 May 8;19(1):87. doi:10.1186/s12944-020-01214-w&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-11"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brown TJ, Brainard J, Song F, Wang X, Abdelhamid A, Hooper L; PUFAH Group. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/bmj.l4697" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Omega-3, omega-6, and total dietary polyunsaturated fat for prevention and treatment of type 2 diabetes mellitus: systematic review and meta-analysis of randomised controlled trials&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;BMJ&lt;/em&gt;. 2019 Aug 21;366:l4697. doi:10.1136/bmj.l4697&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-8"&gt;&lt;p&gt;ElSayed NA, Aleppo G, Aroda VR, et al. 5. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.2337/dc23-S005" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Facilitating positive health behaviors and well-being to improve health outcomes: standards of care in diabetes-2023&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Diabetes Care&lt;/em&gt;. 2023;46(Supple 1):S68-S96. doi:10.2337/dc23-S005&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-9"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bhatt DL, Steg PG, Miller M, et al. REDUCE-IT Investigators. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1056/NEJMoa1812792" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Cardiovascular risk reduction with icosapent ethyl for hypertriglyceridemia&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;N Engl J Med&lt;/em&gt;. 2019;380(1):11-22. doi:10.1056/NEJMoa1812792&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-7"&gt;&lt;p&gt;National Institutes of Health. &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/Omega3FattyAcids-HealthProfessional/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Omega-3 fatty acids: fact sheet for health professionals&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class="mntl-sources__source" id="citation-10"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Martín-Peláez S, Fito M, Castaner O. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu12082236" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Mediterranean diet effects on type 2 diabetes prevention, disease progression, and related mechanisms. a review&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Nutrients&lt;/em&gt;. 2020;12(8):2236. doi: 10.3390/nu12082236&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="author-bio_1-0" class="comp author-bio"&gt;

&lt;p class="author-bio__bio-text"&gt;
&lt;span class="author-bio__bio-title"&gt;By &lt;a href="https://www.verywellhealth.com/colleen-doherty-md-4021130"&gt;Colleen Doherty, MD&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Dr. Doherty is a board-certified internist and writer living with multiple sclerosis. She is based in Chicago.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="trust-ribbon_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon trust-ribbon-expandable-block"&gt; 
&lt;div class="loc expandable-content"&gt;&lt;div id="trust-ribbon__feedback-block_1-0" class="comp trust-ribbon__feedback-block article-feedback mntl-article-feedback"&gt; 
&lt;div class="article-feedback__success-section js-success-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;Thanks for your feedback!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="article-feedback__feedback-section js-feedback-section is-hidden"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-feedback__heading"&gt;What is your feedback?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;button id="helpful-button_1-0" class="comp helpful-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Helpful
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="report-error-button_1-0" class="comp report-error-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Report an Error
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;button id="other-button_1-0" class="comp other-button mntl-button article-feedback__feedback-button"&gt; Other
&lt;/button&gt;
&lt;svg class="icon icon-x close-button"&gt;
&lt;use xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xlink:href="#icon-x" href="#icon-x"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Verywell Health</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:13:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxPU2lnU0FmSjNKeUhZcjJPcHd5ckwtelJHV1JvdndQQkVwRzIzajRFNy1JMzVxUFlMZU5KaS1zcDFjdG9Id3dwU2pXNjNEWGxZTGdHYUg1eHhDaWM1ZS1kYy01NXZpVldUdXZyNE5Fek5uX2czV1B0SHdwVWZFbUhJbA</guid></item><item><title>一位烹饪书作者连续6年每天吃巧克力蛋糕。现在她分享她的食谱- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2026/01/24/health/everyday-chocolate-cake-recipe-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1pxwu004e26p2h8rc0rym@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Go ahead, eat chocolate cake every day. One healthy cookbook author gives us permission — and a recipe that’s protein-packed.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c0006356p1iwz1hx4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Rachel Riggs’ signature unfussy cake asks for just one bowl, a single whisk and 10 minutes to get the oven ready. The result is a chocolate dessert that contains 18 grams of &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/15/health/how-to-eat-more-protein-diet-wellness"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt; per slice and tastes so amazing that Riggs ate a piece as part of lunch daily for six years straight.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c0007356pn407f9a7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            No wonder she named it The Everyday Chocolate Cake.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c0008356pngjnttr2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This is a legit dessert. I think it’s virtually indistinguishable from any mainstream chocolate cake,” said Riggs, who included it in her debut cookbook, “&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Good-Health-Uncomplicated-Allergen-Aware-Nourished/dp/1773272780" target="_blank"&gt;In Good Health&lt;/a&gt;: Uncomplicated, Allergen-Aware Recipes for a Nourished Life.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c0009356p4h09y2d3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In this cake, the almond flour provides healthy fats, and the pure maple syrup, cocoa powder and unsweetened chocolate deliver antioxidants. Eggs are nutrition powerhouses, too,” Riggs explained.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000a356pz4e1uhav@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Each serving of this cake has as much &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0031938420304376" target="_blank"&gt;appetite-taming&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/nutritionreviews/article/79/1/66/5936522" target="_blank"&gt;muscle-building&lt;/a&gt; protein as three large eggs, which is courtesy of the almond flour, eggs and cocoa powder. (The cocoa powder alone adds about &lt;a href="https://fdc.nal.usda.gov/food-details/169593/nutrients" target="_blank"&gt;4 grams per ¼ cup&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;Each egg tacks on 6 grams, and each cup of almond flour layers on 32 grams more protein.) Keep in mind that it also has 39 grams of sugar per slice (including the ganache), courtesy of the natural sweetener maple syrup, so you can determine how often you’d like to slot this into your diet.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000b356p56d96yat@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The inspiration for this cake came from a not-so-sweet place. Riggs has been passionate about food for as long as she can remember.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000c356pyqexetzo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Cheese is where my deepest passion was, so I opened a specialty food shop in 2006. Within four years, there was a substantial shift in my health, so I was forced to close my shop,” the author recalled.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000d356pp0u6wsdf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The symptoms started off subtly but grew over time to the point that the profound fatigue they triggered resulted in “punishing payback for hours, days — or sometimes weeks,” she said. “Like so many people with chronic illness, I went from doctor to doctor, then started broadening my scope and traveling for medical care. It remained a mystery.”
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000e356png00a6nx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            During her mission to try anything that might ease the pain and fatigue, Riggs embarked on a doctor-approved, strict elimination diet.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000f356pit343apj@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I went three months without this whole swath of ingredients,” Riggs said. “Eventually, I was able to start adding those things in, and that’s how you identify if something isn’t a good fit for your body.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000g356p8swkc1o9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Riggs  discovered she felt better eliminating her original potential triggers, including  grains (not just gluten), dairy, refined sugars, legumes, peanuts, shellfish  and nightshades (a class of vegetables that includes tomatoes, potatoes,  peppers and eggplants). She still finds plenty  of different   foods to   eat, such   as meat, fish, seafood, fruits, many nuts, most vegetables, seeds,  herbs and spices.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000h356psee1lqwi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Looking to cook with a limited ingredient   list, Riggs found inspiring options lacking and started  developing  her own recipes “to feed myself and my husband food that didn’t  feel punitive,” Riggs said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000i356px9b8y2a0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The result was her first cookbook, “In Good Health.” When pulling together those recipes, the nonnegotiables, she decided, were nourishment, deliciousness and ease.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000j356p19t1onch@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There aren’t any adaptations or faux foods here,” Riggs said. Instead, “it’s really just whole, nutrient-dense food. These are the recipes that I’ve been relying on for years.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000k356pd3x28q76@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Yes,  berries, sweet potatoes and salmon are on the menu. As is ahi tuna, roasted  almonds, rotisserie chicken and more. “Even if somebody doesn’t have their own restrictions, we’re all cooking for people that do these days,” she said. “This book is a great resource for when you’re cooking for friends or relatives who have dietary restrictions, say, for a holiday, which can be very daunting.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1c000l356prdh44wnt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Start with The Everyday Chocolate Cake&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;and   soon you’ll be trying Morning Glory Muffins,  Zesty Herbed Tahini Dip and Savory French Onion Beef.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000m356pkar5yrq5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Serves 6
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000n356p6gvu0nl8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Prep time:&lt;/strong&gt; 20 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000o356pfvvd9sg4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Bake time:&lt;/strong&gt; 25 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000p356psh8an5o6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Cool time:&lt;/strong&gt; 20 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000q356pd06r6p9c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;strong&gt;Total  cooking time:&lt;/strong&gt; 1 hour 5 minutes
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000r356p4r46y4wq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            One of Riggs’ most beloved cures  for her cravings is this cake, which gets its decadent crumb from the cocoa powder.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000s356pqv19y67i@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            She uses a premium cocoa powder with a higher fat content that gives it a richer flavor. “When you’re cooking with so few ingredients, the ingredients matter,” Riggs said. (That’s why she includes her product picks in the cookbook.)
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000t356p25uauhtc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Once you’ve mastered this version of The Everyday Chocolate Cake, Riggs gives you permission to mix things up. Try adding ⅛ teaspoon of mint extract to the ganache for a minty chocolate cookie vibe, she said, or add a drop or two of orange oil instead. Or bake the same batter in a cupcake pan for a single-serving dessert.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d000u356pfo4iwkd7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “My book also includes a birthday cake variation on this with a thicker, more spreadable ganache, because nobody should have to celebrate a birthday without a birthday cake,” Riggs told me.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmkh1znv0002m356pozqlrn0l@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list_elevate" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ul data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ul vossi-list_elevate__items vossi-list_elevate__items--ul"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Virgin coconut oil, for greasing
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            2 ½ cups (260 grams) superfine blanched almond flour
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ¼ cup (30 grams) cocoa powder, preferably Valrhona
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            1 teaspoon baking soda
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.4.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ¾ teaspoon Himalayan pink salt
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.5.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ¾ cup (235 grams) pure maple syrup
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.6.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            3 large eggs, room temperature
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

  

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmkh1vv1a002g356p5m87h0s3@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list_elevate" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ul data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ul vossi-list_elevate__items vossi-list_elevate__items--ul"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ¼ cup (60 grams) canned full-fat, additive-free coconut milk (see note)
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            2 ounces (57 grams) 100% unsweetened chocolate (see note)
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            2 tablespoons pure maple syrup
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            ⅛ teaspoon Himalayan pink salt
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

  

  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/list/instances/cmkh1rv7s001p356pj7f0j3au@published" class="list-elevate vossi-list_elevate" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
  &lt;ol data-editable="items" class="list__items list__items--ol vossi-list_elevate__items vossi-list_elevate__items--ol"&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.0.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Make the cake: Preheat oven to 350 degrees Fahrenheit (177 degrees Celsius). Thoroughly grease a 9-inch (23-centimeter) nonstick springform pan with coconut oil and line the bottom with parchment paper.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.1.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            In      a medium mixing bowl, whisk together almond flour, cocoa       powder, baking soda and salt, breaking up any      lumps. Add the maple syrup and eggs,      and whisk until smooth and combined well. Pour the batter into the springform pan. Using a rubber      spatula, spread it toward the edges and tap the pan on the counter to      level the batter.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.2.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Bake for 25 minutes on the center rack. Cool for 20 minutes, then transfer the cake to a serving plate.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.3.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Allow      the cake to cool completely before making the ganache.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.4.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Make the ganache: Combine all ganache ingredients in a small glass or porcelain      bowl and microwave for 30 seconds. Using a small whisk, whisk gently for 2      to 3 minutes, until the chocolate is melted, smooth, glossy and slightly      thickened but still pourable.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.5.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Pour the chocolate ganache onto the top (center) of the cake. Using an offset spatula or the back of a spoon, carefully spread the ganache over the cake, nudging it gently over the edge and allowing it to drip down the sides as much as you like.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.6.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Refrigerate the cake, uncovered, for 30 minutes so the ganache can set.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      
      &lt;li data-editable="items.7.text" class="list__item vossi-list_elevate__item inline-placeholder"&gt;
        &lt;span class="list__text vossi-list_elevate__text "&gt;
            Cover      and store at room temperature for up to three days, or in the fridge for up to a week.
        &lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmkh1rs1d0016356p0sjkhxyg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;em&gt;Note: Look for a baking bar that contains only cacao beans, such as baking bars by Guittard. Use full-fat coconut milk that&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;does not contain additives or thickening agents&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;— Riggs likes Trader Joe’s Organic Coconut Milk or Native Forest Organic Coconut Milk Simple.&lt;/em&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmkh1tl5o002a356p3xrmrl8g@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;a href="https://karlawalsh.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Karla Walsh&lt;/a&gt; is a Des Moines, Iowa-based freelance lifestyle writer with more than 16 years of editorial experience.
&lt;/p&gt;

  

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 16:00:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOeXJBZWpaVUhPQlZFVXBleEVEdXZEUkNWWmRUMFhrV1ZuRDBOWW1rU3FlTG1YdDBhaUhiRkx3UXNDRVlacmFvWFhzUUVTVW4ta2pqWTFycmZ4eUFReFJ5YWVhQzhSeDVVY0c3TjRKYk1XcC1rT0I5TlJtZU50N2Z3eU5udw</guid></item><item><title>一旦被枯萎病消灭，成千上万的美国栗树在缅因州生物学家的土地上蓬勃发展-好消息网络</title><link>https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/once-wiped-out-by-blight-thousands-of-american-chestnut-trees-are-thriving-on-biologists-land-in-maine/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_228669" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228669" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-228669" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew.jpg 1400w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-326x175.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-1024x550.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-768x413.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-696x374.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-1068x574.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-782x420.jpg 782w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Dr-Bernd-Heinrich-submitted-by-The-Wild-American-Chestnut-film-crew-530x285.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-228669" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Dr. Bernd Heinrich – The Wild American Chestnut&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wild American chestnut trees, deemed “functionally extinct” decades ago, may already be quietly mounting an unexpected comeback in the northern forests of the US.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thousands of naturally thriving, wild trees in Maine contradict decades of assumptions about the species’ extinction—and how genetic engineering is the only solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever since the accidental importation of an Asian virus in 1904 killed this majestic tree—once abundant along the U.S. East Coast and Canada—ghostly gaps left in the landscape haunted biologists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But a new documentary (&lt;em&gt;watch below&lt;/em&gt;) brought to light a remarkable and little-known success story: thousands of wild, healthy American chestnut trees are flourishing on the Maine forest land of renowned biologist and author Dr. Bernd Heinrich.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He bought 25 saplings for $10 from a nursery 44 years ago. They grew tall and their numbers multiplied as bluejays and squirrels plucked their seeds and buried them in fields as far away as a mile, and today there is no hint of blight in any of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These chestnuts are really taking off,” said the 85-year-old professor, who climbed to the top of one of the trees to fetch a sample of the fruit for the videographers. “And it could very well be that these are blight resistant.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The vigorous natural growth—which shows up in thousands of thriving grandchildren of the original trees—directly counters long-held beliefs that the iconic species survives today only as scattered, doomed sprouts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_228674" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228674" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-228674" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-%E2%80%93-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation.jpg 1400w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-326x148.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-1024x465.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-768x349.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-696x316.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-1068x485.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-925x420.jpg 925w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/Historical-Wild-American-chestnut-trees-–-Courtesy-The-American-Chestnut-Foundation-530x241.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-228674" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Historical American chestnut trees – Courtesy The American Chestnut Foundation&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Heinrich, professor emeritus of the Biology Department at the University of Vermont and author of more than 20 books on biology and 100 scientific papers (including the celebrated memoir &lt;a href="https://amzn.to/4r9hMRj" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;A Year in the Maine Woods&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), has spent more than four decades observing the chestnuts on his hundreds of acres.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ANOTHER CHESTNUT DISCOVERY:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/towering-chestnut-tree-found-in-maine-could-help-save-the-nearly-extinct-species/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Giant Chestnut Tree Found in Maine Could Help Save a Near-Extinct Species&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with University of Vermont students, Heinrich’s &lt;a href="https://bioone.org/journals/northeastern-naturalist/volume-29/issue-3/045.029.0302/The-Continued-Spread-of-a-Wild-Population-of-American-Chestnuts/10.1656/045.029.0302.short" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;team has documented&lt;/a&gt; well over a thousand thriving chestnut trees—some now representing three generations of natural regeneration. Each has been mapped via GPS during a long-term field study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new short film, The Wild American Chestnut, produced by &lt;a href="http://TheWildAmericanChestnut.org" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Global Justice Ecology Project&lt;/a&gt;, also captures Heinrich discussing projections that the American chestnut is shifting its range northward due to climate change, opening new opportunities for survival beyond its historical geographic limits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_228673" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-228673" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-228673" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license.jpg 974w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-326x232.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-768x547.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-100x70.jpg 100w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-696x496.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-589x420.jpg 589w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/American-Chestnut-Nuts-with-Burrs-and-Leaves-Credit-Timothy-Van-Vliet-2004-from-his-Orchard-in-New-Jersey-GNU-Free-license-530x378.jpg 530w" sizes="(max-width: 974px) 100vw, 974px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-228673" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;American Chestnut Nuts with Burrs and Leaves – Credit: Timothy Van Vliet from his Orchard in New Jersey in 2004 -GNU Free license&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These acres of thriving chestnuts magnify the major setbacks for the biotech-based tree restoration strategies of the past three decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In December 2023, The American Chestnut Foundation withdrew its support for a genetically engineered chestnut that was decades in development, after multiple documented research errors revealed the tree to be genetically defective. Discouraging field performance rendered them, in the Foundation’s opinion, unsuitable as the basis for species restoration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MORE FLOWERING SURPRISES&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/look-worlds-largest-prehistoric-flower-preserved-in-amber-is-stunning-reminded-of-natures-beauty/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;World’s Largest Prehistoric Flower Preserved in Amber is Stunning Reminder of Nature’s Wonder–LOOK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This film presents some good news about the wild American chestnut and is a stark contrast to claims by some researchers that genetically engineered trees are the only path to restoration,” said Anne Petermann, Executive Director of the Project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It was stunning to see so many robust trees—three full generations growing naturally—while the efforts to engineer blight-resistant chestnuts have produced nothing but failures.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ebywGe-J730?si=An6NOiQ9KcLGmyfR" title="YouTube video player" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SPREAD SEEDS OF GOOD NEWS By Sharing a Chestnut With Tree Lovers on Social Media…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 15:51:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxPekxKeWoyVTkxMlg3STBVeDVsRFNCVVdqMFhVVzNjcy15OFZvTFJBU3JuUFJ2aWNQYTI2dTZ6YnNtY0VXMzZLUTJHWjN5NE1Vd19vSFFHTEhyVjVYeFJaZlctTHM1V1hEaDY0R19ScUdLMXUzWjhlaEdGUEZ5WExNamZZSVUtYmVzVEVkc1Q0aTRyR3R6Y0VuQ1NaYmlwUmZyLWlyMC1KTUg1TmFGUVdHVnVMWU1sUE5lbGp2bXlLdjdfMjJkVlZTZTI2bVE4ODZX</guid></item><item><title>鲜为人知的补充剂可以帮助保护您免受真正的疾病：研究- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/little-known-supplement-help-protect-144940371.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Move over, multivitamins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell-metabolism/fulltext/S1550-4131(25)00542-X" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:New research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;New research&lt;/a&gt; suggests a little-known supplement could help protect people from severe illness or death after injury or infection, potentially giving the body an extra edge when it’s under attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings offer fresh insight into what scientists call the “disease trajectory” and how simple lifestyle changes might help steer people off a fast track toward decline and back on the road to recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Boosting intake of an essential amino acid may help the body bounce back faster from infection and injury. JGI/Jamie Grill/Blend Images – stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our study indicates that small biological differences, including dietary factors, can have large effects on disease outcomes,” &lt;a href="https://www.salk.edu/scientist/janelle-ayres/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Janelle Ayres;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Janelle Ayres&lt;/a&gt;, a professor at the Salk Institute for Biological Studies and the study’s senior author, said in &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-dietary-supplement-inflammation-injury-death.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a statement;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;a statement&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers focused specifically on methionine, an essential amino acid the body can’t produce on its own and must get from food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Methionine can be found in protein-rich staples like eggs, poultry, fish and beef, as well as plant-based options such as Brazil nuts, sesame seeds, soybeans, tofu, lentils and whole grains like quinoa. It’s also available in supplement form, typically in the form of &lt;a href="https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/compound/L-Methionine" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:L-methionine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;L-methionine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Methionine plays several important roles in the body, building proteins, supporting DNA activity and repairing damaged tissues. But Ayres and her colleagues were especially interested in its role in controlling inflammation, the immune system’s built-in fire alarm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inflammation kicks in whenever the body senses a threat, like an injury or infection. Immune cells swarm the area and release chemical messengers called pro-inflammatory cytokines, which coordinate the attack and kick-start the healing process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But too much of a good thing can seriously backfire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;L-methionine supplements are widely available in various forms, including capsules, tablets and powders. Serhii – stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;When inflammation spirals out of control, it can damage healthy cells and lead to organ damage and tissue death. That can trigger intense symptoms of illness and lead to serious complications, like fluid buildup in the lungs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the immune response never gets turned down, it can turn into &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2024/07/28/lifestyle/how-inflammaging-is-the-new-tool-to-end-cancer/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:chronic, low-grade inflammation;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;chronic, low-grade inflammation&lt;/a&gt; — a major driver of aging and diseases like cancer, diabetes and heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Pro-inflammatory cytokines are ultimately what leads to sickness and death in a lot of cases,” Dr. Katia Troha, a postdoctoral researcher in Ayres’s lab and first author of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The immune system has to balance inflammation to attack the invader without harming healthy cells in the body. Our job is to find the mechanisms it uses to do that, so that we can target them to improve patient outcomes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To see how that balance works, researchers used mice with systemic inflammation caused by the bacterium &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK430717/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Yersinia pseudotuberculosis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Yersinia pseudotuberculosis&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They quickly noticed the sick mice were eating less, a sign that their metabolism was changing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers checked their blood, they that their methionine levels had dropped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That sparked an idea. Troha fed a new group of mice chow supplemented with methionine and found that they were protected against the infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digging deeper, the team discovered methionine was working with an unexpected partner: The kidneys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Methionine supplementation improved kidney function, helping tamp down inflammation in the body. Peakstock – stock.adobe.com&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The amino acid boosted kidney filtration and blood flow, helping the body flush excess inflammatory cytokines out through urine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Importantly, this didn’t weaken the mice’s ability to fight infection. Their immune systems still did the job, just without the collateral damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team then tested methionine in other models, including &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/10/05/health/hidden-infection-kills-millions-of-kids-every-year-here-are-the-symptoms/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:sepsis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;sepsis&lt;/a&gt; and kidney injury, and saw similar protective effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That suggests methionine could have broader potential in inflammatory diseases — especially those involving kidney stress or failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings add to a growing body of evidence that common &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/07/10/health/food-is-medicine-movement-may-reverse-health-decline/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:dietary elements can be used as medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;dietary elements can be used as medicine&lt;/a&gt;,” Ayres said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, researchers stress that the results are based on animal studies — so there’s no need to sprint to the supplement aisle just yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, the team plans to dig deeper into how methionine works, whether other amino acids offer similar perks, and how these findings might translate to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By studying these basic protective mechanisms, we reveal surprising new ways to shift individuals that are fated to develop disease and die onto trajectories of health and survival,” Ayres said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It may one day be possible for something as simple as a supplement with dinner to make the difference between life and death for a patient.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:49:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNdDdhN29WTmszc2t1cjlwSUJVNFk1MWQ0d1pTTlZNRGlTX21RcnpWd1NqQlVCdllvQm5vdC0zdHJ1eW9yWVJ2Rkp5ZnBXc2tGdlJXNHNsZXZEUWlqMDhXa3hDQzB0NG9UZHdMUXlvaEJ1b05Ua0U1NW1IalB0VVpzLUxUczZ6OG8</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现常见补充剂可能有助于预防流感-预防</title><link>https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a70092588/vitamin-d-protect-against-severe-flu-study/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-n3hm4j et2g3wt7"&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="0" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.0"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.0.0"&gt;     New research finds that people low in this vitamin may be more likely to get severe flu infections.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.1"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.1.0"&gt;Scientists say that vitamin D, specifically, may help lower certain groups’ risks of severe complications from a respiratory infection.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="0.2"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="0.2.0"&gt;     Doctors say many may benefit from a vitamin D supplement.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;hr data-node-id="1" class="css-18pb4rg emevuu60"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Cases of the flu continue to be &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2026-week-01.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2026-week-01.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="high" data-node-id="2.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;high&lt;/a&gt; around the country, thanks to the highly infectious &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a69485067/new-flu-variant-subclade-k/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/health/health-conditions/a69485067/new-flu-variant-subclade-k/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="subclade K variant" data-node-id="2.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;subclade K variant&lt;/a&gt;. While there are plenty of natural ways to boost your immune system, new research points to a supplement that may help curb severe reactions to the flu: vitamin D.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="3" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;That’s the takeaway from new research published in &lt;em data-node-id="3.1"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0002916525007713?via%3Dihub" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0002916525007713?via%3Dihub" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition." data-node-id="3.1.0" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; For the study, researchers analyzed health data from 36,258 people who participated in the UK Biobank, a long-term biomedical research resource. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The researchers discovered that people with a severe &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a65478355/vitamin-d-deficiency-risk-factors/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/health/a65478355/vitamin-d-deficiency-risk-factors/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="vitamin D deficiency" data-node-id="4.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;vitamin D deficiency&lt;/a&gt; (measured as less than 15 nmol/L) had a 33% higher rate of being hospitalized for a respiratory tract infection compared to those who had vitamin D levels of 75 nmol/L or higher. For each 10 nmol/L increase in vitamin D, the hospitalization rate for respiratory tract infections dropped by 4%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Given that &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-node-id="6.1" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="18%" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;18%&lt;/a&gt; of Americans have inadequate vitamin D levels, this is worth paying attention to. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="7" class="body-tip css-txvov emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="7.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.jhsph.edu/faculty/directory/profile/3528/amesh-adalja" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.jhsph.edu/faculty/directory/profile/3528/amesh-adalja" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Amesh A. Adalja, M.D." data-node-id="7.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Amesh A. Adalja, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease expert and senior scholar at the Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security; &lt;a href="https://medicine.buffalo.edu/faculty/profile.html?ubit=trusso" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-node-id="7.4" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://medicine.buffalo.edu/faculty/profile.html?ubit=trusso" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Thomas Russo, M.D.," class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Thomas Russo, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; a professor and chief of infectious diseases at the University at Buffalo in New York; Jessica Cording, R.D., C.D.N., author of &lt;em data-node-id="7.6"&gt;The Little Book of Game-Changers&lt;/em&gt;; &lt;a href="https://www.vumc.org/health-policy/person/william-schaffner-md" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.vumc.org/health-policy/person/william-schaffner-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="William Schaffner, M.D.," data-node-id="7.8" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;William Schaffner, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an infectious disease specialist and professor at the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="8" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;This isn’t the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/cid/article/78/5/1162/7479707" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://academic.oup.com/cid/article/78/5/1162/7479707" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="first study" data-node-id="8.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;first study&lt;/a&gt; to link low levels with a higher risk of respiratory infections, raising questions about whether you should be focused on your own levels of the nutrient. Here’s what doctors and a dietitian want you to keep in mind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-may-vitamin-d-lower-the-risk-of-severe-respiratory-infection" data-node-id="9" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="9.0"&gt;Why may vitamin D lower the risk of severe respiratory infection?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="10" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The researchers didn’t dive into that, but doctors aren’t shocked by these findings. “Vitamin D plays a role in optimal immune system function,” says &lt;a href="https://www.jhsph.edu/faculty/directory/profile/3528/amesh-adalja" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.jhsph.edu/faculty/directory/profile/3528/amesh-adalja" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Amesh A. Adalja, M.D." data-node-id="10.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Amesh A. Adalja, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease expert and senior scholar at the Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="11" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Vitamin D enhances both your &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279396/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279396/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="innate immunity" data-node-id="11.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;innate immunity&lt;/a&gt;—your body’s first line of defense against pathogens—and your &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/adaptive-immunity" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/adaptive-immunity" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="adaptive immunity" data-node-id="11.3" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;adaptive immunity&lt;/a&gt;, which is the part of your immune system that “learns” to fight certain germs after you’ve been exposed to them,  explains &lt;a href="https://medicine.buffalo.edu/faculty/profile.html?ubit=trusso" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://medicine.buffalo.edu/faculty/profile.html?ubit=trusso" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Thomas Russo, M.D.," data-node-id="11.5" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Thomas Russo, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; a professor and chief of infectious diseases at the University at Buffalo in New York. “Appropriate vitamin D concentrations are important for an optimal immune response,” he says, noting that even having a “moderate” deficiency in vitamin D may impact your immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="12" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But it’s important to keep two things in mind with this particular study: One is that it’s observational, so researchers simply found an association between having low vitamin D and a greater risk of serious infection. The other is that they focused on those with a severe deficiency. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="13" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;“The literature around vitamin D [supplementation] is yes and no in terms of whether it’s helpful,” says &lt;a href="https://www.vumc.org/health-policy/person/william-schaffner-md" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.vumc.org/health-policy/person/william-schaffner-md" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="William Schaffner, M.D.," data-node-id="13.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;William Schaffner, M.D.,&lt;/a&gt; an infectious disease specialist and professor at the Vanderbilt University School of Medicine. “It would appear the more severe your vitamin D deficiency is, the more likely your immune system is not functioning optimally.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="how-much-vitamin-d-do-you-need" data-node-id="14" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.0"&gt;How much vitamin D do you need?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;The recommended daily allowance (RDA) of vitamin D depends on your age and life stage. However, most adults should get 600 international units (IU) daily, according to the &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/#h4" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/#h4" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="National Institutes of Health" data-node-id="15.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/a&gt; (NIH). (People who are 70 and older should have 800 IU of vitamin D.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-are-the-signs-im-not-getting-enough-vitamin-d" data-node-id="16" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="16.0"&gt;What are the signs I’m not getting enough vitamin D?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="17" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Vitamin D deficiency is more common in people who are lactose intolerant, follow a vegan diet, or those who have limited exposure to sunlight, per the NIH. Symptoms of low vitamin D can be vague or even hard to detect at all, but these are commonly linked to the status, according to Jessica Cording, R.D., C.D.N., author of &lt;em data-node-id="17.1"&gt;The Little Book of Game-Changers&lt;/em&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="18" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt; &lt;li data-node-id="18.1"&gt;Fatigue&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-node-id="18.3"&gt;Brain fog&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-node-id="18.5"&gt;Low mood&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-node-id="18.7"&gt;Getting sick a lot&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li data-node-id="18.9"&gt;Bone fractures (usually only in      severe cases)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 id="how-to-get-more-vitamin-d" data-node-id="19" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="19.0"&gt;How to get more vitamin D&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="20" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Exposure to the sun is the most common way people get vitamin D, but it’s also possible to get the nutrient from foods. These are the biggest vitamin D sources, per the &lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/#h4" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminD-HealthProfessional/#h4" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="NIH" data-node-id="20.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;NIH&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="21" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="21.0"&gt;     Cod liver oil&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="21.1"&gt;     Trout&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="21.2"&gt;     Salmon,&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="21.3"&gt;     Mushrooms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="21.4"&gt;     Fortified milk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="21.5"&gt;     Fortified cereal&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="22" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But you can also get vitamin D from a supplement, Dr. Russo points out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="should-you-take-a-vitamin-d-supplement-for-immune-health" data-node-id="23" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="23.0"&gt;Should you take a vitamin D supplement for immune health?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="24" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;It depends. It’s always important to check with a healthcare provider before taking any kind of supplement, Dr. Schaffner says. In the case of vitamin D, your doctor will likely recommend that you get a blood test to measure your vitamin D levels to see if you have a deficiency, Dr. Adalja says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="25" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Why is this important? Vitamin D is a fat-soluble vitamin, which means that it can build up in your body if you take in too much. “Don’t start taking excessive amounts or you could get into trouble with high calcium levels in your blood,” Dr. Russo says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="26" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But doctors also say that many people in temperate climates are likely to have lower-than-optimal vitamin D levels. If that describes you, “supplementation with a daily vitamin D pill is a generally good practice,” Dr. Adalja says. (Again, just check in with your healthcare provider first to be sure.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="27" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;In terms of a flu-prevention strategy, Dr. Russo says that things like getting vaccinated, avoiding people who are obviously sick, and wearing a mask in crowded indoor settings are still better. “A vitamin D supplement is one more piece that may help,” he says. “There’s little harm as long as you don’t overdo it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="28" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But Dr. Schaffner stops short of recommending that everyone take a vitamin D supplement for immune health. “If you have a special concern or interest in this, you can get a blood test,” he says. “Your doctor can tell you if you ought to take a supplement based on that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Prevention</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:33:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOQXM4N2VzXzdSc0puaWFVa0RkcUE3OVdub0xGVklkMXBaYUFzZWl5QXRLQnVHMjlrNHczM2RFdWdPZWVpNDU1ZENuNWdTeFpONjNvbGd5a0JLdzAydU5pOHBOSkJKWXNhRTZkRVNBZ0FyQW5TX0NveEV6T254Z3A4ZTNTdTg0THVMQTlfTURPTVQ3c1pUeXVRUDFJTldManJZRVBMRGRoR2w</guid></item><item><title>多动症特征对健康的隐性影响- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2026/01/260124073920.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Children who show ADHD traits at age 10 are more likely to experience physical health problems and health-related disability by age 46, according to a study led by researchers at University College London (UCL) and the University of Liverpool.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers say the results likely reflect a broad mix of health risks associated with attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD), along with the long-term effects of how people with ADHD are treated and supported across adulthood.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Published in &lt;em&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/em&gt;, the research is one of the largest and longest-running studies to examine how ADHD traits in childhood are linked to physical health later in life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evidence Points to Lifelong Health Challenges&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Senior author Professor Joshua Stott (UCL Psychology &amp;amp; Language Sciences) said: "Here we have added to the concerning evidence base that people with ADHD are more likely to experience worse health than average across their lifespan.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"People with ADHD can thrive with the right support, but this is often lacking, both due to a shortage of tailored support services but also because ADHD remains underdiagnosed, particularly in people in midlife and older, with needs unaddressed."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How ADHD Can Affect Daily Functioning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People with ADHD experience differences in attention, along with increased levels of hyperactivity or impulsivity. Many have high energy and can focus intensely on activities that capture their interest, but may struggle to stay focused on routine or less engaging tasks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These challenges can affect planning, time management, and impulse control. Over time, this may make school and work more difficult, increasing the risk of longer-term social and occupational difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ADHD begins in childhood, and although it is now widely recognized that it often continues into adulthood, adults in the UK receive less treatment than those in other high-income countries. Support services also remain limited.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tracking Health Outcomes Over Decades&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To examine long-term effects, the researchers analyzed data from 10,930 participants in the UCL-led 1970 British Cohort Study, which has followed individuals from birth into middle age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ADHD traits were assessed using behavior questionnaires completed by parents and teachers when participants were 10 years old. These measures were used regardless of whether a participant had ever received a formal ADHD diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Higher Rates of Chronic Illness and Disability&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study found that people with higher levels of ADHD traits in childhood were more likely to report physical health problems by age 46. They had 14% higher odds of reporting two or more conditions, including migraine, back problems, cancer, epilepsy or diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Among those with elevated ADHD traits at age 10, 42% reported having at least two physical health problems in midlife. By comparison, 37% of those with lower ADHD trait scores reported the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Participants with higher childhood ADHD traits were also more likely to report physical health-related disability (reporting having problems with work or other daily activities as a result of their physical health) at age 46.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Possible Reasons Behind the Health Differences&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that poorer physical health outcomes were partly linked to higher rates of mental health problems, increased BMI, and higher smoking rates among people with ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Previous studies have also shown that people with ADHD are more likely to experience stressful life events and social exclusion, and are less likely to receive timely medical screening and care.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The association between childhood ADHD traits and physical health-related disability appeared to be stronger in women than in men.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Professor Stott added: "All of these potential explanatory factors align with the fact that ADHD makes impulse control more difficult, the need for instant gratification and reward more intense, and is also associated with worse mental health in part due to the social disadvantage people with ADHD face."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Implications for Support and Public Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A separate study published last year by the same research team reported a possible reduction in life expectancy among adults diagnosed with ADHD, although this finding was not part of the current research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lead author Dr, Amber John, who began the work at UCL before moving to the University of Liverpool, emphasized the importance of proper support: "It's important to note that people with ADHD are a diverse group, with a range of different strengths and experiences, and most will lead long, healthy lives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"However, many face significant barriers to timely diagnosis and appropriate support. This is important because providing the right support for and meeting the needs of people with ADHD can help to improve their physical and mental health outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Additionally, public health strategies should consider the needs of people with ADHD, such as by making screening programs and ongoing health monitoring more accessible for people with ADHD."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 14:26:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE9TUC1xVUVkM3pyVGhKNlhTeGtaZHc4V2VmMFR3bGtMRFh3a3BCdFdaRWlzd3NqaGE0NlZNN3NvR2RvdE44OThfcTJULW5LU1RNYjlLaEVkV0ZMMGFsNGtmNG9VRWpqY0VsVFZWRUFsSQ</guid></item><item><title>60岁以上，早起还是多睡一会比较好？专家解释-预防</title><link>https://www.prevention.com/health/sleep-energy/a70098001/is-it-better-wake-up-early-or-sleep-longer-over-60/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-journey-body="standard-article" class="article-body-content article-body standard-body-content css-n3hm4j et2g3wt7"&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="1" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a34453321/sleep-deprivation-health-problems/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/health/a34453321/sleep-deprivation-health-problems/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action data-node-id="1.0" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;&lt;br data-node-id="1.0.0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="2" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/a34453321/sleep-deprivation-health-problems/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/health/a34453321/sleep-deprivation-health-problems/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Getting enough sleep" data-node-id="2.0" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Getting enough sleep&lt;/a&gt; is key to warding off a host of health issues. While falling asleep fast is the goal for some, and staying asleep is the dream for others, it’s normal for your &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/health/sleep-energy/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.prevention.com/health/sleep-energy/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="sleep" data-node-id="2.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;sleep&lt;/a&gt; to change over time. But as we get older, is it better to wake up early or sleep in?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="3" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Sleep medicine specialists stress the importance of keeping a regular sleep schedule for your overall health. “I try to encourage older individuals who are retired to create some sort of consistent wake-up time,” says &lt;a href="https://www.wchriswinter.com/#/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.wchriswinter.com/#/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Christopher Winter, M.D." data-node-id="3.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Christopher Winter, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a sleep medicine specialist, neurologist, and author of &lt;em data-node-id="3.3"&gt;The Sleep Solution: Why Your Sleep Is Broken and How to Fix It&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="3.4"&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="4" class="body-tip css-txvov emevuu60"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="4.0"&gt;Meet the experts&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href="https://www.wchriswinter.com/#/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.wchriswinter.com/#/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Christopher Winter, M.D." data-node-id="4.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Christopher Winter, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, is a sleep medicine specialist, neurologist, and author of &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Sleep-Solution-Why-Your-Broken/dp/0399583610/ref=asc_df_0399583610/?linkCode=ogi&amp;amp;tag=prevention-auto-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C2141.a.69366637%5Bsrc%7Cwww.google.com%5Bch%7C%5Blt%7C%5Bpid%7C2f50c77c-f35a-4612-8bc0-bbc9a75ecf07%5Baxid%7Cd0229f6d-b38a-4172-96de-5f1932748a51%5Bofsxid%7Cpushly_notifications%5Bofsvid%7Cactive-1427056%5Bofsxid%7Cread_time_estimate%5Bofsvid%7Ccontrol-1496370%5Bofsxid%7Creaders_also_read%5Bofsvid%7Con-1489053" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.amazon.com/Sleep-Solution-Why-Your-Broken/dp/0399583610/ref=asc_df_0399583610/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="The Sleep Solution: Why Your Sleep Is Broken and How to Fix It" data-vars-ga-product-id="2f50c77c-f35a-4612-8bc0-bbc9a75ecf07" data-node-id="4.4" data-vars-ga-axid="d0229f6d-b38a-4172-96de-5f1932748a51" data-amazon-ascsubtag="[artid|2141.a.69366637[src|www.google.com[ch|[lt|[pid|2f50c77c-f35a-4612-8bc0-bbc9a75ecf07[axid|d0229f6d-b38a-4172-96de-5f1932748a51[ofsxid|pushly_notifications[ofsvid|active-1427056[ofsxid|read_time_estimate[ofsvid|control-1496370[ofsxid|readers_also_read[ofsvid|on-1489053" data-aps-asc-tag="prevention-auto-20" data-aps-asc-subtag="[artid|2141.a.69366637[src|www.google.com[ch|[lt|[pid|2f50c77c-f35a-4612-8bc0-bbc9a75ecf07[axid|d0229f6d-b38a-4172-96de-5f1932748a51[ofsxid|pushly_notifications[ofsvid|active-1427056[ofsxid|read_time_estimate[ofsvid|control-1496370[ofsxid|readers_also_read[ofsvid|on-1489053" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="4.4.0"&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="4.5"&gt;The Sleep Solution: Why Your Sleep Is Broken and How to Fix It&lt;/em&gt;; &lt;a href="https://www.drjadewu.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.drjadewu.com/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Jade Wu, Ph.D." data-node-id="4.7" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Jade Wu&lt;strong data-node-id="4.7.1"&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, is a behavioral sleep medicine specialist and author of &lt;em data-node-id="4.9"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="4.9.0"&gt;Hello Sleep: The Science and Art of Overcoming Insomnia Without Medications&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="6" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But if the decision on when to get up is yours alone, is it better for your health to rise early or get more rest? Here’s what sleep medicine specialists want you to keep in mind. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="7" data-lazy-id="P0-16"&gt;&lt;h2 title="Is it better to sleep longer or wake up early?" data-anchor-id="is-it-better-to-sleep-longer-or-wake-up-early" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emt9r7s1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="7.0"&gt;Is it better to sleep longer or wake up early?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="8" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;This can be “tricky” to answer, according to &lt;a href="https://www.drjadewu.com/" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.drjadewu.com/" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="Jade Wu, Ph.D." data-node-id="8.1" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;Jade Wu&lt;strong data-node-id="8.1.1"&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; Ph.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a behavioral sleep medicine specialist and author of &lt;em data-node-id="8.3"&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="8.3.0"&gt;Hello Sleep: The Science and Art of Overcoming Insomnia Without Medications&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em data-node-id="8.3.1"&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;“Sometimes waking up early means someone is not getting enough opportunity to sleep, and sometimes it doesn’t,” she says. “Whether this is a good thing also depends on whether you usually get up early or late.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="9" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Dr. Winter agrees. “I don’t really care if you get up later, but I want you to have a wake-up time and decide that is the wake-up time, no matter what happens overnight,” he says. “I just want it to be consistent and in line with what your body naturally wants to do, which is to sleep for seven to nine hours.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="10" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Some people may naturally prefer to stay up later at night, which would push the preferred wake time to later, Dr. Winter points out. But if you like to get in bed on the earlier side, your wake time should reflect that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="11" data-lazy-id="P0-17"&gt;&lt;h2 title="How to figure out what your body needs" data-anchor-id="how-to-figure-out-what-your-body-needs" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emt9r7s1"&gt;How to figure out what your body needs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="12" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;To figure out if an earlier or later wake time is best for you, Wu recommends considering these elements:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="13" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="13.0"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="13.0.0"&gt;     Make sure you’re leaving yourself enough time to sleep.&lt;/strong&gt; The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/sleep/about/index.html" target="_blank" data-vars-ga-outbound-link="https://www.cdc.gov/sleep/about/index.html" data-vars-ga-ux-element="Hyperlink" data-vars-ga-call-to-action="recommended amount" data-node-id="13.0.2" class="body-link css-inlxvj emevuu60"&gt;recommended amount&lt;/a&gt; is seven or more hours.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="13.1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="13.1.0"&gt;     Keep your wake time steady.&lt;/strong&gt; “It’s better to wake up at about the same time every day than to sometimes wake up early and sometimes late,” she says. A consistent wake time helps to anchor your circadian rhythm, which dictates the timing of a lot of processes in your body.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="13.2"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="13.2.0"&gt;     Line up your wake time with your chronotype, which is your body’s natural preference for sleep and wake times. &lt;/strong&gt;“If you’re naturally a morning person, get up early,” Wu says. “If you’re naturally more of a night owl, let yourself sleep.”&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="14" data-lazy-id="P0-18"&gt;&lt;h2 title="Do I need more or less sleep with age?" data-anchor-id="do-i-need-more-or-less-sleep-with-age" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emt9r7s1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="14.0"&gt;Do I need more or less sleep with age?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="15" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Most people need less sleep with age—and that’s something that’s been happening since you were a baby. “Babies need much more sleep than toddlers, who need more sleep than other children,” Dr. Winter says. “The underlying reason is that we tend to lose slow-wave sleep or deep sleep as we get older.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="16" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But there is some variability here. “It also depends on our physical activity levels, stress levels, and hormonal status,” Wu says. So, if you work out regularly and aren’t overly stressed, you may require more sleep than your frazzled counterparts who do less activity on a regular basis. “Each person’s trajectory of sleep needs can be unique,” Dr. Wu says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="17" data-lazy-id="P0-19"&gt;&lt;h2 title="Why do I wake up earlier as I get older?" data-anchor-id="why-do-i-wake-up-earlier-as-i-get-older" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emt9r7s1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="17.0"&gt;Why do I wake up earlier as I get older?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="18" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Every person is different, but your chronotype plays a role. “Our chronotypes—the tendency for our circadian clock to run early, late, or somewhere in between—tend to shift earlier as we age,” Wu says. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="19" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;But while doctors know that people tend to wake up earlier as they age, Dr. Winter says the exact reason is unknown. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;section data-node-id="20" data-lazy-id="P0-20"&gt;&lt;h2 title="When to see a doctor about sleep" data-anchor-id="when-to-see-a-doctor-about-sleep" class="body-h2 css-ne8qws emt9r7s1"&gt;&lt;strong data-node-id="20.0"&gt;When to see a doctor about sleep&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="21" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Dr. Winter recommends seeing a doctor about your sleep anytime you’re concerned about it. But he also notes a few “red flags” to keep in mind. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="22" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Those include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul data-node-id="23" class="css-kw9lqy emevuu60"&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="23.0"&gt;     Feeling like you need far more sleep when you’re older than you did when you were younger.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="23.1"&gt;     You have fragmented sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="23.2"&gt;     You experience excessive sleepiness during the day. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li data-node-id="23.3"&gt;     Your partner says you snore consistently. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p data-journey-content="true" data-node-id="24" class="css-6wxqfj emevuu60"&gt;Frequent nightmares are also a reason to check in with a healthcare provider, Wu says. As for whether you should get up earlier or later, Dr. Winter says it’s really up to you—as long as you’re consistent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-exclude="true" id="journey-inline" class="css-ciejky e1ye6jr30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Prevention</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:33:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPV3pFVThVZTl4TkpicHQ4eGNnWDVsbmtMZzdhWFgxWjRydlNPSjlvVHFXUnRWZjVUZEthbnZJWVVLOHlzMlFhQ1BjNEx6SldZOGlrSTNyWUw4TXp5VE1wMlZZSmI4c1dna0JIUjhSNHJWQjFxdTk5RXNyem1WajQ1XzE5UmkzSW56OTF5SFlsbklCY2ZSbWFOTXZRa2R6bGdfZGU5UTl5cnhyR2Vp</guid></item><item><title>州数据显示，俄勒冈州的医院没有达到预防某些感染的国家安全目标- oregonlive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/health/2026/01/oregon-hospitals-fall-short-of-national-safety-goals-to-prevent-some-infections-state-data-shows.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KMC5D7YOWFGNZBVUMYQDTISP5U"&gt;Oregon hospitals recorded nearly 1,000 infections that patients picked up while receiving care in 2024, resulting in infection levels that missed most national safety standards, according to a &lt;a href="https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/oregon.public.health.division.acute.and.communicable.disease.pre/viz/HospitalHealthcare-AssociatedInfectionsDataDashboard2024/Overview?publish=yes&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=govdelivery" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/oregon.public.health.division.acute.and.communicable.disease.pre/viz/HospitalHealthcare-AssociatedInfectionsDataDashboard2024/Overview?publish=yes&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=govdelivery"&gt;new state report&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6XY2DIJVWVD3PJNR6ANNKKVTL4"&gt;The Oregon Health Authority reviewed data from 61 hospitals statewide and tracked infections that develop after surgery, through catheters and IV lines and from drug-resistant bacteria such as methicillin-resistant Staphylococcus aureus, commonly known as MRSA. These infections can turn routine hospital stays into life-threatening events, especially for older adults and people with weakened immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7E6HCBMF3JE2RKQQBTI25NBYHM"&gt;State health officials measured how Oregon’s hospitals performed against national benchmarks set by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. The &lt;a href="https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/oregon.public.health.division.acute.and.communicable.disease.pre/viz/HospitalHealthcare-AssociatedInfectionsDataDashboard2024/Overview?publish=yes&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=govdelivery" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/oregon.public.health.division.acute.and.communicable.disease.pre/viz/HospitalHealthcare-AssociatedInfectionsDataDashboard2024/Overview?publish=yes&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=govdelivery"&gt;data shows&lt;/a&gt; that hospitals continue to struggle most with preventing surgical site infections and bloodstream and urinary tract infections caused by medical devices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5ZX4VM7NYFHZDPWO3WTPNGWW4Y"&gt;When state officials compared hospital performance to a national 2015 baseline, they found that most surgical infections in Oregon were higher than expected, including those after colon surgery, heart bypass procedures and hip and knee replacements. Only on hysterectomy-related surgeries did Oregon hospitals perform better than the baseline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EW2SSDLHIRB4PFHB736ABB752A"&gt;Hospitals also reported more surgical infections in 2024 than in 2023, according to state data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZAGUSZ27GBBFLNFV6QQQLH7A7I"&gt;Some parts of the system improved. Large acute-care hospitals showed progress in reducing bloodstream infections and MRSA. But many of the state’s smaller, rural critical access hospitals moved in the opposite direction, reporting higher rates of those same infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3M7U5DGZCNGVBHKHUQGSFNZA5A"&gt;Federal health officials also set national targets for reducing hospital-acquired infections. In 2024, Oregon hospitals met only one of those goals: lowering C. difficile infections, which cause severe diarrhea and stomach pain. They failed to reach the target for every other infection category.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="V7DYYJ6BUFF7VN3O6WHJRJ753Q"&gt;Dr. Dat Tran, who oversees the Oregon Health Authority’s infection prevention program, said the data gives hospitals a clear picture of where they need to improve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2664J2N37ZERFMRAQCGAJMNNV4"&gt;“No health care provider wants to see a hospital-associated infection in one of their patients,” Tran said in a statement. “These data are intended to help hospitals and health care providers understand where they’re doing well and where they may need to step up their infection control efforts.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="J2RX4EJP7JECXEFUCEKMMVNV4Y"&gt;The state’s report, however, highlighted one bright spot: all Oregon hospitals now meet national standards for antibiotic stewardship. That means they follow best practices to limit unnecessary antibiotic use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GN73YU2DCNGTBPUIXVAYOYUVLQ"&gt;State health officials say they continue to support hospitals by studying statewide trends, offering one-on-one infection control assistance and working with the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention to train health care workers. They said patients and visitors can also help stop the spread of infection by washing their hands often, following hospital rules and staying home when sick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>oregonlive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2wFBVV95cUxPTWxFRkVCZ1ZfZUMtMVdSY2o2SDBYRy1aODZ4UE5Fbmk5V0o1UFhaXzYtQXVlX2dhSlJWVkpTTldpVlV0TEZIblNVTERtZFU4cG5HMkFjVkpxSjlGYmwtWHV4Vm5FWGdLZWFINGstLVpqSVN1ckhfdl9yYl9XZ2cwdURxbDYzV19faVQtZTNiMkc0TzhobEd1ZVFlVzlmUjR0Ymp4ZmV2WDNzdEVBZkpLVFJhZUxyTXU1azN5YVVPTUJVUXNoZm5yTm9mYzZFTERKdk9zeHdyYjFYemPSAe8BQVVfeXFMUGh2WDk5MDhGai1XZmlQU0dxZGZqVlNjY3hsZ3ZydG9Rc241VmlqWVBicjVmNnVYM29MQklHWFhKbTBCMEpaYnh0QUtUYVpyOFVTVmRiT0tJbzFGZXdQNUk4RFppV2YwbloyOFZrU2RDby1JQjg5cHBUazBiRHVzSnVWOE1EYVZtMHZvN1NMMUJia2JvRWF0TWxlUEZpN2NrckNLczdpUnVvTTBodXdoaG9ucXBTcTY0QzBLeVNSUDZtQzN4NXhxS2tncnNHVlFITHdLRnlvOHNsdjcyX2M2WEhLZFRxNklTMnM2N1czTDg</guid></item><item><title>发现影响肠道细菌平衡和IBD易感性的单基因- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2026-01-gene-gut-bacteria-ibd-susceptibility.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 13:09:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxPNTVSWGdEMmNOSTNHQkllc1ZYa1BFdm1FdldKVEthV2gwdnFuZlVva0dNbkNWRFJibUJEMk56c1hscGtqdklBMEtMbFZ0bjlUbHlNYVZPN2Z1ZUR1TEJHempld0o5NWF3TGNLMVdRNmUtRFJ1WUdBOEpSbHJDNFhuUXozdm1rMWc</guid></item><item><title>生酮饮食与奇怪的瘙痒皮疹有关-但没有人知道为什么- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2026/01/a-weird-itchy-rash-is-linked-to-the-keto-diet-but-no-one-knows-why/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;h2&gt;Diet downsides&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, the keto diet is popular among people trying to lose weight, particularly those trying to lose visceral fat, like the man in the case study. Anecdotal reports promote the keto diet as being effective at helping people slim down relatively quickly while also improving stamina and mental clarity. But robust clinical data supporting these claims are lacking, and medical experts have raised concerns about long-term cardiovascular health, among other things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are also clear downsides to the diet. Ketones are acidic, and if they build up too much in the blood, they can be toxic, causing ketoacidosis. This is a particular concern for people with type 1 diabetes and for people with chronic alcohol abuse. For everyone else, there’s a list of &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK499830/"&gt;common side effects&lt;/a&gt;, including nausea, vomiting, constipation, diarrhea, bad breath, headache, fatigue, and dizziness. Ketogenic diets are also linked to high cholesterol and kidney stones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there’s one side effect that’s well established but little known and still puzzling to doctors: the “keto rash” or &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK599559/"&gt;prurigo pigmentosa&lt;/a&gt;. This rash fits the man’s case perfectly—red, raised, itchy bumps on the neck, chest, and back, with areas of hyperpigmentation also developing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rash was first identified in Japan in 1971, where it was mostly seen in women. While it has been consistently linked to metabolic disorders and dietary changes, experts still don’t understand what causes it. It’s seen not only in people on a keto diet but also in people with diabetes and those who have had bariatric surgery or are fasting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1155/drp/1993385"&gt;a review this month&lt;/a&gt;, researchers in Saudi Arabia noted that a leading hypothesis is that the high levels of ketones in the blood trigger inflammation around blood vessels driven by a type of white blood cell called neutrophils, and this inflammation is what causes the rash, which develops in different stages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While the condition remains poorly understood, effective treatments have at least been worked out. The most common treatment is to get the person out of ketosis and give them an antibiotic in the tetracycline class. Antibiotics are designed to treat bacterial infections (which this is not), but they can also dampen inflammation signals and thwart the activity of neutrophils.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the man’s case, doctors gave him a two-week course of doxycycline and told him to ditch his keto diet. A week later, the rash was gone.&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 12:00:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNOTgwd1dsUW1pSTAtUXROb3M5QTF6c09QdTVwdXVyZVVyWlFKQmxhWmMxU3NLaDZXWVZOMUUtVVFnS0lHcGd0dmR3OEtmckNweXRoLTdRSnoxX2FnajJkOU1hSmRwNUFSeEVfQ3NQU2VjMGNCWGpYMlpKUmg0ZmtnMFdQVEJsNV9KdDhzQXFDakYyY0YzMU5xSWk3MTRDRnJLclU2QnhDYUdFdw</guid></item><item><title>福布斯本周之家：落基山高等艺术-福布斯</title><link>https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2026/01/24/forbes-house-of-the-week-rocky-mountain-high-art/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="fs-article fs-premium fs-responsive-text current-article font-body color-body bg-base font-accent article-body premium-container"&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ESSENTIALS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Firm Name: &lt;/strong&gt;Renée del Gaudio Architecture&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Principal: &lt;/strong&gt;Renée del Gaudio&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Headquarters: &lt;/strong&gt;5595 Sunshine Canyon Dr, Boulder, Colorado&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accolades: &lt;/strong&gt;Forbes Architecture’s “America’s Top 200 Residential Architects,” 2025; Forbes Architecture’s “America’s Best-in-State Residential Architects,” 2025.&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;House Name: &lt;/strong&gt;Betasso Overlook&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location: &lt;/strong&gt;Boulder, Colorado &lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Site Specifics: &lt;/strong&gt;In Sugarloaf, a mile from the trailhead of 1,100-acre Betasso Preserve, 1 acre of rugged ponderosa pine ecosystem marked by meadows and expansive views. Elevation 6,636 feet. Annual snowfall, 79 inches.&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Area &amp;amp; Layout&lt;/strong&gt;: 3,673 square feet, 2BR, 2BA; office; studio; mudroom; laundry room; carport&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;hr class="embed-base rule-embed color-accent border-solid weight-light"&gt;&lt;h2 class="subhead-embed color-accent bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“Architecture is the language of intervention...it intervenes in biologic, social, and political systems, and as such, architects become builders of ideas.” &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;—Elizabeth Wright Ingraham (1922–2013), Colorado Architect&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;hr class="embed-base rule-embed color-accent border-solid weight-light"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;abbr class="drop-cap color-accent font-accent"&gt;A&lt;/abbr&gt;&lt;strong&gt;re we there yet?&lt;/strong&gt; Beyond the actions of the torchbearers among us, have we finally pivoted in how we see and value our houses, departing from the purely egocentric in favor of the ecocentric? From single-minded status- and investment-focused self-interests to—dare we say it—a place somehow closer to representing the greater good? State to state, the work of the &lt;em&gt;Forbes&lt;/em&gt; Architecture lists suggests that, at the scale of the architect-designed custom house, it is indeed happening. Taking us past the beneficial requirements of building codes, a renewed focus on the relationship between architecture and sense of place, a new regionalism, has become impossible to miss. As a badge of honor, the development has rather clandestinely overtaken “Sustainability,” with its decades of exhausted rhetoric, and not a moment too soon. Just don’t let the deniers know that regionalism and sustainability are essentially one and the same. For now, we get to celebrate, in that we &lt;em&gt;are&lt;/em&gt; getting there—closer to reaching critical mass in heeding the advice of Thoreau’s “Walking,” his famous essay calling attention to the lifetime of evercurious detail that awaits the person who commits to learning, within even a 10-mile radius of home, the nuances of their local terrain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-4 bleed" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj KNNlC"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;ABOVE: The 1-acre property gets its name from the 1,100-acre premier biking and hiking nature preserve that it overlooks, Betasso Preserve.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="article_paragraph_7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dedicated to this very path of unearthing and, moreover, evidence of our progress is the Boulder, Colorado, architect Renée del Gaudio, since 2011 a one-woman shop specializing in site-specific residential work and known for taking on only the small number of projects that she, alone, can handle in any given year. Hers is a commitment to quality control and, ultimately, a far deeper level of overall engagement with the client, the site, and the design-and-construction processes, an approach that stems from having confronted deep personal loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Del Gaudio directly experienced Boulder’s 2010 Fourmile Canyon Fire, which destroyed 169 homes, her cabin included, in the process of burning 6,181 acres. For the architect, the fire prompted an existential crisis, an exercise in soul searching and an exploration, amidst the psychologically lingering smoke and ash, of what was essentially called for, architecturally, in the region. She’d leave her position at a prominent, award-winning Denver architecture firm over it, breaking out on her own to begin offering precisely what she had determined the region’s post-fire environment demanded. As part of rethinking her overall creative outlook, she found herself looking back to find the right way forward, materially and formally: in the modest building materials and simple construction methods of the region’s metal-clad miner’s cabins of a century ago, structures built at a time when fires were simply left to burn, del Gaudio found certain truths. It was those discoveries combined with her foundational understanding and appreciation of the importance of “place architecture” (she earned her M.A. in Architecture from the University of Washington, an architecture school with one of the richest regionalist-Modern traditions in the U.S.) that set the course for her future work. Beginning with her own complete rebuild, an expanded house-studio where she and her family would ultimately reside and work (and still do), del Gaudio articulated the fundamental elements of her new architecture. Numerous awards for excellence soon followed, as did new commissions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-7 offset" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;Corrugated metal was the final choice for the roof and the exterior wall cladding—decisions born out of a need for greater fire resistance. ABOVE: The front entrance, where the envelope's dark metal calls attention to the grain of the hemlock-clad soffits and the Douglas fir beams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-11 bleed" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj KNNlC"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;"Ask yourself how you hope your space will feel, rather than how it will look," del Gaudio advises clients who are new to the process of working with an architect. "Avoid looking at precedent imagery too early in the process. Once you, or your architect, gets an image stuck in their head, the creative process is over." ABOVE: The living area, with its soaring 3"x12" Douglas fir double timbers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now fourteen years in, del Gaudio has recently completed Betasso Overlook, a house located only about 11 miles from her own house-studio. For how it reveals nearly all the elements of her evolved signature, the new house, built for a Chicago transplant with a background in design, is exemplary. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The house’s main architectural gesture is the A-frame-like folded form of its metal roofs—plural because the plan is broken into three distinct volumes (working; living; and sleeping), with each resting on its own concrete pad that’s been distinctly placed to follow the slope of the site and with each interconnected by glass-enclosed exterior hallways. As in all del Gaudio’s work, wood is used prominently for its visceral impact, all of it naturally and boldly treated and effected with precise detailing. Structure, on principle, is exactingly expressed and exposed (in a world filled with things manufactured anonymously offshore, exposed-structure architecture lets us see how a house is actually put together, piece by piece, enabling a greatly deepened connection to it). Perhaps most striking of all, however, is that by moving the circulation to the exterior as the architect has, del Gaudio actively promotes movement &lt;em&gt;between&lt;/em&gt; the spaces, which in turn promotes discovery of how the house relates to prevailing winds, to the sun, and to landscape features and vistas—each its own story of the place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-75 offset" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;ABOVE: At an entrance to the glass-enclosed hall that connects the bedroom volume to the living-dining-kitchen volume, del Gaudio's attention to detailing the architecture's component parts comes into focus. As throughout the house, the fastening of the Douglas fir double timbers is handled meticulously, with precisely placed carbon steel bolts in a black oxide finish.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the end, Betasso Overlook is the latest example of del Gaudio’s signature response to certain core region-specific questions that she routinely strives to answer, questions that every work of residential architecture should outwardly address but too often do not: Does the architecture “give back” to the landscape as much or more than it takes from it? Does it acknowledge the traditions of the landscape (flooding, extreme cold or heat, wind, wildfire)? Does it anticipate how people will inevitably evolve in their use of the house over time? Does it promote a deeper level of engagement with the place? Indeed, it does.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-14 bleed" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj KNNlC"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;ABOVE: Taking full advantage of Boulder's near-300 days of sunshine, the living-dining-kitchen areas, with their poured concrete floors, are designed to easily expand onto patios and decks that face the preserve. Many of the lighting fixtures seen were designed by del Gaudio and fabricated by the client, a vintage lighting expert.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-17 bleed" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj KNNlC"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;"I want my work to belong to its place," says del Gaudio. "I craft the architecture until I can no longer imagine it anywhere else but in that specific place. Only then do I feel I have succeeded in creating something authentic." ABOVE: In the living-dining area, structure and nature seamlessly integrate. The sliding doors, like the house's windows, are fiberglass frame with aluminum cladding.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-20 offset" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;ABOVE: In the kitchen, del Gaudio's typical emphasis on artful simplicity of spatial organization and a master carpenter's honesty and clarity of materiality and construction is highlighted. The cabinetry is white oak and the countertops are pre-cast concrete, except for the island, which has a quartzite countertop and an ebony stain applied to the white oak.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-23 bleed" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj KNNlC"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;ABOVE: In the primary bedroom, the floors are done with white oak, while the ceilings, as throughout the house, are finished with hemlock.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-26 offset" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;ABOVE: The primary bath, also with quartzite countertops and backsplash.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-29 bleed" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj KNNlC"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;ABOVE: The front elevation of the bedroom volume, with its workspace off the cedar deck and, at left, the glass-enclosed corridor linking the bedroom to the house's public spaces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-33 offset" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="bMqrj"&gt;&lt;p class="Jp--BF7-"&gt;&lt;span class="Ccg9Ib-7 _8XF2kHYM"&gt;Energy-wise, the house is equipped with a geothermal system, a 9 kW photovoltaic array, and is all-electric, allowing for zero-carbon performance. ABOVE: The interiors aglow under a western sky at dusk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;David Lauer&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="embed-base image-embed embed-102 bleed" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="bMqrj KNNlC"&gt;&lt;small class="pGGCM2aD"&gt;Renée del Gaudio Architecture&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;hr class="embed-base rule-embed color-accent border-solid weight-light"&gt;&lt;h4 class="subhead4-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;h3 class="subhead3-embed color-body bg-base font-accent font-size text-align"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More from Forbes House of the Week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a class="embed-base color-body color-body-border link-embed embed-57" href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2026/01/17/forbes-house-of-the-week--a-carmel-by-the-sea-cottage/" target="_blank" aria-label="Forbes House of the Week:  A Carmel-by-the-Sea Cottage" data-ga-track="forbesEmbedly:https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2026/01/17/forbes-house-of-the-week--a-carmel-by-the-sea-cottage/"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__info"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__provider"&gt;Forbes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__title"&gt;Forbes House of the Week:  A Carmel-by-the-Sea Cottage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small class="link-embed__byline"&gt;By &lt;span class="link-embed__author"&gt;Richard Olsen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail allow-inline-style"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="embed-base color-body color-body-border link-embed embed-61" href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2026/01/10/forbes-house-of-the-week-enlightened--in-la/" target="_blank" aria-label="Forbes House of the Week: Enlightened  in L.A." data-ga-track="forbesEmbedly:https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2026/01/10/forbes-house-of-the-week-enlightened--in-la/"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__info"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__provider"&gt;Forbes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__title"&gt;Forbes House of the Week: Enlightened  in L.A.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small class="link-embed__byline"&gt;By &lt;span class="link-embed__author"&gt;Richard Olsen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail allow-inline-style"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="embed-base color-body color-body-border link-embed embed-64" href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2025/12/20/forbes-house-of-the-week-sedonas-high-desert-radiance/" target="_blank" aria-label="Forbes House of the Week: Sedona’s High Desert Radiance" data-ga-track="forbesEmbedly:https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2025/12/20/forbes-house-of-the-week-sedonas-high-desert-radiance/"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__info"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__provider"&gt;Forbes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__title"&gt;Forbes House of the Week: Sedona’s High Desert Radiance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small class="link-embed__byline"&gt;By &lt;span class="link-embed__author"&gt;Richard Olsen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail allow-inline-style"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="embed-base color-body color-body-border link-embed embed-67" href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2025/12/07/forbes-house-of-the-week-big-island-breakaway/" target="_blank" aria-label="Forbes House of the Week: Big Island Breakaway" data-ga-track="forbesEmbedly:https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2025/12/07/forbes-house-of-the-week-big-island-breakaway/"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__info"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__provider"&gt;Forbes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__title"&gt;Forbes House of the Week: Big Island Breakaway&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small class="link-embed__byline"&gt;By &lt;span class="link-embed__author"&gt;Richard Olsen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail allow-inline-style"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="embed-base color-body color-body-border link-embed embed-70" href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2025/12/13/forbes-house-of-the-week-texas-hill-country-haven/" target="_blank" aria-label="Forbes House of the Week: Texas Hill Country Haven" data-ga-track="forbesEmbedly:https://www.forbes.com/sites/richardolsen/2025/12/13/forbes-house-of-the-week-texas-hill-country-haven/"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__info"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__provider"&gt;Forbes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__title"&gt;Forbes House of the Week: Texas Hill Country Haven&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small class="link-embed__byline"&gt;By &lt;span class="link-embed__author"&gt;Richard Olsen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__thumbnail allow-inline-style"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a class="embed-base color-body color-body-border link-embed embed-73 link-embed--no-thumbnail" href="https://www.forbes.com/lists/architects-best-in-state/" target="_blank" aria-label="Forbes Best In State Residential Architects in America 2025 List" data-ga-track="InternalLink:https://www.forbes.com/lists/architects-best-in-state/"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__info"&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__provider"&gt;Forbes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="link-embed__title"&gt;Forbes Best In State Residential Architects in America 2025 List&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Forbes</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQallCQ2RkTXkwUHEwQXI2NnlKUE50RS1VNTVLUzJBZld0ekJTV2ppWnF4WDM0Q2ttVHBzdjBxY3VuYVY2bHpFdVhvZ0JUYXdnUElydVhuWWFWUUhXMTN4RlZCeTR4ZU5nZUtWU294TnBrQnBjQ2hUbjZzcnBVcGNNazNzYUxWZ0tOSkowVXE4UXY3NFdtR2IyMGxQaXB0bHhsZ0Rtbw</guid></item><item><title>55岁后比健身房机器更快恢复肌肉的4项日常锻炼-吃这个不是那个</title><link>https://www.eatthis.com/exercises-to-restore-muscle-after-55/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content single-post-content"&gt;
																			&lt;p class="tagline"&gt;These exercises are easy to weave into your day—and much more effective than gym machines.&lt;/p&gt;
												
																			
																		
						
						
						&lt;p&gt;One of the most common frustrations that occurs with age is the natural loss of muscle and strength, known as sarcopenia. An &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3060646/" target="_blank"&gt;estimated 5% to 13%&lt;/a&gt; of those between the ages of 60 to 70 are impacted by this condition. In order to combat sarcopenia—and &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/daily-exercises-rebuild-lost-muscle-after-50/" target="_blank"&gt;restore lost muscle&lt;/a&gt;—it’s important to engage in regular &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/strength-test-after-55/" target="_blank"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt;. And this doesn’t necessarily mean heading to the gym to use machines! We spoke with an expert who shares four daily exercises that get the job done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why These Daily Exercises Work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="630025" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-630025" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="back muscles" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-630025" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="back muscles" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2022/03/muscles.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you hit your 50s, maximizing your workout routine is essential. According to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://www.zinzino.com/site/mq/en-gb/blog/brand-ambassadors/meet-the-expert/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Dr. Colin Robertson&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Chief Product Office Zinzino, Sport &amp;amp; Nutrition Scientist, PhD in Exercise Physiology, exercises that recruit multiple joints are beneficial to weave into your day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Short, frequent bouts of loaded movement can raise weekly training volume with less fatigue per session, improving adherence and recovery. Daily, multi-joint patterns (squat/hinge/push/pull/carry) also reinforce motor unit recruitment and coordination, which tends to drift with age and inactivity, making the same muscle mass ‘harder to access.’ You’re not just rebuilding fibres; you’re rebuilding the ability to use them consistently,” Dr. Robertson explains.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;RELATED: &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/5-no-equipment-core-exercises-no-planks/" target="_blank"&gt;5 No-Equipment Exercises That Strengthen Your Core Faster Than Planks After 40&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;6254a4d1642c605c54bf1cab17d50f1e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The Limitations of Gym Machines&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="847086" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-847086" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Woman doing legs exercise on stair steppers machine, in gym. selective cropped photo, fit woman. Closeup." srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-847086" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Woman doing legs exercise on stair steppers machine, in gym. selective cropped photo, fit woman. Closeup." data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/02/shutterstock_1581942262.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When it comes to rebuilding muscle after midlife, gym machines present certain limitations—one of which is decreased demand of the stabilizers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed karma_unit--halfpage"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Many machines offload trunk/hip/scapular control, so strength gains may transfer less to real-life tasks (stairs, lifting, balance),” Dr. Robertson says.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition, machine-based exercises can under-train your gait, rotational control, and grip, which Dr. Robertson calls “key weak links for midlife function and injury resilience.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another downside of gym machines? They’re typically only used two to three times a week in longer workouts. Many individuals in midlife benefit from more frequent, shorter doses that keep flare-ups and muscle soreness at bay while revving up stimulus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Machines can be excellent for isolating and loading a target muscle, but they often provide less demand for coordination, bracing, and force transfer, which are exactly what many people lose after midlife,” Dr. Robertson adds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;4 Daily Moves to Restore Muscle After 55&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The exercises below are scalable and easy to perform without hindering your recovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Robertson instructs, “Pick two exercises per day, alternate A/B days, total time 10 to 20 minutes. The goal is consistent, recoverable exposure, more quality reps per week, not heroic workouts.” Aim to achieve a rate of perceived exertion (RPE) of seven to eight with two to three reps in reserve on working sets.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="sit-to-stand-squats" class="o-slide-title" data-num="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sit-to-Stand Squats&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/IzYftUVNDbw?si=ZIzGRBbfaHtoRG5Z" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Begin seated at the front of a sturdy chair with your feet placed on the floor under your knees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lean forward slightly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Try to stand up without using your knees, hands, or additional support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use control to slowly sit back down.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform 3 to 5 sets of 6 to 12 reps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To make the exercise more challenging, hold a kettlebell or dumbbell and slow your lowering (3 seconds).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="romanian-deadlift" class="o-slide-title" data-num="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Romanian Deadlift&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/5WxMW-Fu5KU?si=RtCWCrm1Dd_ctqTu" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand tall with your feet hip-width apart, holding a dumbbell in each hand. (If you’re not comfortable working with dumbbells, use just your body weight.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend your knees slightly and hold the weights in front of your thighs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press your hips back as you lower the dumbbells down your leg. Maintain a straight back as you do so.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Squeeze your glutes to return to the start position.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform 3 to 4 sets of 8 to 12 reps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="pushups" class="o-slide-title" data-num="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Pushups&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/bt5b9x9N0KU?si=tmly-UoJTqFE9TuR" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start in a high plank with your hands under your shoulders and your body straight from head to heels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Activate your core.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bend your elbows to lower your chest toward the floor. Maintain a long, straight body as you lower.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press back up, straightening your arms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform 3 to 5 sets of 6 to 15 reps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To make this exercise more challenging, add a load, such as a weighted backpack or add a slow eccentric.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="farmers-carry" class="o-slide-title" data-num="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Farmer’s Carry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8OtwXwrJizk?si=zA_Wrb00xKmyQKS3" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hold a heavy dumbbell or kettlebell—50% of your body weight—in each hand at your sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start walking forward, keeping your torso still.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform 4 to 8 carries, walking 20 to 40 meters (or 30 to 60 seconds).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

																		
																	&lt;/div&gt;
										&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio"&gt;
	&lt;p class="c-article-short-bio__name"&gt;Alexa Mellardo&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
		Alexa is a freelance writer, editor, and content strategist based in Greenwich, CT. She has 11+ years of experience covering wellness, fitness, food, travel, lifestyle, and home.					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="c-article-short-bio__more" href="https://www.eatthis.com/author/alexa-mellardo/"&gt;Read more about Alexa &lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Eat This Not That</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:03:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTFBMQ0VTbnhiNVRiTHdQTWxSY1dNRnJwenk5UHUtSE91T2V5ZWdyTXdTcUtwa0M4SGgtMjNNckN5MFBHUEN3V2UxZ2RMN2cteUJIQ2ZkTlppUTJ6Z2R4Q3gwdWpUbFFGM21GVGZBaEZn</guid></item><item><title>女人说医生在9分钟后就打消了她的顾虑。“她仍然遵循她的直觉，然后她的生活永远改变了-雅虎新闻新加坡</title><link>https://sg.news.yahoo.com/woman-says-doctor-dismissed-her-110000247.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;After a woman said a doctor dismissed initial concerns about her health, she received a life-changing diagnosis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Jillian, a schoolteacher, said she was sent home after only nine minutes with the medical professional&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Now, she advises others, "You need to listen to yourself. If you think something's wrong, get it checked out"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A woman received &lt;a href="https://people.com/womans-bruising-led-to-life-changing-diagnosis-exclusive-11739677" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a life-changing diagnosis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;a life-changing diagnosis&lt;/a&gt; when she &lt;a href="https://people.com/mother-urges-parents-to-trust-gut-after-opticians-check-on-sons-lazy-eye-leads-to-brain-cancer-diagnosis-11821170" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:trusted her gut;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;trusted her gut&lt;/a&gt; after a &lt;a href="https://people.com/marine-veteran-facing-paralysis-after-doctor-dismiss-symptoms-11888978" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:doctor dismissed her initial concerns;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;doctor dismissed her initial concerns&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Speaking with &lt;a href="https://www.mamamia.com.au/plastic-surgery-nose-reconstruction" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mamamia;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Mamamia&lt;/a&gt;, the woman, identified only as Jillian, said she noticed a growth on her nose, but her busy lifestyle, &lt;a href="https://people.com/working-moms-juggle-jobs-children-self-care-exclusive-11718186" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:balancing family and her career;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;balancing family and her career&lt;/a&gt; as a schoolteacher, kept her from getting it checked out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;One day, Jillian told the outlet that a student told her, "You've got funny red lines on your nose," which prompted her to schedule an appointment with her general practitioner, who then referred her to a specialist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;That medical professional, Jillian told Mamamia, advised her to stop using her decongestant spray and sent her on her way after only nine minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Doctors performing surgery (stock image).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to Jillian, she &lt;a href="https://people.com/ross-mathews-talks-overcoming-shame-to-prioritize-health-exclusive-8731539" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:doesn't always put her health first;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;doesn't always put her health first&lt;/a&gt;, so she thought nothing of it initially. "I don't normally listen to my body," she admitted to Mamamia. "It tells me a lot of different things, so it's hard to know."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Still, despite the specialist's dismissal, Jillian kept an eye on her nose, and over time, she said the red lines became brighter and she &lt;a href="https://people.com/11-year-old-noticed-a-bump-on-her-temple-months-later-cancer-took-her-eye-exclusive-11861327" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:eventually developed a lump;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;eventually developed a lump&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She eventually sought out a different skin specialist, whom Mamamia reported took biopsies and then referred her to a general surgeon, who told Jillian her medical dilemma was "self-contained" and had "its own blood supply."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Jillian subsequently went for several more biopsies, all while she said she was unable to breathe out of one nostril. "If you looked at me, you couldn't actually see the lump. But I felt it changing, it felt like something was crawling on my skin," she told Mamamia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/people-puzzler-8620185" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now!;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The PEOPLE Puzzler crossword is here! How quickly can you solve it? Play now!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Jillian eventually did a final biopsy, which determined she had &lt;a href="https://people.com/celebs-who-have-shared-skin-cancer-struggles-8666008" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:skin cancer;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;skin cancer&lt;/a&gt;. It also found that the growth had hardened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"The surgeons didn't know where the edges of the cancer were, and they were trying to be conservative and not take more than they had to," Jillian explained to Mamamia. "So, for the first surgery, they just took what looked cancerous to them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Jillian had to undergo numerous follow-up surgeries after the first, and she admitted that each took a toll on her. "Hearing after the first one, 'No, that actually wasn't enough, we need to do it again,' was really quite devastating," she told Mamamia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"I knew when they brought the tissue box over before the doctor came and saw me that it was not good news," she added. "I got a bit numb. It was just, 'No, we need to go back and do more.' And that was really hard to hear every time. The more they took out, the more I didn't feel like myself. I didn't know who I felt like."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; A woman upset in a hospital (stock image).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;After her growth was removed and she received radiation treatment, Jillian &lt;a href="https://people.com/couple-goes-viral-after-husband-documents-wifes-facelift-exclusive-11888132" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:underwent various plastic surgery procedures to reconstruct her face;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;underwent various plastic surgery procedures to reconstruct her face&lt;/a&gt;. "I didn't even know plastic surgeons did that sort of thing. I thought they were all the boobs and [butts]," she joked to Mamamia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Her last procedure occurred in November. Jillian told the outlet, "It was really good to feel more like myself and have a bit more confidence in myself. That was really, really important to feel a bit more normal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Now, it could take up to 12 months for Jillian's swelling to go down. She will then have to undergo bi-annual MRIs, to &lt;a href="https://people.com/mom-thought-had-dry-skin-before-skin-cancer-diagnosis-11793328" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:make sure her skin cancer hasn't returned;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;make sure her skin cancer hasn't returned&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Looking back at her healthy journey, Jillian told Mamamia she has once key piece of advice to share with others: "You need to listen to yourself. If you think something's wrong, get it checked out."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/woman-says-doctor-dismissed-concerns-after-9-minutes-she-then-got-cancer-diagnosis-11890378" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Singapore</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE9HQTlGSUg3R3N1YWpJZUVJYmNTNkFKWk03ZHN6eFhaN3FEam9aWVktYXV0aVVtRUhtTktrWXhQV3hhRkN3eDRBM0NiMllvejlCTlpKeEhUUGUwOTQzemxSX3d2VF8yWGdJc0Y1c284MnR5UUhNd19EZmVOVGI</guid></item><item><title>人们警告说，如果他们发现特定症状，应停止服用维生素D - LADbible</title><link>https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/vitamin-d-dosage-nhs-symptoms-605918-20260124</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;A health expert has issued a warning about the possible side effects from taking too much vitamin D.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Vitamin D is an important nutrient which keeps bones, teeth and muscles &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/health"&gt;healthy&lt;/a&gt; throughout the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/vitamin-d-tablet-warning-nhs-886892-20260122"&gt;A lack of it&lt;/a&gt; can lead to bone deformities in children and bone pain in adults, a condition known as osteomalacia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;For most &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/uk-news"&gt;Brits&lt;/a&gt; who aren't able to get vitamin D naturally from the sun, the NHS &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.nhs.uk/conditions/vitamins-and-minerals/vitamin-d/"&gt;recommends&lt;/a&gt; to take 10 micrograms (mcg) of vitamin D a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Between late March or early April to the end of September, most people can make all the vitamin D they need through sunlight on their skin and from a balanced diet," the health service says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/food-and-drink"&gt;Foods&lt;/a&gt; high in vitamin D include fatty fish like salmon and mackerel, cod liver oil, as well as fortified products like dairy milk, plant milks and orange juice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;The NHS advises Brits to take vitamin D supplementation during the less sunny months (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;But with one in six people taking supplements, a biomedical scientist says there &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/nutritionist-warns-vitamins-harmful-effects-548870-20251017"&gt;are certain symptoms&lt;/a&gt; you need to look out for, as reported &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/vitamin-d-users-told-stop-36586981"&gt;by&lt;/a&gt; The Mirror.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"As the NHS encourages vitamin D in winter, many people are reaching for bottles in the darker months and accidentally overshooting, then blaming the fallout &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.ladbible.com/news/health/flu-strain-fever-symptoms-warning-uk-hospitals-144323-20260113"&gt;on seasonal bugs&lt;/a&gt;," Tobias Mapulanga said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The co-founder of Repose Healthcare noted that symptoms can include 'constant thirst and needing the loo more often, queasiness, tummy pain or constipation, headaches or brain fog, and new aches or cramps'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;The most natural way to get vitamin D is from sunlight (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"The stakes are clear: the right amount supports you, but doubling up can turn a well-meant routine into feeling worse rather than better," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Jana Abelovska, a former Superintendent Pharmacist at Click Pharmacy, also explained &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.getsurrey.co.uk/news/health/pharmacists-vitamin-d-warning-people-30182075"&gt;to&lt;/a&gt; Surrey Live that too much vitamin D can lead to 'hypercalcemia'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"The best way to get vitamin D is through your diet, supported by supplements like tablets, capsules, gummies or sprays that you use directly into your mouth," the health professional said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Vitamin D is fat soluble, which means that it is absorbed into the body along with fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Around one in six adults in the UK have low levels of vitamin D (Getty Stock Images)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"This means taking your vitamin D supplement with food that contains some healthy fats, such as nuts or yoghurt, will help your body absorb it much better."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;She warned: "Don't take too much vitamin D. Because it's a fat-soluble vitamin, it can build up in your body easier than other vitamins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Taking too much vitamin D long term can lead to hypercalcemia, an excess of calcium in the body, which can cause problems with your heart, kidneys and bones."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The NHS advises to consult a doctor if you are unsure about vitamin D supplementation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>LADbible</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:58:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNY2ZyOTBUelRRYjgyakxVTjlEbkpERHZtWUd5ZklJQkZRVHprVnFEUWFNOFVURTcwTUV6MmVFWktHRzVYbFJ4RXZXOVpzU2hjRHZYRkFnUzRkTmJQMVlLemUxcjFpYzRTS3JjQ2FVMEM3QTV1b2puZmtGSnlXbzUwTEpLLS1iOWNzZEE</guid></item><item><title>佛罗里达神经科学家分享了3种对大脑“惊人”的补充剂：促进健康，改善记忆力…… |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/florida-neuroscientist-shares-3-supplements-that-are-amazing-for-the-brain-boosts-health-improves-memory-101769244438097.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt;&lt;p class="content"&gt;The brain is arguably the most important organ in our body, and taking proper care of it is essentially what life revolves around. While a healthy diet goes a long way, sometimes taking supplements helps to enhance the positive effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="artImage leadImage"&gt;&lt;figcaption class=""&gt;Taking supplements alongside maintaining a healthy lifestyle can do wonders when it comes to the brain. (Unsplash)&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;Also Read | &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Obesity specialist shares 3 hard-hitting facts about weight loss people don't believe: ‘Your goal weight is probably…’"&gt;Obesity specialist shares 3 hard-hitting facts about weight loss people don't believe: ‘Your goal weight is probably…’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Taking to Instagram on January 23, Robert WB Love, a Florida-based neuroscientist working on reversing Alzheimer’s, shared three supplements that show promising signs of boosting brain health, improving memory, and reducing the risk of developing dementia later in life.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artContent"&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Vitamin D&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Research shows that a deficiency in &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/orthopaedic-experts-share-5-foods-to-prevent-vitamin-d-deficiency-and-maintain-bone-health-during-sun-deprived-winters-101766582027818.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="vitamin D"&gt;vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; increases the risk of Alzheimer’s disease,” shared Robert. It is also very important for the immune system and maintaining bone health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;For women over 50 in particular, taking a vitamin D supplement along with a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/florida-neuroscientist-explains-the-importance-of-magnesium-shares-the-best-time-to-take-it-101768560394083.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="magnesium"&gt;magnesium&lt;/a&gt; supplement helps build strong bones. The process is aided by going through resistance or weight training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Bacopa Monnieri&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert considers bacopa monnieri, or bacopa in short, as a less popular but extremely beneficial supplement. Among Alzheimer’s patients, the effects of the substance include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improved memory&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improved &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/unable-to-sleep-5-habits-that-help-to-calm-down-the-mind-before-bedtime-101768656405689.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="sleep"&gt;sleep&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Improved quality of life&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Reduced symptoms of Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among children, bacopa is known to help with attention deficit hyperactivity disorder (ADHD) by reducing the symptoms and improving their behaviour at school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;“I have taken bacopa, and I’ve found that it improves my memory, focus, and attention,” shared Robert, explaining, “Bacopa works by increasing a neurotransmitter in the brain called acetylcholine.&lt;/span&gt;”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="content "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. NMN (nicotinamide mononucleotide)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Nicotinamide mononucleotide is a supplement that is becoming increasingly popular, as per Robert, who explains it as “a precursor to an important energy source” for both the body and the brain called NAD (nicotinamide adenine dinucleotide).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;“&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;New research shows that a reduction of NAD in the brain is linked to an increased risk of Alzheimer’s disease,” shared Robert, adding that substances like NMN that increase NAD in the brain can help improve brain function and memory, and reduce the risk of Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="content "&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:15:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwJBVV95cUxPMzFsX2UzQ1REYVF3QVNPaWN0VnotcmI3UnI4X2pyWGF0SERpbFBaSFFTdjJEVGUyZTdUWl9lTUJkajlFRVd5S1JGa1FNakVJaUNZME5jQmo5S1p6b1pSSkMtdjZEVFZ2NWJYUnpld21nV1V2bk1VRXlVdktYbXpnUlQ1NjdSMzdOSWJhcWpRS09VV3A5UFU4bXdNaHlCanp3S2FmZmVPMFQ5VUtqeTNpb2Z2YnNsN2g5QnpXY1E0Z1RnN1NEVXd4RjlGVDJEQjdvakQzdHZxVTFLUnE1ODZtSnhUTVhNMVhLRUxTTkRaV0MyTGFidjU0VkpRTUlkclVmUXNz0gGIAkFVX3lxTE5tOWViZWNtUkF1dTU1SDdkT2Nqa0RmOENwa1Z0YThZdS1EdmdqM0diYTdlN3ppLXRzZnFjclNaUmMxbWpGVjNlQUJRNVZFeTBfaUZwYnVQUXA0VThQTzVVMm82RC1hZXhxSGNJTFpPNUVNX3RNYl92aTFqSkVDSEkzMFVDdzRtU0ZsRUJLX1RmNUxBS09HNFhnaks2MWMwWmZuSWNEVDc2eWV6N0tobm5ncDNYYlQ0Y1RUVlFkOGNvSnlmbmRkTmEzeTJGRXFoVklINzl0RmxkUlgtc1RVMnFyTFpXeUoza1pkV0VORmM3UURTR25pMWZMeGZMZHpNN3FOekRYWGVYUA</guid></item><item><title>关于医学和医疗保健的6个播客-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/24/arts/podcasts-medicine-health-science.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:00:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOd1h5RVF1VnhjR1JEY2hDNTJxTWttcDJxMW9CVnIwOWtuLWI3SzdRYXE3THlBSHBVMkVKRGlINGUzb1ZNdUlsMmx6MHJhUG9xRjZ2Rk5QLU1YNTdhenRBeHlUM0VraFE1VjRoQjBaQk9KQWZPSG9URkd1dkJwbTFfc1ljNA</guid></item><item><title>随着年龄的增长，忘记肌肉质量，专注于力量-纽约时报</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2026/01/24/well/move/muscle-strength-versus-mass.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 10:00:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxNTFpnUUNCMl9IamxhdzF3Y042WW10VmNJazMtN0g0NXJnd2Nia3QyTnBqeXNXM0c3SnBNSVptYnlHRmRfZGFocjkxUGlkYS00ejFpeW5FeHkya05QRnEtVEdMZTRGd1FzdFNLTHFCUFJ0OFI5RDQwMmc3UjBYMlg3ZllqVQ</guid></item><item><title>允许家庭检查风险的NHS癌症基因数据库- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c62v7l4v7gro</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A new NHS database of genes linked to cancer could enable patients and their families in England to find out whether they are at risk of developing the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;People will be able to have their genetic information compared to the world-first register of 120 genes known to increase the likelihood of getting cancer, NHS England has said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Those identified as having an inherited risk will be offered routine check-ups and screening for certain cancers, including breast and prostate cancer. Patients could also be tested to see whether they would respond better to particular treatments, allowing for personalised care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Health Secretary Wes Streeting said the "life-changing and life-saving" tool would fast-track screening and allow more cancers to be caught sooner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Tens of thousands of cancer patients and those with a family history of the disease already undergo genetic testing on the NHS every year. Those known to have a higher risk profile will be added to the new register.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;They will be given tailored information about what they can do to lower their chance of developing cancer or detect it early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS said it was building the register&lt;b id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt; &lt;/b&gt;as part of a 10-year plan to improve prevention and treatment of cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;NHS England's national cancer director told BBC Radio 4's Today programme it was "the first time any health care system has brought together all the information about all the genetic risk into a single place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Peter Johnson said it pulled together the tests patients were already offered to check their cancer susceptibility into a single register, "so that we can contact people to offer them screening and in some cases preventative treatment".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This will allow practitioners to "keep tabs on people" and offer them new tests and treatments as they are rolled out, he added, while stressing it would be "incredibly confidential and secure".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Johnson said that while it could be "very daunting" for people to find out their cancer risk, it meant the disease could be picked up as early as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS National Inherited Cancer Predisposition Register follows a similar database for Lynch syndrome which saw more than 12,000 people offered routine preventative screening after they were identified as being at higher risk, according to the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Charlie Grinstead, a 32-year-old diagnosed with bowel cancer in 2020, said his Lynch syndrome diagnosis gave him access to immunotherapy after unsuccessful chemotherapy - and proved to be the "the key to my recovery".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Streeting said: "One in every two people will get cancer in their lifetime but that does not mean the chances are random - many people face a higher risk through the genes they inherit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"And while we cannot do anything about inherited genes, we can do something about what we do with that information."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He said the "world-leading genetic register" would allow personalised and preventative care to be provided sooner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"This register won't just supercharge innovation - it will be life changing and life-saving, allowing the NHS to develop individual care, fast-track screening and tailored information to enable more cancers to be caught earlier."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Claire Rowney, the chief executive of Breast Cancer Now, said the move would "transform the lives of women who are at increased risk of breast cancer due to their family history or genetics".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said it had to be accessible to all clinicians and designed to ensure those with an increased risk profile received "joined-up care".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 09:28:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1MbEtzWWxNVUptTm9Pb2I0bmpGQ1QtZzlIVzBrMXAzc3pDTGFSaXpTcTJRelhXSkg4X1NmU09EMnd3TnJhMGdWWjVLUG9MZnRDQ3c0WHFmeXJfQdIBX0FVX3lxTFBGSEVLMzhCRjJDSTlWTmZoR25iSnJnOF9yY0poOHNGSHRmclN4aFJCaHA2aGlpdktEbHV1TXFoRlFYTllySG13NFFxdlJ1ZDdRbGJyR18xMHp3cXVkMkk4</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法， 50岁以上的男性应该吃5种抗炎食物- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/anti-inflammatory-foods-men-over-50-should-eat-11891280</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anti-inflammatory foods support gut and heart health and may lower cancer risk in men over 50.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Men over 50 should add foods like oats, fatty fish, berries and beans to their diet.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Managing stress, drinking less and getting ample sleep can also help reduce inflammation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For men over 50, concerns like achy joints, heart health and maintaining muscle often start to feel more front-of-mind. And while inflammation isn’t always harmful—short-term inflammation plays an important role in healing and immune defense—&lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/what-is-inflammation-8766645" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;chronic inflammation is linked to poorer health outcomes&lt;/a&gt;, including a higher risk of heart disease and diabetes.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Regular human metabolism naturally produces inflammation throughout the body, but it tries to control it through anti-inflammatory pathways," shares &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/dustin-moore-phd-rd-a1bb294a/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Dustin Moore, PhD, RD&lt;/a&gt;. "It’s not often discussed, but the pro- and anti-inflammatory mechanisms work in tricky balance with one another, and certain actions can influence that balance." The foods we eat play a big role in either &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/habit-to-avoid-for-chronic-inflammation-8644317" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;triggering or reducing inflammation&lt;/a&gt;. Focusing on fruits and vegetables, lean protein, healthy fats and whole grains is a core piece of anti-inflammatory diets.&lt;span data-cite="1" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; We dug into the research more and chatted with registered dietitians to highlight &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/anti-inflammatory-foods-for-women-over-50-11794640" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;top anti-inflammatory foods that men over 50 should be eating&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-1-fatty-fish"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 1. Fatty Fish &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you're looking for a food to do double duty—&lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7595044/the-10-best-anti-inflammatory-foods-for-heart-health/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reducing inflammation and keeping your heart healthy&lt;/a&gt;—fatty fish should be at the top of your list. Fish like salmon, anchovies and herring deliver omega-3 fatty acids.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/author/christopher-mohr/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Chris Mohr, Ph.D., RD&lt;/a&gt;, recommends, "Sardines. Yes, yes—sardines. They're rich in omega-3 fats, vitamin D, calcium and other important nutrients for everyone." He adds, "Most adults don't eat adequate amounts of omega-3 fats and sardines can help fill the gap for this nutrient and others."&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Omega-3 fats are anti-inflammatory and the American Heart Association recommends eating seafood twice a week to help &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/15297/our-top-15-heart-healthy-foods/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;reduce the risk of heart disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Omega-3's may also help reduce the risk of certain cancers, dementia and age-related macular degeneration.&lt;span data-cite="2" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Not everyone loves sardines, but they work well in salads and pasta dishes. &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/249244/honey-soy-broiled-salmon/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Honey-Soy Broiled Salmon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7944627/garlic-anchovy-pasta-with-broccolini/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Garlic-Anchovy Pasta with Broccolini&lt;/a&gt; are two other yummy ways to get your omega-3's.   
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-2-berries"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 2. Berries &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Berries deliver an antioxidant punch. "Whatever the mix—raspberries, blueberries, blackberries—just eat a serving of berries," says Moore. "They're a rich source of antioxidants, and they also provide a good dose of fiber, a key component of the diet that older men are frequently missing." 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Berries get their color from flavonoids, including anthocyanins, which &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-foods-to-fight-inflammation-11762781" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;help reduce inflammation and disease risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The compounds in berries may also help keep hearts healthy by improving cholesterol, specifically decreasing LDL or "bad" cholesterol levels.&lt;span data-cite="4" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Eat them as is, or throw them in some Greek yogurt with a little granola for crunch," advises Moore. &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/8031379/dietitian-favorite-recipes-with-frozen-berries/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Frozen berries are a great option&lt;/a&gt; to save some money and always keep berries on hand. They work well in smoothies and in these &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/blueberry-pie-inspired-overnight-oats-11721962" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Blueberry Pie-Inspired Overnight Oats&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-3beans"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 3.Beans &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beans and legumes may not be top of mind, but they are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/you-just-started-anti-inflammatory-diet-recipes-to-make-first-8770807" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;part of an anti-inflammatory diet&lt;/a&gt; and contain many plant compounds that help reduce inflammation.&lt;strong&gt;  &lt;/strong&gt;Mohr notes,&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; "The unsung hero of the nutrition world is fiber, and beans top the list as one of the best sources of fiber, among other nutrients as well." Hitting your fiber goals “can drastically lower the risk of cardiovascular disease, many cancers, and more," he adds. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Beans add a source of plant-based protein and can help improve the diversity of your gut microbiome, &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/swap-to-lower-risk-of-heart-disease-and-diabetes-8679543" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reduce your risk for heart disease and type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; and reduce chronic inflammation.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;The polyphenols in beans have antioxidant properties to help keep you healthy. Eating beans may also help with weight loss.&lt;span data-cite="5" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Mohr notes, "Beans are versatile, inexpensive and can complement almost any dish." Try them in soups, salads, casseroles and in this &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/roasted-vegetable-breakfast-grain-bowl-8742347" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Anti-Inflammatory Breakfast Bowl&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-4-cruciferous-vegetables"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 4. Cruciferous Vegetables &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Cruciferous vegetables, which include broccoli, cauliflower and Brussels sprouts, are a good source of antioxidants and fiber," shares Moore. They're known for their key flavonoids, such as quercetin and kaempferol, which help reduce inflammation. Cruciferous veggies, in particular, when eaten as part of a balanced diet, are &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/vegan-vegetarian-cancer-risk-study-11790465" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;linked to reduced cancer risk&lt;/a&gt;. That includes colorectal cancer and prostate cancer, two of the most common cancers in men.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span data-cite="6" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Moore likes roasting his veggies in the oven or in the air fryer with some salt and cheese. There are so many ways to enjoy more cruciferous vegetables: add kale to a salad, cabbage to stir-fry or add them to a soup, stew or curry like this &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/slow-cooker-cauliflower-chickpea-tikka-masala-8580545" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Slow-Cooker Cauliflower &amp;amp; Chickpea Tikka Masala&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-5-oats"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; 5. Oats &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Mohr likes oats because they contain &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/fiber-foods-to-help-lower-cholesterol-11770161" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;soluble fiber, which helps reduce your risk of heart disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Fiber is important for your health in many ways, and it helps reduce inflammation because of what it does in your gut. Eating more fiber from whole grains, including oats, increases the production of short-chain fatty acids in your colon, which feed your gut bacteria, helps reduce your risk of colon cancer, and reduces inflammation in the gut.&lt;span data-cite="8" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Fiber helps keep your blood sugar steadier, which can reduce oxidative stress from glucose spikes, and in turn tamps inflammation.&lt;span data-cite="3" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Oats also contain &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/the-top-nutrients-to-fight-inflammation-8675325" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;anti-inflammatory compounds, like avenanthramides&lt;/a&gt;, to help reduce oxidative stress in the body.&lt;span data-cite="7" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "They can be soaked overnight and enjoyed in the morning, cooked, or eaten raw, with milk and berries," adds Mohr. Get your fill with our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/high-protein-apple-peanut-butter-overnight-oats-11784430" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;High-Protein Apple &amp;amp; Peanut Butter Overnight Oats&lt;/a&gt; or try a classic &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/269639/old-fashioned-oatmeal/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Old-Fashioned Oatmeal&lt;/a&gt;. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-strategies-to-reduce-inflammation"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Other Strategies to Reduce Inflammation &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Manage stress: "&lt;/strong&gt;Uncontrolled and unmanaged stress is well studied and fairly destructive at the cellular level. Long-term, it can even contribute to chronic illness," notes Moore. "I tell men all the time, build and maintain appropriate outlets that help you manage your stress, whether that’s exercise, sports or engaging in hobbies."&lt;span data-cite="9" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Exercise regularly&lt;/strong&gt;: Research links exercise with &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7908639/the-fastest-way-to-reduce-inflammation/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reducing chronic low-grade inflammation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span data-cite="10" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Find movement that you enjoy and commit to staying active. That might look like walking, swimming, cycling, jogging, lifting weights or yoga. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Prioritize sleep&lt;/strong&gt;: It's recommended to get at least 7 hours of sleep per night but about a third of Americans aren't getting enough sleep. Falling short on sleep not only leaves you feeling tired, it can also &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/how-inflammation-ages-you-8744048" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;increase inflammation&lt;/a&gt;. Getting adequate sleep can also help reduce your risk of high blood pressure and type 2 diabetes.&lt;span data-cite="11" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;,&lt;span data-cite="12" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Turn off screens before bed, limit caffeine in the afternoon and try to establish a healthy evening routine to be sure you're getting enough shut-eye.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Limit alcohol:&lt;/strong&gt; While the occasional beer or glass of wine isn't likely to do much harm, drinking alcohol can cause oxidative stress and inflammation.&lt;span data-cite="13" class="inline-citation-node"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Keep your alcoholic drinks to a minimum for your overall health and for the most anti-inflammatory diet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It might feel overwhelming to start making changes to your diet, but there's no need for an overhaul. Start small by adding a handful of berries to breakfast or making oatmeal a few times a week. "It’s never too late to start," adds Moore. "There’s still plenty of life ahead of you. Make a simple change today, do it again tomorrow, and keep that practice going until it becomes habitual."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_55-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; While these anti-inflammatory foods can benefit everyone, they may be especially important for men over 50 to help improve gut health, heart health and reduce the risk of certain cancers. When you think of an overall diet to reduce inflammation, aim to eat a variety of colorful plant foods and a well-balanced diet. And it's not about perfection. "The most important factor is consistency with any lifestyle habit, whether it is a dietary change, lifestyle change or other," notes Mohr.  
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:48:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQYWUwd3I5Vlo1WVBEWjBjNkFDZTlzLW9TRnM3cUdNd0JacmI4Zzhmd2lZREJBQnlNdVlmV09lZWpvbkQ1TWdXSUVFNlo1b0Q0eDRLWEV2TC1iSUFHYjRkTTMyNzN6M0tSRDZvOGFWVHJuOTJCRXNxREJfemtlbk1yajdDX01BUktxY3c</guid></item><item><title>专家说，即使你锻炼身体，这种日常习惯也会缩短你的寿命--《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/health-and-fitness/sitting-work-heart-disease-risk-live-longer-b2897509.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gIQPHK sc-jbiisr-1 sc-1wfc891-0 fooWDH" id="main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="big-letter"&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;re you sitting comfortably? Probably. According to the NHS, many UK adults spend upwards of nine hours each day sitting down. But too much sitting could seriously damage your health, according to &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.brunel.ac.uk/news-and-events/news/articles/Sitting-for-long-stretches-raises-heart-and-diabetes-risks"&gt;new research&lt;/a&gt; from Brunel University – even if you meet weekly &lt;a href="/topic/exercise"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt; recommendations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We reviewed the published evidence available regarding associations between sedentary behaviour [sitting or lying down] and different risk markers for &lt;a href="/topic/heart-disease"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="/topic/diabetes"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; in people aged 60 and above,” says sedentary behaviour specialist Dr Daniel Bailey who is, perhaps predictably, stationed at a standing desk during our video call. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review found that people who sat down for large chunks of their day were far more likely to have a higher waist circumference and body fat levels. They also recorded worse readings for several biomarkers linked to heart disease and diabetes, such as blood pressure, glucose levels, triglycerides and cholesterol. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Those risks were there regardless of the amount of physical activity these older adults were engaging in,” he adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How much sitting is too much?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people spend upwards of eight hours at a desk each day. Add in the journey home from work and sofa time watching telly, and it’s easy to see how daily sitting times are so high for many of us. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Over the past few decades, we’ve seen all of this technology come into play, which gives us more opportunities to sit down,” Dr Bailey says. “With that, we have seen a massive increase in obesity and the diseases that come with it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data suggests older populations are the most sedentary group, and it is this demographic that will likely experience the greatest benefits from cutting down their daily sitting time. However, Dr Bailey adds, “It is an important consideration for all ages,” with studies on children and working-age adults also linking excessive sitting to increased health risks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Some studies show the threshold is somewhere between seven and 10 hours of sitting per day being too much,” Dr Bailey tells me. “That’s where your risk of early mortality and several different diseases really starts to increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/strength-training-for-longevity-b2826608.html"&gt;The science-backed exercise method that can help fight the effects of ageing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obviously, if you move less, you burn less energy during the day, which can contribute to weight gain. Muscles can lose strength when unused, joints can become stiff, and because you are asking less of your heart and lungs each day, fitness can fade away. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bcLYNA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/11/08/16/woman-work-desk.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/11/08/16/woman-work-desk.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/s3fs-public/thumbnails/image/2019/11/08/16/woman-work-desk.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Many people spend nine hours or more of their day sitting down, according to the NHS" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-264724"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Many people spend nine hours or more of their day sitting down, according to the NHS&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research shows that the negative effects of excessive sedentary time are linked to the amount of time you spend sitting down at a time. “There have been a number of studies that show the benefits of breaking up your sedentary time every 30 to 60 minutes,” explains. Dr Bailey added that the mechanism behind this is not yet fully understood. He describes it as a series of “metabolic switches that help regulate blood sugar, glucose levels and cholesterol levels.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you’re not doing regular muscular contractions, these metabolic switches switch off. That’s when we get higher levels of glucose in the blood, higher cholesterol in the blood, and our blood pressure isn’t as well regulated.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/10000-steps-walking-workout-heart-health-b2886117.html"&gt;If you struggle to walk 10,000 steps a day, a scientist recommends trying this instead&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to fight back&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The primary ways to fight the negative effects of sitting down is to do less of it, and to ensure you are getting regular muscular contractions – ie using your muscles and moving. Based on his research, Dr Bailey prescribes trying to move in some form every 30 to 60 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 bHmhpR"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/24/13/iStock-2210705103.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/24/13/iStock-2210705103.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/24/13/iStock-2210705103.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Regular muscular contractions – through moving or simply standing up – can combat the negative effects of too much sitting" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-264725"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Regular muscular contractions – through moving or simply standing up – can combat the negative effects of too much sitting&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Every movement counts,” he says. “We’ve published a lot of studies in our group that show how regular, short bouts of light activity keep these metabolic switches turned on, and your blood sugar levels and cholesterol stay lower throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It doesn’t need to be structured exercise. Simply standing up seems to be beneficial in people that are overweight, obese or have type two diabetes. We’ve also looked at slow walking – people can get these metabolic benefits from things we do in our everyday lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Every half an hour, get up, move around for a few minutes, and that should help reduce your risk of the different diseases we’ve discussed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/exercise-snacking-workouts-heart-health-b2859776.html"&gt;The science-backed two-minute daily workouts for improving heart health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another easy change Dr Bailey suggests is reorganising your workstation to encourage more movement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Changing your setup so not everything is at hand can help,” he explains. “If you need a pen, to print something or put something in the bin, having those things located away from your desk might encourage you to move more often. And rather than sending a colleague an email, go and talk to them at their desk.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="4" class="sc-awdjp1-0 iLHiBm"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/17/15/12/iStock-2194826147.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/17/15/12/iStock-2194826147.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/12/17/15/12/iStock-2194826147.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Dr Daniel Bailey recommends moving for a few minutes every half an hour where possible" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-264726"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 gtVitN hgzWpY"&gt;Dr Daniel Bailey recommends moving for a few minutes every half an hour where possible&lt;span class="sc-1cbdeug-7 exGSyR"&gt; (Getty/iStock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;You could also make a conscious effort to move after you finish certain tasks at your computer, he adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Sometimes you might ignore an alert to move from your wearable or an app because you are working on something. Instead, wait until the end of a task, then use that as your cue to get up and move around. If you’re working from home, you could spread your housework across the day rather than doing it in one big chunk, and use these opportunities to do it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-kk992l-0 dDVXDN"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Reap the benefits &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that the results of reducing your daily sitting time and making even these small tweaks are pretty remarkable. “If we can limit our sedentary time and be physically active, we’re going to live a longer and healthier life, which is what I think we’re all striving for,” says Dr Bailey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Benefits you might see and feel quite quickly are [a] better mood, more energy and less fatigue. Then, in the longer term, you might start to see reductions in body fat or body weight because you are burning more calories from movement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The deeper impacts won’t be as obvious, but you could benefit from a reduction in blood sugar levels and a reduction in blood pressure. That will help reduce your risk of heart disease, stroke, diabetes and some cancers as well.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Read more: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/health-and-fitness/heart-health-attack-cardio-exercise-b2785415.html"&gt;A cardiac nurse says these five daily behaviours can reduce your risk of heart disease&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jan 2026 06:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxQM3ZmU291bUhjUFRiX0kwQUJsTDUtVFJybVlJR2MxbUlENW1yTnRQUENtZlMwYVBSMkRUWE5xeUUyMWlVcURISU5HUTkwNjk3dVFfNm15SFBNMWFRYmEybkxwYk55WmFkYkRySW1RS0FoaUVJMlM3dGRzOTR5VHU2WTNwSFRhZ2lLWXhUcWdtMkhWN09rWk51SDRlNzFqM2lTS0RKNjA2VXpGQQ</guid></item></channel></rss>