<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>营养师揭示了像Ozempic一样起作用的改变游戏规则的补充剂-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15446727/ozempic-supplements-weight-loss-effects.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A dietitian has revealed the unlikely supplements that may help supercharge the effects of blockbuster &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-e4da46d0-ed67-11f0-9035-67da10d0cb2b"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt; drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Taken by one in eight American adults (30 million people) injections like Ozempic and Wegovy have &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15422983/ozempic-reshaping-american-diet-buying-grocery-store.html"&gt;changed the landscape of weight loss&lt;/a&gt;, diet and &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-ccfa0710-eda5-11f0-be85-7d59e2a2da28"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; care. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The drugs work by mimicking glucagon-like peptide-1 (GLP-1), a naturally present hormone in the gut that slows digestion, regulates blood sugar and tells the body it's full - which helps control diabetes and weight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because GLP-1 medications slow gastric emptying, those taking them often have to adjust their diets and supplement regimens to avoid potentially debilitating side effects like nausea, constipation, diarrhea and bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In her new book, Your Best Shot: The Personalized System for Optimal Weight Health - GLP-1 Shot or Not, California-based dietitian Ashley Koff revealed the ins and outs of the weight loss shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Speaking to the Daily Mail, Koff, a dietitian for more than 25 years, identified the supplements science suggests may help boost the effects of the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She noted that while tried and true supplements like omega-3s and fiber help aid digestion and satiety, lesser known ones like berberine and Amarasate may enhance the body's natural production of GLP-1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, she cautioned that no supplement can replace a medication for those whose doctors have deemed it necessary for health control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A dietitian has revealed the key supplements to take to maximize the effects of GLP-1 agonists &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There is a lot of misinformation about supplements,' Koff told the Daily Mail. 'There is no "nature's Ozempic," there's no supplement that works exactly like the medications do because [medications] stay working for 24 hours, for seven days a week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'There are a couple [supplements] on the market that are helping our bodies have more GLP-1, but nothing that would compare to a medication.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Berberine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Berberine is a yellow plant-derived compound found in herbs like barberry and Oregon grape. Long used in herbal medicine for infections and digestive issues, it is now sold in supplement form for blood sugar, cholesterol and weight control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Costing between $10 and $50 per bottle, berberine is a type of bitter, meaning it stimulates the body's bitter taste receptors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Stimulating these receptors in the gut triggers cells in this area to release more GLP-1, adding on to the benefits of a weight loss shot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'If they stimulate the bitter taste receptors, that's going to help our own body's hormones,' Koff said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, berberine has been shown to interact with medications that control blood pressure and cholesterol, so doctors recommend caution if you are taking one of those drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Ashley Koff (pictured) cautioned that while supplements may enhance GLP-1 production, there is no 'nature's Ozempic'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Probiotics&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt; Probiotics are 'good' bacteria naturally found in the gut and in fermented foods such as kimchi, doenjang and kefir.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They have been shown to promote healthy digestion and help the body absorb vital nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Koff specifically pointed to Akkermansia muciniphila, which has been shown to strengthen the intestinal barrier and reduce inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Mucinophilia means it likes mucin, so it goes in and it chews up the mucin and the mucosal layer,' Koff said. 'In doing that, it's going to help to stimulate the production of GLP-1.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Akkermansia muciniphila does not directly come from food, but its growth in the gut and can be boosted by eating foods rich in polyphenols such as berries, green tea and dark chocolate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is also available as a supplement in pill or gummy form, costing anywhere from $20 to $80 per bottle depending on the brand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Glutamine&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="mol-img-group floatRHS"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Pictured: Koff's book, which was released on January 6&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Koff also recommended glutamine, the most abundant of 20 amino acids in the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the body produces its own, it can also be found in animal products like beef, chicken, fish, eggs, milk, yogurt and cheese, as well as plant-based sources such as legumes, spinach and whole grains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As a supplement, bottles with 60 to 180 capsules tend to cost anywhere from $10 to $35. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Glutamine is also available as a powder, with prices ranging from $10 to $40 depending on the size and brand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Similar to berberine, glutamine in food or supplement form triggers intestinal cells to secrete additional GLP-1.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It has also been shown to help strengthen intestinal lining, which helps lower inflammation that could otherwise interfere with GLP-1 signaling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead health-ccox"&gt;Amarasate &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hailing from New Zealand hops, Amarasate is, much like berberine, a natural bitter extract. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sold as an appetite control supplement, a 90-capsule bottle costs about $70 to $90.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Similar to berberine, Koff explained the supplement stimulates bitter taste receptors that trigger the natural release of GLP-1, promoting feelings of fullness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Koff told the Daily Mail that Amarasate may be particularly useful for people coming off a GLP-1 agonist like Ozempic or Wegovy since it naturally stimulates hormone production with minimal side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Amarasate also works to reduce hunger in as little as 30 minutes, she noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span class="mol-style-italic"&gt;Your Best Shot: The Personalized System for Optimal Weight Health - GLP-1 Shot or Not is available now through Amazon, Barnes &amp;amp; Noble, HarperCollins Publishers and others. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 20:49:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxONzdrUlpYSDVKbEVaWXF2ckhYZGlHTkFMbnlQeWxlWDhTRjFWNHhheXRZelA1WHlRM1ljZ3E1d3hpZDN1V3ZDUHA4QmNCMW8wa2pSRzFELXBCV004SlpDai1rY2JVLUswc3hqOFlVcXdRbm5LZEF6UjllQThvTm55aTZ6WkI2c0RJTUVQV0FNWEhNbXFCbWdZQ1BfUFc</guid></item><item><title>亨廷顿警告居民在赫克歇尔公园附近发现死鹅-新闻日报</title><link>https://www.newsday.com/long-island/environment/bird-flu-testing-huntington-xxlulg0n</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="continue-reading ContinueReading_continue-reading__uTArZ active ContinueReading_active__SOMMR"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A half-dozen geese found dead in and near Heckscher Park in Huntington this month are being tested for possible avian influenza, according to a post on the&lt;a class="nd-link" href="https://www.facebook.com/photo?fbid=1284350360406443&amp;amp;set=pcb.1284350490406430"&gt; Town of Huntington's Facebook page&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The town said official lab results may not be available for as much as a month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="nd-link" href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/livestock-poultry-disease/avian/avian-influenza"&gt;Highly Pathogenic Avian Influenza&lt;/a&gt;, commonly called bird flu, was first identified in New York in 2022. The disease most often infects wild water fowl such as geese and ducks but also can also infect raptors, corvids (ravens and crows) and mammals, according to the state Department of Environmental Conservation. Songbirds do not appear to be very susceptible, the state says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease can be passed to domestic birds such as chicken and even to cattle. Occasionally humans who have had direct contact with an infected animal — usually farmworkers at chicken or diary facilities — can be infected. Severe illness is not common, according to the state Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been no known cases of bird flu in humans in New York, the agency said. "While avian influenza continues to affect wildlife, the risk to humans remain low," state Health Commissioner James McDonald said in a statement earlier this month. "New Yorkers can stay safe by avoiding contact with sick or dead birds and animals and reporting anything unusual."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms include sneezing or nasal discharge, lethargy, neurologic problems such as stargazing or seizures, diarrhea and weakness. The disease generally peaks in the winter months, according to the DEC. There is no treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts advise that people should not touch a dead bird and to keep pets away as well. If it’s necessary to move a bird, wear gloves and a mask.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If residents find a dead bird, the town of Huntington asks that they call the town's animal control at 631-754-8722.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Possible avian flu cases can also be reported in the &lt;a class="nd-link" href="https://survey123.arcgis.com/share/dee381c0ee8a4114a83dc1892fc0f7ed"&gt;DEC’s online form&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Newsday</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 20:44:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQbTFLQi1DYzR5alBPLWJNOFRHNVRDS0s5emZLTUlLNHRodC01ZU1YeS1zQmk5eVdlRl9uNTZXRko3UGNnRTctdldNUm83UXFLczd5dldweXctUXlOMXNzUndfdm9FUFp4WTRYSTZHRXRkZHFFM3VrLXhjZTFzaTFFdnBHTkhDVGFxYlBvYg</guid></item><item><title>什么是“代谢健康” ，为什么它很重要？ -《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/what-is-metabolic-health-and-why-does-it-matter/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxQUUIyaS05T2ZrMnJ1TE1FSjZqVGh0ZFJSSngtTS1ENVl2aldjQl9fQkpYMV93NHdOYlBmQnUybU94SXlySmhZTklmY3NzV25TUTRTY3pJYmR6bmhlWFdpaXhKck1RUEtCRE1UM096a2NZRlJMakpjRUtxRWdJNXdZTGNhZmM5SU83dGJzUnN5Q0hvdnps?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;What is ‘metabolic health,’ and why does it matter?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqNggKIjBDQklTSGpvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoRUtEd2k2bC1DdUVCSDJkSFFEWmY3VC1DZ0FQAQ?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&amp;amp;oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View Full Coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQUUIyaS05T2ZrMnJ1TE1FSjZqVGh0ZFJSSngtTS1ENVl2aldjQl9fQkpYMV93NHdOYlBmQnUybU94SXlySmhZTklmY3NzV25TUTRTY3pJYmR6bmhlWFdpaXhKck1RUEtCRE1UM096a2NZRlJMakpjRUtxRWdJNXdZTGNhZmM5SU83dGJzUnN5Q0hvdnps</guid></item><item><title>南卡罗来纳州爆发克莱姆森大学主校区麻疹确诊病例- WRAL</title><link>https://www.wral.com/lifestyles/health/confirmed-measles-case-clemson-university-jan-18-2026/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
					&lt;p id="font-resize" class="font-resize-container"&gt;
						&lt;button id="small-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa small-buttom-font-svg" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="medium-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="large-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;

					
						&lt;p&gt;A case of measles was confirmed at Clemson University, according to the school. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://news.clemson.edu/confirmed-case-of-measles-on-clemson-main-campus/"&gt;press release published&lt;/a&gt; Saturday, Clemson officials were informed by the South Carolina Department of Public Health that an individual affiliated with the university was confirmed to have measles. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
								
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;This person has been isolated per the department's requirements, and the department is conducting contact tracing with people who may have been exposed. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The release added that according to the most recent data from Clemson's Student Health Services, nearly 98% of main campus students have provided proof of immunity. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;A person infected with measles is contagious four days before and after a rash begins. Isolation of an actively infectious case lasts until four full days have passed after the onset of the rash, and dates of isolation are determined by DPH. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Quarantine for measles is reserved for exposed individuals without documented immunity and lasts for 21 days after the last exposure per DPH guidelines. If a person without documented immunity receives a dose of the MMR vaccine within 72 hours after the last exposure, they do not have to quarantine. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;This announcement by the university comes in the &lt;a href="https://www.wral.com/news/ap/5fe1a-measles-cases-jump-again-in-south-carolina-rising-to-more-than-550/"&gt;midst of a surge in reported measles cases in South Carolina&lt;/a&gt;. As of Friday, Jan. 16, cases surged by almost 30%, according to state health officials. &lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/lifestyles/health/confirmed-measles-case-clemson-university-jan-18-2026"&gt;
								&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/lifestyles/health/confirmed-measles-case-clemson-university-jan-18-2026/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The South Carolina health department reported 124 new cases since last Tuesday, bringing the state's total to 558 in a wave of infections centered around an outbreak in Spartanburg County.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Since the holidays, South Carolina's measles outbreak has exploded into the worst in the U.S. Measles also have been reported this year in Arizona, Florida, Georgia, North Carolina, Ohio, Oregon, Utah and Virginia, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;


				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRAL</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 18:05:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPRzhLb2pLd3E1OEtZOWRjQmhqVG1ETXJEbHg0ek4zcV9pTkk1N1RMRWlHM1ZiemFkVXV5MEZ0LVRkcGZfVk1OWG9ZNXpDTk1ldS12SWpoekRJcFIwakdLaFNtc29QZ192MEpCU253ejBKY1hMYXhXd1BYV2RDWE9BZVU1Q0YybVJ6NXpVR2ZwUE1KMWY1N2lwdg</guid></item><item><title>金毛猎犬用可爱的视频踩着小脚趾走路- PetHelpful</title><link>https://pethelpful.com/pet-news/golden-retriever-walks-on-tippy-toes</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PetHelpful</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFBvWUpYaFd3ajNKYU1SOTJYM29ZYmxwc1FCTzJDMDhlOGlpaGgzQVFyN1ZHYkhIMEFUeG95YTRXekEzTnJBbDU5RXhtS2JFLW0wdjRaTGlhcHlsemstNG1pUGdsbmd4NTNEdk9jZjBnTTNmMng1LXU4</guid></item><item><title>为什么今年的流感季节如此糟糕？ - Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/flu/why-is-flu-season-so-bad-this-year</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;

&lt;p id="0960ebee-87f3-457d-b3b1-610c775ca499"&gt;If it feels like everyone around you has come down with the flu, you're not imagining it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of Jan. 9, the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) estimates that at least &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;15 million people have gotten sick with the flu&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; this season. Of those, 180,000 have been hospitalized, and 7,400 people have died from flu so far, including 17 children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="0960ebee-87f3-457d-b3b1-610c775ca499-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;These numbers make the current flu season one of the worst the U.S. has seen in decades. According to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.syramadad.com/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.syramadad.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Syra Madad&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, an epidemiologist at the Harvard Belfer Center and chief biopreparedness officer at NYC Health + Hospitals, who publishes a weekly analysis of respiratory virus trends in her newsletter &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://criticalhealthvoices.substack.com/" target="_blank" data-url="https://criticalhealthvoices.substack.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Critical Health Voices&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the country is experiencing the highest number of flu cases in nearly 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="5ef416f7-2021-4dd3-8046-b833385fa92d"&gt;At Phoenix Children's Hospital, flu cases have been high since mid-December 2025, said pediatric infectious disease specialist &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://phoenixchildrens.org/find-a-doctor/monica-abd-el-nour-md" target="_blank" data-url="https://phoenixchildrens.org/find-a-doctor/monica-abd-el-nour-md" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Monica Abdelnour&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although the CDC [currently] estimates this flu season to be of moderate severity, the rates we are seeing are similar to, and in some cases slightly higher than, those observed in the 2024-2025 season, which was deemed high-severity," she told Live Science in an email. "It remains possible this flu season may ultimately be categorized as high severity as well."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the CDC reported a slight dip in the number of lab-confirmed flu cases in the first week of 2026, compared to the last week of 2025, Madad told Live Science that it's "too early to declare we are past the peak." Flu activity in the U.S. &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/season.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/season.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;usually peaks sometime between December and February&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The CDC also noted that the small drop in confirmed cases could be linked to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;&lt;u&gt;expected decreases in doctor visits and testing during the holidays&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, not an actual drop in flu spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;section class="article__schema-question" id="0b8fe7a5-084e-48bb-ab1f-5e956fdb47fe"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What is subclade K?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;article class="article__schema-answer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of the talk about this year's flu season has centered on something called "subclade K."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand what this is, it's important to know that flu viruses are constantly evolving, gaining small genetic mutations as they spread. Scientists keep track of how flu viruses change using a system similar to a family tree, Madad said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big branches of this tree are called "types." This includes influenza A and B, which are broad groups of flu viruses. These big branches sprout off into smaller branches called subtypes, such as A(H3N2) or B/Victoria lineage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The letters H and N, which are used to differentiate influenza A subtypes, stand for two proteins on the virus's surface: hemagglutinin (H) and neuraminidase (N). There are many possible versions of each protein — &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/viruses-types.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/about/viruses-types.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;18 and 11 versions, respectively&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; — which consequently gives rise to a large variety of flu viruses, of which only a few routinely infect humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going even further down a branch, scientists identify "clades," which are groups of viruses that came from a common ancestor and share similar genetic traits. A subclade is an even smaller group within a clade — a newer "twig" on the tree — that shares recent mutations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This flu season, the CDC reported that &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;most flu cases are being caused by the influenza subtype A(H3N2)&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Of the more than 430 samples of influenza A(H3N2) virus collected since late September 2025, over &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;91% were identified as part of a closely related group called subclade K&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="article__schema-question" id="94b8df27-c4ef-4fc9-a6f4-8e30e853e6b4"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Is subclade K a "super flu"?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;article class="article__schema-answer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer is no. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subclade K carries distinct mutations in parts of the virus that our immune systems usually recognize, Madad said. Because of this, our immunity from past flu infections or vaccinations is lower than it might be if the subclade looked more "familiar." This enables the virus to spread more easily, resulting in more cases and, as a result, more hospitalizations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, that does not automatically mean subclade K is more deadly or causes more severe illness than other circulating flu viruses, Madad said. Current epidemiologic data show that subclade K does not lead to more severe disease than other seasonal flu strains than are spreading now, she noted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Flu symptoms this year are similar to those seen in previous seasons," Abdelnour added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with the flu commonly experience fever or chills, cough, nasal congestion, muscle and/or body aches, headaches and fatigue. In severe cases, flu infections can lead to complications such as sepsis and pneumonia. Adults 65 and up; young children, especially those under 2; pregnant people; and people with chronic conditions like asthma, diabetes or heart disease are at highest risk for severe flu complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="article__schema-question" id="15787d1f-02c3-4f0b-85af-902cef030c3f"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Is this year's flu vaccine working, and is it too late to get it?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;article class="article__schema-answer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flu vaccine "may be a less perfect match for subclade K" than it could be, Madad said, but she stressed that vaccination still plays a critical role in preventing serious illness. Abdelnour said that the annual flu vaccine reduces the risk of serious complications, such as sepsis, pneumonia and significant neurologic symptoms, such as seizures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data from the Southern Hemisphere, which experiences flu season before the Northern Hemisphere, suggests that this year's flu vaccine works just as well as past vaccines at lowering the risk of being hospitalized with the flu, Abdelnour said. This past flu season, the flu vaccine reduced flu-related doctor visits and hospitalizations by 50% in the Southern Hemisphere, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7436a3.htm" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7436a3.htm" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;CDC report published in September 2025&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is within the typical range, and it's anticipated we should experience similar levels of protection in the United States," Abdelnour said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, fewer people are getting vaccinated against the flu this year, and that's especially true of children, Madad said. "Only about 42% of U.S. children have received the flu vaccine so far this season, down from roughly 53% at the same point in 2019–2020." As of Jan. 3, about &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/index.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/fluvaxview/dashboard/index.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;44.1% of adults reported having received a flu vaccination&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Poor vaccination rates can have real consequences, Madad said. During the 2024-2025 flu season, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7436a2.htm" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7436a2.htm" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;280 children in the U.S. died of flu-related illness&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and of those, about 9 in 10 had not been vaccinated against the virus. Madad, who is also a mother of four, noted that all of her children receive the flu shot every year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though flu season started in the fall, "it is not too late to get the flu shot," Abdelnour emphasized. "Given the current surge in cases, getting vaccinated now is strongly recommended to protect yourself and those around you."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Madad echoed that advice, urging anyone who hasn't yet received a flu shot this season to do so, especially adults ages 65 and older, pregnant people, those with weakened immune systems, and people living with chronic health conditions, who are at higher risk of severe cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="article__schema-question" id="041d126b-e6c4-440b-9f19-4d4a3ba460bb"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;How else can you protect yourself from flu?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;article class="article__schema-answer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccination is just one layer of protection. Madad emphasized wearing a well-fitting mask in crowded indoor spaces and improving ventilation for indoor gatherings. Additionally, people should stay home when sick to avoid the risk of spreading flu to others. These steps help limit the spread not only of flu, but of other respiratory viruses like COVID-19 and &lt;a href="https://www.livescience.com/rsv" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/rsv"&gt;&lt;u&gt;RSV&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (respiratory syncytial virus), as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abdelnour also noted the importance of practicing proper hand hygiene. "Special attention should be given to childcare environments such as schools and daycare centers," she said. "This includes recommending children get their flu shot, encouraging handwashing with soap and water for at least 20 seconds and keeping children home when they are ill to prevent the spread of infection to others."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;section class="article__schema-question" id="9e2684ae-1104-4d1a-b4a3-dd99db9c9a82"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Are there treatments for flu?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;article class="article__schema-answer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For people who do get sick, antiviral medications such as Tamiflu can help. These prescription drugs can &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/treatment/antiviral-drugs.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/treatment/antiviral-drugs.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;reduce the severity of symptoms and shorten the time you are sick&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, especially when taken within the first day or two after symptoms begin. Evidence suggests they can be &lt;a href="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/hospitalized-patients-with-flu-need-tamiflu-the-day-theyre-admitted-cdc-says" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/hospitalized-patients-with-flu-need-tamiflu-the-day-theyre-admitted-cdc-says"&gt;&lt;u&gt;especially helpful to people hospitalized for flu&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p id="d29dfe78-f795-4148-8368-1730a38a4e44"&gt;The CDC recommends prompt treatment for people with suspected flu symptoms who are at increased risk of serious flu complications, including pregnant women and people with chronic health conditions, such as asthma, lung disease, diabetes, or heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-gMcYSfmZ9B8NxP8DC42BKU" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-gMcYSfmZ9B8NxP8DC42BKU slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Madad said that flu antivirals are "underused" and reminds people at high risk of severe flu or who are caring for someone who is high risk to ask their doctors about antivirals shortly after they suspect an infection. The good news is that current data show subclade K is still responsive to the standard antiviral medications doctors use for influenza, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mb-6" id="a4d1e963-6ac7-4fe1-a3d4-810e8e7197e0"&gt;
&lt;div class="[&amp;amp;_a]:text-[#2f6e91] [&amp;amp;_a]:visited:text-[#09c] p-5 bg-[#F5F5F5] text-sm text-[#333]"&gt;

&lt;p class="infoDisclaimer tracking-[.02em] pt-2 font-normal"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and is not meant to offer medical advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTFA1eE9xSkcxbV9ZeDlwVGJCSkVjdjRuaThWNnBfSEM0V0llcVdRMmJKNnNrTWJNLUVHd3V1RjBRNHhveE96SkVQNFNsVzgxWlg4ZWZwOVVnUVN5VG5CZ0FUZUJWcjNSSmhfSHcxcmxEVzJSaHpQZ08zb0huQU1QZw</guid></item><item><title>男孩， 2岁，在生日前几周突然死于流感样症状的罕见疾病：他“拥有最大的个性” -雅虎加拿大新闻</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/boy-2-dies-suddenly-rare-155421238.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A 2-year-old boy died from a rare disease with flu-like symptoms, just weeks before his third birthday&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Hudson Hughie Martin died after collapsing on the stairs in his family home on Jan. 8&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The child was diagnosed with the rare Kawasaki disease when he was just 7 months old&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A 2-year-old boy died from a rare disease with flu-like symptoms, just weeks before his third birthday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;On Jan. 8, Hudson Hughie Martin collapsed on the stairs in his family home. He was pronounced dead at the scene, despite paramedics spending over an hour trying to restart his heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“They did absolutely everything they could,” the boy's father, Damien Martin, told &lt;a href="https://www.bristolpost.co.uk/news/bristol-news/bristol-toddler-dies-suddenly-home-10751867" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Bristol Live;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Bristol Live&lt;/a&gt;. “His heart just wouldn’t come back.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Hudson was diagnosed with Kawasaki disease when he was just 7 months old, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/hudson-martin" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:GoFundMe;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/a&gt; created by his aunt, Danielle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Kawasaki disease causes inflammation in the walls of medium-sized blood vessels that carry blood throughout the body, and most often affects children, per the &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/kawasaki-disease/symptoms-causes/syc-20354598" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mayo Clinic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. It also causes swelling in lymph nodes and mucous membranes inside the mouth, nose, eyes and throat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;gofundme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Hudson Hughie Martin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"He was deteriorating day by day, and pretty much ended up laying in bed, not moving,” dad Damien recalled to Bristol Live of the weeks before Hudson received his diagnosis. “All they were doing was taking blood, doing tests, that’s all they could do.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Hudson’s mom, Natalie, added, “It took someone coming in and saying, ‘He’s got all the symptoms, why hasn’t he been treated for Kawasaki disease?’ ”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;After his diagnosis, Hudson went through two rounds of treatment. And though he began to show improvement in his behavior and symptoms, test results remained a cause for concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"His numbers weren’t coming back down to where they should be, and even though he was up showing signs that he was well — he was waking up, he was moving around and he started eating — the doctors every day kept coming in with bad news and saying there was nothing they could do, his numbers aren’t moving,” Damien explained. “They were basically preparing us and saying he was not going to make it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When he was finally discharged from the hospital, Danielle said that Hudson was left with a “giant aneurysm” by his heart, and the child spent the next few months taking various medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Despite the hardships faced, Hudson's loved ones said he never let it show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You would have never known he was poorly," his aunt Danielle said. “He was your typical boy. He loved to dance and loved a beat. His three brothers, Kieran, Preston and Ashton, absolutely adore him.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;gofundme&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Hudson Hughie Martin&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“You’d never know anything was wrong from pictures or videos,” dad Damien added. “He bounced off everything. He loved climbing, dancing, music, he was a proper daredevil.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Mom Natalie also said, “He wanted to do everything himself — he climbed the highest slides, bounced constantly, and had the biggest personality. He was just full of life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;After their son's death, Damien and Natalie are now determined to warn other parents about the symptoms of Kawasaki disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Explaining that the only way to diagnose the illness is by ruling out other conditions, as there is no test for Kawasaki disease, they told Bristol Live, "People should push for it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"If parents can see the symptoms and be more aware of what to look for, they can question professionals a little bit more,” the parents added. “It’s rare, and sometimes professionals just don’t know enough about it.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/boy-2-dies-from-rare-disease-with-flu-like-symptoms-weeks-before-his-birthday-11887897" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:54:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE1qRkRNdXhEZ1o2M21Ed2hXU1pkSlE4bGQyZkFuUTNKdTF4alpmcFFGSHNNUUoxWGtmYlROam85ZXl3d0FDM25Qd2pHby1OaXF3YUJrUV9uamxJSk14Um9JemZOVmJ6a2F0OHcydUgxY0lhSFk</guid></item><item><title>接受实验性猪肾移植的男性现在有了人体器官- KSL新闻</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51434690/man-who-received-experimental-pig-kidney-transplant-now-has-a-human-organ</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;ATLANTA — Tim Andrews was among the world's first recipients of a genetically modified pig kidney on year ago. Now, he is the first in that small group of pioneers to receive a human kidney.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm the first one that went across the bridge. … I'm the only person in the world that's ever had a pig kidney and then had a human kidney after it," he told CNN from the hospital on Thursday. "Nobody's ever been across that bridge. That is cool!"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrews, who has diabetes and was living with end-stage kidney disease, received a pig kidney on Jan. 25, 2025, and lived with it for a record 271 days. After his body rejected the organ, it was removed in October, and Andrews returned to dialysis — a grueling process that kept him alive but made him so miserable it had driven him to the experimental xenotransplant in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I cried," said Andrews, 67. He told his family he didn't expect to make it through the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But at nearly midnight on Jan. 12, Mass General Brigham called to tell him that a human kidney — a near-perfect match — had been identified. He was scheduled for transplant surgery at 8 a.m. the following day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrews now expects to be discharged to his home in New Hampshire on Friday, just days after the milestone organ transplant that made him a living example of the promise of xenotransplantation: Organs from animals may help keep humans alive and healthy enough for a longer-term solution and a new shot at life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;An answer to organ shortages&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xenotransplantation – the transplant of different species' organs – has been touted as a possible solution to the current shortage of organ donors. The transplanted pig organs are genetically modified to control for rejection and size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At any given time in the U.S., there are more than 100,000 people waiting for an organ, about 80% of them in need of kidneys. But only the sickest of the sick are listed; just &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2831874#" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;1 in 8&lt;/a&gt; patients with end-stage renal disease are on the waitlist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/health-statistics/kidney-disease" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;more than 800,000 people with kidney failure&lt;/a&gt;, nearly 70% are on dialysis. But dialysis is trying to compress into just a few hours every week the work that the body typically does 24/7. The five-year survival rate for patients on dialysis hovers around &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2824363" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;40%.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Dialysis is not able to reproduce what the body needs in terms of clearing the waste," said Dr. Leonardo Riella, medical director of kidney transplantation at Mass General Brigham Hospital and Andrews' doctor. "It has a huge burden on the patient, both in their quality of life, but most importantly on their health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrews was hooked up to a dialysis machine three days a week for up to six hours at a time. Six months after starting dialysis for the first time, he had a heart attack. "It takes a toll on you emotionally and physically; you just get exhausted and I got sick. I was throwing up all the time," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While organs remain in short supply, Riella sees xenotransplantation as a solution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Even if it is a bridge," Riella said, "it would be better than (Tim) just staying on dialysis."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To prepare Andrews for the human transplant, the team at Mass General tested Andrews for new antibodies that could potentially react with the new human kidney and found none. His most recent transplant took just about three hours, and he said his new immunosuppressant regimen is about a third of what he took when he had a pig kidney.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;'This will do something for humanity'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Andrews, getting the xenotransplant wasn't just a matter of hope away from dialysis but hope for patients with end-stage renal disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This will do something for humanity," he told CNN Chief Medical Correspondent Dr. Sanjay Gupta in the documentary "Dr. Sanjay Gupta Reports: Animal Pharm."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Immediately following his xenotransplant last year, Andrews felt different. "I was clear. I was not what I call dialysis foggy. I wasn't tired or anything. All of a sudden, I had energy," he remembered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the path forward had ups and downs. Andrews took 52 pills a day to help keep his pig kidney, which he named Wilma, and his immune system in agreement. Ultimately, over the course of nine months, the kidney began showing signs of rejection. He had two infections. Riella said they adjusted Andrews' immunosuppressant protocol, but the kidneys had become damaged in the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There was some damage to the filters of the kidney that, unfortunately, were not reversible," Riella said. Ultimately, they removed Wilma, and Andrews had to return to dialysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mike Curtis, president and CEO of eGenesis, the company that provided the donor pig for Andrews' kidney, said it was a slow rejection that scientists could see coming for months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We just could not figure out how to how to push it back," Curtis said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But biopsies and research into Andrews and the pig kidney may have helped them pinpoint what led to the rejection, which may help future kidney recipients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have a much better idea of what was causing that low-level rejection, so we can then tune the suppression," Curtis said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andrews' experience has helped refine treatment for the next xenotransplant patients. Since his surgery in January 2025, Mass General and eGenesis have teamed up to perform two more xenotransplants before starting a clinical trial in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;An alternative to dialysis&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Riella also sees the xenotransplant as a success for Andrews. Wilma was able to keep him off dialysis for nine months. After Andrews returned to dialysis, his overall function dropped again, and he was losing muscle mass and energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point, Riella said, the comparison of xenotransplant may not be to a human kidney but to dialysis. "It's a much better treatment to maintain the kidney function compared to what dialysis is able to offer," he said. "Our goal is to basically ban dialysis as a long-term treatment."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But an alternative to dialysis isn't the end goal, said Dr. Robert Montgomery, director of the NYU Langone Transplant Institute. Montgomery wasn't involved in Andrews' care, but has also been at the forefront of the field of xenotransplantation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"As this gets better and xenografts last longer, it will be a destination," said Montgomery, who was the first doctor to transplant pig organs into brain- dead patients and is leading the &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/news/first-gene-edited-pig-kidney-transplant-clinical-trial-begins-nyu-langone-health" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;first FDA-cleared clinical trial into xenotransplant at NYU.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Montgomery believes that xenotransplantation will be a viable solution for patients within the next five years. "In the future, I think a single patient with renal failure will cycle through both xenografts and allografts throughout their lifetime."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Riella says it's impossible to know what would have happened to Andrews if he had not tried an experimental xenotransplant. But Andrews said he has no doubt that Wilma was key to getting him to this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If I didn't take Wilma, I'd have been dead by now. I wasn't gonna make it another year," Andrews said. "I'm looking at years now. I can think ahead."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What he's thinking of now is sharing his own story and urging others to become organ donors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People need to step up and help," Andrews said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/reel/1409657407616008" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;message&lt;/a&gt; Andrews posted to social media on Friday, he thanked the family of his donor, who has not been identified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I grieve with you. It's got to tear you apart, but I'm here to tell you, the donation of a kidney has saved my life, and you have given hope to millions. Your family member is a hero. He's a hero, not just to me, but to the entire world," Andrews said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'll never be able to repay you, but I promise you it'll be in my heart. And it will be cared and loved for as long as I live, and I will spend my life basically preaching, and I'm not a preacher, about what this love did."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL News</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:49:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxOczBNNFloZjVhdjNQalFqLXdqSlhMbjlldTBxWUcyRklMN0ZaM0lkbGRoT1lRTWhKMEVfc1M3bkFjY1dab05QT1d1ZFhpYzlRd2hPcTNGaFdIOW9GOWhSYVNQTGpEVHhoVk04dHVqdWlxc05uQ3FXRDBpN3JHb3NRcjlmQzdRZ3ZqNXAzMUpjNVVsUmhveXlHMDJVU0tXQkJXemZzYmJORFg3Qm0wajRB</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，简单的血液检测可以预测哪种乳腺癌治疗效果最好-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2026/jan/18/simple-blood-test-can-predict-which-breast-cancer-treatment-will-work-best-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Scientists have developed a simple DNA blood test that can predict how well patients with breast cancer will respond to treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;More than 2 million people globally each year are diagnosed with the disease, which is the world’s most prevalent cancer. Although treatments have improved in recent decades, it is not easy to know which ones will work best for which patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Now researchers have designed a liquid biopsy that tells doctors how likely a patient is to respond to a specific treatment, even before it begins. The test has the potential to be gamechanging because it means patients could be offered alternative options, and avoid treatments that won’t help them, boosting their chances of beating the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The test, developed by a team at the Institute of &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/cancer" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Cancer&lt;/a&gt; Research, London (ICR), analyses circulating tumour DNA (ctDNA), which is released into the blood of patients by cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Researchers measured these microscopic levels of cancer DNA in blood samples from 167 patients. The test was trialled before treatment began and again four weeks later, after a single treatment cycle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There was a strong association between low levels of ctDNA at the start of treatment, and treatment response, according to the team. A similar association was seen with the results taken at four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Iseult Browne, a clinical research fellow at the ICR and first author of a study detailing the test, said: “Our study shows that a simple blood test measuring circulating tumour DNA can provide an early prediction of whether a patients’ breast cancer will respond to treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Knowing this at the earliest stage – in this case, at the start of treatment, or after just four weeks – means that we can avoid giving patients drugs that won’t work and provide them with alternatives before their cancer has a chance to grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“For example, they could be given an alternative targeted therapy, a combination of drugs, or even enrolled into a clinical trial to test a novel drug. Trials are now under way to see if adapting a patient’s treatment based on these early blood tests does indeed improve their outcome – giving them more time of living well with their cancer kept at bay.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the study, funded by Breast Cancer Now, Cancer Research UK, the NIHR Biomedical Research Centre at the Royal Marsden NHS foundation trust and the ICR, the team analysed blood samples from 167 people with advanced breast cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The patients were split into two groups based on the type of breast cancer and mutations they had. The first group included patients whose cancers had an ESR1, HER2, AKT1, AKT or PTEN mutation, and who received targeted treatments matched to those mutations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The second group consisted of people with triple negative breast cancer, an aggressive form of the disease that constitutes 10-15% of cases globally and has no targetable mutation. They received a combination of the PARP inhibitor olarparib, and the ATR inhibitor ceralasertib.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;For patients in the second group, low ctDNA levels before treatment began were associated with longer progression-free survival – 10.2 months, compared with 4.4 months. The percentage of patients who responded to treatment – seeing their tumours shrink or disappear – was 40% for those with low ctDNA levels, compared with 9.7% for those with higher levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A similar, although weaker, association was observed between pre-treatment ctDNA levels and clinical outcomes in the first group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After just four weeks of treatment, patients in the first group with undetectable ctDNA went on to have particularly good outcomes. Their cancer was kept at bay for 10.6 months, compared with 3.5 months for those whose ctDNA was still detectable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the second group, the blood test after four weeks of treatment also showed a strong link between ctDNA levels and patient outcomes. Patients whose ctDNA was no longer detectable had their cancer kept at bay for 12 months, compared with 4.3 months in patients who still had detectable ctDNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“By analysing circulating tumour DNA in blood samples from patients with advanced breast cancer, we identified a clear link between these levels, both at the start and after one cycle of treatment, and how well patients responded to therapy,” Browne said. “These findings support the use of ctDNA as a non-invasive biomarker for predicting outcomes and monitoring treatment response.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Nicholas Turner, a professor of molecular oncology at the ICR and a consultant medical oncologist at the Royal Marsden, said: “This research looked at advanced breast cancer, but these tests could also work for early-stage breast cancers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The liquid biopsy “has the potential to make treatment decisions faster, more personalised and ultimately more effective,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 15:27:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizwFBVV95cUxPdzVXNmN3dzdIdExnV3QyZ0xVeElJVjR0N0hDSDNXSFFmY082NURKaDFIcTJnSUlHTklBcG81V1gzSzg2Zl9laDdRRXpMQm5FRVh5OEV5d1JXaGdKclhpaTlqbWxRTEFKZWRacGg2OE1wd0R4QkhaQUdEQTBmcE01RmkzVE9CX2s3TVIwcThPQjk0SXRheVV2d1RRNS1ObmJKNU1nenZxVEs4ZVdkMXkwOFdmc3lBM0VRRlFJLUZWMzhwU2ItNHVCNHFSbmFuODA</guid></item><item><title>你不仅有五种感官–新的研究表明，人类可能有多达33种感官- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/you-dont-have-just-five-senses-new-research-suggests-humans-may-have-up-to-33/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 14:31:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPeVZpSjRobDQ1eGJwWFlqWmFVeHlvZEcySjNQWElFbi1Hc1dzc0tUV18teXR2a0h2aEtNVmRYSUNaSE9JYXhwRmlRa3JJRm4zcHFTRmw4X2dHZUlEaXUtVDBuSGg3Y1BXYUhYcnhHblBsQk4xS0ZFSlpiX0hzX3A3WTN1R29OX3NTcS15NzRESjRuUE9TMjlQeG55bVVQNlcxbWd6SDZR</guid></item><item><title>我研究了200多名儿童-这是真正教导儿童情商的头号“神奇短语” - CNBC</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2026/01/18/child-psychologist-the-no-1-magic-phrase-that-truly-teaches-kids-emotional-intelligence.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-articleBody--AEqcE" id="MakeItRegularArticle-ArticleBody-5" data-module="ArticleBody" data-test="articleBody-1" data-analytics="MakeItRegularArticle-articleBody-5-1"&gt;&lt;span class="HighlightShare-styles-makeit-hidden--MFwCR"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a child is upset, most parents reach for the same question instinctively: "What's wrong?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's well-intentioned and it comes from care. But after years of teaching conscious parenting and &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/12/21/ive-studied-over-200-kids-if-you-want-your-kids-to-always-be-close-with-you-do-7-things.html"&gt;studying over 200 kids&lt;/a&gt;, I've seen how often that question does the opposite of what parents hope. Instead of opening children up, it can shut them down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/01/if-you-use-these-phrases-every-day-you-have-high-emotional-intelligence-say-psychology-experts.html"&gt;Emotional intelligence&lt;/a&gt; develops when children feel safe enough to reflect. Without that foundation, even the most caring questions can feel overwhelming in the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across my research, one sentence reliably helped children pause, reflect, and communicate more openly: "Tell me what feels hard right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This magic phrase works because it matches how children actually experience emotions in real life. Rather than pushing for clarity or explanations, it creates the conditions where insight can emerge naturally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;1. It reduces defensiveness before the conversation even begins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;During meltdowns, after-school emotional releases, or moments of sudden irritability, children are already on edge. The word "hard" feels human and non-threatening. It signals to your child that they aren't in trouble and don't need to justify their feelings, making it easier to stay engaged instead of shutting down or pushing back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;2. It allows emotional language to develop organically&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children don't need to label emotions precisely. They can describe a situation, a sensation, or a moment that felt overwhelming. Over time, this gently expands emotional language, allowing insight to develop naturally rather than being forced before a child has the words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline2"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;3. It establishes emotional safety before problem-solving&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before problem-solving, before advice, before correction, this phrase tells a child: "I can handle what you're feeling." Emotional intelligence grows in welcoming environments where emotions are met with steadiness instead of urgency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline3"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;4. It gives children agency over what they share&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than demanding an explanation, this question invites reflection. The child decides how much to share and when, reinforcing a sense of agency over their emotional experience, which is an essential foundation for self-regulation and confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline4"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;5. It helps calm the nervous system first&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When children feel emotionally safe, their stress response begins to settle. This phrase is especially effective when behavior feels disproportionate or confusing because it prioritizes regulation before reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline5"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;6. It normalizes emotions as part of everyday life&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;By focusing on what feels hard, parents communicate that emotions can be noticed without being rushed or fixed. It teaches kids that feelings can be experienced and moved through rather than avoided or suppressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline6"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;7. It demonstrates emotional intelligence in real time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children learn emotional intelligence through experience, not instruction. When parents respond with calm curiosity instead of control or urgency, they model how to approach emotions with steadiness and reflection. These are skills children eventually apply to themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our job as parents is to create an environment where our children feel safe sharing their inner worlds. When you adjust your language, you shape the emotional tone of your relationship. Over time, children learn that their feelings are important signals that deserve attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.highloveparenting.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reem Raouda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is a leading voice in conscious parenting and the creator of the BOUND and FOUNDATIONS journals, now offered together as her &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.etsy.com/listing/4299019663/the-1-parenting-bundle-emotional-safety?etsrc=sdt" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Emotional Safety Bundle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. She is widely recognized for her expertise in children's emotional well-being and for redefining what it means to raise emotionally healthy kids. Connect with her on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/highloveparenting" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Instagram&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to give your kids the ultimate advantage?&lt;/strong&gt; Sign up for CNBC's new online course, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://smarter.cnbcmakeit.com/p/how-to-raise-financially-smart-kids?utm_source=cnbc&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=makeitarticle&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=bottom" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Raise Financially Smart Kids&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Learn how to build healthy financial habits today to set your children up for greater success in the future. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-relatedContent--nvEkA" id="MakeItRegularArticle-RelatedContent-1"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-container--UeiCK"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-nonCollapsibleContent--jmjdo"&gt;&lt;h2 class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-header--DqhoP"&gt;Take control of your money with CNBC Select &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CNBC Select is editorially independent and may earn a commission from affiliate partners on links.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="ArticleBody-MobileAdhesion" class="MobileAdhesion-container" data-module="mps-slot"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:39:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPMDVkc084TWFvTkFTUnM4c1BLR0taVmhoVk5oaUtva3ZOc3IxcFZaTnhBWk9hLW5QdkNpdGt4WllHd1FFZXVRckMxYm1fdTZmY1BzajZycm03LXJuN1NEeXBoOUJRYllPaGg4R2RPdWlzZUhFLUE0Z3c5QUw4OWd1dVNPNG0yaFhuQ2xoSlJrZ0ZVd0hFNF82bVZEZFBPUTBENVBRM196SVZDdm1lS0ZZT2JvM3VvR2x5a2M5VUFpYnlhUQ</guid></item><item><title>我研究了200多名儿童-这是真正教导儿童情商的头号“神奇短语” - CNBC</title><link>https://www.cnbc.com/2026/01/18/child-psychologist-the-no-1-magic-phrase-that-truly-teaches-kids-emotional-intelligence.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-articleBody--AEqcE" id="MakeItRegularArticle-ArticleBody-5" data-module="ArticleBody" data-test="articleBody-1" data-analytics="MakeItRegularArticle-articleBody-5-1"&gt;&lt;span class="HighlightShare-styles-makeit-hidden--MFwCR"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a child is upset, most parents reach for the same question instinctively: "What's wrong?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's well-intentioned and it comes from care. But after years of teaching conscious parenting and &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/12/21/ive-studied-over-200-kids-if-you-want-your-kids-to-always-be-close-with-you-do-7-things.html"&gt;studying over 200 kids&lt;/a&gt;, I've seen how often that question does the opposite of what parents hope. Instead of opening children up, it can shut them down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="lazyload-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2023/04/01/if-you-use-these-phrases-every-day-you-have-high-emotional-intelligence-say-psychology-experts.html"&gt;Emotional intelligence&lt;/a&gt; develops when children feel safe enough to reflect. Without that foundation, even the most caring questions can feel overwhelming in the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across my research, one sentence reliably helped children pause, reflect, and communicate more openly: "Tell me what feels hard right now."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This magic phrase works because it matches how children actually experience emotions in real life. Rather than pushing for clarity or explanations, it creates the conditions where insight can emerge naturally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline0"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;1. It reduces defensiveness before the conversation even begins&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;During meltdowns, after-school emotional releases, or moments of sudden irritability, children are already on edge. The word "hard" feels human and non-threatening. It signals to your child that they aren't in trouble and don't need to justify their feelings, making it easier to stay engaged instead of shutting down or pushing back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline1"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;2. It allows emotional language to develop organically&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children don't need to label emotions precisely. They can describe a situation, a sensation, or a moment that felt overwhelming. Over time, this gently expands emotional language, allowing insight to develop naturally rather than being forced before a child has the words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline2"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;3. It establishes emotional safety before problem-solving&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before problem-solving, before advice, before correction, this phrase tells a child: "I can handle what you're feeling." Emotional intelligence grows in welcoming environments where emotions are met with steadiness instead of urgency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline3"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;4. It gives children agency over what they share&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than demanding an explanation, this question invites reflection. The child decides how much to share and when, reinforcing a sense of agency over their emotional experience, which is an essential foundation for self-regulation and confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline4"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;5. It helps calm the nervous system first&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When children feel emotionally safe, their stress response begins to settle. This phrase is especially effective when behavior feels disproportionate or confusing because it prioritizes regulation before reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline5"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;6. It normalizes emotions as part of everyday life&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;By focusing on what feels hard, parents communicate that emotions can be noticed without being rushed or fixed. It teaches kids that feelings can be experienced and moved through rather than avoided or suppressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="ArticleBody-styles-makeit-subtitle--JP3GH"&gt;&lt;a id="headline6"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;7. It demonstrates emotional intelligence in real time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children learn emotional intelligence through experience, not instruction. When parents respond with calm curiosity instead of control or urgency, they model how to approach emotions with steadiness and reflection. These are skills children eventually apply to themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our job as parents is to create an environment where our children feel safe sharing their inner worlds. When you adjust your language, you shape the emotional tone of your relationship. Over time, children learn that their feelings are important signals that deserve attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.highloveparenting.com/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reem Raouda&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; is a leading voice in conscious parenting and the creator of the BOUND and FOUNDATIONS journals, now offered together as her &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.etsy.com/listing/4299019663/the-1-parenting-bundle-emotional-safety?etsrc=sdt" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Emotional Safety Bundle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. She is widely recognized for her expertise in children's emotional well-being and for redefining what it means to raise emotionally healthy kids. Connect with her on &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/highloveparenting" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Instagram&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to give your kids the ultimate advantage?&lt;/strong&gt; Sign up for CNBC's new online course, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://smarter.cnbcmakeit.com/p/how-to-raise-financially-smart-kids?utm_source=cnbc&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=makeitarticle&amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=bottom" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Raise Financially Smart Kids&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Learn how to build healthy financial habits today to set your children up for greater success in the future. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-relatedContent--nvEkA" id="MakeItRegularArticle-RelatedContent-1"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-container--UeiCK"&gt;&lt;div class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-nonCollapsibleContent--jmjdo"&gt;&lt;h2 class="RelatedContent-styles-makeit-header--DqhoP"&gt;Take control of your money with CNBC Select &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="group"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;CNBC Select is editorially independent and may earn a commission from affiliate partners on links.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="ArticleBody-MobileAdhesion" class="MobileAdhesion-container" data-module="mps-slot"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:39:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxPMDVkc084TWFvTkFTUnM4c1BLR0taVmhoVk5oaUtva3ZOc3IxcFZaTnhBWk9hLW5QdkNpdGt4WllHd1FFZXVRckMxYm1fdTZmY1BzajZycm03LXJuN1NEeXBoOUJRYllPaGg4R2RPdWlzZUhFLUE0Z3c5QUw4OWd1dVNPNG0yaFhuQ2xoSlJrZ0ZVd0hFNF82bVZEZFBPUTBENVBRM196SVZDdm1lS0ZZT2JvM3VvR2x5a2M5VUFpYnlhUdIBxwFBVV95cUxPd3VyRnl4b3FVOFVBTzdmV1ZJWFdFRDNiWk93a1V1VVhMTHB1YmRCSHl1OGNnUnF3R3M5RllsQlg1Ukt3ZEt3SWFHel8td1E3S1oyZkdaVFdZYlJpUmp3N0hxc1V6OU1aVkc4bFo2d1dicmFsSlVjYk56UHVPaHVGTHMwVjZxcGxGMWhpdGdIUlVBT3V3dXRZbzNRU29qSElnejJ6bEVaZkRWQVk2dlJPalNvYmdYaml2NlFIMU5BZWpIMWpYUS13</guid></item><item><title>男性从超级昂贵的MRI扫描中获得干净的健康状况，然后得到可怕的消息-未来主义</title><link>https://futurism.com/future-society/mri-body-scan-stroke-lawsuit</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-wrapper"&gt;
		
&lt;p class="pw-incontent-excluded article-paragraph skip"&gt;A 35-year-old New York City man paid about $2,500 for a whole body magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) scan that came up healthy — but then suffered a massive stroke less than a year later that the expensive procedure flagged no sign of, &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2026/01/13/prenuvo-lawsuit-full-body-scan/" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; reports&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Now the stroke victim, Sean Clifford, is &lt;a href="https://iapps.courts.state.ny.us/fbem/DocumentDisplayServlet?documentId=JejAC0DPndWW/Bequek7Xw==&amp;amp;system=prod" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;suing&lt;/a&gt; the MRI company behind the scan, Prenuvo — which has &lt;a href="https://people.com/we-tried-it-the-full-body-scan-celebrities-love-7509820" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;been endorsed by celebrities&lt;/a&gt; ranging from Paris Hilton to Cindy Crawford — for missing in the scans that 6o percent of his &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/mca-stroke" rel="nofollow noreferrer" target="_blank"&gt;proximal right middle cerebral artery&lt;/a&gt;, a common site for strokes, had narrowed and showed “irregularity.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Clifford, who suffered a stroke in the same area where the blockage was missed by Prenuvo, is now paralyzed on his left side and permanently disabled — throwing into high relief that these scans, which prey on people’s fears, aren’t exactly fool proof-despite extravagant claims that they can pick up anything from tumors to brain aneurysms.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;A judge approved for the lawsuit, which was filed in September 2024, to proceed last month, according to &lt;em&gt;WaPo&lt;/em&gt;. A statement from Prenuvo to the newspaper stated that “we take any allegation seriously and are committed to addressing it through the appropriate legal process. Our focus remains on delivering safe, high quality, proactive care to the patients who place their trust in us every day.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Full body scans are controversial in the medical field because some doctors think they pick up details that could be false alarms that send patients down a rabbithole of expensive and unnecessary testing, according to &lt;em&gt;WaPo&lt;/em&gt; — or, as in Clifford’s case, the scans can miss glaring signs of danger. Most conventional doctors instead use MRIs to focus on one area of the body that’s giving patients trouble.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;Mirza Rahman, a physician and ex-president of the American College of Preventive Medicine, told &lt;em&gt;WaPo&lt;/em&gt; that the problem with these scans is that they give people a “false sense of reassurance.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;“Do the radiologists have sufficient time to carefully look at the bones, the vessels, the organs, and all the other information that is generated by such scans?” Rahman said. “That is a question that needs to be answered.”&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More on MRI scans:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://futurism.com/neoscope/mri-scan-contrast-dye-toxic"&gt;MRI Scans Causing Nasty Material to Form Inside Body, Scientists Find&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="article-paragraph skip"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Futurism</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 13:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE04aXpxczRLZDhZbFdNWTdRZ044cldlc21nMHNBb1ZRNXRFRVBRWUhrUUQ1VjRSQW1SMkxwZElwd3EzLVo5MzZQSXhSa2Vya3ExU1ktZFcwSzdXQkNXb0NvbGZBbURfVzJYdXpla0VtRTQ5Zw</guid></item><item><title>医生确认：每天吃这种流行的韩国配菜可以增强您的免疫系统-印度国防评论</title><link>https://indiandefencereview.com/eating-popular-korean-side-dish-daily-boost-immune-system/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dynamic-entry-content"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new South Korean study shows that kimchi, when consumed daily in powdered form, increases the immune system’s ability to identify and respond to threats, while avoiding the risk of overstimulation.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Led by Dr. Wooje Lee at the &lt;em&gt;World Institute of Kimchi&lt;/em&gt; (&lt;a href="https://www.wikim.re.kr/eng/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;WiKim&lt;/a&gt;), the 12-week trial involved adult participants who consumed kimchi powder made through different fermentation methods. Using advanced gene sequencing tools, researchers tracked how immune cells reacted before and after the intervention. The results pointed to a clear biological shift: better antigen recognition and inflammation control, two core pillars of a resilient immune system.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The research arrives at a time when interest in functional foods and microbiome health is rising. While previous studies have suggested general benefits of fermented foods, this investigation went further by examining individual immune cell activity using &lt;em&gt;single-cell RNA sequencing&lt;/em&gt;. The work highlights not just a boost in defense, but a recalibration of the immune response, a balance often missing in immune supplements.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Targeted Changes in Immune Cell Behavior&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Blood samples taken from the &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT05898802" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;study’s 13 overweight participants &lt;/a&gt;revealed key changes in &lt;em&gt;peripheral blood mononuclear cells&lt;/em&gt;, which include &lt;em&gt;T cells&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;monocytes&lt;/em&gt;. After kimchi powder supplementation, researchers observed a notable increase in &lt;em&gt;antigen-presenting cells&lt;/em&gt;, those that capture protein fragments from pathogens and present them to other immune cells for recognition.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="" alt="Overview Of Single Cell Transcriptomic Profiling And Immune Cell Annotation Following Intervention" class="wp-image-104159" data-lazy-srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention.jpg 1980w" data-lazy-sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px" data-lazy-src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-1200x727.jpg"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-1200x727.jpg" alt="Overview Of Single Cell Transcriptomic Profiling And Immune Cell Annotation Following Intervention" class="wp-image-104159" srcset="https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-1200x727.jpg 1200w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-380x230.jpg 380w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-520x315.jpg 520w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention-1536x931.jpg 1536w, https://indiandefencereview.com/wp-content/uploads/2026/01/overview-of-single-cell-transcriptomic-profiling-and-immune-cell-annotation-following-intervention.jpg 1980w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Overview of single-cell transcriptomic profiling and immune cell annotation following intervention – © npj Science of Food. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;These cells showed greater activity in &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK26926/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;MHC class II&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/a&gt;proteins, molecules critical to mounting a specific immune response. According to &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/kimchi-korean-side-dish-provides-a-great-immune-system-boost/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Earth.com&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, immune cells treated with kimchi extracts were able to absorb and process more protein targets. This reflects a heightened readiness to detect viruses and bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;At the same time, gene patterns indicated that &lt;em&gt;CD4+ helper T cells&lt;/em&gt; were moving toward a more controlled, regulated activation. This restrained yet responsive behavior suggests a reduction in unnecessary inflammation, a key factor in preventing tissue damage during immune responses. “&lt;em&gt;Our research has proven for the first time in the world that kimchi has two different simultaneous effects: activating defense cells and suppressing excessive response&lt;/em&gt;,” Dr. Lee stated.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Starter Culture Made a Difference&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The method of fermentation played a distinct role in&lt;a href="https://indiandefencereview.com/this-tiny-immune-cell-anti-aging-science/" data-type="post" data-id="95975"&gt; the immune&lt;/a&gt; effects observed. Participants were divided based on whether they consumed kimchi powder made through traditional fermentation or with a starter culture containing the strain &lt;em&gt;Leuconostoc mesenteroides&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;According to the same source, the starter culture version triggered stronger immune signaling, with more pronounced gene activity. Controlled fermentation using specific bacterial strains can shape the biochemical composition of kimchi, possibly enhancing certain health-related compounds. Still, both types of kimchi powder pushed immune cells in the same general direction, suggesting a shared underlying benefit.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The findings point to the influence of manufacturing decisions in determining the final immune impact of a &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/34256014/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;fermented food product&lt;/a&gt;. Even dried and processed, the kimchi powder retained immune-active properties, reinforcing its potential as a functional supplement.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Precise Activation, Not Systemic Overstimulation&lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Researchers emphasized that not all immune cells were affected by the kimchi powder—an important observation in the context of immune regulation.  &lt;em&gt;B cells&lt;/em&gt; (which produce antibodies) and cytotoxic &lt;em&gt;T cells&lt;/em&gt; (which kill infected targets) remained mostly unchanged, indicating that the supplement did not globally ramp up immune activity.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Instead, the effects appeared targeted. &lt;em&gt;Helper T cells&lt;/em&gt; matured more rapidly, and a specific subgroup of proliferating T cells increased slightly, hinting at cellular renewal rather than exhaustion. Lab tests showed that kimchi extracts influenced &lt;em&gt;interferon-gamma&lt;/em&gt; production, which in turn activated MHC class II gene expression. When a blocking drug (&lt;em&gt;ruxolitinib&lt;/em&gt;) was introduced, the activation was reduced but not entirely stopped, indicating multiple immune pathways were at work.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While these findings are promising, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41538-025-00593-7" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;the study &lt;/a&gt;did not measure actual illness rates or symptom reduction. Still, they represent an important step in understanding how fermented foods can interact with immune function. “&lt;em&gt;We plan to expand international research on kimchi and lactic acid bacteria in relation to immune and metabolic health in the future&lt;/em&gt;,” Dr. Lee said.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Indian Defence Review</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:35:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxNTGxIMDJjeGFaQjEtWFAyaTJnMjFfdVo0SWsxdXBibVZ4SDFZd1cwNmRBZy1rVGRNVndDaXNaZUI5bTRNNEcwZS1IMExNeElIT3BRWHh1T3NYQjFfckRldW5YT2FWWENCbWJ2a0dzNk5nVEExYVQxVENVQTFGQU5zRTV1cW5QY2lSRWoxeEV5RzRVZHpE</guid></item><item><title>科学家揭示了喝咖啡的“最健康”方式，但大多数人并不是这样做的- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/scientists-reveal-healthiest-way-drink-160000730.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;Image Credit: Shutterstock PeopleImages&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a lot of people, coffee isn’t a habit. It’s a lifeline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Morning routines revolve around it, afternoons depend on it, and for many, the way coffee is prepared feels non-negotiable. But according to scientists, &lt;strong&gt;how you drink your coffee may matter just as much as how much you drink&lt;/strong&gt;, and the findings are making some caffeine lovers uneasy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the “healthiest” way isn’t necessarily the most popular one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Biggest Health Factor Isn’t the Coffee, It’s What’s Added to It&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers point out that coffee itself contains compounds linked to potential benefits, including antioxidants and anti-inflammatory effects. The problem starts when coffee turns into a dessert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugars, flavored syrups, whipped toppings, and heavy cream can quietly transform a cup of coffee into a high-calorie, high-sugar drink that cancels out most of those benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists say the healthiest coffee habits tend to look much simpler than what most people are used to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Timing Matters More Than People Realize&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another surprising finding has to do with &lt;em&gt;when&lt;/em&gt; coffee is consumed. Drinking coffee too early in the morning or too late in the day may interfere with natural hormone cycles and sleep quality. Poor sleep, in turn, affects metabolism, heart health, and inflammation, even if the coffee itself is “healthy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers suggest that &lt;strong&gt;moderate, well-timed coffee intake&lt;/strong&gt; may support energy without disrupting the body’s natural rhythm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why Black or Light Coffee Comes Out on Top&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When scientists describe the healthiest way to drink coffee, they usually mean:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is why black coffee or coffee with a small amount of milk often ranks highest in health discussions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not about suffering through bitterness, it’s about avoiding excess ingredients that quietly shift coffee from beneficial to burdensome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Temperature and Brewing Style Play a Role Too&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some studies have also examined brewing methods and temperature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain brewing styles may filter out compounds that can raise cholesterol, while extremely hot beverages may irritate the digestive tract for some people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The takeaway isn’t that one method is dangerous, it’s that &lt;strong&gt;small &lt;a href="https://parentdiaries.com/15-times-saying-no-is-the-best-parenting-choice-you-can-make/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:choices add up over time;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;choices add up over time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, especially for daily coffee drinkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why This Advice Feels Hard to Accept&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;What makes this information uncomfortable is that coffee is emotional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s comfort. It’s ritual. It’s one of the few daily pleasures many people protect fiercely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So when scientists suggest dialing things back, fewer add-ins, better timing, more moderation, it can feel like an attack on something personal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Part Most People Miss&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers aren’t saying you need to give up your favorite coffee order forever. They’re pointing out that &lt;strong&gt;what you do most days matters more than what you do occasionally&lt;/strong&gt;. A simple coffee routine most of the time, with indulgent versions as a treat, appears to offer the best balance between enjoyment and health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Question Coffee Drinkers Are Asking Now&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If coffee is something you consume &lt;a href="https://www.aol.com/lifestyle/5-frugal-habits-never-heard-140000241.html" data-ylk="slk:every single day;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;every single day&lt;/a&gt;, is it helping you, or quietly working against you? That’s the question this &lt;a href="https://www.aol.com/lifestyle/research-highlights-vitamin-d-potential-154500597.html" data-ylk="slk:research leaves people;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;research leaves people&lt;/a&gt; sitting with. And once you start thinking about it, it’s hard not to notice how quickly a “simple cup of coffee” can turn into something very different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:22:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNVE9pS0UtbXNZZUJ5eWZWc0FTbDB1QVU2d3VyakZXQjNxc2FnWTRfb1lxTDdnMTJvdlNIQ0pheUx5eUs5MU1WOW1keERfUzB6VWs0b045MjNnY3NWcFVzR19rbHIyeDVJcnFJT0VZb3EwVmpZV3hBVVR6dWp6UUcwN3VOTkJIUWJzRVE</guid></item><item><title>男性易激综合征（ IMS ）是一种实际情况—它可以解释很多- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/irritable-male-syndrome-ims-is-an-actual-condition-and-it-could-explain-a-lot-goog_l_696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We seem to have reached peak “get off my lawn” culture, with men having temper tantrums all over the damn place. Whether they’re typing shrill all-caps messages, foaming at the mouth with road rage or aggressively punching holes in your drywall, men seem to be angrier than ever. And with a “boys will be boys” cultural mindset that provides a free pass on bad behavior to men well into their final decades, it’s hard to know when, or if, these antics will ever end.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Would it make you feel any better to know that there’s not only a possible medical reason, but even an accepted syndrome designation, for this way many men have of interacting with the world? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Maybe not, but the term “irritable male syndrome”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt; does&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; exist, and in the two decades since it was coined, it’s become accepted in medical and psychological circles. While not a clinical diagnosis, experts say it’s an accurate description of a cluster of symptoms that often appears in aging men. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Along with the term ‘andropause,’ which refers to male menopause, it’s a useful shorthand for describing what happens to men through gradual testosterone decline and hormonal changes,” said Dr &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.houmanmd.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Justin Houman" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://www.houmanmd.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Justin Houman&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, assistant professor of urology at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Andreas Kindler via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Andreas Kindler via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Gradual testosterone decline can contribute to a number of symptoms, including mood changes, low energy and fatigue.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to Houman, the most common symptoms are: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mood changes, including irritability, lower motivation and feelings of depression&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cognitive changes, like difficulty concentrating or memory lapses&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Low energy and fatigue that isn’t explained by poor sleep alone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Reduced libido and fewer spontaneous erections&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Loss of muscle mass and strength despite regular exercise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Increased body fat, particularly around the midsection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sleep disturbances, including insomnia or poor-quality rest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;These symptoms don’t happen overnight, he said. “Male hormonal decline is gradual, with testosterone levels peaking in the late teens to early 20s, remaining relatively stable through the 30s, and starting to decline by about 1% per year after age 40. Most men start noticing symptoms like those listed above between 40 and 60, though lifestyle, chronic illness and genetics can accelerate or delay onset.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How we got here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term “irritable male syndrome” (IMS) was coined in 2001 by Dr. &lt;a href="https://www.endocrinology.org/endocrinologist/138-winter-2020/general-news/gerald-lincoln-1945-2020-a-man-for-all-seasons/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Gerald Lincoln" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.endocrinology.org/endocrinologist/138-winter-2020/general-news/gerald-lincoln-1945-2020-a-man-for-all-seasons/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Gerald Lincoln&lt;/a&gt;, a Scottish scientist known for his work in endocrinology and reproductive biology. He was researching testosterone levels in sheep when he observed a correlation between &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/11999307/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="declining testosterone levels and increased irritability and aggression" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/11999307/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;declining testosterone levels and increased irritability and aggression&lt;/a&gt; in rams after the mating season. He observed similar behaviors in other males when their testosterone levels dropped, eventually identifying the syndrome in red deer, reindeer and even Indian elephants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“It’s a state of hypersensitivity, anxiety, frustration and anger that occurs in males that’s associated with biochemical changes, hormonal fluctuations, stress and loss of male identity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__attribution caption-cli"&gt;- Dr. Jed Diamond&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;As years passed, the term was picked up by psychologists and men’s health experts to describe similar emotional and behavioral patterns they were observing in human men, particularly in relation to age-related testosterone decline or stress-induced hormonal shifts. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Psychotherapist and author Dr. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jed-diamond-aa0b1227b#:~:text=Jed%20holds%20a%20Ph.,is%20www.MenAlive.com." role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Jed Diamond" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jed-diamond-aa0b1227b#:~:text=Jed%20holds%20a%20Ph.,is%20www.MenAlive.com." data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jed Diamond&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; has written the books “&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://www.amazon.com/Irritable-Male-Syndrome-Understanding-Depression/dp/1594862915/ref=sr_1_1?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" role="link" data-amazon-link="true" data-aps-asin="1594862915" data-aps-asc-tag="thehuffingtop-20" data-aps-asc-subtag="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0,-1,-1,d,0,0,hp-fil-am=0,0:0,0,0,0" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Irritable Male Syndrome" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://www.amazon.com/Irritable-Male-Syndrome-Understanding-Depression/dp/1594862915/ref=sr_1_1?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Irritable Male Syndrome&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;” and “&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://ebook/dp/B003K15MLI/?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;pd_rd_w=rUyVs&amp;amp;content-id=amzn1.sym.0fb2cce1-1ca4-439a-844b-8ad0b1fb77f7&amp;amp;pf_rd_p=0fb2cce1-1ca4-439a-844b-8ad0b1fb77f7&amp;amp;pf_rd_r=144-0902517-2468818&amp;amp;pd_rd_wg=20hZu&amp;amp;pd_rd_r=335e0e43-7344-48b9-a64c-404bc5e60c8c&amp;amp;ref_=aufs_ap_sc_dsk" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Mister Mean: Saving Your Relationship From The Irritable Male Syndrome" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://ebook/dp/B003K15MLI/?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;pd_rd_w=rUyVs&amp;amp;content-id=amzn1.sym.0fb2cce1-1ca4-439a-844b-8ad0b1fb77f7&amp;amp;pf_rd_p=0fb2cce1-1ca4-439a-844b-8ad0b1fb77f7&amp;amp;pf_rd_r=144-0902517-2468818&amp;amp;pd_rd_wg=20hZu&amp;amp;pd_rd_r=335e0e43-7344-48b9-a64c-404bc5e60c8c&amp;amp;ref_=aufs_ap_sc_dsk" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mister Mean: Saving Your Relationship From The Irritable Male Syndrome&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.” He described IMS this way: “It’s a state of hypersensitivity, anxiety, frustration and anger that occurs in males that’s associated with biochemical changes, hormonal fluctuations, stress and loss of male identity. While it does usually occur in men later in life, I’ve seen men in their 20s or 30s, who have poor diets, high stress and other factors, can also experience IMS.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We react differently to this syndrome because it’s more likely to “sneak up” on those who have it and those who love them, said coaching psychologist &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jamesdavis/?originalSubdomain=uk" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="James Davis" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jamesdavis/?originalSubdomain=uk" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;James Davis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. “The hormonal changes of women’s menopause happen in a relatively narrow window of time, but with age-related testosterone decline, it can be more of a ‘slow drip’ rather than a sudden moment. This means symptoms can often be passed off as being caused by aging, stress or a combination of both.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While hormonal changes might jump-start IMS, other factors can play a role, Davis said. “Those hormonal changes make men more anxious, which in turn can lead to irritability. There can be a crisis of self-identity that comes from declining physical performance, loss of muscle and lowered libido. When you overlay the stresses of managing a career, finances and relationships, plus the state of the world in general, you can see that many factors could make a man more irritable. Then add in broken sleep, a lack of experience or framework for expressing vulnerability or issues and increasing social isolation, and you can see how multiple factors can pile up to impact an individual.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One man’s experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/israel.cassol/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Israel Cassol" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.instagram.com/israel.cassol/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Israel Cassol&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is a podcaster who began trying to raise awareness of “male menopause” after he was diagnosed with the condition shortly after turning 40. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2021/10/29/influencer-40-wants-acknowledgment-of-male-menopause/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="He told the New York Post" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="696931bae4b09fa9c797ddc0" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://nypost.com/2021/10/29/influencer-40-wants-acknowledgment-of-male-menopause/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;&lt;span&gt;He told the New York Post&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;span&gt; “I was hesitant to share such intimate details of my life, but I needed to know if this was an issue others were facing. I couldn’t believe the response I received from men describing similar symptoms I had suffered from.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These days, he still promotes issues of men’s health, offering this advice to HuffPost: “Men shouldn’t see this as a weakness or something shameful. It’s a natural part of life for many, and talking about it helps break the stigma around men’s emotional health. The sooner we recognize what’s going on, the sooner we can take steps to improve things, and that makes a huge difference not just for men, but for their families and relationships, too.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suspect you may have IMS? Here’s what to do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Diamond said that the first step should be a doctor’s appointment: “I’d say that any man over 45 who is experiencing these symptoms consistently should see their doctor for a blood test to check testosterone levels.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What happens if those levels &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;are&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; low? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“There are effective lifestyle adjustments men can make to boost levels naturally, and there is also the option of testosterone replacement therapy, which is something that requires careful consideration,” Davis said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What to do if a loved one seems like a likely candidate for IMS? Besides that medical evaluation, Diamond mentioned, Houman suggested encouraging healthy lifestyle changes like more balanced nutrition, regular exercise, good sleep hygiene and reduced stress. “Keep communication open and non-judgmental, and seek counseling if a relationship strain develops,” he said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happens next&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s important to demonstrate compassion for this issue, Davis explained. “You need to realize that this isn’t a personality change per se, but is likely a result of hormonal changes that affect behavior, emotion, cognition and even how that person shows up in the world,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also said that this is an issue that needs more attention. “We need to bring andropause out into the open so that both men and women can appreciate what’s going on with male hormones and psychology at this time of life. Midlife men are the highest suicide cohort, with a rate almost five times that of women of all ages, so the issue is significant and we shouldn’t marginalize it by questioning its existence or attempting to downplay it,” Davis added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, Cassoll offered this encouragement: “Patience and understanding are very important, because men going through this phase don’t always realize what’s happening to them. It helps if loved ones encourage healthier habits and also create space for honest conversations without judgment. Suggesting a medical check-up can be really helpful, because it reassures the man that he’s not ‘going crazy,’ and that there are ways to feel better.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The original version of this story was published on HuffPost at an earlier date.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:00:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1wFBVV95cUxNUlJwQmtGOXEwc1hwOG9iWXJwazEtam11RzRMeDcwcVBpUE1VTE5Ca2hOT0tFWERlWHNnMDdNVGdkVHFDMnhmWXBZVnJRUjJOQU9aRmgyOXVHb2ZKRjNDcld1STd5TTZQV3EzTnBKcFB6THRqY0taMVljdzdLaHJ0V092OXNQMjBvcWw3bm4zVUxVLVVMdWk1WDhQUV9MVWE2eVNSSjNHUHdicGRISEs2Qm9kX215QWpRTzlNdW50alhneElKOUNtWXBUNl9oenBURUptTzFDRdIB3AFBVV95cUxNdlF1QnF6aDBacVZlSHpxVzBNZ3YxOTdQQklkbHBRTHBJVUlZaUs3ZXZTN254ZWQ5eG9yWEs0ckFlWkx3aUpaUElqOXBITkxqQXNyU1Y1WU56X2xTZnNiVXlQVlRFNURJYXZsUFkzMjMtcU9zWDBTajZRSlpueURiRmlmNng5RGdFOUhnZ2hzRXUxVWtwb1RuWllYQ3YxUVllUEQwQUd4c3J3Tm4wa19wTU52dlRwX01wa2xfclFCUzFNV19xRUpiTVMyeGk3d1puUzNGYWo5ckxpVGlI</guid></item><item><title>这种高度传染性的冬季病毒病例比前几个季节更糟糕。“以下是您需要了解的信息。- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/high-flu-rates-united-states-goog_l_69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re in the middle of a severe and record-breaking &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/life/topic/winter-health" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="flu" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/life/topic/winter-health" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;flu&lt;/a&gt; season throughout the United States. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu-related doctor’s visits are at an all-time high as millions of people come down with the virus. Flu deaths have also been reported in states across the country, including &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/child-dies-from-the-flu-in-nj-marking-first-pediatric-case-as-infections-increase.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="New Jersey" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2026/01/child-dies-from-the-flu-in-nj-marking-first-pediatric-case-as-infections-increase.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.wmur.com/article/flu-cases-new-hampshire-deaths-010926/69960950" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="New Hampshire" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.wmur.com/article/flu-cases-new-hampshire-deaths-010926/69960950" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;New Hampshire&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://kutv.com/news/local/4-year-old-ogden-girl-dies-after-complications-from-influenza" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Oregon" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://kutv.com/news/local/4-year-old-ogden-girl-dies-after-complications-from-influenza" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Oregon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.fox8live.com/2026/01/08/louisiana-reports-first-child-flu-death-2026-cases-surge-statewide/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Louisiana" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.fox8live.com/2026/01/08/louisiana-reports-first-child-flu-death-2026-cases-surge-statewide/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Louisiana&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This flu season seems to be worse than previous flu seasons in that we are seeing more cases and we are seeing more hospitalizations associated with influenza than we have in previous years,” said &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/1821/suruchi-sood" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Suruchi Sood" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/1821/suruchi-sood" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;Suruchi Sood&lt;/a&gt;, an assistant professor at Johns Hopkins University in Baltimore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://familiesfightingflu.org/medical-advisor/1413/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Jeb Teichman" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://familiesfightingflu.org/medical-advisor/1413/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;Dr. Jeb Teichman&lt;/a&gt;, a former pediatrician and medical adviser for &lt;a href="https://familiesfightingflu.org/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Families Fighting Flu" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://familiesfightingflu.org/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;Families Fighting Flu&lt;/a&gt;, the U.S. has experienced 15 million flu cases so far this season compared to 9.1 million cases at this point last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flu season is expected to worsen before it improves. Here’s what to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flu rates are “high” or “very high” in more than half of U.S. states. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_2-u-s-virologic-surveillance" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="data" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-53.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_2-u-s-virologic-surveillance" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, as of the week ending Jan. 3, 2026, flu rates were “high” or “very high” across more than half of the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This includes states all over the U.S., such as New York, Maine, Colorado, Tennessee, Georgia, California, Pennsylvania, Iowa, New Jersey, South Carolina and many more. (See the full, color-coded map of flu activity below.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Flu rates are "high" or "very high" in most of the United States right now.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positive flu test rates are down, but experts don’t think they’ll stay that way.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, positive flu test rates are down from 32.9% in the last week of December to 24.7% in early January. While this marks a large decrease, it does not mean the flu has peaked. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What the CDC is saying is that people weren’t seeking care during the holidays,” Teichman explained. This is likely the reason behind the drop in cases, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If people were sick with the flu but not getting tested, flu rates would appear lower — even if they’re not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sood added that folks who already had time off from work for the holidays may have decided to get better at home and not seek testing or treatment. So, if folks were off the week between Christmas and New Year’s, flu rates through early January may appear lower than they actually are. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not really clear if the cases are going down because the actual incidence of infection is going down, which I hope is the case, or if it’s just backlog or less people seeking care and testing during the holidays and right after the holidays,” Sood added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s good to see that cases may be starting to tail off, but I would caution people that it’s still early days ... we would want to see a continuing trend, a downward trend, before we let down our guard,” said &lt;a href="https://physiciandirectory.brighamandwomens.org/details/1636/daniel-kuritzkes-infectious_disease-boston" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Daniel R. Kuritzkes" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://physiciandirectory.brighamandwomens.org/details/1636/daniel-kuritzkes-infectious_disease-boston" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;Dr. Daniel R. Kuritzkes&lt;/a&gt;, senior physician in the division of infectious diseases at Mass General Brigham in Boston. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What I’m reading in this report is that the CDC is expecting [flu cases] to go back up. We are not at peak yet ... most commonly we peak in February, but we’ll see,” Teichman added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This rough flu season is likely being caused by “a slight mismatch” between the prevalent circulating flu strain and the flu shot, according to Kuritzkes. This is because a new flu strain emerged after the flu shot formulation was decided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flu hospitalizations and deaths are up throughout the country.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hospitalizations and deaths from the flu are up from the prior week, according to the most recent CDC data. Experts say this makes sense after the particularly high surge in cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We always say that hospitalization and mortality are lagging indicators because people have to have caught the flu and then progressed to the point where they’re sick enough to be hospitalized,” Kuritzkes noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt; If you are not feeling well, stay home.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to avoid getting the flu? Here’s what you can do.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People should still be continuing to take all the precautions that they ordinarily would, in terms of careful attention to washing your hands when you come in from being out and about, wearing a mask if you’re in crowded indoor circumstances, staying away from people who are coughing and sneezing,” Kuritzkes said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Try also to avoid contact with high-touch surfaces, Teichman suggested. For instance, if you’re out and about, use your sleeve to open doors or press elevator buttons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are not feeling well, stay home. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/early-symptoms-flu_l_695e6cb5e4b05bed6f971f03" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="Common flu symptoms" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="695e6cb5e4b05bed6f971f03" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;Common flu symptoms&lt;/a&gt; include fever, body aches, headaches and a sore throat. And if you notice any flu symptoms, take a flu test. You can find flu tests at your local pharmacy and &lt;a href="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://www.amazon.com/iHealth-COVID-19-Authorized-Non-invasive-Discomfort/dp/B0D3T1X1FS/ref=sr_1_6?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" target="_blank" role="link" data-amazon-link="true" data-aps-asin="B0D3T1X1FS" data-aps-asc-tag="thehuffingtop-20" data-aps-asc-subtag="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc,-1,-1,d,0,0,hp-fil-am=0,0:0,0,0,0" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="online" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://www.amazon.com/iHealth-COVID-19-Authorized-Non-invasive-Discomfort/dp/B0D3T1X1FS/ref=sr_1_6?tag=thehuffingtop-20%26ascsubtag%3D69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;online&lt;/a&gt;. Medical providers can also administer flu tests at your local urgent care or doctor’s office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Testing would be great, not just for preventing transmission, but for the person’s own sake,” Sood said. “There’s treatment for influenza and there’s treatment for COVID-19, so knowing that you have it might actually be beneficial for treatment options.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vaccination remains a crucial way to protect yourself and your loved ones from getting really sick.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The most important thing is that if you have not yet gotten the vaccine, and many fewer people this year have been vaccinated than in past years, it is not too late,” Kuritzkes said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The vaccine may not keep you from getting the flu, but it will help protect you from getting as sick, ending up in the emergency room or worse, according to Teichman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;While recent flu guidance from the Department of Health and Human Services &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/public-health/states-health-organizations-reject-new-cdc-vaccine-guidance" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="no longer unilaterally" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69695a14e4b0774cc19f78bc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/public-health/states-health-organizations-reject-new-cdc-vaccine-guidance" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;no longer unilaterally&lt;/a&gt; recommends flu vaccination, experts say the flu shot remains the best way to protect yourself this winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the last flu season, we lost 289 pediatric patients, children under 18. Ninety percent of those who succumbed to the flu were not vaccinated,” said Teichman, who added that half of the children who died didn’t have any conditions that put them at high risk for death from the flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:00:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxQME5LdzZMLXNndjhIZFNsaVR4Q29VbjRKTHRPN3VqX0xoZmcyQl9lLTBCM3lmSnZwZDFmaGxGRy13OXYyekZqVWtWQXNLUldIRTNoekR1U3ZHcnZDN1F4S1RFUTBYMFp0dDFZZWQtV0lpU2REZkZMWU9CQWpxUkgxZlVTb0luN01ldVl2dW5lZjNRTFVjNmfSAZsBQVVfeXFMTlFRN1VKSXQ5RXpibWdMU19VNy01Z0RWQWNlWldUYUFVTVRHcjdmQVlENndNZUFpVDZqbTAtUWJOb2R6Zm44TDJPX2R6cTV4UkFZNEJKTWNqdmJDejQ3clFmNEM3QWl1bUJyX3FlbkxLeWxWV2xWeW83eTJJRFlpdE14T256eHhxVEd5TXk2MVloanM1TzF3SWw2OE0</guid></item><item><title>6分钟的早晨例行公事，使腹部变平，比50岁后的腹部锻炼更好-吃这个不是那个</title><link>https://www.eatthis.com/belly-overhang-after-50-morning-routine/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content single-post-content"&gt;
																			&lt;p class="tagline"&gt;Start this 6-minute routine today to target belly overhang after 50, stay consistent.&lt;/p&gt;
												
																			
																		
						
						
						&lt;p&gt;Building a healthier waistline after 50 starts with what you do most often, not what you do occasionally. &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6378489/" target="_blank"&gt;Morning routines&lt;/a&gt; work because they anchor your day with intention before distractions, stress, or fatigue creep in. When movement becomes automatic, consistency follows, and that’s where real body changes begin.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fat loss, especially &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/chair-exercises-for-belly-fat-over-65/" target="_blank"&gt;around the belly&lt;/a&gt;, responds best to process-driven habits. You don’t wake up one morning with a &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/morning-core-drills-tighten-midsection-better-than-crunches-after-45/" target="_blank"&gt;flatter midsection.&lt;/a&gt; You earn it by stacking small, repeatable actions that improve circulation, wake up dormant muscles, and set your metabolism in motion. A short daily routine outperforms longer workouts that occur only occasionally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consistency matters just as much as exercise selection. The best movements in the world won’t help if they’re skipped. This routine focuses on simple, joint-friendly exercises that reinforce posture, breathing, and total-body tension. When your body learns to &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://www.eatthis.com/morning-routine-to-flatten-lower-belly-after-55/" target="_blank"&gt;move well&lt;/a&gt; first thing in the morning, it carries that efficiency into the rest of the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This five-minute routine delivers quick wins. It elevates your heart rate, fires up your core, and encourages fat-burning activity without stressing your joints. You’ll feel more upright, more energized, and more connected through your midsection before breakfast even hits the table. Here’s exactly how to do it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;5-Minute Morning Core and Metabolism Reset&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="458127" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-458127" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=640,427&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=768,513&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=1024,684&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=473,316&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=400,267&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=800,534&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-458127" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=640,427&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=768,513&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=1024,684&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=473,316&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=400,267&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2019/12/woman-motivated-sunrise-fitness-run.jpg?resize=800,534&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;What You Need&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just your bodyweight and a small patch of floor space. No equipment required. The entire routine takes five minutes from start to finish and works best first thing in the morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed karma_unit--halfpage"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;The Routine&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Standing March with Core Brace (40 seconds)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bodyweight Squat to Reach (40 seconds)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incline Plank Shoulder Taps (40 seconds)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rest for 20 seconds between exercises&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Repeat the circuit once for a total of five minutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Directions&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Move through each exercise for 40 seconds, then rest for 20 seconds before transitioning to the next movement. Focus on controlled breathing and smooth transitions. Complete the full circuit twice. Read on for the detailed instructions.&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="standing-march-with-core-brace" class="o-slide-title" data-num="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Standing March with Core Brace&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/shdbEBpDUTk?si=mjk5FA1PyeVWOG1q" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This movement wakes up your deep core muscles while gently elevating your heart rate. Marching challenges balance and coordination, which forces your abs to stabilize your pelvis and spine with every step. It also encourages better posture, which helps flatten the appearance of belly overhang throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Do It:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand tall with your feet hip-width apart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brace your core as if you’re tightening a wide belt around your waist.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift one knee to hip height while keeping your torso upright.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower the foot under control and switch sides.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continue alternating at a steady pace while breathing smoothly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Best Variations:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="bodyweight-squat-to-reach" class="o-slide-title" data-num="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bodyweight Squat to Reach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ujNy4KGkMnQ?si=tmBgrcrG09Yr47p2" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This exercise trains your legs, glutes, and core together, boosting calorie burn and reinforcing full-body coordination. The overhead reach encourages thoracic mobility and lengthens the front of the body, helping counter the slouched posture that can make belly overhang more noticeable.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Do It:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet slightly wider than hip-width.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit your hips back into a comfortable squat.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive through your heels to stand up tall.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reach both arms overhead as you fully extend your hips.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reset and repeat with controlled tempo.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Best Variations:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chair-assisted squat to reach&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quarter squat with a slower reach&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="incline-plank-shoulder-taps" class="o-slide-title" data-num="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Incline Plank Shoulder Taps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="YouTube video player" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/GzpmFU7qaFE?si=oB0t72HwhOfmb2kG" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Incline planks reduce strain while still challenging your core, shoulders, and hips. Shoulder taps add anti-rotation demand, forcing your abs to work harder to keep your body steady. This helps strengthen the muscles that pull the waist inward and support better trunk control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to Do It:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Place your hands on a bench, bed, or sturdy surface.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Step your feet back into a straight-body plank.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Brace your core and squeeze your glutes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tap one shoulder with the opposite hand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alternate sides while minimizing hip movement.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Best Variations:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;h2&gt;The Best Tips for Flattening Belly Overhang After 50&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="888114" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-888114" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Yoga, man and breathe meditation in home, house or living room floor for energy, fitness or mental health. Relax, stress relief and zen person with mindfulness for pilates, spiritual healing or peace" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-888114" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Yoga, man and breathe meditation in home, house or living room floor for energy, fitness or mental health. Relax, stress relief and zen person with mindfulness for pilates, spiritual healing or peace" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/11/shutterstock_2603756041.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Flattening belly overhang takes patience and daily commitment, but the payoff compounds quickly. This routine works best when paired with smart lifestyle choices that support fat loss and recovery.&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;6254a4d1642c605c54bf1cab17d50f1e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Anchor the habit:&lt;/b&gt; Perform this routine at the same time every morning to lock in consistency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Breathe with intention:&lt;/b&gt; Slow nasal breathing during the workout improves core activation and stress control.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Prioritize protein:&lt;/b&gt; Adequate protein intake supports muscle maintenance and metabolic health.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stay upright throughout the day: Walking and standing reinforce&lt;/b&gt; the posture benefits of this routine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Track progress weekly:&lt;/b&gt; Focus on how you feel, how your clothes fit, and your energy levels rather than daily scale changes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Five minutes won’t feel dramatic in the moment, but done daily, it becomes a powerful tool for reshaping your waistline and reclaiming control over your body after 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;References&lt;/h4&gt;


																		
																	&lt;/div&gt;
										&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio"&gt;
	&lt;p class="c-article-short-bio__name"&gt;Jarrod Nobbe, MA, CSCS&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
		Jarrod Nobbe is a USAW National Coach, Sports Performance Coach, Personal Trainer, and writer, and has been involved in health and fitness for the past 12 years.					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="c-article-short-bio__more" href="https://www.eatthis.com/author/jarrod-nobbe/"&gt;Read more about Jarrod &lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Eat This Not That</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:01:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE5ULUFxY2VJd1Y2NHp4aFFSWEhUajJCWUV1YXdSb2JBYW5IU3Jqem1LdWFBYV9Telh3Szh4WHBxTzlid1NzRVVDcm9qX1A2UWxiMU9pWWtMR0w0Tkw2Q0pkTmcteWtQcmFCcEM2YWhFVFNkdw</guid></item><item><title>患有脂肪肝？这种简单的生活方式改变可以带来很大的健康变化- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/skebx4csbe</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="ArticleHeaderComponent" class="ArticleHeaderEngComponent1280 selectableShareable for-print" role="header" aria-label="article header"&gt;&lt;p class="mainTitleWrapper"&gt;&lt;h1 class="mainTitle"&gt;Have fatty liver disease? This simple lifestyle change can make a big health difference&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="subTitleWrapper"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span disabled class="subTitle" contenteditable="false"&gt;A large international study led by Israeli researchers found that even exercising just one or two days a week, if intense enough, can lower the risk of fatty liver disease, heart problems and early death — with benefits similar to daily workouts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 10:19:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE8xaDJVSGpvVGlnQXRWMWNja0t1SVBQTHlrcHpMU1pXcTV0Z0xHSE5WUjlsLTlJQVJ6dFRtS1dramtXSDhfMFJra2psNG80NUFUZmJ5ZEthcDBnVGZzZ2NXTmpRRkpndWRJSnc</guid></item></channel></rss>