<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>心脏病和BMI与绝经后妇女乳腺癌风险增加相关- Scimex | Heart disease and BMI linked with increased breast cancer risk in postmenopausal women - Scimex</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxNQWlWcmRwdnJRQUN6Uzc5amN1cHZhMzFncUtvVFBtMGk5M0loQzk2SS1CVkZhRzRicEIySm9tVkhCbFVLNHJ4WTU3M3p1dkJLbUtob1ZBX2RaOFVadk9RbjJiRjY5T0kxem9oQnd4eG44S19kZXBhMGxaY2YzbTFObVYxZjRkTmI1VE5PVHl6V1Q3Q00wVE90OG5UTE56ZDU3T2t4S1FETTdGN205eVowelB2WQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="story-summary"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="story-summary-text"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In postmenopausal women with heart disease, excess weight could be linked to an especially high risk of developing breast cancer, according to international researchers. The team looked at data from over 168,000 postmenopausal women who did not have type 2 diabetes and cardiovascular disease when they agreed to participate. After a follow-up of around 10 years, over 6,000 developed breast cancer, and the team found that in women who developed cardiovascular disease during the study, each 5 point increase in BMI was associated with a 31% higher risk of breast cancer when compared to women without cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
                  
                

                
                &lt;div class="story__notes"&gt;
                  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Journal/conference:&lt;/strong&gt; CANCER&lt;/p&gt;
               
                  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Research: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/cncr.35911" target="_blank"&gt;Paper&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                  
                  &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Organisation/s:&lt;/strong&gt; The International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC), World Health Organization&lt;/p&gt;
                  
                                  &lt;/div&gt;
                  
                  

                  &lt;div class="story-content"&gt;
                                            &lt;h2&gt;Media release&lt;/h2&gt;
                    
&lt;strong&gt;From:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt; Wiley

                                        
                    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How does body mass index affect breast cancer risk in postmenopausal women with and without cardiovascular disease?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysis shows that weight-associated breast cancer risk is higher in women with cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New research reveals that excess weight is linked to an especially high risk of developing breast cancer in postmenopausal women with cardiovascular disease. The findings are published by &lt;a href="https://zwly9k6z.r.us-east-1.awstrack.me/L0/https:%2F%2Fwww.wiley.com%2F/1/01000197cb39c7fe-8757bfab-e5e9-498d-a8c0-092e46891925-000000/ar_rreNj0Y8xYzsWyvyAKaqESzY=433"&gt;Wiley&lt;/a&gt; online in &lt;a href="https://zwly9k6z.r.us-east-1.awstrack.me/L0/https:%2F%2Facsjournals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com%2Fjournal%2F10970142%3Fdmmsmid=73865%26dmmspid=22624228%26dmmsuid=1961220/1/01000197cb39c7fe-8757bfab-e5e9-498d-a8c0-092e46891925-000000/dJyVq8jWm3Qmy5Q9R1Pd5vB3IZw=433"&gt;CANCER&lt;/a&gt;, a peer-reviewed journal of the American Cancer Society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although higher body mass index (BMI) is a known risk factor for breast cancer in postmenopausal women, it’s unclear whether this risk differs among women with and without cardiovascular disease or type 2 diabetes. To investigate, a team led by Heinz Freisling, PhD, of the International Agency for Research on Cancer (the specialized cancer agency of the World Health Organization) analyzed data from the European Prospective Investigation into Cancer and Nutrition (EPIC) and UK Biobank on 168,547 postmenopausal women who did not have, type 2 diabetes, and cardiovascular disease when they agreed to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a median follow-up of 10.7 years in EPIC and 10.9 years in UK Biobank, 6,793 postmenopausal women developed breast cancer. In a pooled analysis of both studies, each 5 kg/m&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt; increase in BMI was associated with a 31% higher risk of breast cancer in women who developed cardiovascular disease during follow-up and a 13% higher risk in women without cardiovascular disease. The development of type 2 diabetes did not seem to affect breast cancer risk: women with or without type 2 diabetes had a similarly elevated breast cancer risk related to higher BMI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The combination of overweight (BMI≥25 kg/m&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt;) and cardiovascular disease was estimated to lead to 153 more cases of breast cancer per 100,000 people per year than expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The findings of this study could be used to inform risk-stratified breast cancer screening programs,” said Dr. Freisling. “This study should also inspire future research to include women with a history of cardiovascular diseases in weight loss trials for breast cancer prevention.”&lt;/p&gt;

                  &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Scimex</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:41:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxNQWlWcmRwdnJRQUN6Uzc5amN1cHZhMzFncUtvVFBtMGk5M0loQzk2SS1CVkZhRzRicEIySm9tVkhCbFVLNHJ4WTU3M3p1dkJLbUtob1ZBX2RaOFVadk9RbjJiRjY5T0kxem9oQnd4eG44S19kZXBhMGxaY2YzbTFObVYxZjRkTmI1VE5PVHl6V1Q3Q00wVE90OG5UTE56ZDU3T2t4S1FETTdGN205eVowelB2WQ</guid></item><item><title>吃什么来保护衰老的肌肉-《华盛顿邮报》 | What to eat to protect your aging muscles - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxQN1ZsUFQ2a0ZRS2luMmtFTXlzUjN3M0RJZ0hvYVdOM2QzTTdXc0JrdTRiNDFHZFpUcGhHWG95THJnNmJ3U3RudHh2Wl8xQ2ZyNlhwTThTQnJocG9FM1MxdUlHdmIzbXRIc3l2WXU3cjZVRE95ZlRzUUNhY254eHpYMUt1Y3FQMWpJSEJYWGdB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VGH2W2CZRRCELDS66TNLXGPQHQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Consumer Reports&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; has no financial relationship with any advertisers on this site.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HZ65C7ZJVNDWRJG42ZRTQPSNBA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Have you found yourself feeling a little weaker than you used to? Are you having trouble climbing stairs or carrying groceries? The reason may be reduced muscle mass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2U62Z4LKXBHNBDSAO56OBTTLBA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;With age comes some decline in muscle, and for many people that’s accompanied by a drop in strength and function. Severe muscle loss, known as sarcopenia, can increase the risk of illness and even death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WNR4OFYXRFBMVGKN7IDZN7XLEY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Although you can’t prevent all age-related muscle loss, you can slow it down significantly and even boost your strength level in the process. You’ve probably heard that exercise, especially weight training, can help you build and maintain muscle. What isn’t discussed as often is the role that diet plays in keeping your muscles in good shape. “You can’t get stronger without eating properly, so diet is essential,” says Elizabeth Klingbeil, an assistant professor in the department of nutritional sciences at the University of Texas at Austin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4H4DJGMYNBH3TJOWSLUP2MO45Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Follow these eating tips to fuel muscle growth and feel stronger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="3LFVGOBZ4JGZXLVNOIISFQVNHM" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="3LFVGOBZ4JGZXLVNOIISFQVNHM" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Bump up your protein&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="T57RJ4CAXJH4HDK6EDJEMNXNUE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Protein is core to building muscle and, even more so, maintaining it, Klingbeil says. The National Academy of Sciences recommends that adults eat 0.36 grams of protein per pound of body weight per day. But an &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s12603-019-1174-1" target="_blank"&gt;analysis of data from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey&lt;/a&gt; found that 42 percent of men and 50 percent of women over age 70 don’t get that much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZBDPN3YSSJAXLD2WTHH6OSUXA4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Some experts recommend even more protein for older adults to compensate for muscle loss and the fact that building new muscle becomes harder with age, Klingbeil says. Aim for 0.45 to 0.59 grams per pound per day — that’s 72 to 94 grams for a 160-pound person. (But if you have kidney disease, check with your doctor about your protein intake because too much can tax your kidneys.) Dietitians generally recommend spreading protein throughout the day because that may help your body absorb it better, but Klingbeil says that getting enough is the most important thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YDDEDAEALRBLDEND2P6Q6IUGTA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The source of protein isn’t super important for building muscle, says Travis Masterson, the principal investigator of the Health, Ingestive Behavior, and Technology Laboratory at Pennsylvania State University. &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/healthy-eating/how-red-meat-can-fit-into-a-healthy-diet-a3360518260/" target="_blank"&gt;Animal foods&lt;/a&gt; tend to have more per serving than plant sources. But for other aspects of your health, it’s best to get at least some of your protein from plants, such as beans, nuts and tofu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IRDQYIYNQRADVN33ET622RPCSA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A plant-based diet that includes mostly whole foods is good for your heart and brain, and it lowers your risk of certain cancers. “It also appears to be gentler on the kidneys than a diet high in animal protein as we age,” says Judy Lester, a clinical dietitian at the University of North Carolina Health Care System in Chapel Hill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GH2FAXJWWBAZRD7IUXPWZ2N2JM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There are 20 grams of protein in a cup of tofu; about 18 grams in a cup of lentils, white beans or edamame; 8 grams in a cup of quinoa or whole-wheat pasta; and 7 grams in an ounce of peanuts. Beef and chicken breast have about 24 grams in 3 ounces. A 5.5-ounce serving of plain nonfat &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/yogurt/healthy-yogurts-that-taste-great-too-a1114386696/" target="_blank"&gt;Greek yogurt&lt;/a&gt; has 16 grams, a cup of low-fat milk has about 8 grams, and an egg has 6 grams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="ZK4XCWDUMFAJ3ITFWG4HWXFO3Q" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="ZK4XCWDUMFAJ3ITFWG4HWXFO3Q" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Get enough calories&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BSOR7IS6WZDDDOGXPMEKFMTYPM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“If you’re not getting enough calories, your body will break down muscle,” Klingbeil says. Calorie needs vary based on height, weight, gender and activity levels, but eating somewhere between 1,800 to 2,400 calories per day is probably adequate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="TWVS7NA4JNGBXOYJQIGUBT24JE" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="TWVS7NA4JNGBXOYJQIGUBT24JE" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Choose quality carbs&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4HLP2AP2TNAFNKCC5MXNOHELNY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Carbohydrates fuel your muscles, so they can help you feel stronger. The best sources are whole grains, &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/canned-foods/best-tasting-canned-beans-a6489833691/" target="_blank"&gt;legumes&lt;/a&gt;, fruits and vegetables. Refined carbs like white bread, crackers, soda and desserts can boost short-term energy, but unlike high-quality carbs, they don’t have the advantage of being rich in fiber and other nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N6ONHD5KMVEHBAJ6XW6J6I33BQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Research shows that fiber may help build or preserve muscle mass, possibly because it increases the level of healthy bacteria in the gut that produce short-chain fatty acids. These compounds are involved in muscle development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="3FNHAQMUYVBQBHPGNURK34JYWY" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="3FNHAQMUYVBQBHPGNURK34JYWY" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Check your vitamin D&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WWMN4HG46ZHJHCLGQCGQ5CM52Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Some studies show a connection between vitamin D levels and muscle strength, although it’s not clear whether getting more vitamin D from your diet or a supplement will help you become stronger. Still, we know that the vitamin is important for bone, muscle and overall health, Klingbeil says, so getting the recommended 20 micrograms (800 IU) per day is smart. New guidelines from the Endocrine Society don’t recommend regular vitamin D testing for healthy adults, so ask your doctor what’s right for you given your particular health picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="KRXJGKPPORF3LMBN4RULB7XRXE" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="KRXJGKPPORF3LMBN4RULB7XRXE" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Add omega-3s&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BKKYM6XZBJHNRFONVSUNDH5PLU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;These fats, found in fish, may help protect from normal age-related declines in muscle. In a 2020 &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7071242/" target="_blank"&gt;review of research on sarcopenia published in the journal Nutrients&lt;/a&gt;, researchers noted that eating fatty fish was linked to increases in muscle mass and better performance on muscle-strength tests. Other studies have shown similar benefits for people who took omega-3 supplements, but the science isn’t conclusive. For now, aim to eat two servings of fatty fish like salmon or sardines per week, which is the American Heart Association’s recommendation for heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="3OMT3BM3TREURCJBIUXZG7Y4DE" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="3OMT3BM3TREURCJBIUXZG7Y4DE" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Stay hydrated&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AWSQBKKSIZGC7FGU5ZXELUELOU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Getting plenty of fluids is important for overall health and preserving muscle, Lester says. Muscle is 70 to 75 percent water, and insufficient water content inside muscle cells has been linked to changes in muscle strength and the ability to do daily activities, as well as a higher risk of frailty in older adults. Drinking water is obviously helpful, but you can also get fluids from other healthy beverages (coffee, tea and milk, for instance) and eating fruits, vegetables and soup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="27RN3PBZ6ZHQXEEXMNXSKMZB7I" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="27RN3PBZ6ZHQXEEXMNXSKMZB7I" data-testid="article-header"&gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Ask your doctor about creatine&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZGWRCV2EIRAR3EQS6T5VAC7NGU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;This compound in muscle tissue is found in meat and seafood, and your body also makes it. But taking it in pill or powder form may be helpful for some people. “Creatine in the muscle is used for producing energy, especially in that initial onset of a contraction, the first one to two seconds,” Masterson says. “The more creatine you can get into the muscle, the more effective that first bit of contraction is going to be.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VQTOXJB2GBHX5KYLJJ4B2OO6CE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Creatine is often used by athletes looking to improve exercise performance, but some research suggests that older adults may benefit from it, too. A &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6518405/" target="_blank"&gt;review published in 2019 in the Journal of Clinical Medicine&lt;/a&gt; found that creatine — in combination with regular &lt;a href="https://www.consumerreports.org/health/dumbbells/strength-training-using-adjustable-dumbbells-a3150717795/" target="_blank"&gt;strength training&lt;/a&gt; — may help reduce the risk of sarcopenia and falls. (Muscle is important for balance, too.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XEJOXQIGZZGEVKU4PSOFP4NWDQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“I’m pretty anti-supplement overall,” Masterson says. “But creatine is one where there are no known side effects, and it’s pretty cheap. Will it drastically change someone? No, but it could give you more energy for exercise or even provide more oomph as you’re trying to get out of a chair.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="IE7DIX3Y5JHS7GHE2JWWDYXWM4" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="IE7DIX3Y5JHS7GHE2JWWDYXWM4" data-testid="article-header"&gt;The importance of strength training&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UIXS4T3OTJG6TG26T7KBGMDTCY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There’s no getting around the fact that exercise is crucial for your muscles. But that doesn’t mean you have to take up bodybuilding to get stronger in your 60s, 70s and beyond. Activities like walking and simple &lt;a href="http://cr.org/4strength" target="_blank"&gt;strength-training&lt;/a&gt; moves such as chair squats (repeatedly sitting and standing) and wall push-ups — and just being active and moving more in general — are a good way to preserve muscle and keep bones and joints strong, Masterson says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KVHCJMREWFCDJEQKMKIJQX6PQM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If you want to go further, you can find weight-focused classes that use dumbbells or other simple equipment at gyms or community recreation centers, or online. (Check out the &lt;a href="http://youtube.com/@nihaging" target="_blank"&gt;workout videos from the National Institute on Aging&lt;/a&gt;.) Try to time your workouts so you’ll be having a meal or snack within a few hours afterward, Masterson says. Both exercise and eating protein stimulate muscle development, so combining them will lead to greater effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p id="MX42FHQYCNA47FRI3ZJH4W7M4Q" class="wpds-c-esEUdQ wpds-c-esEUdQ-hqvHjm-isBold-false wpds-c-esEUdQ-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="MX42FHQYCNA47FRI3ZJH4W7M4Q" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Copyright 2024, Consumer Reports Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NGIOUE72HRGJHDJS2MZ36HBWDU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Consumer Reports is an independent, nonprofit organization that works side by side with consumers to create a fairer, safer and healthier world. CR does not endorse products or services, and does not accept advertising. Read more at &lt;a href="http://www.consumerreports.org/"&gt;ConsumerReports.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 11:40:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQN1ZsUFQ2a0ZRS2luMmtFTXlzUjN3M0RJZ0hvYVdOM2QzTTdXc0JrdTRiNDFHZFpUcGhHWG95THJnNmJ3U3RudHh2Wl8xQ2ZyNlhwTThTQnJocG9FM1MxdUlHdmIzbXRIc3l2WXU3cjZVRE95ZlRzUUNhY254eHpYMUt1Y3FQMWpJSEJYWGdB</guid></item><item><title>随着疫情蔓延，美国麻疹病例达到33年来的新高--《华盛顿邮报》 | U.S. measles cases reach 33-year record high as outbreaks spread - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE9FRG16Q1huYnZOeHE5ZGVlcUtaMmx4M09NeFlkdERTLWhZa1NnMngyWTNXR1ZwV3VyRVRCRHZoU0M1b21QQVF5Sk5pSFlPU201dkxRZ0pTSGh4VE5rVC02UzhVXzJFdlRVQmtoQ3RaRVg5YTI3Ul92b0hsRjV2U00?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TUMTDIR4INADZPOTBGMDJGGIEE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The United States has reached its highest annual measles case tally in 33 years, hitting at least 1,277 confirmed cases across 38 states and the District of Columbia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YUX2HRFOKRD4LHDZVLA5RJ7JVY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The milestone marks a public health reversal in defeating a highly contagious, vaccine-preventable disease as the anti-vaccine movement gains strength.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4BNSIPRQORC35LFHUYC3YFFHZY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The nation surpassed infections reported in&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2019/04/29/us-officials-say-measles-cases-hit-year-record/" target="_blank"&gt; 2019,&lt;/a&gt; reaching the largest number of cases since &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;1992,&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;when officials recorded more than&lt;a href="https://washpost.arcpublishing.com/ellipsis/#!/edit/GL3L5OPSSBENDLNKJIFCV42LDA/"&gt; 2,100&lt;/a&gt; infections, according to &lt;a href="https://cori.centerforhealthsecurity.org/resources/measles-outbreak-response" target="_blank"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; published Friday&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from the Johns Hopkins University Center for Outbreak Response Innovation (CORI).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IIUQXZCV4JFTVEOR62HTLW6Y6M" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“It’s devastating,” said Claire Hannan, executive director of the Association of Immunization Managers, a national organization of state and local immunization officials. “We worked so hard to eliminate the threat of measles and to keep it at bay.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CTOXBKSGEVDB7ML4D6BVYMZNMI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Authorities said at least &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;155 people have been hospitalized &lt;/a&gt;and three people have died of measles-related complications this year. The dead include &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/06/measles-texas-death-outbreak-vaccine/" target="_blank"&gt;two otherwise healthy children &lt;/a&gt;in Texas and a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/03/06/measles-death-outbreak-new-mexico/" target="_blank"&gt;man in New Mexico,&lt;/a&gt; all of who were unvaccinated. In contrast, only three measles deaths were reported between 2001 and 2024, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CCMWQ5NIWJDQJDORYT3SBJ2MGI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;About 92 percent of measles cases in 2025 were in people who were either unvaccinated or whose vaccination status was unknown, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JP66LFKCVJEJ3NXF6S7SMPA6BA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Data from the CDC does not yet reflect the record as it is updated weekly on Wednesdays, while the Johns Hopkins’ site validates data every weekday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DZDKRATFOBFJBI2IFXIQR54DSI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The largest outbreak has been in West Texas, where officials have recorded more than 750 cases since late January and believe the true toll is much higher. Data shows that outbreak has slowed, but that it has spread to surrounding states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="B2DIVDW6KFCYXNO7ZIEHLZR6XA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Unrelated clusters of cases emerged elsewhere, usually originating with an unvaccinated person who traveled abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-image subtype-StaffPhoto" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="A26FIGIMSJDAJPPLUTIFOKI2GU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Measles was &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/about/history.html"&gt;officially eliminated from the U.S. in 2000&lt;/a&gt; with high vaccination coverage&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and rapid outbreak response. Cases still popped up periodically. But in recent years, large outbreaks with 50 or more cases have become more frequent, especially in close-knit communities with low vaccination coverage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RJ7C6RHGGVFQHOTG3PCLXJC72Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Public health experts say the U.S. is on track to lose the elimination status if there is continuous spread of linked measles cases for more than 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XLTSLTOXNVGERIZ6ERL3M45I7E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“It’s a harbinger of things to come,” said Eric Ball, a pediatrician who heads the California chapter of the American Academy of Pediatrics. “Once we see a resurgence of measles, we know that other diseases are going to come behind it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="Q3LXJSWL35CPDLDUML4KRDPAYQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="Q3LXJSWL35CPDLDUML4KRDPAYQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Consequences of vaccine distrust&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XSE4UUHLJRBB3LGE2BMHSPE4BE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/antivaxxers-go-viral-in-communities-battling-measles/2019/05/20/a476417c-78d7-11e9-bd25-c989555e7766_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;Misinformation &lt;/a&gt;about the safety and effectiveness of the measles, mumps and rubella vaccine fueled the 1,274 cases recorded in 2019, according to public health officials and researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="S4CLA7EOU5DR7HJMGOJRBNTBX4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The outbreaks that year were concentrated in &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/new-york-city-vaccination-order-shines-spotlight-on-insular-jewish-community/2019/04/11/fd59b098-5bc3-11e9-a00e-050dc7b82693_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;ultra-Orthodox Jewish communities &lt;/a&gt;in New York, highlighting the risks in tight-knit communities where vaccine distrust takes hold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BF737NVPJVAWND3BFIAPWMHRO4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Confidence in public health measures, especially vaccines, has fallen since then, and is sharply divided along political lines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="23IOQE4B5FAJ3HP7EIHS7OJ4ZQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The national rate for MMR vaccination among kindergartners was slightly above 95 percent in 2019, the level of community protection scientists say is needed to prevent measles outbreaks. But that rate is now &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/73/wr/mm7341a3.htm" target="_blank"&gt;under 93 percent and falling, &lt;/a&gt;according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="O7SW2JKJONADNMGKBBI7MJXPEI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Even in states with high vaccination coverage, pockets of unvaccinated people tend to cluster together. Measles is so contagious that a person without immunity exposed to the virus is highly likely to be infected and to spread it days before they develop symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="W7TW4BAVEVBL3OYR7NCKRCUOFI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A recent study showed that if U.S. vaccination rates continue to decline, the nation could &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/24/measles-cases-deaths-vaccine-rates-rfk-jr/" target="_blank"&gt;face millions&lt;/a&gt; of cases over the next 25 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WZGOXF73QZBBXGJ3QVHGVPFSVE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A&lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/poll-amid-multi-state-measles-outbreak-79-of-americans-support-routine-childhood-vaccine-requirements/?utm_source=chatgpt.com" target="_blank"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/poll-amid-multi-state-measles-outbreak-79-of-americans-support-routine-childhood-vaccine-requirements/?utm_source=chatgpt.com" target="_blank"&gt;poll conducted in March&lt;/a&gt; by the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health and the de Beaumont Foundation found that 79 percent of adults say parents should be required to have children vaccinated against preventable diseases such as measles, mumps and rubella to attend school. Support was stronger among Democrats, 90 percent, than among Republicans, 68 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TNYGNRFW7ZEVVGVR4TEPR4TFN4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Five years after the start of the coronavirus pandemic, less than half the public says it has at least some confidence in federal health agencies to carry out core public health responsibilities, according to a &lt;a href="https://connect.kff.org/e3t/Ctc/RB+113/c1ThL04/VVK5501sYLjFW6bKZXX6WMnh3W5j5c_V5wcn3yN1vWRrn5nR32W5BWr2F6lZ3mWW8wtK6h4-m88gW5SkMMf5MZX2XW1VyVdt2bfDssW7GLKwD7mRPV9W4KnxR68MGwJCN8hDdQ5SWLx2VJVgQK2wk2NJW5bq1Ds3vKdmQW1LXb9x8GMkknW4xb2pD7ysxY8W4P3Qgz8JKw-kW6zzrjG19ZL7gW4v9zXY6Rq2WSN67wxcV16S16W7BwWvs6vYcVmVxd6N87Y9YJ6N2QJRGtBWsRNW4nTtxj8BsCmxN1fkBfzT84w-W1FqQW25PGwsMW5QTqPf1GJKwKW7jj4y97HrfG5W1kcNjg5q16PPW2bVG5j8_Lxz2W3N6slZ5WJtHnVD1j2H1K4V2wW4pj-_f7SvTjlW7wb13P3NJ2sgW1PqX3b5JgWt1W6_5CBH2yyXdsW66Pvl62kSpVvW8f2Wll26Q712W5ZZqV_1tTdxwW2QNyz65NGMxQf60bwLb04" target="_blank"&gt;poll conducted in April by the health care think tank KFF. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RZM4SUND7BGQ7CNKHDBICERWOY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., a longtime anti-vaccine activist who ascended to&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;be the top U.S. health official, has offered &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/05/11/vaccines-measles-rfk-jr-health/" target="_blank"&gt;mixed messages&lt;/a&gt; about measles and the vaccine to prevent it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="K654CNPIJBBKBCQZTP2PWH3UZY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;He initially &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/02/26/measles-texas-unvaccinated-death/" target="_blank"&gt;downplayed the seriousness of the Texas outbreak&lt;/a&gt; after the first child died, saying: “We have measles outbreaks every year.” He accompanied his calls for vaccination with caveats, raising concerns about the shots that public health experts called unfounded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LV76A2NLSNAYLKSPNXKGMQBLDY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Nola Jean Ernest, a pediatrician in rural southeastern Alabama, said many of her patients trust others who share their political views more than her when it comes to vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6JWCF3D2DRAJZAHY3NJ23KB5ZA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;She now sees patients who vaccinated older children refuse to vaccinate their infants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Y7GMRUGIXJBOVMSKM3WLY6Z7CI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“I’ve had several conversations in the last few months where they will say, ‘We still trust you, we just don’t trust the vaccines,’” Ernest said recently. “That really breaks my heart.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="YBUTKDDX4RAPNOFA4MYXHY3WOQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="YBUTKDDX4RAPNOFA4MYXHY3WOQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Anatomy of an outbreak&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="UVIT3NA7TVGBVMFBJO4UKLGGFQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In Texas, infections in late January &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/03/02/measles-outbreak-texas-vaccine-hesitancy-death/" target="_blank"&gt;spread quickly&lt;/a&gt; within Gaines County’s Mennonite community, some of whom educate their children at home or at private schools without vaccine mandates. The county had among the lowest kindergarten MMR vaccination rates in Texas, about 82 percent, according to state immunization data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3NCTWUJSXZFCRCVV32SWLU6C7Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Public health officials said they faced challenges in controlling the outbreak because many people were not getting tested or vaccinated for measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NN22J4SY3JCPDCSRLNQUPAFR5E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Anti-vaccine groups mobilized quickly on the ground. Many Mennonite families turned to a prominent anti-vaccine doctor who offered unproven alternative treatments. Kennedy praised that doctor and his methods in a visit to the region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BDWEDEWYRRFYZGSKW2LYVZFBVU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Children’s Health Defense, an anti-vaccine group founded by Kennedy, interviewed the parents of a 6-year-old girl who died of measles, blaming her death on medical error rather than vaccination status. The organization did not immediately return a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3SJMB7YJJZD7ZDWLLHZA2AGQ3E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Eventually, 36 Texas counties reported measles cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N6T7LSAV65CHRFIEKMGDUWUMIA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Young adults from El Paso who work in oil fields close to Gaines County were among those infected this spring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SUPIOULXYBB5BKAAFLLXLP75FA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;El Paso went from five cases to 53 in a month, said Hector Ocaranza, director of the city and county health authority. Ocaranza said his community was vulnerable because a growing number of young adults, listening to what they see and hear on social media, are not getting vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LDTO4BBLMBGTDPMXKMILHNWRMU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lara Anton, a spokeswoman for the Texas Health Department, said last week that the reporting of new measles cases has slowed, crediting rising population&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;immunity from infections and increased vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2AZ7MRVB3BEOBKQHVIRIWQM5ZQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But the outbreak is not over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YZSSD6VMTRFNPM2JZOZ5FLWQNU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Transmission is continuing in Gaines County, as well as Lamar County, in northeast Texas bordering Oklahoma, according to health department data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AU7ROGVAHFERHIPMEVWFJNLIQQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In Chihuahua, Mexico, which borders Texas and New Mexico, a child who visited Texas in February started a large measles outbreak that now exceeds 2,400 cases and eight deaths as of last week, according to &lt;a href="https://www.paho.org/en/documents/epidemiological-update-measles-americas-region-1-july-2025" target="_blank"&gt;data &lt;/a&gt;from the Pan American Health Organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="RRL4D7GJDNALVFZ4QZEUZ5QSR4" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="RRL4D7GJDNALVFZ4QZEUZ5QSR4" data-testid="article-header"&gt;A costly disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KYL3ETR64ZE3RPCKSW3TRXC2E4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Measles outbreaks require vast personnel, time, dollars and messaging, public health experts say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AQDCXNBYX5FEXEMX3VUKX2GOPA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The 2019 outbreak cost New York City $8.4 million with 550 staff involved in the response, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1912514" target="_blank"&gt;2020 report &lt;/a&gt;in the New England Journal of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TSREL5YMSRAVDBES2XTEOGMAWI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Funding for state and local public health agencies, including immunization programs, has been slashed after increasing during the pandemic. Public health workers have been laid off because of &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/01/hhs-senior-leaders-put-on-leave-nih/" target="_blank"&gt;widespread budget cuts &lt;/a&gt;across the federal health agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WQFEDRCAMZGMDF5EJYH4RWH4VM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Because of the decreased funding, Texas&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;had to &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/04/16/texas-measles-response-funding-cuts/" target="_blank"&gt;pull resources&lt;/a&gt; and staff from other parts of its health department to respond to the outbreak, David Sugerman, a senior CDC scientist, &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/02/20/cdc-vaccine-advisory-panel-meeting-postponed/" target="_blank"&gt;told a committee&lt;/a&gt; of agency vaccine advisers in April.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QUFY5QQ2J5FWXFMCBZTUEIWMBY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In Dallas, which has had one measles case this year, health officials had to lay off 16 immunization staff because of federal cuts, said&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;Philip Huang, director of the county’s &lt;a href="https://www.dallascounty.org/departments/dchhs/" target="_blank"&gt;health and human services &lt;/a&gt;department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="BTAMU3QEIVBTHJKMUIGYBGZ5LU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“The fact that this is occurring at the same time that we are seeing more measles cases in Texas than we have seen in more than 30 years makes absolutely no sense,” Huang said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 10:04:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE9FRG16Q1huYnZOeHE5ZGVlcUtaMmx4M09NeFlkdERTLWhZa1NnMngyWTNXR1ZwV3VyRVRCRHZoU0M1b21QQVF5Sk5pSFlPU201dkxRZ0pTSGh4VE5rVC02UzhVXzJFdlRVQmtoQ3RaRVg5YTI3Ul92b0hsRjV2U00</guid></item><item><title>新英格兰正在经历多年来最糟糕的蜱虫季节之一--《波士顿环球报》 | New England is seeing one of its worst tick seasons in years - The Boston Globe</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxOX3NST2hpbnF4c19IRWdxZW8xd2VXb25fM0pVd3FrSE8xUTFwTk0wMnRSQmtYa2dvQ2NJUVdOZElVWVNwaWlPZTI2UWhFWjRTaHpyOS1ZR0ZPWHE2dUNXazlyRjdoZHlTV0YwWmJWN0lGb29OQ2VMcWNZNldyd01fTmVxbll4RDM2SVVyZHlB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body | gutter_16--desktop gutter_16--tablet paywalled_content
              "&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;New Englanders are used to dealing with a vast assortment of ticks, including Lone Star ticks, deer ticks that carry Lyme disease, and American dog ticks that can transmit Rocky Mountain Spotted Fever. But this season is shaping up to be a particularly bad one, with a surge of tick-borne diseases and tick exposures across the country, especially in the Northeast. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;In June, visits to emergency rooms for tick bites reached their highest levels in at least five years in New England and other nearby states, according to data from the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/data-research/facts-stats/tick-bite-data-tracker.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/data-research/facts-stats/tick-bite-data-tracker.html"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. Last month, 233 out of 100,000 ER visits in the Northeast were for tick bites, nearly double the national average of 118. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The trend is similar in Massachusetts. According to monthly records published by the state’s department of public health, &lt;a href="https://www.mass.gov/lists/monthly-tick-borne-disease-reports#2025-" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.mass.gov/lists/monthly-tick-borne-disease-reports#2025-"&gt;more than 0.6 percent&lt;/a&gt; of visits to an emergency department in May were for tick exposure, up from around 0.4 percent from 2022 to 2024. Visits typically peak in July. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Massachusetts State Epidemiologist Dr. Catherine Brown said that although the data doesn’t capture visits to urgent care and primary care providers for tick exposure, it points to a real increase in interactions between ticks and humans in the state. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“This year is definitely an outlier for us,” Brown said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Thomas Mather, director of the University of Rhode Island’s Center for Vector-Borne Diseases, said that higher levels of tick-borne diseases in New England are mostly caused by higher numbers of blacklegged, or deer tick, nymphs. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The nymphs are around the size of a poppy seed, and about 20 percent of them in the New England region carry Lyme, Mather said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;They thrive in humid weather. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“It’s not related to how warm it is in the winter … if it’s dry in the early spring when they first emerge, they start dying,” Mather said. “Whenever there were low-humidity episodes early in the season in late May and early June, we always had fewer ticks and fewer disease cases.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;All in all, New England is seeing more humidity in the spring and summer now compared to the previous two decades, said Ken Mahan, the Globe’s lead meteorologist.&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;This is a direct result of a warming atmosphere because warmer temperatures hold more moisture. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“When dew points push above 65, that’s when a big change in available moisture can be felt,” said Mahan. “[There has been an] increasing trend in the number of 70-degree dew point days across Boston over the years.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Deer tick populations are also positively correlated with the populations of small rodents and deer, the animals that serve as their most important food sources.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Mather said that the migration of Lone Star ticks, which were formerly common only in the South, over the past five years has been the biggest change in the trend of tick-borne diseases in New England. Mather runs an &lt;a href="https://web.uri.edu/tickencounter/tickspotters/submit/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://web.uri.edu/tickencounter/tickspotters/submit/"&gt;online project called TickSpotter&lt;/a&gt; where people across the country can send in photos of ticks they encounter so that his team of scientists can identify what kind of tick it is. Data from TickSpotter showed a more than 300 percent increase in people encountering these ticks in the past three years. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Rhode Island and Southeastern Massachusetts are right on the edge of the northward expansion of these ticks … Martha’s Vineyard and Narragansett Bay are completely infested with them,” Mather said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Allison Cameron Parry, a professional bodybuilder and mother of two who lives on Martha’s Vineyard, said that almost everyone in her family has Alpha-gal. After giving up meat and dairy, she has had to work harder to supplement those nutrients, which are necessary for her athletic training. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Cameron Parry also said she was worried about her 3-year-old son playing outside. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Long grass literally gives me anxiety … We use a natural spray in our yard, because I have a young child. Unfortunately, the smaller the child, the bigger the risk, because they don’t know to stay out of the bush,” Cameron Parry said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;At a virtual panel held by the Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health last week, experts from Harvard and Boston University spoke about preventing tick-borne diseases. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Richard Pollack, senior environmental public health officer at Harvard University, recommended that people treat their clothes with permethrin, an EPA-registered tick repellent derived from an ingredient&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;found in chrysanthemums. Pollack also advised people to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/after-a-tick-bite/index.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/ticks/after-a-tick-bite/index.html"&gt;pull ticks off of their skin&lt;/a&gt; as soon as they notice them, because ticks attached for 24 to 36 hours can transmit the infection that causes Lyme disease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“You don’t necessarily need to go to the emergency room to have somebody pull the tick off. You might be sitting for six hours, in some cases, before you’re actually seen,” Pollack said. “So just pull the tick off, save it, and then you can delve into what it was later.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Dr. Daniel Solomon, infectious disease specialist at Mass General Brigham, recommends that people take the antibiotic doxycycline within 72 hours of removing a tick that was attached to their skin. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“By the book, the CDC would say that the tick needs to be attached for 36 hours or more [for a patient to take the antibiotic], but we don’t know when ticks attach,” Solomon said. “So if there’s a tick attached, it’s plausible that it could have been on there for a day or more, so take a single dose of doxycycline.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Brown, the state epidemiologist,&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;said the increase in tick exposure should not discourage people from enjoying the outdoors. She recommended people use tick repellents, wear light-colored, long-sleeved clothing so it’s easier to spot and remove ticks, and put their clothes in the dryer on high heat after returning home to kill ticks that are hard to see.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;For pets, Pollack said that there were oral medications for dogs as well as topical ointments that can be applied at the back of the neck once a month to prevent tick bites. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;Patrick and Lily Marvin of Topsfield have three golden retrievers and have noticed more ticks on their dogs this summer when they go for hikes in Beverly. Two summers ago in Nantucket, one of the dogs, Kevin, contracted Lyme disease despite wearing a medicated collar. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“He was lethargic, didn’t want to eat, and would cry whenever we gave him antibiotics,” Patrick said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;He has since recovered, and the Marvins have been proactive about giving their dogs chewable tablets to keep them safe from ticks. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;The speakers at the panel also noted that there are vaccines in the works to fight tick-borne diseases. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lyme/about/lyme-disease-vaccine.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;Lyme disease vaccine developed&lt;/a&gt; by Valneva and Pfizer is in late-stage clinical trials. The University of Massachusetts Medical School’s MassBiologics has also developed an antibody designed to be used as pre-exposure prophylaxis (PrEP) for Lyme disease, but human trials haven’t begun yet. A Lyme disease vaccine called LYMERix had been approved by the FDA in 1998 but was discontinued in 2002 because of a lack of consumer demand. There isn’t a prophylaxis being developed for Alpha-gal yet, though &lt;a href="https://che.engin.umich.edu/2024/08/12/tick-borne-red-meat-allergy-prevented-in-mice-through-new-nanoparticle-treatment/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://che.engin.umich.edu/2024/08/12/tick-borne-red-meat-allergy-prevented-in-mice-through-new-nanoparticle-treatment/"&gt;University of Michigan scientists&lt;/a&gt; tested a nanoparticle treatment that successfully reduced allergies in mice bitten by Lone Star ticks. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;This is welcome news to McCormack. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paragraph | gutter_20_0"&gt;&lt;span class="html-render"&gt;“Ticks are scary because they’re so small and they carry such life-altering diseases,” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="tagline_hr | border_foreground border_half gutter_20_28--mobile
               margin_none text_align_left width_100px"&gt;&lt;p class="tagline | font_primary inline_block  margin_top_32"&gt;Angela Mathew can be reached at &lt;a href="mailto:angela.mathew@globe.com" class="" target="_blank"&gt;angela.mathew@globe.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Boston Globe</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 10:02:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOX3NST2hpbnF4c19IRWdxZW8xd2VXb25fM0pVd3FrSE8xUTFwTk0wMnRSQmtYa2dvQ2NJUVdOZElVWVNwaWlPZTI2UWhFWjRTaHpyOS1ZR0ZPWHE2dUNXazlyRjdoZHlTV0YwWmJWN0lGb29OQ2VMcWNZNldyd01fTmVxbll4RDM2SVVyZHlB</guid></item><item><title>更有效、更合法的大麻将一些人送往医院：纽约市中心在急诊就诊中处于领先地位- Syracuse.com | More potent and legal cannabis sends some to hospital: Central NY leads state in ER visits - Syracuse.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizwFBVV95cUxQZENvd0p3eDl3OV9vWi1ab0V5eHRaeWN6bktfUjJFa1IxSVVBSUVpdWV6am91UU9KZXhoc3lzRFFxMUh5LWJ4X0VsUURrdFBZVnNST3k3Z09TWU8xRldEZnR2VEJtOGhSUHhBLTdNOVg2ck93anpiV0tDbDhtVDJyQWN4NzBENllka1dKV1YtTWgtQWF2Y2wtb09INXZHUVMtOWF3S2licVktbzYzWUdhcWZLTFZMN05pc1hrR1gwLVhKZ0hha29hYlBURDNKLUHSAeMBQVVfeXFMT3dFTmZudFRpRmU4RDNySkh0UVlsTHhOVUFxNk5QZmhnUUI4SDRBMHlwR3otMm5FRldZemtKcFByV3RCVWc5TTFZX2Nsd3BiMzUxVlEwa29mSXNOWVZqUlV4OTBYbGs4aDFoR0RPc2lPNWdVc2MtbG9POVpCV0d0V1I2T2JzeWVidkNMRE5pY3duZF9mUGhoaUhsU0hmUmVkS1RDcmg2RFdDMzI1ek56TmtHMjU0ejFKcjlxb0hfWnd1elFhVlNrT0g3VXNGeU9uRDZsWktIcUJPU3dzb2t2cHI5aTg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="arc-COY5EMNYQJF6VOVT6F3YA5HSLM" class="article h-entry" data-type="article"&gt;&lt;div class="multimedia-main"&gt;&lt;figure class="article__image"&gt;&lt;div class="article__image-wrapper"&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source media="(max-width: 500px)" srcset="https://www.syracuse.com/resizer/v2/JG32KNUPFVCTRJA6PSZNCP2CZE.jpg?auth=99c1bfe32c06b174eef0935633ddd696e4e62ffe7acd6655177ae96fb04170c5&amp;amp;width=500&amp;amp;quality=90 500w"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(max-width: 800px)" srcset="https://www.syracuse.com/resizer/v2/JG32KNUPFVCTRJA6PSZNCP2CZE.jpg?auth=99c1bfe32c06b174eef0935633ddd696e4e62ffe7acd6655177ae96fb04170c5&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;quality=90 800w"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://www.syracuse.com/resizer/v2/JG32KNUPFVCTRJA6PSZNCP2CZE.jpg?auth=99c1bfe32c06b174eef0935633ddd696e4e62ffe7acd6655177ae96fb04170c5&amp;amp;width=1280&amp;amp;quality=90 1280w"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://www.syracuse.com/resizer/v2/JG32KNUPFVCTRJA6PSZNCP2CZE.jpg?auth=99c1bfe32c06b174eef0935633ddd696e4e62ffe7acd6655177ae96fb04170c5&amp;amp;width=500&amp;amp;quality=90" sizes="50vw" fetchpriority="high" loading="eager" alt="Cannabis injuries addressed by Upstate Medical doctor" decoding="async" class="article__image-content"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="article__image-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="article__mm-image-caption-text"&gt;Dr. Deborah Mann, Assistant Professor of Emergency Medicine at Upstate Medical University, has seen scores of people in the ER after consuming too much cannabis. Photo taken on Wednesday, June 11, 2025. (N. Scott Trimble | strimble@syracuse.com)&lt;span class="article__mm-image-credit"&gt;N. Scott Trimble | strimble@syracuse.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   paywall"&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XMRLOOQGJRB53AHD4HPVWPDXOA"&gt;Syracuse, NY – Since New York legalized recreational cannabis, emergency rooms are treating thousands more people for endless vomiting, a racing heart and belief they are dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HPAREY5TGRFILLB3HF5U3P3H34"&gt;Cannabis-related ER visits statewide topped 135,000 in 2023, nearly double the cases from before legalization two years earlier. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="content-blocker-piano " id="content-blocker-piano"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Syracuse.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizwFBVV95cUxQZENvd0p3eDl3OV9vWi1ab0V5eHRaeWN6bktfUjJFa1IxSVVBSUVpdWV6am91UU9KZXhoc3lzRFFxMUh5LWJ4X0VsUURrdFBZVnNST3k3Z09TWU8xRldEZnR2VEJtOGhSUHhBLTdNOVg2ck93anpiV0tDbDhtVDJyQWN4NzBENllka1dKV1YtTWgtQWF2Y2wtb09INXZHUVMtOWF3S2licVktbzYzWUdhcWZLTFZMN05pc1hrR1gwLVhKZ0hha29hYlBURDNKLUHSAeMBQVVfeXFMT3dFTmZudFRpRmU4RDNySkh0UVlsTHhOVUFxNk5QZmhnUUI4SDRBMHlwR3otMm5FRldZemtKcFByV3RCVWc5TTFZX2Nsd3BiMzUxVlEwa29mSXNOWVZqUlV4OTBYbGs4aDFoR0RPc2lPNWdVc2MtbG9POVpCV0d0V1I2T2JzeWVidkNMRE5pY3duZF9mUGhoaUhsU0hmUmVkS1RDcmg2RFdDMzI1ek56TmtHMjU0ejFKcjlxb0hfWnd1elFhVlNrT0g3VXNGeU9uRDZsWktIcUJPU3dzb2t2cHI5aTg</guid></item><item><title>脂肪肝在脸上出现的4种方式-印度时报 | 4 ways fatty liver disease can show up on your face - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi5gFBVV95cUxOQ2VjN0pZbm1WQU91Q29Ob1FmZFUyQ3c0ZFJlSE01N1J1ZDUtSnVsODhidW9HYkY5VUI0ZFg2TlZ3MVdNMzhjVTBSZWtzRmRmYWttRVFPcngwcTJpWDJ3OVRyMmtCMEZVZ0g1U2xlZVI2djVxU3JhNlJ5REhjMTVzekItbDJqNGdfVnBXeXlfb2plbEdETXdXd3pKY01UWE00OUFPWTgxZkdRN1ZRS25ibWZtVGNZTlFLSTA4U1NfZmhRc0Z2MGhwTEw3M1JiSFRGajhIRnNndUdubzcwWlctZ3Y5eUp1UdIB6wFBVV95cUxQTmV1Yk11U3ZLQXdUM0k0RFgxc09YLUkwQlZSbF9HbnFicDY4MTJ6QjVSNmlCN3JKR3dPam9FNjdMM0pSa1NDb1M2dnMzb2pSaGh3RTdraGVjR190bHREaFR1cW90VUNVMlJzbVZyTnBRN05fem9YTWEtbF9xRFhSdzN2YXZ4SHBOMUduQjhmZV9weTJWUk1NV3F5Smw5U0NkM2xZLVdGOGlsWVE1UENDRXVvenBDRGtLS1ZpUDZEekVTUHFWenpsZzdMSkRUX0c3QlV1VENoRGFTbk9wY0NnV3Z2SGZ3OFVlcXVz?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fatty liver disease, particularly Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease (NAFLD), is a growing health concern, affecting an estimated 30.2% of the world's population. Prevalence varies by region, with rates above 40% in the Americas and Southeast Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is Non-Alcoholic Fatty Liver Disease (NAFLD)?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-alcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD) is a condition where excess fat builds up in the liver, not caused by heavy alcohol consumption. It's often linked to obesity, type 2 diabetes, and metabolic syndrome. NAFLD encompasses a spectrum of conditions, from simple fat buildup (NAFL) to more serious inflammation and scarring (NASH).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Often termed the "silent epidemic," NAFLD is often symptomless in its early stages. However, the liver’s strained function can manifest surprisingly on your face. Subtle signs like puffiness, discoloration, dryness, and rashes may seem cosmetic, but they often signal deeper metabolic or inflammatory processes. Recognizing early indicators of fatty liver disease allows you to read the warning signals and seek timely medical attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Puffiness and swelling around the face&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;What you might notice:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A consistently swollen or bloated appearance – especially around the cheeks and under the eyes – sometimes referred to as “fluid retention puffiness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Why it matters:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; As liver function deteriorates, its ability to maintain proper protein synthesis and fluid balance diminishes. This results in capillary leakage and fluid buildup, causing puffiness, particularly around the eyes and cheeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Health note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; If puffiness persists despite normal sleep, low salt intake, and good hydration, consider checking liver function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Skin discoloration: Yellowing, dark circles, and spider veins&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Yellow tint (Jaundice)&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A yellow hue in the skin or the whites of your eyes. This is known as jaundice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Underlying cause:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Bilirubin, a breakdown product of red blood cells, accumulates when the liver cannot process it effectively – a hallmark of advanced liver dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Dark circles and hyperpigmentation&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Persistent dark under‑eye circles or dusky patches, even with adequate rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Possible cause:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Toxin accumulation and impaired blood filtration due to liver strain can manifest as persistent dark circles. Insulin resistance – a common feature of NAFLD – can also cause acanthosis nigricans in skin folds like the neck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Spider veins and rosacea&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Small red lines (spider angiomas) across the cheeks or nose, or facial redness that’s blotchy and persistent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Why it shows:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Impaired estrogen breakdown in liver disease increases blood flow to superficial vessels, causing spider veins. Additionally, inflammatory conditions like rosacea are linked to fatty liver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Acne, oiliness, and mouth rashes&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Unexpected adult acne, oilier skin, especially around the chin or jawline, and rashes or bumps around the mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Connection:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Acne and oily skin:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; When the liver’s detox and hormone regulation falter, androgen and toxin levels build up, leading to hormonal acne.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="71"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Perioral rash:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Chronic zinc deficiency – common in NAFLD – can trigger dermatitis around the mouth, visible as small fluid- or solid-filled bumps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Itching, dryness, and an itchy rash&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Observation:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Constant itching or dryness on the face and facial skin rashes that don’t resolve with usual skincare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="80"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="82"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Medical insight:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Itching (pruritus) is often due to bile salt buildup when liver excretory function is compromised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Dry red patches/rash:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Linked to both nutrient deficiencies and toxin retention. Zinc deficiency may also worsen skin dryness and itching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="88"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="89"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why your face reflects your liver:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The liver is our primary detox and metabolic organ. When overwhelmed – by fat, toxins, or insulin resistance – its inability to filter effectively shows externally. Facial skin, highly visible and sensitive, becomes an early signal. Recognizing these signs allows for proactive intervention through diet, exercise, and medical evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="94"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your face is more than the reflection of your beauty – it can forewarn about your liver. Listen to your skin’s signals, get evaluated, and embrace lifestyle changes early. Early recognition can prompt action – medical guidance, lifestyle adjustments, and targeted nutrition – that often reverses fatty liver and restores both internal health and skin vitality. So, next time you take a close look standing in front of the mirror, listen to your skin – it might be protecting your liver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="96"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt; This article is for informational purposes only and does not substitute professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult a qualified healthcare provider before making any decisions based on this content. If you experience persistent facial changes or health concerns, please seek medical attention promptly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="99"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="100"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;7 Ways to check for fatty liver at home&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="102"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="103"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:29:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5gFBVV95cUxOQ2VjN0pZbm1WQU91Q29Ob1FmZFUyQ3c0ZFJlSE01N1J1ZDUtSnVsODhidW9HYkY5VUI0ZFg2TlZ3MVdNMzhjVTBSZWtzRmRmYWttRVFPcngwcTJpWDJ3OVRyMmtCMEZVZ0g1U2xlZVI2djVxU3JhNlJ5REhjMTVzekItbDJqNGdfVnBXeXlfb2plbEdETXdXd3pKY01UWE00OUFPWTgxZkdRN1ZRS25ibWZtVGNZTlFLSTA4U1NfZmhRc0Z2MGhwTEw3M1JiSFRGajhIRnNndUdubzcwWlctZ3Y5eUp1UdIB6wFBVV95cUxQTmV1Yk11U3ZLQXdUM0k0RFgxc09YLUkwQlZSbF9HbnFicDY4MTJ6QjVSNmlCN3JKR3dPam9FNjdMM0pSa1NDb1M2dnMzb2pSaGh3RTdraGVjR190bHREaFR1cW90VUNVMlJzbVZyTnBRN05fem9YTWEtbF9xRFhSdzN2YXZ4SHBOMUduQjhmZV9weTJWUk1NV3F5Smw5U0NkM2xZLVdGOGlsWVE1UENDRXVvenBDRGtLS1ZpUDZEekVTUHFWenpsZzdMSkRUX0c3QlV1VENoRGFTbk9wY0NnV3Z2SGZ3OFVlcXVz</guid></item><item><title>一位培训师说，您所需要的只是您的体重和每天一分钟来建立健康的锻炼习惯-她的新锻炼挑战今天开始- Fit&amp;Well | A trainer says all you need is your bodyweight and one minute per day to build healthy exercise habits—her new workout challenge starts today - Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAJBVV95cUxQOFp3bXlDZy1fbFVKLW4tUGRUWEV1NFRSdVVNSEdDQ0lzME9scURndlhldjI1QXpfM2t2dDhYZ1doenFfUllPZWR1VlhoWHhkeHY0dlJwUC1Ta1RSYlhOQ0JPbTJEcURIZlVmUzZsZDJqVmcyWU9RNUk4ckZ5R1JPTVJ6MldtN2xXME9BdG1lV3dRRHRVT05aZHBUSWNNcmZqckxXQVpLSTJkdzNGTnNfcThnaTBtVC1sZjcyZUxLV0FkeWwxSHI5VDlrY0diMDZ4N3F6N3FBMllzN24yT0NnR3djcE1EM3ZYQzVtVURjaEdSUGZVT2dLbmdaV0JtaWdXTkVUb0dJeHR5YnljQ0VjbzNnNi1TT3hDc0RfZDdZV2FidHVU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Convenience and accessibility are two essential ingredients in any effective workout regimen, ensuring you’re able to stay the course and see long-term benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that’s exactly what online trainer Rachael Sacerdoti is serving up with her new 14-Day Mini Movement Challenge launching on Monday, July 7 on &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.instagram.com/itssosimple_rs" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.instagram.com/itssosimple_rs" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;her Instagram channel&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She’ll be sharing a quickfire workout every day for two weeks to help you build consistent, sustainable habits with nothing more than your bodyweight. Each routine takes just 60 seconds—and can be done while waiting for the kettle to boil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This 14-day challenge is perfect if you’re short on time but want to feel stronger, more energized and more in control of your day,” she tells &lt;em&gt;Fit&amp;amp;Well&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“No gym. No equipment. Just you and one minute of movement.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One minute of daily exercise might not transform your physique and fitness overnight, but research suggests that even short bursts of vigorous movement can lead to serious long-term health results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's according to a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/59/5/316?rss=1" target="_blank" data-url="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/59/5/316?rss=1" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published earlier this year in the &lt;em&gt;British Journal of Sports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;, which found ultra-short doses of vigorous physical activity—between an average of 1.5 to 4 minutes a day—can be enough to halve cardiovascular risk in middle-aged women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-vPnb2YHgunXhpvV9FzfL46" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-vPnb2YHgunXhpvV9FzfL46 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-this-60-second-fitness-challenge-builds-good-habits"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How this 60-second fitness challenge builds good habits &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sacerdoti is keen to stress that this challenge isn’t about quick fixes and shortcuts. Instead, she says, it’s about consistency, confidence and momentum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Life is full. Most of us are juggling work, family and everything in between,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The idea of carving out 45 minutes for a workout can feel impossible some days. But movement doesn’t have to be all or nothing and this challenge is here to prove that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are multiple benefits, she adds, but primarily the challenge will build and reinforce healthy habits that you can sustain without relying on motivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“[Each workout will] also give your brain and body an instant energy and mood boost, while building confidence through movement repetition, helping you perfect your form.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Day one features four moves: a squat to punch, jumping jacks, standing cross-body crunches and high knees. Perform each move for 15 seconds and you’re done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For added accountability, Sacerdoti encourages you to invite a friend or housemate to join you in the challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As we’re all about keeping things simple, this challenge is here to help people move their bodies daily in a way that feels doable,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you can find just 60 seconds while your coffee brews, you can start building a habit that sticks.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 06:22:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAJBVV95cUxQOFp3bXlDZy1fbFVKLW4tUGRUWEV1NFRSdVVNSEdDQ0lzME9scURndlhldjI1QXpfM2t2dDhYZ1doenFfUllPZWR1VlhoWHhkeHY0dlJwUC1Ta1RSYlhOQ0JPbTJEcURIZlVmUzZsZDJqVmcyWU9RNUk4ckZ5R1JPTVJ6MldtN2xXME9BdG1lV3dRRHRVT05aZHBUSWNNcmZqckxXQVpLSTJkdzNGTnNfcThnaTBtVC1sZjcyZUxLV0FkeWwxSHI5VDlrY0diMDZ4N3F6N3FBMllzN24yT0NnR3djcE1EM3ZYQzVtVURjaEdSUGZVT2dLbmdaV0JtaWdXTkVUb0dJeHR5YnljQ0VjbzNnNi1TT3hDc0RfZDdZV2FidHVU</guid></item><item><title>一位步行专家说，这是您每天保持健康的最少步数（远低于10,000步） - Fit&amp;Well | A walking expert says this is the minimum number of steps you should take every day to stay healthy (and it’s a lot lower than 10,000) - Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgJBVV95cUxQaE41b0F3a0F5VjJhUWNWOEY3aUtGZzJQeXREbmNsczBSWUJQMEpub2x0dDZXZUdhSmtkeFB1TWxiOVlXek9ZV3hVMm82LURrV2tkT1dSRDF3OWhmSHZ2ZEIwbmtrVldQdDlnNEdmNEh1QXowRUpJV3h6MmJPR2kzdEExQ01IWkRhekN2am1Ib2hVRTBpSUdGQXhnVUtZcjdxYUQ0ZzU5bm12ZEg0Vk5mQUpnNGtlOHVMMkF3aEJENEp2Y2t1VlBfOVJiZnZOaVRJbVJfQkd6NVF3Vkp4a045NmNoN0ZXZEpZbU5IYWo3bHRZVXpTSlhEOVQySk9YRWVTVXZWeHRn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all know that regular walking is good for us, but information around step count goals can sometimes be confusing. Most people have heard of the 10,000 steps a day target by now, but a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpub/article/PIIS2468-2667(21)00302-9/fulltext" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpub/article/PIIS2468-2667(21)00302-9/fulltext" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2022 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; found that you can get significant health benefits from fewer steps a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which may leave you wondering, is there a lower limit?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, there are walking experts like Milica McDowell, a doctor of physical therapy, exercise physiologist, and VP of operations for &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://gaithappens.com/" target="_blank" data-url="https://gaithappens.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Gait Happens&lt;/a&gt;, who are more than happy to share their expertise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDowell outlined the figures for me and explained why you should be worried if you’re walking fewer than 2,500 steps a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McDowell’s advice is based on findings from a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2023 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; that appeared in the &lt;em&gt;European Journal of Preventive Cardiology.&lt;/em&gt; The research collected data from more than 250,000 participants over multiple years, meaning the findings can be reliably used to make informed recommendations by experts like McDowell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this information motivates you to walk more to regularly hit that minimum, that’s great, but just make sure to &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/how-do-you-increase-your-step-count-safely-an-exercise-physiologist-weighs-in" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/how-do-you-increase-your-step-count-safely-an-exercise-physiologist-weighs-in"&gt;increase your step count safely&lt;/a&gt;—building up slowly over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-why-2-500-steps"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Why 2,500 steps?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; mentioned above explains that you need to walk a minimum of 2,500-4,000 steps a day to see a reduction in the risk of all-cause mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-GgGtB3NtSUZj35XNFS3srY" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-GgGtB3NtSUZj35XNFS3srY slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;From 2,337 steps a day, the risk of cardiovascular mortality specifically begins to reduce, so McDowell rounds that up to a more memorable 2,500 steps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cardiovascular mortality encompasses all deaths caused by diseases of the cardiovascular system—your heart and blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re walking fewer than 2,500 steps a day, your risk of heart disease, stroke and cardiovascular events is increased. Over 2,500 steps, those risks begin to decrease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“2,500 is the utter basement. If you’re lower than that, you are at risk for all sorts of horrible things,” says McDowell. “So, please get above 2,500. Most people take about 100 steps per minute, so 2,500 is roughly 25 minutes of walking per day.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember that all steps count—even getting something from another room—and this ambient walking, as it known, quickly adds up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-many-steps-should-you-aim-for"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How many steps should you aim for?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout " data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;p class="credit"&gt;(Image credit: Getty Images / sdominick)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 id="3-000-to-4-000-steps-3"&gt;3,000 to 4,000 steps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If 2,500 is the absolute basement and you increase by 500 steps per day to 3,000, your risk of dying goes down 7%,” says McDowell. “If you go up 1,000 steps a day, from 2,500 to 3,500, you reduce your risk of dying by 15%.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37555441/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2023 study&lt;/a&gt; states that from around 3,867 steps a day, the risk of mortality from all causes&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;begins to reduce. This includes deaths from any illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="5-000-steps-3"&gt;5,000 steps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anything under 5,000 steps a day is considered sedentary, with 5,000 to 7,500 classed as low activity. Other benefits kick in at 5,000, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We know that when we hit that 5,000 step mark, it’s very good for managing depression symptoms,” says McDowell. “So if you have a family history or if you’ve struggled with those conditions in the past, there are prescriptive amounts of walking that can reduce the symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://publichealth.jmir.org/2024/1/e48355/" target="_blank" data-url="https://publichealth.jmir.org/2024/1/e48355/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2024 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;JMIR Public Health and Surveillance&lt;/em&gt; found that walking can be used as “an evidence-based intervention for reducing anxiety and depression.” You might not be able to add walking to your list of medications, but a higher step count could make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That’s an important message because we know that anxiety, depression, and a lot of mental health disorders impact people’s longevity,” says McDowell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="6-000-to-8-000-steps-3"&gt;6,000 to 8,000 steps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you’re older than 60, you should be aiming for between 6,000 and 8,000 steps a day for optimal health and longevity, after which the benefits stop increasing with the number of steps you walk. This recommendation is based on data from a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpub/article/PIIS2468-2667(21)00302-9/fulltext" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpub/article/PIIS2468-2667(21)00302-9/fulltext" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;2022 &lt;em&gt;Lancet &lt;/em&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; exploring the benefits of walking for longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When you hit around the 7,000 mark, it’s good for reducing your risk of developing depression in the first place,” says McDowell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="8-000-to-10-000-steps-3"&gt;8,000 to 10,000 steps&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are under 60 years old, the point of diminishing returns mentioned earlier is slightly higher, between 8,000 and 10,000 steps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking 8,000 steps at a moderate pace (about 3mph) will take you about 90 minutes to walk, depending on your stride length.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember, you don’t have to do that 90 minutes all in one go: you can break it up into smaller chunks like three 30-minute walks or three 20-minute walks and one 30-minute walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-how-to-walk-more"&gt;&lt;span&gt;How to walk more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I asked McDowell for her top tip to squeeze more steps into a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I encourage people to do micro walks,” she says. “They can go out for five minutes because most people walk at 100 steps per minute. So even five minutes can make a significant difference. And if we get them to add 10 minutes a day consistently, we’re looking at a significant impact on their longevity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-if-i-do-other-cardio-should-i-still-walk-for-health"&gt;&lt;span&gt;If I do other cardio should I still walk for health? &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of my colleagues do other forms of exercise, and I wondered if doing more cardio exercise means you can skip hitting your steps that day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rowing, biking and swimming are all good for you, but they don’t provide the specific &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/what-are-the-benefits-of-walking" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/features/what-are-the-benefits-of-walking"&gt;benefits of walking&lt;/a&gt;. They surely provide other benefits, but your body needs a certain number of steps per day to achieve optimal health,” says McDowell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-shop-walking-shoes"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Shop walking shoes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're in need of a new pair of walking shoes, our guide to the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.fitandwell.com/buying-guides/best-shoes-for-walking" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/buying-guides/best-shoes-for-walking"&gt;best walking shoes&lt;/a&gt; can help. Are are the top three picks in brief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="product-container hero-product-container product-block-no-wrap"&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="c4e09e1b-da08-4334-9e27-0da7195a6174"&gt;
&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1920-80.jpg.webp 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1600-80.jpg.webp 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1280-80.jpg.webp 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1024-80.jpg.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-768-80.jpg.webp 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-415-80.jpg.webp 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-360-80.jpg.webp 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-320-80.jpg.webp 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK.jpg" alt="Brooks Glycerin Max" class="featured_image" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1920-80.jpg 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1600-80.jpg 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1280-80.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-768-80.jpg 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-415-80.jpg 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-360-80.jpg 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK-320-80.jpg 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)" loading="lazy" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/QNyTvfRWzM7FKevCQKedYK.jpg"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label hero__label"&gt;Best Overall&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="6adbf704-d76c-4c12-bdf4-ce16e9ca5822"&gt;
&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1920-80.jpg.webp 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1600-80.jpg.webp 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1280-80.jpg.webp 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1024-80.jpg.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-768-80.jpg.webp 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-415-80.jpg.webp 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-360-80.jpg.webp 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-320-80.jpg.webp 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL.jpg" alt="Columbia Konos TRS Hiking Shoe" class="featured_image" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1920-80.jpg 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1600-80.jpg 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1280-80.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-768-80.jpg 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-415-80.jpg 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-360-80.jpg 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL-320-80.jpg 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)" loading="lazy" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/yZRkF8fRy5SYXxwDJ7uSxL.jpg"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label hero__label"&gt;Best on a budget&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="93dbdbc6-1654-49d5-9ddb-b1160f324e02"&gt;
&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check&gt;&lt;picture&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1920-80.jpg.webp 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1600-80.jpg.webp 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1280-80.jpg.webp 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1024-80.jpg.webp 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-768-80.jpg.webp 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-415-80.jpg.webp 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-360-80.jpg.webp 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-320-80.jpg.webp 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM.jpg" alt="Hoka Clifton 9" class="featured_image" srcset="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1920-80.jpg 1920w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1600-80.jpg 1600w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1280-80.jpg 1280w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-1024-80.jpg 1024w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-768-80.jpg 768w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-415-80.jpg 415w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-360-80.jpg 360w, https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM-320-80.jpg 320w" sizes="(min-width: 710px) 670px, calc(100vw - 30px)" loading="lazy" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM.jpg" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/wkThthWpzH7T8gxEKoXfQM.jpg"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label hero__label"&gt;Best for Concrete&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxQaE41b0F3a0F5VjJhUWNWOEY3aUtGZzJQeXREbmNsczBSWUJQMEpub2x0dDZXZUdhSmtkeFB1TWxiOVlXek9ZV3hVMm82LURrV2tkT1dSRDF3OWhmSHZ2ZEIwbmtrVldQdDlnNEdmNEh1QXowRUpJV3h6MmJPR2kzdEExQ01IWkRhekN2am1Ib2hVRTBpSUdGQXhnVUtZcjdxYUQ0ZzU5bm12ZEg0Vk5mQUpnNGtlOHVMMkF3aEJENEp2Y2t1VlBfOVJiZnZOaVRJbVJfQkd6NVF3Vkp4a045NmNoN0ZXZEpZbU5IYWo3bHRZVXpTSlhEOVQySk9YRWVTVXZWeHRn</guid></item><item><title>科学家解释为什么随着年龄的增长，时间似乎移动得更快并“飞逝” - Earth.com | Scientists explain why time seems to move faster and 'fly by' as we age - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirwFBVV95cUxPNTNRaXFET2w2MkRxWHRsLTU1Qjl4QllUeWZvQzE2NVJyOElIUE1jUnI5VmlmSDVRV0t6endfZEtLbExDWHJxYnFsVHNQa2FYT1ZGSktFbC1VSlB0R2N6dVV2cE9NdnFBdmNfR2ZHeDhUUlAyRFV6NDVHakc2eXNCUk5wN05LYmpsNTQ3VFdmNU5OQ3dwVXMyd1N4WTN3Skt0bk1JSjBmdUZZc3NaV3Jv?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of us have heard a parent or grandparent say, “Time goes by faster every year,” while shaking their head at how quickly July 4 seems to roll around. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you’re twelve, however, the brain has a different perception of time – the wait for summer vacation feels endless, and a single school day can feel as slow as a traffic jam in August heat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That gap between the child’s long afternoon and the adult’s lightning-fast month isn’t just storytelling, it’s how our brain’s perception of time changes, altering the way it measures all of the moments that make up our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-first-vs-fresh-experiences"&gt;First vs. fresh experiences&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children cram their days with firsts: a first dive into the pool, a first try at long division, a first sleepover away from home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These fresh experiences swarm the brain with new images to file away, stretching the subjective length of a single afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adults, by contrast, tend to replay &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/extreme-heat-impacts-our-daily-routines-and-transportation/"&gt;familiar routines&lt;/a&gt;. With fewer novel snapshots to store, the days collapse into something closer to a highlight reel than a feature film.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to psychologist Marc Wittmann at the Institute for Frontier Areas of Psychology and Mental Health &lt;a href="https://igpp.de/en/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;(IGPP&lt;/a&gt;), the feeling that time accelerates is tightly linked to how much new material our brains record each day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He points out that &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/memory-clutter-speeds-up-aging-in-the-brain/"&gt;memory&lt;/a&gt; and time perception sit on the same neural bench; when one slows, the other shrinks. “Newness” holds the key to this phenomenon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-human-brain-and-time-perception"&gt;Human brain and time perception&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whenever a brain encounters something it has never processed before, a quick surge of attention flags the event as worth keeping. The more flags raised, the thicker the &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/human-brains-use-storage-trick-to-keep-your-memories-in-sequential-order/"&gt;memory log&lt;/a&gt; becomes, and the longer that span later feels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kids, still green to nearly everything, throw flags left and right. A lunchroom joke, a new word in science class, or a game of tag – each registers as its own small chapter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adults often glide through copy-and-paste days that differ only by the date on the calendar. With fewer chapters recorded, the book of any given week reads as a short story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research using immersive virtual reality in 2024 showed that older volunteers underestimated simple time intervals by roughly 15 percent, highlighting how novelty &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S096800042300302X" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sharpens the inner clock&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Routine doesn’t just compress the past; it also drains the present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies tracking holiday seasons in several countries found that people who stuck to predictable daily rhythms felt that Christmas or Ramadan arrived sooner every year, while those who sprinkled in new activities reported a slower march toward the festivities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-brain-processing-speed-linked-with-time"&gt;Brain processing speed linked with time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every sensation has to travel from eye or ear to cortex. In youngsters, those &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/speech-pattern-wfd-that-is-a-clear-indication-a-person-is-in-cognitive-decline/"&gt;neural highways&lt;/a&gt; are short and well-paved. As bodies grow, the routes lengthen, and the conduction speed though still quick can’t match its earlier zip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add natural age-related slowing of signal processing and the brain starts sampling the world less often each second.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fewer samples mean fewer “ticks” on the subjective stopwatch, so a morning meeting seems to vanish faster for a forty-year-old than for a fourth grader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This sampling &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-link-pupil-dilation-to-brains-working-memory-levels/"&gt;shows up in the eyes&lt;/a&gt;. Our eyes jerk from point to point in rapid saccades, pausing in brief fixations while the brain grabs a visual frame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young, rested eyes squeeze in more fixations per minute. Older or fatigued eyes lag, offering the brain fewer still frames to stitch together. With a thinner film strip, the projection of the day speeds along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists studying eye movements liken perception to a flipbook. Each fixation is a page; flip them fast enough and you see smooth action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When fixations slow, the flipbook loses pages. Motion still appears, but the storyline gets choppy, and, in recall, it shortens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-sleep-and-alertness"&gt;Sleep and alertness&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A single night of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/sleep-can-boost-memory-in-a-surprising-way/"&gt;good sleep&lt;/a&gt; can pull the brake on runaway days. When neurons are well-rested, they fire faster, notice more, and form clearer memories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Athletes know the flip side: stepping onto the field after too little shut-eye makes the whole match blur. The plays happen, but the mind records only a highlight or two before the final whistle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Students grinding through an all-nighter meet the same fate – an exam that seems to finish moments after it starts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/what-is-the-best-treatment-for-excessive-daytime-sleepiness/"&gt;Chronic fatigue&lt;/a&gt; magnifies the effect. Continually short-changing rest lowers baseline alertness, trimming snapshots day after day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over months, life can feel like it’s slipping through the cracks, not because the clock sped up but because the recorder slowed down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/mind-and-mood/dopamine-the-pathway-to-pleasure" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Dopamine&lt;/a&gt;, a neurotransmitter tied to motivation and time estimation, also dips with sleep debt, further warping the &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/psychology/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2024.1364166/full" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;sense of duration&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Endless feeds promise variety, yet most algorithms serve look-alike posts. Swipe through video after video of the same dance trend, and the brain barely registers a change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hours evaporate while the memory log remains nearly blank. Compound that with the blue-light-induced bedtime delay, and you have a double punch: fewer snapshots captured and fewer hours slept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cutting back on passive scrolling or swapping it for an activity with genuine novelty – trying a new recipe, learning a chord on guitar – feeds the brain more distinct moments. Those moments stretch subjective time, turning a blur of an evening into something that feels full.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-with-age-comes-responsibility"&gt;With age comes responsibility&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond slower processing, adults juggle long lists of responsibilities. Focus narrows to tasks at hand – emails, errands, budgets – scanning less of the environment for new input. Novelty drops, and subjective days shorten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.tiaa.org/public/institute/publication/2023/young-adults-their-attitudes-and-outlook-toward-retirement-and-the-future" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;A 2023 survey&lt;/a&gt; comparing young adults with retirees found that the older group reported the year as “rushing by” nearly twice as often, linking the feeling to the predictability of daily routines rather than to health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even so, not every senior feels the rush. Researchers tracking so-called “&lt;a href="https://www.nm.org/healthbeat/healthy-tips/4-habits-super-agers" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;super-agers&lt;/a&gt;” note that those who keep learning new skills and staying socially engaged maintain sharper senses of time, along with stronger memory performance. Variety keeps the brain’s camera clicking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-use-your-brain-to-slow-time-perception"&gt;Use your brain to slow time perception&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s the good news – the tools to lengthen your days fit into ordinary life. Go to bed on a schedule that honors the seven-to-nine-hour rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plan at least one activity each week that forces you out of autopilot: a different jogging route, a museum you’ve never visited, a new language app.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While doing it, pay close attention to sights, sounds, and textures. Engagement packs extra snapshots into the mental album.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay curious daily. Swap a lunchtime scroll for a short walk and notice five things you’ve never clocked before – a mural, a bird call, the scent of a bakery vent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those micro-discoveries add pages to the flipbook, expanding the subjective afternoon. Over time, the habit can “thicken” the memory book that tells the story of a year, making December feel like it belongs twelve full months away, right where the calendar says it should be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/european-review/article/why-the-days-seem-shorter-as-we-get-older/2CB8EC9B0B30537230C7442B826E42F1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;European Review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 23:45:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxPNTNRaXFET2w2MkRxWHRsLTU1Qjl4QllUeWZvQzE2NVJyOElIUE1jUnI5VmlmSDVRV0t6endfZEtLbExDWHJxYnFsVHNQa2FYT1ZGSktFbC1VSlB0R2N6dVV2cE9NdnFBdmNfR2ZHeDhUUlAyRFV6NDVHakc2eXNCUk5wN05LYmpsNTQ3VFdmNU5OQ3dwVXMyd1N4WTN3Skt0bk1JSjBmdUZZc3NaV3Jv</guid></item><item><title>这棵流行树的叶子可以改善血液循环并防止血栓- Earth.com | Leaves from this popular tree may improve circulation and prevent blood clots - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxONnBNaDY3VV9zOVd4M2tWNUJkLUE0YVFVb1QtZmR6Zjg1T0ZvX2dBbDNudmhxSjJmLWJZWnBtemhyd2wzaDA0WXprOGxRSktmRnZIWjF3NDQ5dlg3aXFRcUI1U2o4VTJVQmRtd0Q4Y0lucU05UHNvT2tLcHBEaFZEWUtvcnFwbXZROTJQYkxtYlpvdFRfMFNhSm5KZWlrMWND?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Varicose veins bulge and twist across the calves of up to 30 percent of adults, a reminder that blood sometimes pools instead of flowing home to the heart. When sluggish blood flow lingers, clots can form and, in rare cases, travel to the lungs or brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Centuries ago physicians in China brewed teas from &lt;a href="https://www.missouribotanicalgarden.org/PlantFinder/PlantFinderDetails.aspx?kempercode=z990" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ginkgo biloba&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; leaves to sharpen memory. Today researchers wonder whether the same ginkgo leaves might support weary leg veins and cut the risk of small, yet dangerous, blood clots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-why-circulation-can-falter"&gt;Why circulation can falter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blood rising from the feet must fight gravity, and faulty valves can leave veins stretched and valves leaky. The lingering pressure distends vein walls, encourages &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/fasting-helps-the-body-fight-inflammation-and-chronic-diseases/"&gt;inflammation&lt;/a&gt;, and slows platelet aggregation, the first step toward clotting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slow venous return creates the setting for deep‑vein thrombosis as well as the aching, throbbing symptoms many patients feel after a day of standing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That overlap has pushed vascular specialists toward plant‑based compounds that might tone the vein wall and limit sticky platelets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After logging stroke cases at Xuanwu Hospital in Beijing, neurologist &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/scientific-contributions/Xiangqian-Huang-2265510495" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Xiangqian Huang&lt;/a&gt; of &lt;a href="https://ccmu.cucas.cn/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Capital Medical University&lt;/a&gt; began probing ginkgo’s effects on clot behavior in the brain, work that now informs leg‑vein research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-ginkgo-leaves-and-blood-flow"&gt;Ginkgo leaves and blood flow&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ginkgo extract made &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/drinking-from-plastic-bottles-linked-to-high-blood-pressure-and-heart-problems/"&gt;blood platelets&lt;/a&gt; less sticky when triggered by one type of chemical but didn’t have much effect when triggered by another. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Xiangqian Huang and the team also noticed that blood took slightly longer to clot after treatment with the extract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The leaf contains natural compounds that seem to interact with enzymes responsible for forming clots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a 2025 animal &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/40462336/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;, researchers found that ginkgo reduced damage inside blood vessels in rats with clotting problems and slightly increased the time it took for their blood to clot. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-insights-from-a-beijing-stroke-ward"&gt;Insights from a Beijing stroke ward&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huang’s real‑world study followed 99 patients for five days. Among stroke survivors who received ginkgo plus baby &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/daily-aspirin-use-strongly-tied-to-colorectal-cancer-prevention/"&gt;aspirin&lt;/a&gt;, arachidonic‑acid platelet aggregation fell more than in peers on aspirin alone, while major bleeding did not rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minor nose or gum bleeds surfaced in four of thirty‑three combination patients, a signal that enhanced anticoagulation deserves monitoring. No severe hemorrhages occurred, suggesting short‑term safety when doses stay low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The design also enrolled participants with internal jugular venous stenosis, a group whose &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/artificial-sweetener-erythritol-sugar-substitute-linked-to-blood-clots-heart-disease/"&gt;clots&lt;/a&gt; mirror those in leg veins. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In that arm ginkgo alone curbed blood platelet stickiness within 24 hours, and the effect held steady through day five.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-aspirin-ginkgo-and-blood-clots"&gt;Aspirin, ginkgo, and blood clots&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A team of &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/17982321/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;scientists&lt;/a&gt; led by &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/profiles/christopher-gardner" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Christopher Gardner&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Stanford Department of Medicine&lt;/a&gt; examined the potential adverse effects of concomitant aspirin and Ginkgo biloba on blood platelet function after giving the duo to older adults for four weeks. The worry was that the herbs might blunt or boost common drugs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gardner and colleagues detected no dangerous bleeding, yet laboratory tests showed additive platelet inhibition, suggesting that low‑dose pairings could protect high‑risk patients who cannot tolerate stronger pharmaceuticals. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors, however, should adjust regimens around surgeries or when other blood thinners enter the mix.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the leaf targets arachidonic‑acid pathways that aspirin already touches, the partnership makes pharmacologic sense. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, anyone taking nonsteroidal anti‑inflammatory drugs should discuss timing and dosage to avoid stacking identical mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-helping-legs-feel-lighter"&gt;Helping legs feel lighter&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deep veins are not the only place where endothelial cells detach under strain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a classic double‑blind trial, scientists found that a capsule combining ginkgo, troxerutin, and heptaminol cut circulating endothelial cell counts by 14.5 percent in patients with chronic varicose veins, placebo achieved only 8.4 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK26848/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Endothelial cells&lt;/a&gt; are early barometers of vein injury, so their decline hints at real structural healing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants also reported reduced ankle swelling and night cramps, benefits echoed by later Russian and Italian studies that tracked leg circumference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Modern &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/home/phl" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;phlebology&lt;/a&gt; still relies on compression stockings and laser ablation, yet many sufferers ask for gentler first steps. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A standardized ginkgo formula, already licensed for vascular disorders in parts of Europe, may slot neatly between lifestyle changes and invasive procedures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-blood-clot-prevention-with-ginkgo"&gt;Blood clot prevention with ginkgo&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yang’s rat data showed lighter &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cause-of-strokes-cervical-artery-dissection-has-increased-400-percent-since-2005/"&gt;clots&lt;/a&gt;, higher nitric‑oxide levels, and longer clotting times after gavage with 60 milligrams per kilogram of extract. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nitric oxide relaxes vessel walls and counters platelet stickiness, aligning with human data from stroke and vein clinics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26030402/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Network‑pharmacology&lt;/a&gt; maps place AKT1, ALB, and TNF at the center of ginkgo’s target web. Those same genes regulate inflammation, suggesting that the tree’s reach extends beyond platelets to the very lining of our veins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because oxidative stress weakens venous valves, the antioxidant side of the extract warrants equal attention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flavonols scavenge free radicals, potentially slowing the progressive dilation that makes early spider veins blossom into rope‑like cords.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-talking-with-your-doctor"&gt;Talking with your doctor&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ginkgo supplements crowd store shelves, yet extracts used in clinical trials are highly standardized. Look for&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/12757407/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt; EGb 761&lt;/a&gt; or products specifying at least 24 percent flavonol glycosides and 6 percent terpene lactones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients on warfarin, &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/JAHA.120.017559" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;direct oral anticoagulants&lt;/a&gt;, or upcoming dental work should alert their clinicians before starting any form of ginkgo. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health professionals may stagger doses, check clotting labs, or advise pausing the herb to keep bleeding risk low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those with aching calves and a family history of clots, discussing ginkgo as an adjunct to compression or low‑intensity exercise could make sense. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Evidence remains preliminary, yet the plant’s dual action on platelets and vein walls is steadily moving from bench to bedside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future multicenter trials ought to track long‑term safety and measure quality‑of‑life changes such as heaviness, itch, and nightly restlessness. If findings stay positive, an ancient tree might soon earn a modern role in vascular medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11803947/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Thrombosis Journal&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read?&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt; Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt; EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt; Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 21:11:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxONnBNaDY3VV9zOVd4M2tWNUJkLUE0YVFVb1QtZmR6Zjg1T0ZvX2dBbDNudmhxSjJmLWJZWnBtemhyd2wzaDA0WXprOGxRSktmRnZIWjF3NDQ5dlg3aXFRcUI1U2o4VTJVQmRtd0Q4Y0lucU05UHNvT2tLcHBEaFZEWUtvcnFwbXZROTJQYkxtYlpvdFRfMFNhSm5KZWlrMWND</guid></item><item><title>科学家逆转小鼠帕金森症状： “我们对成功感到惊讶” -好消息网络 | Scientists Reverse Parkinson’s Symptoms in Mice: ‘We were astonished by the success’ - Good News Network</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxPeUpQNElWaHVYQWQ2V2xObEZTcFRzTVZORFVHRDhhdFZkQUZZRzFET295REFSeG55V2dXbi0zUTF0Z0hGRzdpTU8xODl5RlktSkd0UW5SN0pKVndvSU81X0JjNENOMTFndGg3LTdORkZ0MzZKXzlnN0VUWkhWaGNOZThSNEY0Snc4S0VQRC1CVEcyNzBQNDNjNThfSS15TzZfcGdoc3VoT01IaDUzR00wWWprdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_157158" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-157158" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-157158" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets.jpg 1400w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets-530x282.jpg 530w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets-326x174.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets-1024x546.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets-768x409.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets-696x371.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets-1068x569.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets-788x420.jpg 788w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/01/doctor-brain-medicine-alzheimers-public-domain-anna-shvets-600x320.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 1400px) 100vw, 1400px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-157158" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;By Anna Shvets&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Groundbreaking research by the University of Sydney has identified a new brain protein involved in the development of Parkinson’s disease and a way to modify it, paving the way for future treatments for the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the aim of finding new treatments to slow or stop its progression, the research team has spent more than a decade studying the biological mechanisms underpinning the condition—which is the second most common neurological condition after dementia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2017, they identified for the first time the presence of an abnormal form of a protein—called SOD1—in the brains of patients diagnosed with Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Normally, the SOD1 protein provides protective benefits to the brain, but in Parkinson’s patients it becomes faulty, causing the protein to clump and damage brain cells.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The newest study by the same team, led by Professor Kay Double from the Brain and Mind Centre, &lt;a href="https://actaneurocomms.biomedcentral.com/articles/10.1186/s40478-025-02048-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;was just published&lt;/a&gt; in Acta Neuropathologica Communications. It found that targeting the faulty SOD1 protein with a drug treatment using copper improved the motor function in mice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We hoped that by treating this malfunctioning protein, we might be able to improve the Parkinson-like symptoms in the mice we were treating – but even we were astonished by the success of the intervention,” said Professor Double&lt;a href="https://www.sydney.edu.au/news-opinion/news/2025/06/26/targeting-newly-identified-brain-protein-brings-hope-of-new-parkinsons-disease-treatment.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; in a media release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“All the mice we treated saw a dramatic improvement in their motor skills, which is a really promising sign that it could be effective in treating people who have Parkinson disease too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ALSO CHECK OUT:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a title="First Advanced Parkinson’s Patient to Walk Again with New Spinal Implant, ‘It’s Incredible’" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/first-advanced-parkinsons-patient-to-walk-again-with-new-spinal-implant-its-incredible/" rel="bookmark"&gt;First Advanced Parkinson’s Patient to Walk Again with New Spinal Implant, ‘It’s Incredible’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study involved two groups of mice with Parkinson-like symptoms. One group was treated with a special copper supplement for three months, while the other received a placebo.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Throughout the study (which was partly funded by the Michael J. Fox Foundation), the mice receiving only the placebo saw a decline in their motor symptoms. The mice receiving the special copper supplement, however, did not develop movement problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The results were beyond our expectations,” said Prof. Double. “They suggest, once further studies are carried out, this treatment approach could slow the progression of Parkinson’s disease in humans.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At present there is no known cure and only limited treatments for Parkinson’s disease, which is a degenerative disorder in which dopamine-producing cells in the brain die, leading to a range of symptoms including tremors, muscle stiffness, slow movement and impaired balance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But researchers hope understanding the causes of the disease will lead to improved treatments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MORE GOOD NEWS FOR PATIENTS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
• &lt;a title="Severe Shaking in Parkinson’s Patient Calms Down in Just 6 Days With New Drug –Watch the Transformation" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/severe-shaking-for-parkinsons-patient-is-completely-ended-in-just-6-days-with-new-drug-watch/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Severe Shaking in Parkinson’s Patient Calms Down in Just 6 Days With New Drug –Watch the Transformation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
• &lt;a title="Parkinson’s Disease Symptoms ‘Reversed’ by Mini Implant Bringing Hope" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/parkinsons-disease-symptoms-reversed-by-mini-implant-bringing-hope/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Parkinson’s Disease Symptoms ‘Reversed’ by Mini Implant Bringing Hope&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“As our understanding of Parkinson’s disease grows, we are finding that there are many factors contributing to its development and progression in humans – and faulty forms of the SOD1 protein is likely one of them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Just as researchers found with HIV, Parkinson’s disease is a complex condition that likely requires multiple interventions. A single treatment may have a small effect when used alone but, when combined with other interventions, contributes to a significant overall improvement in health.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers’ next step is to identify the best approach to targeting the faulty SOD1 protein in a clinical trial, which could be the start of a new therapy to slow the development of Parkinson’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CELEBRATE THE BREAKTHROUGH By Sharing on Social Media…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 18:00:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxPeUpQNElWaHVYQWQ2V2xObEZTcFRzTVZORFVHRDhhdFZkQUZZRzFET295REFSeG55V2dXbi0zUTF0Z0hGRzdpTU8xODl5RlktSkd0UW5SN0pKVndvSU81X0JjNENOMTFndGg3LTdORkZ0MzZKXzlnN0VUWkhWaGNOZThSNEY0Snc4S0VQRC1CVEcyNzBQNDNjNThfSS15TzZfcGdoc3VoT01IaDUzR00wWWprdw</guid></item><item><title>根据胃肠病学家的说法，排名第一的高蛋白零食可以改善肠道健康- EatingWell | The #1 High-Protein Snack for Better Gut Health, According to a Gastroenterologist - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE5KNVREaFN0eUFLbGliR3F6UWpaU3pCU1ZvaDd1OFVEMVk4c3ZWRy10S1VtSW5GeHk5a0FUWHFMNElJUEFmZ0ZvOVRCMTZBTHpObDk3S2RFeVlNV0xfeGtmRDB5b2pZeFJvQUMxUEpHYkFmajBmVzJxLUFTOVdDbU0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Snacks rich in protein and fiber help curb hunger, support digestion and boost fullness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Edamame delivers protein, fiber and gut-friendly benefits in one easy and budget-friendly snack.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Choosing whole-food snacks like edamame may improve gut health and support weight management.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; We are a nation of snackers: Most U.S. adults &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/7893359/easy-healthy-snacks-for-anytime-of-day/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;eat at least one snack every day&lt;/a&gt;. Snacking is so significant, data suggests snacks contribute to approximately 20% of most adults’ total calorie intake per day.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It isn’t hard to find a snack that tastes good. From chips to chocolate, a tasty nosh is easy to come by. But it can be challenging to find the perfect snack that balances both taste and nutrition. Specifically, finding a snack that checks two important boxes—high in protein and &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8021156/foods-to-improve-gut-health-overnight/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;good for gut health&lt;/a&gt;—can feel like a tough task.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In this article, we'll explore a gastroenterologist’s top pick for a high-protein snack that is fantastic for your gut health—and tastes great to boot! Whether you're looking for something to fuel your workout, tide you over between meals or simply improve your digestive system, we've got you covered.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-choosing-healthy-snacks"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Choosing Healthy Snacks &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Choosing the right snacks can offer many potential health perks, from helping alleviate potential digestive health concerns to adding important nutrients to your diet.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “The key is to choose snacks that actually empower our health rather than the ones that zap our energy and ruin our afternoon,” says &lt;a href="https://zoe.com/learn/dr-will-bulsiewicz" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Will Bulsiewicz, M.D.&lt;/a&gt;, a gastroenterologist and U.S. medical director of Zoe.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The perfect way to accomplish this? Bulsiewicz&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;says to look for choices that are considered both high in protein and fiber. “This is the ideal combination for satiation, meaning less 'hangry' with a happy, satisfied tummy. Both protein and fiber &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8053298/best-nutrient-for-weight-loss-according-to-gastroenterologist/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;stimulate GLP-1&lt;/a&gt; release, the natural version of Ozempic,” he says. How so? Fiber feeds gut bacteria, producing anti-inflammatory chemicals that stimulate the release of this natural hormone in our bodies, Bulsiewicz explains.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Published research conducted by Zoe shows that consuming lower-quality, ultraprocessed snacks that have little fiber and protein, like candy or cookies, is associated with higher triglycerides, worse blood sugar control and more hunger. Snacks that are minimally processed, like fresh fruit and vegetables, nuts and seeds, however, had the opposite effect, says Bulsiewicz. “This study proves that snacking is in no way bad, but when you snack you want to choose high-quality snacks,” he says.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-best-snack-is-edamame"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The Best Snack is Edamame &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;br&gt;When looking for a high-protein snack that supports gut health, there are some snacks that check both of those boxes. When we asked Bulsiewicz for his top pick, he was happy to share that &lt;strong&gt;edamame&lt;/strong&gt; is the best high-protein snack for better gut health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Why edamame? The young, tender soybeans are “inexpensive, delicious and snacking on a cup delivers 18 grams of protein and 8 grams of fiber tightly squeezed into just 188 calories,” Bulsiewicz says. He also points out that this snack may help keep you full to support weight-management goals because of its protein and fiber content.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; His go-to way for preparing edamame is to purchase frozen edamame pods, pour them into a microwave-safe bowl with 2 tablespoons of water at the bottom, seal it and microwave for 3 to 4 minutes. “Add a sprinkle of salt for flavor. You can go with sea salt, but next level would be flaky Maldon salt,” he recommends. Dusting them with &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/262111/edamame-with-aleppo-pepper/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Aleppo pepper &lt;/a&gt;is a nice option, too. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Preliminary evidence suggests that soy protein may have noteworthy effects on gut health. For example, research on animals showed positive effects on the gut microbiota when soy protein was consumed.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Data on postmenopausal women also found that intake of soy isoflavones (compounds found in soybeans that have estrogen-like properties) may be linked to beneficial changes in gut bacteria.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Edamame can also be enjoyed as a hummus or as an ingredient in falafel. An alternative option is dry-roasted edamame, which can be found in a variety of flavors prepackaged in the snack aisle in many stores. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-other-snack-ideas"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Other Snack Ideas &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Try these other high-protein, gut-friendly snacks:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/best-nut-to-lower-cholesterol-11756216" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Almonds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: “A half-cup of almonds packs in 15 grams of protein and 8 grams of fiber, not to mention the healthy fats and minerals,” says Bulsiewicz. Research shows that, when digesting almonds, the body produces butyrate, a short-chain fatty acid that serves as the primary energy source for colon cells, promoting a healthy colon lining.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8015607/greek-yogurt-benefits/" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Greek yogurt&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/strong&gt; Packed with &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8037462/benefits-of-taking-probiotics/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;probiotics&lt;/a&gt;, Greek yogurt is not only high in protein but also excellent for gut health.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/is-hummus-good-for-you-8659418" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;Hummus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Made from chickpeas, hummus provides both protein and fiber, promoting a healthy gut.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7664397/what-is-kefir/" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="5"&gt;Kefir&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Similar to yogurt, kefir is a probiotic-rich drink that also contains protein.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/chia-seed-pudding-8430793" link-destination-recommendation="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="6"&gt;Chia seed pudding&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: Made from chia seeds, this pudding is full of protein, fiber and omega-3 fatty acids, which all contribute to gut health.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Incorporating edamame into your diet can be a highly beneficial snack choice for promoting gut health while providing a substantial protein boost. By choosing nutrient-dense foods like edamame, you can satisfy your hunger and support your overall well-being. Embracing a holistic approach to gut health means considering all aspects of your diet, and making mindful snack choices is an excellent step toward a healthier lifestyle.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 18:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE5KNVREaFN0eUFLbGliR3F6UWpaU3pCU1ZvaDd1OFVEMVk4c3ZWRy10S1VtSW5GeHk5a0FUWHFMNElJUEFmZ0ZvOVRCMTZBTHpObDk3S2RFeVlNV0xfeGtmRDB5b2pZeFJvQUMxUEpHYkFmajBmVzJxLUFTOVdDbU0</guid></item><item><title>美联社将推出人工智能驱动的蚊虫控制计划--大安得拉邦 | AP to launch AI-driven mosquito control programme.. - Great Andhra</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOYmdnVmhGaHlEeV9iaTl4Rzc1eUtZZkxlVDFjaXlmei1taEF4YnJ0WWV0Ul94RWI1TU5QQWsxM1ZsQ1dSOHk2OUJ1OU1NV0VDYUFxUHhaallrbDBGeE9fek1IOFRnVU00cG50eEJFd0JGUFVydzJrWTJycTlQOXMtTEZMVGlKekRFcE55b3M4UlFlNE1hbHY2Snk1NzJQU2RLWkZoeE1td3PSAZ4BQVVfeXFMTm0tQWNEX3E2RXhWRHE2TTVrQk5pUVdOU0RhZHN0MnNOZDAydmd1cDIybEFjVWhjOGhaZVNkRTViV0x4ZFRmWmt1ZWhDUlZGSTdKNkQ3UUVwMHg5aHFKb3RLM1ZjY19XUUdVRG9DODFfXzY3U0s3YzJ6ay1rbDJFY3BHVUZRVFhjWEtGYVFWa2xvOHhrZ3UxY3ktZGRaQlE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="unselectable"&gt;

					
						
												&lt;p&gt;Andhra Pradesh's Municipal Administration and Urban Development Department is launching a focused "smart mosquito control" programme using deep technology to check vector-borne diseases. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Artificial Intelligence-powered Smart Mosquito Surveillance System (SMoSS) will be launched on a pilot basis at 66 locations in six major municipal corporations in the state, the department announced on Sunday.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SMoSS will primarily safeguard public health by curbing the dreaded mosquito menace, and it will also reduce operational burden on civic staff and cut costs of Urban Local Bodies, it said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The programme will be closely and effectively monitored with the help of Internet-of-Things like drones, sensors, heat maps and traps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pilot will soon be launched at 16 locations in the Greater Visakhapatnam Municipal Corporation, four in Kakinada, five in Rajamahendravaram, 28 in Vijayawada, seven in Nellore, and six in Kurnool.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MAUD's Principal Secretary, S. Suresh Kumar, and Director of Municipal Administration, P. Sampath Kumar, recently studied the AI-powered SMoSS, developed by a private agency, to assess its efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;AI-powered smart mosquito sensors will be installed in key mosquito-prone zones in the selected urban local bodies as part of the pilot project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These smart sensors will detect the mosquito species, their gender, density, temperature and humidity. SMoSS will trigger automatic alerts when mosquito density crosses a threshold level in any particular area. Data thus generated will be continuously streamed to a central server and visualised on a real-time dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"This will enable close monitoring and ensure prompt fumigation in the affected areas in a data-driven approach for effective control of mosquitoes instead of the present ‘blind spraying’ process that has little impact. The IoT sensors will monitor mosquito density and guide the targeted activity," an official said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use of drones for spraying the larvicide would result in an efficient application by covering large areas with less chemical use, time, and cost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evidence-based spraying, prevention of chemical overuse and promotion of public health safety are the key elements in the whole operation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"We will be outsourcing the operations completely to specialised agencies, and payment will be result-oriented by fixing operational accountability. Complaints, if any, from the citizens and field-level functionaries will be tracked via mobile applications (Vector Control and Puramitra),” they said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A system is also being put in place for reporting daily on cases like malaria, dengue and chikungunya from hospitals. Based on the data, mosquito hotspots will be identified for focused action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Special action plans are being drawn for scheduled fogging and larval treatment in hotspots, the officials added.&lt;/p&gt;





							
							&lt;p class="vuukle-powerbar"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							


						 &lt;/div&gt;
						 &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Great Andhra</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 15:01:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOYmdnVmhGaHlEeV9iaTl4Rzc1eUtZZkxlVDFjaXlmei1taEF4YnJ0WWV0Ul94RWI1TU5QQWsxM1ZsQ1dSOHk2OUJ1OU1NV0VDYUFxUHhaallrbDBGeE9fek1IOFRnVU00cG50eEJFd0JGUFVydzJrWTJycTlQOXMtTEZMVGlKekRFcE55b3M4UlFlNE1hbHY2Snk1NzJQU2RLWkZoeE1td3PSAZ4BQVVfeXFMTm0tQWNEX3E2RXhWRHE2TTVrQk5pUVdOU0RhZHN0MnNOZDAydmd1cDIybEFjVWhjOGhaZVNkRTViV0x4ZFRmWmt1ZWhDUlZGSTdKNkQ3UUVwMHg5aHFKb3RLM1ZjY19XUUdVRG9DODFfXzY3U0s3YzJ6ay1rbDJFY3BHVUZRVFhjWEtGYVFWa2xvOHhrZ3UxY3ktZGRaQlE</guid></item><item><title>加重背心是否值得炒作？ -《西雅图时报》 | Are weighted vests worth the hype? - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPbjUyMVBJT0lCYko3V0N2ZjVSbTBCMFNKVzRVVDBUTDJSQU1KTXhkR3hMSHJITDBEYUpYX2tBNy16c1FoZk1XbFdxZnFoY1VDVmlnZV9CbVo0TEFneW9EeUUyZEhDamlnaktZZDQ5SWdoLVdYMTVFWFJrQ0hzVmxYaVpPNmdJRFN0cDdJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPbjUyMVBJT0lCYko3V0N2ZjVSbTBCMFNKVzRVVDBUTDJSQU1KTXhkR3hMSHJITDBEYUpYX2tBNy16c1FoZk1XbFdxZnFoY1VDVmlnZV9CbVo0TEFneW9EeUUyZEhDamlnaktZZDQ5SWdoLVdYMTVFWFJrQ0hzVmxYaVpPNmdJRFN0cDdJ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Are weighted vests worth the hype?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxQNThNVDRKWnpLMzNhOFVfYVJxVVFLY3l1ZXV1V2FrNDVKdWxXX2hHWm9aZjgzSUl5LUZOTWNyQmhaREZFSC1yT0hVcnVpazJqWXZJNE1DaGxMWDRQbE9Edm44TENOeWlLOEF3YlNFSWJVNE5GZXRzaW1JbWswNi1jYjB1ZXhQZzM0dXlvSnNZWXl2SWhuckc1VNIBVEFVX3lxTE05VzVkVnpHZGZsMTJ0Q1FPUWVja3NMWHVSc0tQcl8zUnJvbGZodG1HSVNzbmk2YldnWUlUaEl5QU4zWVRvWEtUTEhHSkFDRzk4VDZESw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;How a Trainer Uses His Daily Walks to Build Bone Strength&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;TODAY.com&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxNMVU4LUZRY2hyWllOWW52UGk5NXBkNkRSbkx0QnBlRGJLWEpHVy1fbWhXSHJvUUtIcFZQWmJJc1ZRbjNFYzFKRXBuaDNXN3RENUl0dk5BM21XSUt1Q1c0LVM2OTk2dlFaVGdUSElVS2pXV0J4TkJ2QkMtWmpkbHdvTTVGSG5aUmFHSjk0?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Wake Forest study finds weighted vests, resistance training doesn't limit bone loss in older adults&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Winston-Salem Journal&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi4AFBVV95cUxOeWQwV0xvTkdZdzlxdl8tdzdUcEM5ZlBQTGxZaHJaRDAtV3dER2Rpd1U0WTlfZmhKOEJoN3hycXUtOFRqMzA5Zk9oSVI3RWpzc045Mi1XSWlLSDdzSFoyalhwdk1tMVJ6c1dIRHJwMk1wbUVfSjhodGtkMnhLZlJzZU9SdTFZajJmSGh2U2hWUWd1dUpablBQb0x2UXZJeDZRVFB3OC1vUEcxRklrMFpzcjFGUUZsUG1ST1YtbWZmQkdMVXRRNkJpbHZTT29pS3ducEVXZU5oUTVXNzFoeEVFbw?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Weighted vests are 'great' for women in menopause. I put one to the test — and it's on sale ahead of Prime Day&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Yahoo&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 15:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPbjUyMVBJT0lCYko3V0N2ZjVSbTBCMFNKVzRVVDBUTDJSQU1KTXhkR3hMSHJITDBEYUpYX2tBNy16c1FoZk1XbFdxZnFoY1VDVmlnZV9CbVo0TEFneW9EeUUyZEhDamlnaktZZDQ5SWdoLVdYMTVFWFJrQ0hzVmxYaVpPNmdJRFN0cDdJ</guid></item><item><title>美国麻疹病例接近25年来的最高水平。查看新泽西州的哪些地区面临风险。- NJ.com | Measles cases in the U.S. approach 25-year high. See which parts of N.J. are at risk. - NJ.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivgFBVV95cUxOaHhzMlNReXljLVU1WkhlTDRnWDFIakJES1Zndjdndzcwc1Z5MnhrS3FPdVd4R0tlRjM1MzhrbnFGekNmTENqMWVYQ2pIQks3RWx3N1haN1lpNGlpOHNDZEdacWh1SWR6blhsUHNmeERxY2Y4eUM5bFp5d3g3REtnaUFxemZYb29MendoanM3ZDlmMkFJa3B1SGVaME03OGxOOGxXNGt4NWNjaThWVjNfVEt2TnFrOXdsM1I5b0hn0gHSAUFVX3lxTE1NcF9pRWl6eUZfN2NCSUJvWldKdzVWTEtuYWZVOVRwaFRIb3pUOV9sTWJ1MFZ5d2tITERRVU8xdkJkY0J0dlhwa0pnSEYwemNCVGdNVXd5d1FLeHF5alFrNk5zZWxZd2hSQ3pqYXNNdkVJaUw4UExpOWtITFUyZzN0N19DdURwVWVJUDA0SGphaE5QclhXYXVYLWJPMmRUWmxNZEdGVFdyc2dCNUNxUmJDLWQyQ2gwVHljbEI1aEhCRU1fbXJnaU9HYW5MYXF4Mm1mdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="KPU4VAMIT5HDZJFRVYBTJNK5GQ"&gt;The United States is on track to report the highest number of measles cases in a single year since the country declared measles eliminated in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QBYBHBCW6VGFXDS2TDFYYSXSOY"&gt;A total of 1,267 confirmed measles cases were reported by 38 states so far this year, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_10-measles-cases-in-2025" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_10-measles-cases-in-2025"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. Of those infected, 155 have been hospitalized. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QSXHX74JFNBYFGSYZFQ4MKVOVU"&gt;That’s more than triple the number of cases reported in all of 2024, and the second highest annual case count in the U.S. in 25 years. There have also been three documented deaths — in New Mexico and Texas — the first measles deaths in the U.S. in over a decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="K7MT3KQCEZELDPCJ6YJ3NAWIOQ"&gt;In 2019, measles infected 1,274 people. At the time, it was the worst outbreak the country has seen since endemic measles was declared eliminated in 2000 as a direct result of widespread coverage with the measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FUTAD3SXQVAQLKEJ4R4MS6OFLQ"&gt;&lt;b&gt;ALSO: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/03/do-i-need-a-measles-vaccine-booster.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/03/do-i-need-a-measles-vaccine-booster.html"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Do I need a measles vaccine booster?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="I4WEWP43UBFI3LNMFGHTHV4F5Q"&gt;Currently, “there is no ongoing community spread in New Jersey,” according to the latest measles update on the state health department &lt;a href="https://www.nj.gov/health/measles/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.nj.gov/health/measles/"&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="THA6S7R53RDD5CHCHYMERQ4P3U"&gt;The state health department did not immediately respond Wednesday to a request for comment on the surge in measles cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7RLPMWKZVBG6TEY73AV54JY52E"&gt;However, due to an increase of measles cases across the U.S., the New Jersey Department of Health is urging all residents to make sure they’re “up to date on MMR and other routine vaccines, especially before travel.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ATUC5BAMDBEOVCHMWQACI2WC34"&gt;Residents traveling internationally with an infant aged 6 to 11 months are advised by New Jersey health officials to “talk to your pediatrician about the MMR vaccine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6M6I3ULJ65A6NC6XN6E2ZOEFAI"&gt;New Jersey residents can verify their immunization records using the &lt;a href="https://www.nj.gov/health/covid-19/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.nj.gov/health/covid-19/"&gt;Docket App&lt;/a&gt;, which provides access to information stored in the New Jersey Immunization Information System. Vaccination records may also be available through healthcare providers, former schools, colleges, employers, the military, or obstetricians’ offices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OJIPAXQZAFB73F7FZBC542QQJQ"&gt;The Garden State has reported three measles cases among residents so far in 2025, all of which were part of a &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/02/new-measles-cases-tied-to-nj-patient-who-visited-3-health-facilities.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/02/new-measles-cases-tied-to-nj-patient-who-visited-3-health-facilities.html"&gt;household outbreak&lt;/a&gt; in February. The cases involved unvaccinated people. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SQSYHG2VZND7HJLL4K65YU7XPQ"&gt;Measles is a highly contagious respiratory disease that spreads easily through coughing and sneezing. Even after an infected person has left the room, the virus can remain present in the air for up to two hours, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="M4ES5GTBINCH7DHGSRJNUFU6KY"&gt;Symptoms of measles include a high fever, cough, runny nose, watery red eyes, and a red rash that begins at the hairline, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CNLMBFEJUJCCTA6ZFY4R3QCAMM"&gt;The rash usually starts three to five days after the other symptoms. People can spread measles to others from four days before through four days after the rash appears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="V6DRV5JCD5BIRLYGQBTPVJJMWM"&gt;It poses the biggest risk to those who have not been fully vaccinated or have not had measles in the past. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SJWIHE5JCNCEXBTKLQUMEASBDM"&gt;Although measles was declared eliminated 25 years ago, large outbreaks with 50 or more cases have become more frequent, especially in close-knit communities with low vaccination coverage, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PUGQH7IVYND7RNPMR6VWEET53Y"&gt;In fact, 92% of the cases reported in the U.S. so far in 2025 are among people who had not received the MMR vaccine or have unknown vaccination status. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DR6TXXDHQVAD3D6YB7NUZKMXGY"&gt;A study published June 2 in the Journal of the American Medical Association found that of 2,066 counties across the U.S., 78% reported a decline in vaccination rates for measles, mumps and rubella after the COVID-19 pandemic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2WBMM6UNLBBZ7MVYUHTHGCXVYE"&gt;“If vaccination rates continue to decline, measles is likely to return to endemic levels,” according to the peer-reviewed study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3BVEUPVUP5GV7CSV23UIQ6TTEY"&gt;New Jersey residents are at a greater risk for measles now that the state no longer has &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/04/njs-herd-immunity-from-measles-is-gone-get-your-kids-vaccinated-early-experts-warn.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.nj.com/healthfit/2025/04/njs-herd-immunity-from-measles-is-gone-get-your-kids-vaccinated-early-experts-warn.html"&gt;herd immunity&lt;/a&gt;. Public health experts say that measles control depends on herd immunity of 95% vaccination coverage and that rate has been declining in the U.S. and in New Jersey, while the number of people going unvaccinated climbs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HPT2XD55TFDHRFVAYXXOND72UE"&gt;The CDC recommends children get two doses of MMR vaccine, starting with the first dose at 12 to 15 months of age, and the second dose at 4 to 6 years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HQZ3DCJTXZFFDFGV7IN7UBW72I"&gt;As of 2023, 93% of kindergartners in the state have received two or more doses of MMR vaccine, which is slightly above the national average of 92.7%, but still a decline from the state’s 2022-23 vaccination rate of 94.3%, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/72/wr/mm7245a2.htm" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/72/wr/mm7245a2.htm"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="72HAHSEZQBGKZMEC7YKYRXDWJM"&gt;The MMR vaccine, administered in two doses, is mandatory for children who attend school or day care centers in New Jersey, unless their parent or guardian seeks a medical or religious waiver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BXJHEUJUXVC6VG4SXWJZE2PNGA"&gt;Over the last ten years, the number of New Jersey children skipping vaccines through religious exemptions has more than doubled, according to state immunization reports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L77THO3SHNFBVPDIYERSBLXVRM"&gt;In the 2014-15 school year, 9,115 pre-Kindergarten, Kindergarten, first grade, sixth grade, and transfer students received religious exemptions from mandatory immunization, compared to 24,962 in 2024-25, according to&lt;a href="https://www.nj.gov/health/cd/statistics/imm-status-reports/?_gl=1*157py0p*_ga*MTM1ODkwODMyOS4xNzQ1MDkxNDU5*_ga_5PWJJG6642*czE3NTE0ODQzODMkbzM4JGcwJHQxNzUxNDg0MzgzJGo2MCRsMCRoMA.." target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.nj.gov/health/cd/statistics/imm-status-reports/?_gl=1*157py0p*_ga*MTM1ODkwODMyOS4xNzQ1MDkxNDU5*_ga_5PWJJG6642*czE3NTE0ODQzODMkbzM4JGcwJHQxNzUxNDg0MzgzJGo2MCRsMCRoMA.."&gt; New Jersey Annual Immunization Status Reports&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3H5XDZPXZ5GEZFSDVA5TMZ3H7E"&gt;Atlantic, Cape May, Monmouth, Ocean, and Sussex counties currently have the highest percentage of children who have not received any vaccinations due to religious exemption. They also have the lowest percentage of children meeting all immunization requirements. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OHRUZFTTHBHC7H6JJ6OORMKZQY"&gt;See the percentage of children in each county meeting all immunization requirements to assess the risk in your area. Note: Percentages have been rounded to the nearest whole number.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol class="article__ordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="EISWHOFZSVDVRJQE2K2QCAACBA"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Atlantic — 88%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="UPBPXT5P7FHNBI2JECVGL3DZMI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Bergen — 94%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="JQUDZXXNSVH6HG2SJXULPM6BNA"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Burlington — 93%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="5XAAWFL7CJA7LLDAJRLMSWS7TA"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Camden — 92%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="TKWQZUPRRFFG5BCIUOI2EPD424"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cape May — 87%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="7A37T7BKRJATTKDC2DCKMZSCZI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cumberland — 93%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="UL5R4THG6JEJTPNX3IVBEYVZ6U"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Essex — 90%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="2NSYKDCGUZF7FK3G6ENQSXOYTA"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Gloucester — 92%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="LG7ERVB7RVBYDFHWHP2DRU2WL4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hudson — 92%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="4U5AQ4IXMZF3XHV66XCWYAAVWQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Hunterdon — 91%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="45ZCZ75UGJCVJAMQ57HM5HSWY4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mercer —93%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="SRCP7RXMBJGVLCAZH7BJLARDCQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Middlesex — 92%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="HURXOWQSXFGWNMBDJX6H662JS4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Monmouth — 88%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="2R6ZWGMGQBBFHAQPZIJDGIZF3U"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Morris — 93%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="SKVWGBMXP5BGPN3NKAADBZ4JDY"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Ocean — 83%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="MH4YNFJCJRDDHNUWA4NW2IJTMQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Passaic — 93%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="Y44L4PVICVHS7PDXQNY72U3NAM"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Salem — 94%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="VK7XJABENBCTRJRWWCYV6TUPOA"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Somerset — 90%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="NTNL2V5DN5A77NIU6EPGLDZVBQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sussex — 90%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="C37S7R4Z55D2PPQ2RMTCJN6YN4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Union — 94%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="FERHYKUNPBGIRK6YEYUZ6U62QM"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Warren — 92%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-28" data-gaid="inarticle-28"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:57HNMHOWWJH2DLBMSJ3ONBSMNU" data-fusion-component="57HNMHOWWJH2DLBMSJ3ONBSMNU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:57HNMHOWWJH2DLBMSJ3ONBSMNU" data-fusion-component="57HNMHOWWJH2DLBMSJ3ONBSMNU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-29" data-gaid="inarticle-29"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5DEF6JIWYZCU5C6RYPKDOA6GUY"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thank you for relying on us to provide the local news you can trust. Please consider supporting &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;NJ.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; with a voluntary subscription.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-30" data-gaid="inarticle-30"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FC35OKZGUVEGBGEETBZMAWPIQU"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/staff/jroman/posts.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;Jackie Roman&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; may be reached at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:jroman@njadvancemedia.com" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;jroman@njadvancemedia.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-31" data-gaid="inarticle-31"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxOaHhzMlNReXljLVU1WkhlTDRnWDFIakJES1Zndjdndzcwc1Z5MnhrS3FPdVd4R0tlRjM1MzhrbnFGekNmTENqMWVYQ2pIQks3RWx3N1haN1lpNGlpOHNDZEdacWh1SWR6blhsUHNmeERxY2Y4eUM5bFp5d3g3REtnaUFxemZYb29MendoanM3ZDlmMkFJa3B1SGVaME03OGxOOGxXNGt4NWNjaThWVjNfVEt2TnFrOXdsM1I5b0hn0gHSAUFVX3lxTE1NcF9pRWl6eUZfN2NCSUJvWldKdzVWTEtuYWZVOVRwaFRIb3pUOV9sTWJ1MFZ5d2tITERRVU8xdkJkY0J0dlhwa0pnSEYwemNCVGdNVXd5d1FLeHF5alFrNk5zZWxZd2hSQ3pqYXNNdkVJaUw4UExpOWtITFUyZzN0N19DdURwVWVJUDA0SGphaE5QclhXYXVYLWJPMmRUWmxNZEdGVFdyc2dCNUNxUmJDLWQyQ2gwVHljbEI1aEhCRU1fbXJnaU9HYW5MYXF4Mm1mdw</guid></item><item><title>我是一名长寿医生。这些是我保持年轻的日常习惯-《每日电讯报》 | I’m a longevity doctor. These are my daily habits to stay young - The Telegraph</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxNX2hOUWNnV1NzQlozX0hwOThCQmJneXFrRFlYUWhRN3czQkpZTldNN2RjQl9NTExpeDhuRHJkaER3UC0xM19udGdaOENsSDNuODVHUk5sb1BBNG1DV3g2bkhSc1dFcDR1OTlCQTd4eXFJbk52VFBFWWtsWVc0MXphWFlkSm1McmNwNHRyR0s1OTdYN1NCUXc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dr Mohammed Enayat is a London-based GP and the Founder of HUM2N Longevity Clinic. Here, he walks us through how he structures his day, making simple tweaks to his diet and lifestyle, to ensure he lives a longer, healthier life.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Wake up&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m up at 6am every day and the first thing I do is take myself out to the garden to do some breathing. I live with my parents in their house in north-east London at the moment, and they’re lucky enough to have a lovely garden. I moved in with them 18 months ago just as I was opening my longevity clinic HUM2N. It made sense financially for me as I was setting up my business, but they’re also in their mid-70s now and being there means I can spend more quality time with them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m getting married this summer and then I’ll split my time between my parents’ and my future wife’s, who lives on the Kent coast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once I’m outside, I’ll do breathing exercises or pray for a few minutes, but just putting my bare feet on the ground helps me to wake up. Even when it’s been raining!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, I’ll brush my teeth and hop in the shower. Only then do I switch my mind to work, looking at my phone and checking emails and messages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Breakfast: 0 calories&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I rarely eat breakfast because I’ve worked out I feel more energised when I do &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/nutrition/diet/intermittent-fasting-benefits-downsides-weight-loss/"&gt;intermittent fasting&lt;/a&gt;. So I’ll have my last meal of the day by 8.30pm, and then my first meal at lunch. It means I’m &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/diet/weight-loss/fasting-versus-low-carb/"&gt;carbohydrate free&lt;/a&gt; for the whole morning, so biologically, I’m in a fasted state five days a week. When you haven’t eaten for 10-12 hours, glycogen stores in the liver become depleted, and so your body begins breaking down protein and fat stores for energy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before I leave for work, I’ll take my morning supplements with some water. I’m always adjusting the amount and the ones I take depending on what my body needs. I take up to eight some days, but others I don’t take any at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have annual blood tests taken at my own clinic that help me decide on which supplements to take. These tests aren’t typically available on the NHS, but will look at an extensive list of 120 biomarkers that indicate what’s going on in our bodies &lt;strong&gt;–&lt;/strong&gt; from our immune system to our hormones and digestive health &lt;strong&gt;–&lt;/strong&gt; and identify areas of health that need attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m 41 now, and I do think your 40s can be a slippery slope in terms of health, which is why the annual blood test is worth doing. People don’t become sick overnight. There are silent things that can accumulate in the body and if you can catch these as early as possible, you can do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This turns medicine on its head a bit, because we’re not looking to treat an individual symptom or organ, we’re looking to treat a whole human. As a doctor, I find I can improve people’s health much better when I’m looking at all of their systems together, rather than in bits and pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Annual blood tests inform my morning supplements&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The last time I had my blood tests taken, I discovered elevated levels of the protein zonulin in my blood, indicating I have a leaky gut at the moment. That’s where the lining of the small intestine becomes damaged, allowing bacteria, toxins, and undigested food particles to leak into the bloodstream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So now I’m on a supplement plan that contains L-glutamine, digestive enzymes, and &lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/diet/gut-health/probiotics-gut-health/"&gt;probiotics&lt;/a&gt;. I’ve also removed dairy from my diet for now as it was flagged as one of the leaky gut drivers for me. I’ve noticed that my bloating has gone down and the dry skin I was also experiencing has gone away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood test also showed that I have adrenal fatigue too, and that my stress responding hormones aren’t working as well as they should be. Symptoms that people can look out for are feeling “wired but tired”, getting colds and flus more often, and feeling generally run down. As well as taking supplements to help with this, I’m being more mindful of my workload, and making sure I’m bringing down my cortisol levels in the evening with a few minutes of meditation or deep breathing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m also taking peptides to support tissue repair and recovery as I’m doing a lot of strength training ahead of my wedding. One of these peptides is called BPC 157, and the other is called Ipamorelin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;My commute&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I commute on the Central Line from my parent’s home to my clinic in South Kensington and it takes about an hour. I’ll listen to podcasts on the way. At the moment I’ve been listening to Robin Sharma, humanitarian, author of &lt;em&gt;The Wealth Money Can’t Buy&lt;/em&gt;, which I enjoyed a lot. I’ll also plan for the day ahead by taking notes or journaling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have my first coffee at around 9am, before starting my day at work. Every day is different, and I have some days where I’m seeing back-to-back clinical patients, and then some that are full of management meetings with my team. I try to take some of those meetings as walking meetings so that I can get my steps up, and get some more daylight and fresh air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love my patient time because I love working with people. I do a day a week as a GP with the NHS, so most weeks I’m working six days. Within the week, I also spend about 20 per cent of time educating my team and leading in-house learning with different specialists and building out our team of experts. It’s full on, but I feel like I have important work to do that will hopefully help people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;How I make time to exercise&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At lunchtime, I take an hour and a half break and go for strength and conditioning training at a nearby gym which, at the moment, is focused on my core and posterior strength development. I’d started to get some back pain from being quite sedentary. It’s not too bad yet, but I wanted to prevent it from becoming a bigger issue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m getting married in August, which is really motivating me to get fitter and healthier, because that can slip when you’re busy. I’ve got my sights set on a really nicely-fitted suit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I also do boxing once or twice a week, and that’s my cardio. My training regime does tend to vary. I love to be outside when I can, so in the warmer months I’ll do my boxing and circuits outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the days that I’m not commuting, I try to go for a run outside or do some skipping. You should always make time to move your body, it’s one of the most important things you can do for your mental and physical health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-colour"&gt;Snack: 185 calories&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If I feel like I need something to keep me going until lunchtime, I’ll have a smoothie with blueberries, a scoop of almond butter, 22g of collagen protein, greens powder, oat milk and water.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 14:56:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNX2hOUWNnV1NzQlozX0hwOThCQmJneXFrRFlYUWhRN3czQkpZTldNN2RjQl9NTExpeDhuRHJkaER3UC0xM19udGdaOENsSDNuODVHUk5sb1BBNG1DV3g2bkhSc1dFcDR1OTlCQTd4eXFJbk52VFBFWWtsWVc0MXphWFlkSm1McmNwNHRyR0s1OTdYN1NCUXc</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，早餐习惯与抑郁症状有关- PsyPost | Breakfast habits are associated with depressive symptoms, study finds - PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxNblM5VWxUOTBLT2g3dWV4blRBTWpXTmp3a3hZRVBXR3FxTHNEc2xJZ2lPNjZYYkRNMVVvYnJOTElkZ3NBajdkNTV6ZmdlSlJnN0ZsaXA0VElxbXpiREtoSFM1ZHZ1N202N3RYMDJ1Q0lncF9YSzlzMV9tUFNHaFNwT3duNmpXVDk1aWR1UzRiVzhEekdLci15cA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study of young people in Hong Kong found that individuals with higher levels of depressive symptoms and those prone to impulsive reactions were slightly more likely to skip breakfast. Breakfast skipping was also associated with anxiety, but the strength of this association was negligible. The research was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fpsyt.2025.1574119"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Frontiers in Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breakfast is the first meal of the day, typically eaten in the morning after a night’s sleep. People around the world eat different foods for breakfast depending on culture, tradition, and availability. In many Western countries, breakfast includes eggs, toast, cereal, fruit, or yogurt. In East Asia, breakfast often consists of rice, soup, pickled vegetables, or steamed buns. Some people prefer a light breakfast like a smoothie or coffee, while others opt for a hearty meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breakfast is considered important because it helps replenish energy and provides essential nutrients after a long overnight fast. Studies have shown that eating breakfast can improve concentration, memory, and academic performance in children. It may also help regulate metabolism and support healthy weight management. Skipping breakfast has been associated with an increased risk of overeating later in the day and poorer overall diet quality. For many, breakfast is also a time to begin the day with a moment of calm or connection with family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study author Stephanie Ming Yin Wong and her colleagues aimed to explore patterns of breakfast consumption among youth in Hong Kong and to investigate the associations between breakfast skipping, impulsivity, and symptoms of depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They analyzed data from the Hong Kong Youth Epidemiological Study of Mental Health (HK-YES), the first territory-wide household-based mental health study in Hong Kong specifically targeting young people aged 15 to 24. Data were collected between 2019 and 2022. Fifty-eight percent of participants were female.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This analysis included data from 3,154 participants, with an average age of 20 years. Participants answered questions about their breakfast habits and completed assessments of impulsivity (using the Barratt Impulsiveness Scale–11), depressive symptoms (Patient Health Questionnaire–9), anxiety symptoms (Generalized Anxiety Disorder Scale–7), and overall functioning (measured by self-reported productivity loss due to mental health problems and an interviewer-rated Social and Occupational Functioning Assessment Scale).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results showed that 85% of participants consumed breakfast either daily or intermittently, while 15% regularly skipped breakfast. Individuals who skipped breakfast tended to be slightly more impulsive, particularly in terms of attentional control and self-control. They also reported slightly more severe depressive symptoms and marginally higher anxiety symptoms. Compared to peers who ate breakfast, those who skipped it reported just under one additional day of reduced productivity per month and slightly poorer social and occupational functioning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Breakfast skipping is associated with elevated depressive symptoms in young people, with impaired attentional control being an important mechanism in this relationship. Encouraging young people to build regular breakfast habits may be incorporated as part of future lifestyle interventions for mental disorders and be further emphasized in public health policies,” the study authors concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study sheds light on the links between breakfast-related habits and mental health. However, it should be noted that the reported associations were all very weak and detectable only because the sample was very large. Additionally, the study was exclusively conducted on residents of Hong Kong. Results on other cultural groups may differ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fpsyt.2025.1574119"&gt;Breakfast skipping and depressive symptoms in an epidemiological youth sample in Hong Kong: the mediating role of reduced attentional control&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Stephanie Ming Yin Wong, Olivia Choi, Yi Nam Suen, Christy Lai Ming Hui, Edwin Ho Ming Lee, Sherry Kit Wa Chan, and Eric Yu Hai Chen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 14:14:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxNblM5VWxUOTBLT2g3dWV4blRBTWpXTmp3a3hZRVBXR3FxTHNEc2xJZ2lPNjZYYkRNMVVvYnJOTElkZ3NBajdkNTV6ZmdlSlJnN0ZsaXA0VElxbXpiREtoSFM1ZHZ1N202N3RYMDJ1Q0lncF9YSzlzMV9tUFNHaFNwT3duNmpXVDk1aWR1UzRiVzhEekdLci15cA</guid></item><item><title>房客专栏|患者对放射治疗的看法：这就是它的感觉-《华盛顿邮报》 | Guest column | A patient’s eye view of radiation therapy: This is what it feels like - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilgFBVV95cUxOQmY4dUlwczhBSE8ybE1fUTRSWTNiZWdRMXNXNlJBMlZxcURwb0VYNUhCaGdybmhCNmVfMHhIcVd1Q284Rlpha0dSSkNtZ3d5d0NScDE5M1dfMHJMMGplR1VMNXc3SV9RT3lMNE5OUjJwRnJfVUN6cFJCcENIQWRzWXV4MFppV2lXQ3JVUzRMTGJVR1R0QUE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JZSB4XGRABFM5LMNSFIICNUECY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Too often in pop culture, “cancer” is synonymous with chemotherapy and depressing scenes of noble patients enduring hair loss and intravenous drips. But for many people, including palliative care patients like me, radiation therapy can provide another avenue to slow disease and reduce pain with fewer side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZRJBIY76KVEQRHMZV6QQ73T4SI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Although it can also be a robust part of curative treatment for a range of cancers (including &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/prostate-cancer/treating/radiation-therapy.html" target="_blank"&gt;prostate&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/tests-procedures/radiation-therapy-for-breast-cancer/about/pac-20384940" target="_blank"&gt;breast&lt;/a&gt; cancers), in my case, it quickly — and disappointingly — became clear that radiation wasn’t going to jolt my &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/06/16/terminal-cancer-diagnosis-palliative-care/" target="_blank"&gt;metastatic Ewing’s sarcoma&lt;/a&gt; into retirement (never the likeliest outcome). But it ameliorated some discomforts and with notably less wear and tear than the chemo alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="E6T5ZHEZKVG4RPFLBKOWA3EF6I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;This piece is meant to shine some light on radiation treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YXCZF362XBDWZFOF2HDDFC4CO4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;So far, I have had three 10-day courses of radiation zaps. We’ve treated a lung nodule, my upper arm bones, a bunch of mean-looking cells in the mediastinum area between my lungs, a lesion in my right pelvic bone and a nearby rump bump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="IGSSL7SYGFHFFN774WIQSMCEKU" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="IGSSL7SYGFHFFN774WIQSMCEKU" data-testid="article-header"&gt;The drill&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QS4I4X5XPZEFFLCW5VFAYWIBXY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;On treatment days, I zip into Sibley Memorial Hospital’s radiation oncology reception area, scan my blue plastic patient card, and chat with the women who schedule appointments and answer a stream of emails and calls while still taking time to make us feel welcome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KOYNIMGYKBDYHBRUN4EQTKLWSU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Then it’s off to the locker room, where I grab one of those icky hospital gowns with the open backs, graciously augmented with a second shapeless garment to keep from flashing one’s butt at passersby. Along the way, I might stop to talk with other patients who share my time slot or with Freddy Mancilla, who restocks the hospital gowns and water bottles; he has worked at Sibley for 39 years, and his fellow staff members dote on him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2RCHCYMTJNBHLEV6VWB6UUEFHI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When I get into the radiation room, I recite my name and birth date and disrobe as required for the body parts in question. Then I lie down, and a team of two or three therapists makes sure I’m precisely positioned for the rays to get to the right place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="L3RW5OEIYNBFTKXAEVHZXCFFOY" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="L3RW5OEIYNBFTKXAEVHZXCFFOY" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Teamwork&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NJMBQ42R5RG2RD5BX5ATJABQQU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I confess to becoming a fan of this radiology department, admiring the employees’ technical skill, sensitivity and seamless teamwork. I have yet to see a patient treated rudely or to hear an argument among the staff. There is, however, a lot of good-natured teasing and laughing. Coordinating this complex ballet falls to Terelle Cook, Sibley’s chief radiation therapist manager.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XHZZ65LPCRFXBLTGTX7ZFWJW5A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“How do you build a team like ours?” Fung Mei Chiang, one of my regular therapists, responds when I ask. “Through a lot of mutual respect. As much as we love our patients, we also take care of each other.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Y3KUWUWFEZA4DNW7GGBKILF57E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Over the past few years, there has been new research about the &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/close-encounters/202312/how-daily-small-talk-can-improve-well-being" target="_blank"&gt;positive effects&lt;/a&gt; of micro-interactions — the casual chat with your supermarket checker or the gardening tip exchanged with a neighbor — on general well-being. For many patients, the small daily interactions with the therapists help ease what can be a disheartening experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QQICXFI53VCBRJJF5YD2DBTGWM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;As the therapists push and prod my body, we usually banter. “We see people every day for weeks on end,” therapist Myla Bennette tells me, “and so we get to know a little bit about you guys, and you get to know a little bit about us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GHUR7LS6E5AEVIICLRXP27AOO4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;During my radiation weeks, I’ve had mini-conversations about films and restaurants, families and future plans, and about life on the front lines of health care. One day, I asked how they learned to handle patients’ bodies with a detached professionalism — while still treating us like humans — and how they learned to deal with the inevitable deaths of so many of the people they treat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EXAMY5P22FD3LDZLPUAUEX47AM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;They cited extensive classroom training and clinical practice rotations, but life experience and empathy also play a role. Many of them came to the profession after caring for a loved one with a mortal illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4Y4ZMURD5FC5FHAQCVKHFW7CVQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Once the therapists have me perfectly aligned for treatment, they leave me and head for the control desk outside. Lying on the bed of the radiation machine, with darting red and green beams above me and large mechanical eyes and grids humming and moving around me, I feel as though I’m in a 1950s sci-fi movie, slightly cheesy and cool at the same time. Make that cold. The machines get finicky at warmer temperatures; for most patients, a highlight of treatment is when they cover you with a nice warm blanket. Then you can concentrate on, or ignore, whatever soundtrack happens to be playing and stare at the photos of tulips on the ceiling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RYSGNLVBAVHDHPKEFGYERAPF6E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My radiation treatment didn’t hurt, although you do have to lie very still. For the lung nodule, I had to suck on a tube that looked like a snorkel, then hold my breath for a bit longer than seemed comfortable. But, for the rest, I just had to maintain whatever awkward position would put the X-rays in line with the delinquent cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MQHD5ECVAFFAHORJOP5X5UPDOQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Then it’s over. The therapists come back in and liberate me. We wish each other a good day. And it’s back to the real world. Until next time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 14:01:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxOQmY4dUlwczhBSE8ybE1fUTRSWTNiZWdRMXNXNlJBMlZxcURwb0VYNUhCaGdybmhCNmVfMHhIcVd1Q284Rlpha0dSSkNtZ3d5d0NScDE5M1dfMHJMMGplR1VMNXc3SV9RT3lMNE5OUjJwRnJfVUN6cFJCcENIQWRzWXV4MFppV2lXQ3JVUzRMTGJVR1R0QUE</guid></item></channel></rss>