<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>诺华获批首款针对新生儿和婴儿的疟疾药物--路透社 | Novartis wins approval for first malaria drug for newborns and babies - Reuters</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiyAFBVV95cUxNeVV1Qm1UcHdjbTJiRzc2NUJqb21ndTN5T3hjdVZ4N3k0UlNoQ2FmM2lWSXB6ZTU5eGIwTDBxaGVWQkhSYW5ZQTdDZmFaR2xIZ3MxeENxb291RDBHSVhQX2c1YjY5LWEtRXFhV3o1dmNzYWNRNXNBRFB6V3VXdThlc1hNR0VxSHpMWGZmbk9lUGxyRERtc2dYLVl6OXRDeDh5VWJVQ0hFRU51X2pUOHdkM2RQWU1QTXVKbFVXTk9YVXVDSlQ4eW9mSQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 14:17:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiyAFBVV95cUxNeVV1Qm1UcHdjbTJiRzc2NUJqb21ndTN5T3hjdVZ4N3k0UlNoQ2FmM2lWSXB6ZTU5eGIwTDBxaGVWQkhSYW5ZQTdDZmFaR2xIZ3MxeENxb291RDBHSVhQX2c1YjY5LWEtRXFhV3o1dmNzYWNRNXNBRFB6V3VXdThlc1hNR0VxSHpMWGZmbk9lUGxyRERtc2dYLVl6OXRDeDh5VWJVQ0hFRU51X2pUOHdkM2RQWU1QTXVKbFVXTk9YVXVDSlQ4eW9mSQ</guid></item><item><title>惊喜脱发突破： DNA糖凝胶触发强劲再生- ScienceAlert | Surprise Hair Loss Breakthrough: DNA Sugar Gel Triggers Robust Regrowth - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxNZlU4TUdGWTBVaVZxYTFyTmY3eHBOVnBGbFBfRXBfNnlDWXJ1V0NQc0VqLTJnYURJOWN6VzEzdlB6TWVSLWZ6WDU5d2VNbll1MTF5QzBvbUg5N1hQQ3Z3d0NqR2phUE5tQ3hyRnV5TVlkVUZyb1drTzVJV0Jac0QxOGlldm1qamJRYWYyenFSZW5YZ0F4eWx5eVhsZEVQX1c0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;In 2024, scientists stumbled upon a potential new treatment for hereditary-patterned baldness, the &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/a_to_z/hereditary-patterned-baldness-a-to-z"&gt;most common cause of hair loss&lt;/a&gt; in both men and women worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It all started with &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC8583821/"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; on a sugar that naturally occurs in the body and helps form DNA: the '&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deoxyribose"&gt;deoxyribose&lt;/a&gt;' part of deoxyribonucleic acid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While studying how these sugars &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/ijms222111437"&gt;heal the wounds of mice&lt;/a&gt; when applied topically, scientists at the University of Sheffield and COMSATS University in Pakistan noticed that the fur around the lesions was growing back faster than in untreated mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intrigued, the team decided to investigate further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the video below for a summary of their research:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a study published in June 2024, they took male mice with testosterone-driven hair loss and removed the fur from their backs. Each day, researchers smeared a small dose of &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deoxyribose"&gt;deoxyribose&lt;/a&gt; sugar gel on the exposed skin, and within weeks, the fur in this region showed 'robust' regrowth, sprouting long, thick individual hairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deoxyribose gel was so effective, the team found it worked just as well as minoxidil, a topical treatment for hair loss commonly known by the brand name Rogaine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our research suggests that the answer to treating hair loss might be as simple as using a naturally occurring deoxyribose sugar to boost the blood supply to the hair follicles to encourage hair growth," &lt;a href="https://www.sheffield.ac.uk/news/cure-male-pattern-baldness-given-boost-sugar-discovery"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; tissue engineer Sheila MacNeil from the University of Sheffield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/protein-that-calms-waking-hair-follicles-could-lead-to-alopecia-treatment?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Protein That Calms Waking Hair Follicles Could Lead to Alopecia Treatment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hereditary-patterned baldness, or &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pattern_hair_loss"&gt;androgenic alopecia&lt;/a&gt;, is a natural condition caused by genetics, hormone levels, and aging, and it presents differently in males and females.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_155531" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-155531" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/male_baldness_642.jpg" alt="male pattern baldness" class="wp-image-155531 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/male_baldness_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/03/male_baldness_642-600x388.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-155531" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Hereditary-patterned baldness presents differently in men and women. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEx62El90M/"&gt;Oleg Elkov/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disorder impacts &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/a_to_z/hereditary-patterned-baldness-a-to-z"&gt;up to 40 percent of the population&lt;/a&gt;, and yet the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) has only approved two drugs to treat the condition thus far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While over-the-counter minoxidil can work to slow hair loss and promote some regrowth, it doesn't work for all those experiencing hair loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If minoxidil isn't effective, then male patients can turn to finasteride (brand name Propecia) – a prescribed oral drug that inhibits the conversion of testosterone to dihydrotestosterone. It's not yet approved for female patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finasteride can slow hair loss in about &lt;a href="https://www.aad.org/public/diseases/hair-loss/treatment/male-pattern-hair-loss-treatment"&gt;80 to 90 percent of male patients&lt;/a&gt;, but it needs to be taken continuously once it is started. The drug can be associated with unwanted, sometimes severe &lt;a href="https://www.nps.org.au/assets/medicines/c8584165-82ab-4a0f-8b3c-a53300ff8b32-reduced.pdf"&gt;side effects&lt;/a&gt;, such as erectile dysfunction, testicular or breast pain, reduced libido, and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depression" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73097" data-postid="167110" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The treatment of androgenetic alopecia remains challenging," MacNeil and her colleagues, led by biomaterial researcher Muhammad Anjum from COMSATS, &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/pharmacology/articles/10.3389/fphar.2024.1370833/full"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, the team designed a biodegradable, non-toxic gel made from deoxyribose, and applied the treatment to mouse models of male-pattern baldness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Minoxidil was also tested on balding mouse models, and some of the animals received a dose of both sugar gel &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; minoxidil for good measure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared to mice that received a gel without any medicine, those that received a gel with deoxyribose sugar began to sprout new hair follicles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both minoxidil and the sugar gel promoted 80 to 90 percent hair regrowth in mice with male pattern baldness. Combining the treatments, however, did not make much more of a difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Photographs were taken at various stages throughout the 20-day trial, and the effect is clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_133589" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-133589" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/fphar-15-1370833-g002-642x330.jpg" alt="Deoxyribose Gel" class="size-medium wp-image-133589" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/fphar-15-1370833-g002-642x330.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/fphar-15-1370833-g002-807x415.jpg 807w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/fphar-15-1370833-g002-768x395.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/fphar-15-1370833-g002-600x309.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/fphar-15-1370833-g002.jpg 1030w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-133589" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Photographs of mice with male pattern baldness at different time intervals, including mice without any treatment (NC), mouse models of male pattern baldness (T-1), gel without medicine (T-2), gel with deoxyribose sugars (T-3), minoxidil (T-4), deoxyribose sugar and minoxidil gel (T-5). (&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/pharmacology/articles/10.3389/fphar.2024.1370833/full"&gt;Anjum et al., &lt;em&gt;Front. Pharmacol.&lt;/em&gt;, 2024&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers aren't sure why the deoxyribose gel stimulates longer and thicker hair growth in mice, but around the treated site, the team did notice an increase in blood vessels and skin cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The better the blood supply to the hair bulb, the larger its diameter and the more hair growth," the researchers &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/pharmacology/articles/10.3389/fphar.2024.1370833/full"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_133597" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-133597" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/HairThickness.png" alt="Hair Shaft Thickness" class="size-full wp-image-133597" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/HairThickness.png 520w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/HairThickness-267x415.png 267w" sizes="(max-width: 520px) 100vw, 520px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-133597" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Photographs of hair shafts from different treatment groups. (&lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/pharmacology/articles/10.3389/fphar.2024.1370833/full"&gt;Anjum et al., &lt;em&gt;Front. Pharmacol.&lt;/em&gt;, 2024&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the deoxyribose gel also proves effective in humans, it could be used to treat alopecia or even stimulate hair, lash, and eyebrow regrowth following chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a badly under-researched area, and hence new approaches are needed," &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/pharmacology/articles/10.3389/fphar.2024.1370833/full"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the authors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current experiments were only conducted among male mice, but further research might find the use of these natural sugars could also work for female mice experiencing testosterone-driven alopecia, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The research we have done is very much early stage," &lt;a href="https://www.sheffield.ac.uk/news/cure-male-pattern-baldness-given-boost-sugar-discovery"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; MacNeil, "but the results are promising and warrant further investigation."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/pharmacology/articles/10.3389/fphar.2024.1370833/full"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Frontiers in Pharmacology&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was first published in July 2024&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 13:01:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxNZlU4TUdGWTBVaVZxYTFyTmY3eHBOVnBGbFBfRXBfNnlDWXJ1V0NQc0VqLTJnYURJOWN6VzEzdlB6TWVSLWZ6WDU5d2VNbll1MTF5QzBvbUg5N1hQQ3Z3d0NqR2phUE5tQ3hyRnV5TVlkVUZyb1drTzVJV0Jac0QxOGlldm1qamJRYWYyenFSZW5YZ0F4eWx5eVhsZEVQX1c0</guid></item><item><title>西澳百日咳病例上升；婴儿是“最悲惨的患者” --《西雅图时报》 | Whooping cough cases rise in WA; babies are 'the most miserable patients' - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitgFBVV95cUxOeEREZ01XUENSSFZzLVMtYVlBOUtKNEJobkwtalR3Um1oMEotRGJ0d2JTWUhzdVpPcXcxdXFKUDh2WC1DdFZocTkycTBaTWJNM21BR1NRVV9QdGRSZFB1bURRNG9jaWt1UzRHZ0MxdnlsM1JKZ2lkaUh6cU1Ta181Z1Bld2lqZXlXVkZXUEo0X1Voc3k3MjU0Um9vV0ljSE1XV1Z5SXI4c01mS1Z4VkE4OEU2YnlZUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitgFBVV95cUxOeEREZ01XUENSSFZzLVMtYVlBOUtKNEJobkwtalR3Um1oMEotRGJ0d2JTWUhzdVpPcXcxdXFKUDh2WC1DdFZocTkycTBaTWJNM21BR1NRVV9QdGRSZFB1bURRNG9jaWt1UzRHZ0MxdnlsM1JKZ2lkaUh6cU1Ta181Z1Bld2lqZXlXVkZXUEo0X1Voc3k3MjU0Um9vV0ljSE1XV1Z5SXI4c01mS1Z4VkE4OEU2YnlZUQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Whooping cough cases rise in WA; babies are 'the most miserable patients'&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxOeEREZ01XUENSSFZzLVMtYVlBOUtKNEJobkwtalR3Um1oMEotRGJ0d2JTWUhzdVpPcXcxdXFKUDh2WC1DdFZocTkycTBaTWJNM21BR1NRVV9QdGRSZFB1bURRNG9jaWt1UzRHZ0MxdnlsM1JKZ2lkaUh6cU1Ta181Z1Bld2lqZXlXVkZXUEo0X1Voc3k3MjU0Um9vV0ljSE1XV1Z5SXI4c01mS1Z4VkE4OEU2YnlZUQ</guid></item><item><title>您的排便时间表对您的整体健康有很大影响，建议您进行研究- ScienceAlert | Your Poop Schedule Says a Lot About Your Overall Health, Suggests Study - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxPVGp5QzQtV3pjbDlpZTJBQ1NkTkdwbGowMnVEWTFNUkV4RWJMR1kwQ3VQNndPWk5obFl1U3djZkFMMGNLZFF1LVJSRS1lRXI3Umc3UEFjcy11RVppaHltQkIyZXhUVmdPZXFCYTBud3NsdGhUcENlSXFXTjB5VExPbnZOWkhDWEx6T2poa3RjcjZheGdlZ09GSE1HMGgtenVT?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;"How often do you poop?" might sound like a very personal question, but your answer could reveal quite a lot about your overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study published in July 2024 investigated how often 1,425 people went number two, and compared those stats to their demographic, genetic, and health data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pooping too often or too rarely were both associated with different underlying health issues, while the healthiest participants reported pooping once or twice a day – a 'Goldilocks zone' of bowel movement frequency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This study shows how bowel movement frequency can influence all body systems, and how aberrant bowel movement frequency may be an important risk factor in the development of chronic diseases," &lt;a href="https://isbscience.org/news/health/timing-is-everything-isb-study-finds-link-between-bowel-movement-frequency-and-overall-health/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; University of Washington microbiologist Sean Gibbons, the corresponding author of the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/something-in-your-poop-may-predict-an-imminent-death?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Something in Your Poop May Predict an Imminent Death&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These insights could inform strategies for managing bowel movement frequency, even in healthy populations, to optimize health and wellness."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, led by a team from the Institute for Systems Biology (ISB), investigated the bathroom habits of people who were "generally healthy" – that is, with no history of kidney or gut issues like kidney disease, irritable bowel syndrome, or Crohn's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_132891" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-132891" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1-642x578.jpg" alt="A graphic depicting the studied variables" class="size-medium wp-image-132891" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1-642x578.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1-461x415.jpg 461w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1-600x540.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/07/gr1.jpg 765w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-132891" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Participants provided samples of blood plasma and stool, in addition to filling out extensive diet, health, and lifestyle questionnaires. (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell-reports-medicine/fulltext/S2666-3791(24)00360-4"&gt;Johnson-Martínez et al.,&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell Reports&lt;/em&gt;, 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;These participants self-reported how often they dropped the kids off at the pool, and the researchers organized them into four categories: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-constipation-could-be-having-a-serious-impact-on-your-heart"&gt;constipation&lt;/a&gt; for those reporting one or two bowel movements per week; low-normal for three to six movements per week; high-normal for one to three movements per day; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/severe-diarrhea-cases-surging-across-uk-and-scientists-dont-know-why"&gt;diarrhea&lt;/a&gt; for four or more watery stools per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also analyzed patients' blood metabolites and chemistry, their genetics, and the gut microbes present in their stool samples. The team then looked for possible associations between bowel movement frequency and these health markers, as well as other factors like their age and sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In general, those who reported less frequent bowel movements tended to be women, younger, and with a lower body mass index (BMI). But even accounting for these factors, people with constipation or diarrhea showed clear links to underlying health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bacteria usually found in the upper gastrointestinal tract were more common in stool samples from participants with diarrhea. Their blood samples, meanwhile, showed biomarkers associated with liver damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stool samples from people with less frequent bowel movements had higher levels of bacteria associated with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/mnfr.201100542"&gt;protein fermentation&lt;/a&gt;. This is a known hazard from constipation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If stool sticks around too long in the gut, microbes use up all of the available dietary fiber, which they ferment into beneficial short-chain fatty acids. After that, the ecosystem switches to fermentation of proteins, which produces several toxins that can make their way into the bloodstream," &lt;a href="https://isbscience.org/news/health/timing-is-everything-isb-study-finds-link-between-bowel-movement-frequency-and-overall-health/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Johannes Johnson-Martinez, a bioengineer at ISB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sure enough, some of these byproducts were found in these patients' blood samples. Particularly enriched was a metabolite called indoxyl-sulfate, a known product of protein fermentation which can damage the kidneys. The team suggests this is potential evidence of a causal link between bowel movement frequency and overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is some hope that people can change their habits and as a result, their health. Those in the Goldilocks zone of pooping reported eating more fiber, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/first-of-its-kind-study-lists-health-benefits-of-drinking-more-water-each-day"&gt;drinking more water&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/pooping-before-you-exercise-has-an-incredible-effect-on-performance"&gt;exercising more often&lt;/a&gt;. Their stool samples showed high levels of bacteria associated with fermenting fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, everybody's found themselves at one extreme or the other at some point in their lives, after catching a stomach bug or eating too much cheese. But this study was looking more at people's everyday routine, and how our own version of 'normal' could hint at health issues we weren't aware of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was published in the journal &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.xcrm.2024.101646"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cell Reports Medicine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 12:01:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxPVGp5QzQtV3pjbDlpZTJBQ1NkTkdwbGowMnVEWTFNUkV4RWJMR1kwQ3VQNndPWk5obFl1U3djZkFMMGNLZFF1LVJSRS1lRXI3Umc3UEFjcy11RVppaHltQkIyZXhUVmdPZXFCYTBud3NsdGhUcENlSXFXTjB5VExPbnZOWkhDWEx6T2poa3RjcjZheGdlZ09GSE1HMGgtenVT</guid></item><item><title>麻疹病例达到自2000年从美国消灭以来的最高点- NBC新闻 | Measles cases reach highest point since the disease was eliminated from U.S. in 2000 - NBC News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiugFBVV95cUxPb1VQRDNUMFV6QlAwaGRxQlhvNUczM0s5SFQ1MzZjS05xT0x4TVdXMWNjSXByNElsUnM4dWdKRURIR1gwMi1LT3U4N05EN2lQOWtlZ2dYaVlYblppY1RLYkJYbEFueGtvZUQzeDFWZlBrWmUzUEREOFhYTEdPZ01EcVluUE9rNnk5SGtwVWpoc29DblozQ2JQTDVsZEpqWVZiNUhkZEoxV0ZEUG40RjNmNkRLeXB3bnV2emfSAVZBVV95cUxPV1N2RjZlUmVBdk1KS0J5WU01YTd6RFgxSVBuVWZkN001OFhicDhYN0RxRFdqM1RPVmx5bGoyM2RlY0wzRDlub0d5RG4tMFVDZGo4QnpsQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Measles cases in the United States are the highest they’ve been since the country eliminated the disease in 2000. The U.S. has reported 1,277 cases since the start of the year, according to NBC News’ tally of state health department data. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Earlier this year, the U.S. also recorded its first &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;measles deaths&lt;/a&gt; in a decade: two children in Texas and an &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/measles-new-mexico-resident-tests-positive-death-rcna195231" target="_blank"&gt;adult in New Mexico&lt;/a&gt;. All were unvaccinated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;For the past 25 years, measles has been considered eliminated in the U.S. because it has not continuously spread over a year-long period. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;There are still periodic outbreaks, however, including one that took off in in a Mennonite community in West Texas earlier this year. Vaccination rates in Gaines County, the center of the outbreak, are particularly low: As of the 2023-24 school year, 82% of kindergarteners in the county had received two doses of the measles, mumps and rubella vaccine (MMR) vaccine, far below the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/global-measles-vaccination/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;95% rate needed to curb spread&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. David Sugerman, a senior scientist at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, said at a meeting of the CDC’s vaccine advisory committee in April that measles would have to keep spreading through January 20 of next year for the U.S. to lose its elimination status. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Most of the cases so far this year are linked to the Southwest outbreak — there have been more than 700 cases in Texas alone — though a number of smaller outbreaks, resulting from international travel, have been detected across the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt; The resurgence of measles can be attributed, in part, to declining vaccination rates both globally and nationally. During the 2023-24 school year, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/73/wr/mm7341a3.htm?s_cid=mm7341a3_w" target="_blank"&gt;less than 93% of kindergartners&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. received the recommended two doses of the MMR vaccine, down from 95% during the 2019-20 school year.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;The West Texas outbreak parallels one in 2019 among &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/68/wr/mm6840e2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;Orthodox Jewish communities in New York&lt;/a&gt; with low vaccination rates. The U.S. recorded 1,274 cases that year. A vaccination campaign, which included a vaccine mandate in New York City and officials &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/68/wr/mm6840e2.htm" target="_blank"&gt;administering 60,000 doses&lt;/a&gt; in affected communities, &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1912514" target="_blank"&gt;helped contain the spread&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;New York’s response was “an incredible feat and something we’re obviously trying to emulate,” Sugerman said. But he noted that the loss of Covid grant money has created “funding limitations” in Texas. The CDC &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-pulling-back-11b-covid-funding-sent-health-departments-us-rcna198006" target="_blank"&gt;slashed $11.4 billion in Covid funding&lt;/a&gt; last month, some of which helped state health departments respond to disease outbreaks. Each measles case may cost $30,000 to $50,000 to address, which “adds up quite quickly,” Sugerman said.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Many disease experts have also &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/measles-texas-rfk-jr-response-vaccines-doctors-wary-rcna194510" target="_blank"&gt;expressed concern that the federal messaging&lt;/a&gt; around vaccines could make the outbreak harder to contain. While Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has called for people to get the measles vaccine, he has also framed vaccination as a personal choice, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/kennedy-draws-misinformation-playbook-touting-inhaled-steroid-treat-me-rcna200085" target="_blank"&gt;emphasized unproven treatments&lt;/a&gt; like steroids or antibiotics and &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/health-secretary-rfk-jr-measles-vaccine-falsely-claims-wanes-rcna200636" target="_blank"&gt;falsely claimed that immunity from measles vaccines wanes quickly&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Dr. Ana Montanez, a pediatrician who treats patients in Lubbock and Gaines County, said at a press conference in April that misinformation was the “biggest nemesis” for healthcare providers. She was aware of some patients taking vitamin A instead of getting vaccinated, she said. Kennedy has played up the role of vitamin A in helping measles patients, though &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/vitamin-a-measles-virus-texas-cdc-what-know-rcna194288" target="_blank"&gt;it’s unclear how beneficial it is&lt;/a&gt;. The CDC says vitamin A can be administered under the supervision of a healthcare provider, but it’s not a treatment for the disease.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;“Countering the misinformation put out there about using vitamin A for treatment of measles has been a struggle, an upward struggle,” Montanez said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;By contrast, two doses of the MMR vaccine are 97% effective against measles and offer lifelong protection. The virus is particularly dangerous for babies and young children, whose immune systems aren’t always developed enough to fight an infection. In Texas, officials recommended an &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/texas-measles-outbreak-vaccine-effort-parents-babies-rcna207819" target="_blank"&gt;early dose for babies ages 6 to 11 months&lt;/a&gt;. Unvaccinated children over 12 months old should get one dose, according to the state, then a second dose 28 days later.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="body-graf"&gt;Measles often starts with a high fever, cough, runny nose and pink or watery eyes. From there, people may develop white spots on the insides of the cheeks near the molars and a blotchy rash of flat, red spots. Severe cases can progress to pneumonia or swelling of the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="endmark body-graf"&gt;Roughly 1 to 3 out of every 1,000 children with measles die from respiratory and neurological complications, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:45:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxPb1VQRDNUMFV6QlAwaGRxQlhvNUczM0s5SFQ1MzZjS05xT0x4TVdXMWNjSXByNElsUnM4dWdKRURIR1gwMi1LT3U4N05EN2lQOWtlZ2dYaVlYblppY1RLYkJYbEFueGtvZUQzeDFWZlBrWmUzUEREOFhYTEdPZ01EcVluUE9rNnk5SGtwVWpoc29DblozQ2JQTDVsZEpqWVZiNUhkZEoxV0ZEUG40RjNmNkRLeXB3bnV2emfSAVZBVV95cUxPV1N2RjZlUmVBdk1KS0J5WU01YTd6RFgxSVBuVWZkN001OFhicDhYN0RxRFdqM1RPVmx5bGoyM2RlY0wzRDlub0d5RG4tMFVDZGo4QnpsQQ</guid></item><item><title>Mounjaro用户对奇怪的副作用引发明显的体重增加感到震惊： “感觉就像我在扩张” -每日邮报 | Mounjaro users horrified as bizarre side effect triggers apparent weight GAIN: 'feels like I'm expanding' - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxOdWYxQ08tM19LNTFZWl84bjlsUm9VUm43bnpJdURrTUlpN3BtcTk1T1lQNDV5SklPdm9tZDdFLUFfTGs5QVVIX00tR3hjTUhEQW9LeVllUzJJaUIwRVI0TG9xWU9UTXQ2eUJGVE1oYl9jbm4zWEQzRHZxVXB1aGt6SHc2MFlMa3A4ek9iMHlwT1p2UWxtQmtlRjk1a3RtZ195WHZZ0gGoAUFVX3lxTE9GT1JGNWo3SVZCVFVYSE1LbzQ1bW5mc3NQamZDcXZBMzlyNV9ELWhQUjJKMjg3RThEaWRkR0w2X1BqN1JZZHlOczVxcVdjOVZHWXI5N2JkNmk0RUdpNVRCYzNVS2FXZllyUml1UF9famI2bkJ5dHdRX0hMTFFPQ0hVc2RTNFZPRFNrZW9aU3l3MlJ2QVQxdjhxMFJZYkRHem9sWmRzRmNwcg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A mother-of-three who shed two stone in just nine weeks by using weight loss injections has warned other users of a painful side-effect—which has left her looking bigger than ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Once aimed at &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-cad313e0-5be3-11f0-9818-43978d934320"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt; patients, Mounjaro has been dubbed the 'King Kong' of skinny jabs, bringing about rapid &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-cadcfef0-5be3-11f0-9818-43978d934320"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt; by reducing appetite. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the injections often come with side effects including severe bloating, nausea, diarrhoea and in some severe cases, life-threatening organ damage.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kayleigh, 37,  from Kent, weighed over 19 stone (120kg) and dropped to around 17 stone (107kg) within just nine weeks of taking Mounjaro. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The jabs, which can now be prescribed by GPs free of charge in England, initially vastly improved Kayleigh's relationship with her body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But she shared shocking images taken before and after her weekly dose which reveals she suffers from extreme bloating—causing her stomach to balloon to more than double its normal size. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The photos, taken just 24 hours apart after taking a 5mg dosage of the medication, show Kayleigh clutching her abdomen, which looks swollen and very painful. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The mother-of-three shared the agonising side-effect with her &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@kleelin2/video/7521755316015435030?is_from_webapp=1&amp;amp;sender_device=pc&amp;amp;web_id=7494180809390786070"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt; followers, adding that the &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14609885/GP-persistent-bloating-sign-deadly-cancer.html"&gt;bloating &lt;/a&gt;is usually accompanied with vomiting and diarrhoea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Kayleigh shared her symptoms with her 6,000 TikTok followers, saying that she suffers painful bloating every time she takes the medication&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The jabs spur weight loss by mimicking the actions of hormone GLP-1, which is naturally released in the gut after eating&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other jabbers flooded her post with support and tips, with some complaining of similar symptoms, whilst others suggested it could be caused by slower digestion triggered by the medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One commented: 'Any time I eat something it's like I'm pumped up!'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another said: 'Every meal I eat my stomach swells like a balloon too.'  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The injection, like other weight loss jabs such as Ozempic and WeGovy, works by mimicking the actions of a hormone released in the gut after eating, called GLP-1. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As well as signaling the pancreas to produce more insulin, Mounjaro disrupts signals between the gut and brain, keeping users fuller for longer and delays the stomach from being emptied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14860347/bizarre-effect-weight-loss-jabs-drunk-alcohol-reddit.html"&gt; Professor Penny Wad,&lt;/a&gt; a pharmaceutical experts at King's College London, this alone could be enough to trigger painful bloating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Delayed stomach emptying might delay the transit of carbohydrate through the gut,' she explained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This gives certain foods more time to produce gas in the intestine, through gut bacteria digesting and fermenting them—causing painful bloating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bloating can also be caused by various medical conditions such as IBS, Crohn's disease and small intestinal bacteria overgrowth (SIBO), which occurs when there is an abnormal increase in the amount of bacteria in the small intestine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alongside bloating these conditions can also cause other distressing digestive issues, such as cramps, diarrhoea, nausea and blood in the stool. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Alongside the bloating, which usually happens around 24hours after taking the jab, Kayleigh also experiences nausea, vomiting and diarrhoea - common side-effects of the blockbuster jabs &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Kayleigh told her followers that her bloating is reduced by taking Wellgard probiotics which support digestion and bowel regulation by boosting the number of healthy bacteria in the gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, bloating is not the only adverse side-effect experienced by Mounjaro users. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Last month, the UK medicines regulator launched a probe into the safety of fat jabs, after hundreds of users developed pancreatitis, leaving ten dead. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA) said it has received more than 560 reports of people developing an inflamed pancreas after taking the jabs since they were first launched. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Side effects such as these continue to be a significant burden on the NHS and studies have shown they account for one in six hospital admissions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is predicted that adverse drug reactions could cost the NHS more than £2.2 billion a year in hospital stays alone, Dr Alison Cave, the MHRA’s chief safety officer said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These blockbuster jabs have also been credited with lowering blood sugar levels for people with type 2 diabetes, but experts have warned they are not a silver bullet and can come with a number of serious side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Last year a sobering report suggested Britain's spiraling obesity levels—which costs the economy around £75billion a year—have fuelled a staggering 39 per cent rise in type 2 diabetes among people under 40. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Kayleigh has lost two stone on the medication &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Recent estimates suggest that about 1.5 million people in the UK are taking weight loss jabs, which can help users lose up to 20 per cent of their body weight in just a few months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And the numbers using them privately where it costs around £250 a month are even higher. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It comes as severely obese patients in England with a BMI over 40 and at least four obesity-related health conditions such as type 2 diabetes or high blood pressure, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14838139/GPs-dish-King-Kong-weight-loss-jab-Mounjaro-TODAY-free-NHS-YOU-qualify.html"&gt;will be offered Mounjaro &lt;/a&gt;free of charge from their GP. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The weekly injection will be offered to around 220,000 people over the next three years under new NHS prescribing rules. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Within 12 years, around for million Britons are expected to be receiving the jabs on the NHS.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, like any drug, side effects are wide-ranging and include issues like nausea and abdominal pain as well as digestive problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:43:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxOdWYxQ08tM19LNTFZWl84bjlsUm9VUm43bnpJdURrTUlpN3BtcTk1T1lQNDV5SklPdm9tZDdFLUFfTGs5QVVIX00tR3hjTUhEQW9LeVllUzJJaUIwRVI0TG9xWU9UTXQ2eUJGVE1oYl9jbm4zWEQzRHZxVXB1aGt6SHc2MFlMa3A4ek9iMHlwT1p2UWxtQmtlRjk1a3RtZ195WHZZ0gGoAUFVX3lxTE9GT1JGNWo3SVZCVFVYSE1LbzQ1bW5mc3NQamZDcXZBMzlyNV9ELWhQUjJKMjg3RThEaWRkR0w2X1BqN1JZZHlOczVxcVdjOVZHWXI5N2JkNmk0RUdpNVRCYzNVS2FXZllyUml1UF9famI2bkJ5dHdRX0hMTFFPQ0hVc2RTNFZPRFNrZW9aU3l3MlJ2QVQxdjhxMFJZYkRHem9sWmRzRmNwcg</guid></item><item><title>腿上的标志很容易被忽略，这可能表明你有致命的疾病，在50多岁以下成为一种流行病-每日邮报 | Easy to dismiss sign on your legs which could indicate you have killer condition that's becoming an EPIDEMIC in under 50s - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxOa19KSW9OcWdmbFp3Q1NzM1o0a2lCTDhZQ0VuYzhZUDJGTThrVDloU1NUcmRIZDhKeUNReWVsY2poVUdKWVVQR0pCVlc1aV9fajdaZUV2SWVwdnFOdm52SWt3aEE0NHh1WEtVWmEzdXlYQmY1WC1vU0lKZl9uaUxFblFodk1sM0FaUDlDbmNiaWw0T3lKUzlVa1I2M1c0YnZlazBFetIBqgFBVV95cUxOdlZPcWhuUzVFdnBsMDMzMldOaElSQ0NVZllYWUREQi1jNWFwV0h6Wkw5MEVnVDdGQ3VvdEJrdkdmQnRsTzJ6OGNjUDNvNURwTVRnTVhORmdpV3hfbXRvbHA0eTB6UkJhdnpCRzhMYzNvbGs0Nm4zSEo5YVRuTG1DMG94QVdsMkZnb0lJeDE2VGUwazF0ajl5QURsNnRjZmhyeXlwS0syN2Nrdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If the skin on your legs, feet and toes is starting to look bald and 'patchy' it might be the first signs you've developed a life-threatening disease, an expert has warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hair loss on your legs and toes can be a tell-tale sign of &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-ae0f0660-5bd4-11f0-b17b-91b8673311f0" class=""&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, which can lead to debilitating and uncomfortable complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;US-based diabetes expert Kenneth Harless says that hair loss on the lower limbs and extremities can be a sign of diabetic neuropathy, which is when the disease damages nerve cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Numbness in the hands and feet is one of the most common signs of the disease, which affects 5.8million Britons and 38.4million Americans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@drkenny11/video/7524279266771619103?_r=1&amp;amp;_t=8oct1F2d79C&amp;amp;fbclid=PAZXh0bgNhZW0CMTEAAaeYosRhx_t-pw2gLVvLFgVzsJQQPlHy59wMyCTtliLZec7IgvFnKl4xw2PYDQ_aem_0BV6Fnut3EZk8N-r6AVwvQ"&gt;video &lt;/a&gt;posted on &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/tiktok/index.html" id="mol-ae16a780-5bd4-11f0-b17b-91b8673311f0"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt; to his more than 180,000 followers, he explained: ‘It takes strong circulation to get that blood all the way to those capillaries in the hair in your toes and feet.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He continued: 'When your body develops insulin resistance (it) damages circulation patterns all the way to the nerves and the blood vessels at the hair follicle base.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This will cut off nutrients to your skin and hair follicles (causing hair loss). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So, he warned: 'The higher the diabetic neuropathy the person had, the more loss of hair on their distal (the part farthest from the centre of the body) feet and toes.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The diabetes expert warned that hair loss on the lower legs and feet can be a sign of the disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His claim is backed up by a 2019 study of 107 patients, which found hair loss as a reliable indicator of nerve damage due to the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other symptoms he said may appear after the hair loss include brain fog, wound healing issues, vision loss, and kidney damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The diabetes expert, who has suffered from insulin resistance himself, now shares tips to overcome blood sugar, cholesterol and belly fat issues on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It comes as the number of people in the UK suffering from diabetes has reached a record high&lt;span&gt;—especially in the under 50s.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Diagnoses among the under-40s rose by 23 per cent between 2016/17 and 2020/21 but by 18 per cent among those aged 40 and over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Almost 4.3million people were living with diabetes in 2021/22, according to the latest figures for the UK. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are now around 3.78million people living with type 2 diabetes in the UK, of which 148,344 are under 40.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are two types of diabetes. Type 1 is an autoimmune disease diagnosed from birth, while type 2 is when the body struggles to produce enough insulin later in life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;It comes as cases of diabetes in the UK reaching a record high amid the nation's obesity crisis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If you experience any of these symptoms, you should make an appointment with your GP who can arrange a blood test to check how high your blood sugar levels are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Type 2 diabetes can damage your blood vessels, causing potentially fatal complications like coronary heart disease and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The leading causes of type two diabetes are lifestyle factors like a poor diet, obesity and a lack of exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other symptoms of type 2 diabetes are increased thirst and urination, excessive hunger, fatigue, and losing weight without trying to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In some cases, people will be diagnosed with prediabetes—which is when your blood sugar levels are high, but not yet enough to be diagnosed with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The main treatment is to make lifestyle changes such as eating a diet rich in fruit, vegetables, wholegrain foods and pulses like lentils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, some people who need medication may be offered metformin, which lowers the amount of glucose (sugar) in their blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a bid to tackle the obesity crisis in the UK, the government recently allowed GPs to prescribe weight loss medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This includes Mounjaro, which has long been hailed toe 'King Kong' of slimming jabs, despite initially being developed as a diabetes medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Earlier this year, US researchers found those on the injections typically lost a fifth of their body weight in just over a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, in recent weeks there has been growing concern over the side effects of the 'quick fix' medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Last month, the UK's drug watchdog found weight loss jabs were potentially linked to more than a hundred deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A total of 111 deaths were logged with the regulator, the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA), up to and including May 29. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;None of the fatalities, which have all been reported since the jabs were licensed for use in the UK, are proven to have been caused directly by the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, health chiefs tasked with policing the safety of medicines admitted reports of side effects indicate 'a suspicion' they may have been to blame. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:51:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxOa19KSW9OcWdmbFp3Q1NzM1o0a2lCTDhZQ0VuYzhZUDJGTThrVDloU1NUcmRIZDhKeUNReWVsY2poVUdKWVVQR0pCVlc1aV9fajdaZUV2SWVwdnFOdm52SWt3aEE0NHh1WEtVWmEzdXlYQmY1WC1vU0lKZl9uaUxFblFodk1sM0FaUDlDbmNiaWw0T3lKUzlVa1I2M1c0YnZlazBFetIBqgFBVV95cUxOdlZPcWhuUzVFdnBsMDMzMldOaElSQ0NVZllYWUREQi1jNWFwV0h6Wkw5MEVnVDdGQ3VvdEJrdkdmQnRsTzJ6OGNjUDNvNURwTVRnTVhORmdpV3hfbXRvbHA0eTB6UkJhdnpCRzhMYzNvbGs0Nm4zSEo5YVRuTG1DMG94QVdsMkZnb0lJeDE2VGUwazF0ajl5QURsNnRjZmhyeXlwS0syN2Nrdw</guid></item><item><title>专家显示， 50多岁以下的杀手病情飙升的迹象被忽视-《每日邮报》 | Expert shows overlooked sign of killer condition surging in under 50s - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipAFBVV95cUxOa19KSW9OcWdmbFp3Q1NzM1o0a2lCTDhZQ0VuYzhZUDJGTThrVDloU1NUcmRIZDhKeUNReWVsY2poVUdKWVVQR0pCVlc1aV9fajdaZUV2SWVwdnFOdm52SWt3aEE0NHh1WEtVWmEzdXlYQmY1WC1vU0lKZl9uaUxFblFodk1sM0FaUDlDbmNiaWw0T3lKUzlVa1I2M1c0YnZlazBFeg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If the skin on your legs, feet and toes is starting to look bald and 'patchy' it might be the first signs you've developed a life-threatening disease, an expert has warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Hair loss on your legs and toes can be a tell-tale sign of &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-ae0f0660-5bd4-11f0-b17b-91b8673311f0" class=""&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, which can lead to debilitating and uncomfortable complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;US-based diabetes expert Kenneth Harless says that hair loss on the lower limbs and extremities can be a sign of diabetic neuropathy, which is when the disease damages nerve cells. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Numbness in the hands and feet is one of the most common signs of the disease, which affects 5.8million Britons and 38.4million Americans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.tiktok.com/@drkenny11/video/7524279266771619103?_r=1&amp;amp;_t=8oct1F2d79C&amp;amp;fbclid=PAZXh0bgNhZW0CMTEAAaeYosRhx_t-pw2gLVvLFgVzsJQQPlHy59wMyCTtliLZec7IgvFnKl4xw2PYDQ_aem_0BV6Fnut3EZk8N-r6AVwvQ"&gt;video &lt;/a&gt;posted on &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/tiktok/index.html" id="mol-ae16a780-5bd4-11f0-b17b-91b8673311f0"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt; to his more than 180,000 followers, he explained: ‘It takes strong circulation to get that blood all the way to those capillaries in the hair in your toes and feet.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He continued: 'When your body develops insulin resistance (it) damages circulation patterns all the way to the nerves and the blood vessels at the hair follicle base.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This will cut off nutrients to your skin and hair follicles (causing hair loss). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So, he warned: 'The higher the diabetic neuropathy the person had, the more loss of hair on their distal (the part farthest from the centre of the body) feet and toes.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The diabetes expert warned that hair loss on the lower legs and feet can be a sign of the disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His claim is backed up by a 2019 study of 107 patients, which found hair loss as a reliable indicator of nerve damage due to the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other symptoms he said may appear after the hair loss include brain fog, wound healing issues, vision loss, and kidney damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The diabetes expert, who has suffered from insulin resistance himself, now shares tips to overcome blood sugar, cholesterol and belly fat issues on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It comes as the number of people in the UK suffering from diabetes has reached a record high&lt;span&gt;—especially in the under 50s.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Diagnoses among the under-40s rose by 23 per cent between 2016/17 and 2020/21 but by 18 per cent among those aged 40 and over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Almost 4.3million people were living with diabetes in 2021/22, according to the latest figures for the UK. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are now around 3.78million people living with type 2 diabetes in the UK, of which 148,344 are under 40.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are two types of diabetes. Type 1 is an autoimmune disease diagnosed from birth, while type 2 is when the body struggles to produce enough insulin later in life&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;It comes as cases of diabetes in the UK reaching a record high amid the nation's obesity crisis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If you experience any of these symptoms, you should make an appointment with your GP who can arrange a blood test to check how high your blood sugar levels are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Type 2 diabetes can damage your blood vessels, causing potentially fatal complications like coronary heart disease and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The leading causes of type two diabetes are lifestyle factors like a poor diet, obesity and a lack of exercise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other symptoms of type 2 diabetes are increased thirst and urination, excessive hunger, fatigue, and losing weight without trying to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In some cases, people will be diagnosed with prediabetes—which is when your blood sugar levels are high, but not yet enough to be diagnosed with the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The main treatment is to make lifestyle changes such as eating a diet rich in fruit, vegetables, wholegrain foods and pulses like lentils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, some people who need medication may be offered metformin, which lowers the amount of glucose (sugar) in their blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a bid to tackle the obesity crisis in the UK, the government recently allowed GPs to prescribe weight loss medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This includes Mounjaro, which has long been hailed toe 'King Kong' of slimming jabs, despite initially being developed as a diabetes medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Earlier this year, US researchers found those on the injections typically lost a fifth of their body weight in just over a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, in recent weeks there has been growing concern over the side effects of the 'quick fix' medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Last month, the UK's drug watchdog found weight loss jabs were potentially linked to more than a hundred deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A total of 111 deaths were logged with the regulator, the Medicines and Healthcare products Regulatory Agency (MHRA), up to and including May 29. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;None of the fatalities, which have all been reported since the jabs were licensed for use in the UK, are proven to have been caused directly by the drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, health chiefs tasked with policing the safety of medicines admitted reports of side effects indicate 'a suspicion' they may have been to blame. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:51:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxOa19KSW9OcWdmbFp3Q1NzM1o0a2lCTDhZQ0VuYzhZUDJGTThrVDloU1NUcmRIZDhKeUNReWVsY2poVUdKWVVQR0pCVlc1aV9fajdaZUV2SWVwdnFOdm52SWt3aEE0NHh1WEtVWmEzdXlYQmY1WC1vU0lKZl9uaUxFblFodk1sM0FaUDlDbmNiaWw0T3lKUzlVa1I2M1c0YnZlazBFeg</guid></item><item><title>在奶奶和爷爷家观看黄金猎犬小狗日的视频-雅虎 | Video Shows a Golden Retriever Puppy’s Day at Grandma &amp; Grandpa’s - Yahoo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilAFBVV95cUxQbUsxMlZhNnhmbDBmdjBMMktDeTFqcGdBVWUyeUp2TXdBQ3p1V0JDNlV2cF9DQlV5azJtVjY0T2RIZG5jektHUnQtQVk3N0VQbnFza2tSYXFVRl91dktJeUZEUF8zTGNKTGRLdmQwYzRQa3JVSWh6aldEZkhNeHNtcExXejMyMlZLbG1vNzVrRUgwTjQy?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Every dog needs a change of scenery, and when it’s their favorite place, they show their happiness through actions. In one such Instagram video, a &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com/dog-breeds/golden-retriever" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Golden Retriever;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Golden Retriever&lt;/a&gt; puppy named Handsome enjoys his time at his grandma and grandpa’s house. From running freely in the backyard to having a heartfelt breakfast, the fur baby shows how he spends his day at his grandparents’ house. Aside from his adorable behavior, the clip also gains attention for the funny voiceover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;Instagram video shows what a Golden Retriever puppy does on his visit to grandparents’ home&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In an Instagram video, an owner captures their Golden Retriever puppy Handsome’s day when the latter visits his grandparents’ home. The uploader adds a voiceover, which explains what the pooch does at his favorite place. Meanwhile, the caption reads, “Favorite grand child status.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The video begins with Handsome introducing himself and informing that he will show his day at his grandma’s place. As he roams around inside the house with an attitude, the pooch then settles down for his breakfast. The voiceover, expressing the &lt;a href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/golden-retriever-toddler-reunion-video-064720789.html" data-ylk="slk:dog;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;dog&lt;/a&gt;’s thoughts, claims that he has to eat to avoid “bloating since it is swimsuit szn.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The puppy runs outside on the grass but claims it is his “least favorite part of” the day. Handsome seems to prefer lying under a shade as he is spotted under various trees, stating that he wants to prevent “wrinkles” and “spots.” Then, the pooch shows his eagerness to come inside to avoid the sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the next scene, the dog is in a crate in a moving vehicle, revealing that he is now going to visit “Grandpa and Grandma Jan’s house.” He is worried because his mom said that grandpa is not fond of dog hair. Despite the warning, the pup runs around the house and also tries to befriend a pet cat. At the end of the clip, his paw parent has to trick him with a treat to convince him to go to bed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Naturally, viewers lauded Handsome and his “cute” actions. They showered their “love” on him and also laughed at his behavior. Since the upload, the Golden Retriever puppy’s video with his grandpa and grandma has garnered over 1K likes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The post &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com/news/181940-golden-retriever-puppy-grandma-grandpa-visit-instagram-video" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Video Shows a Golden Retriever Puppy’s Day at Grandma &amp;amp; Grandpa’s;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Video Shows a Golden Retriever Puppy’s Day at Grandma &amp;amp; Grandpa’s&lt;/a&gt; appeared first on &lt;a href="https://dogtime.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:DogTime;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;DogTime&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:49:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxQbUsxMlZhNnhmbDBmdjBMMktDeTFqcGdBVWUyeUp2TXdBQ3p1V0JDNlV2cF9DQlV5azJtVjY0T2RIZG5jektHUnQtQVk3N0VQbnFza2tSYXFVRl91dktJeUZEUF8zTGNKTGRLdmQwYzRQa3JVSWh6aldEZkhNeHNtcExXejMyMlZLbG1vNzVrRUgwTjQy</guid></item><item><title>五分之一的心脏病发作没有表现出任何症状： Shriram Nene博士分享了应该注意的4个警告信号-印度时报 | 1 in 5 heart attacks show no symptoms: Doctor Shriram Nene shares 4 warning signs one should watch out for - The Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogJBVV95cUxNMkdPZ09QM01WczNYNUpIVko1T3BiYjV4di1zdzlZYkwwdWNfS2k2RFJEVElHZ0ViSXgxdUxMTXNXSDRITXVOYmRGLUwxNE9td0RNUTEtRk5xS09FSTMyNmpubjNMaVpVaU1hREdkMmlia2xJX0IzbXl0aVF4QndWbktlbFA0cXlNS0QzQVlWS0Y0Z0p4bjBKM1F3YTJJSjRQUEZhUnltYmxJaUVqYVFILXlublpvdDRtMnVpdm9CS0V4QjJ0UXNzNnpBVUZWS0EyOTMxWGhIa1dUbTl4ZWZpSF91UTczaUNGQ1dHMzZBYXhuZExsRVJOd1lHZ1FZMlowbU1GUG1udkh5aXdETmxhOC1HMEx2UUhGb1BrbVk2YV93dw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s a dangerous assumption floating around, that heart attacks only happen to the elderly or the visibly unfit. But as Dr Nene explains, that’s far from true. Even young, fit individuals may have hidden risks, genetic conditions, undetected artery issues, or stress-triggered cardiac events.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;A clean lifestyle doesn’t always mean a clean bill of heart health. This is why understanding silent signs and not relying only on traditional symptoms becomes so crucial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;[This article is intended for informational purposes only and does not substitute professional medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare provider for diagnosis and treatment of heart-related issues]&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;​&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 10:39:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogJBVV95cUxNMkdPZ09QM01WczNYNUpIVko1T3BiYjV4di1zdzlZYkwwdWNfS2k2RFJEVElHZ0ViSXgxdUxMTXNXSDRITXVOYmRGLUwxNE9td0RNUTEtRk5xS09FSTMyNmpubjNMaVpVaU1hREdkMmlia2xJX0IzbXl0aVF4QndWbktlbFA0cXlNS0QzQVlWS0Y0Z0p4bjBKM1F3YTJJSjRQUEZhUnltYmxJaUVqYVFILXlublpvdDRtMnVpdm9CS0V4QjJ0UXNzNnpBVUZWS0EyOTMxWGhIa1dUbTl4ZWZpSF91UTczaUNGQ1dHMzZBYXhuZExsRVJOd1lHZ1FZMlowbU1GUG1udkh5aXdETmxhOC1HMEx2UUhGb1BrbVk2YV93dw</guid></item><item><title>SNAP上的5个人分享了食品计划的正确和错误-雅虎 | 5 people on SNAP share what the food program gets right — and wrong - Yahoo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMizAFBVV95cUxQcGhTRlMtYXFtZUlSRFpSdzQzcmxMSGxkMml0ZUxMZWFNVlRES0liZUNIakFQSTl5TEdOUEtxY3ZDNElfeHpLUVIzREptcDcwQkN1NUhzYXh0U3JUbFg1eFphb25JbnU3LXI4NHB3T3FZQjM0ak0xNFdqYU95cGg5RGEwb0ZiWHpRWUtwR280SzlJZGx4SHU4M3RSQVAzanpxcUR4OXNLX19nbXlrTTJZTW5fdWg3bGxKVGVZNC1DU1hfdEQycmJHakc1WHE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:1;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.fns.usda.gov/snap/supplemental-nutrition-assistance-program" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:1;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program&lt;/a&gt; (SNAP), formerly known as food stamps, helps &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:2;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.cbpp.org/research/food-assistance/a-closer-look-at-who-benefits-from-snap-state-by-state-fact-sheets#Alabama" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:one in eight;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:2;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;one in eight&lt;/a&gt; Americans put food on the table, according to the Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (CBPP). SNAP is a lifeline for many individuals, families and people with disabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;More than 62% of SNAP recipients are part of families with children. In 2022, 20% of &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:3;pos:1" class="link " href="https://ifstudies.org/blog/food-stamps-and-family-snap-recipients-by-family-structure" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:children under 18;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:3;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;children under 18&lt;/a&gt; nationwide were in families receiving SNAP benefits. More than 38% of SNAP recipients are from working families. And more than 37% of families receiving SNAP include someone who is &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:4;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.cbpp.org/research/food-assistance/a-closer-look-at-who-benefits-from-snap-state-by-state-fact-sheets#Alabama" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:disabled or elderly;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:4;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;disabled or elderly&lt;/a&gt;, according to the CBPP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“Without SNAP, families miss meals. Kids show up to school hungry. Parents skip groceries to keep the lights on. We’re not talking about convenience. We’re talking about survival,” Erica Williams, executive director of the nonprofit &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:5;pos:1" class="link " href="http://www.aredcircle.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:A Red Circle;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:5;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;A Red Circle&lt;/a&gt; and co-author of the peer-reviewed food policy brief &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:6;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.foodsystemsjournal.org/index.php/fsj/article/view/1349" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Food Pricing and Consumer Choice;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:6;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Food Pricing and Consumer Choice&lt;/a&gt;, tells Yahoo. SNAP is crucial because “it’s the most direct tool we have to reduce hunger,” she says. Most of the families Williams works with tell her that they don’t want to be on SNAP forever but need help while they “get stable,” she points out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;SNAP can be used to buy &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:7;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.fns.usda.gov/snap/eligible-food-items" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:a variety of foods;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:7;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;a variety of foods&lt;/a&gt;, including dairy products, meat, poultry, fish, fruits and vegetables and snack foods. However, the program has limitations. “You can’t buy hot food or household goods like soap and diapers,” Williams says. “You also can’t buy prepared meals, which means parents working two jobs can’t just grab something healthy on the go. It reinforces exhaustion.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Although SNAP helps many people get by when they don’t earn enough to buy groceries, it often isn’t enough. Rising food costs and eligibility restrictions make it challenging for many SNAP recipients to meet their needs. Yahoo talked to five people about what being on SNAP is really like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="were-both-trying-but-were-still-hungry"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'We’re both trying. But we’re still hungry.'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Danielle, a single mother in Missouri, works full-time in administrative support. She started receiving SNAP benefits when her son Marcus, now 20, was a baby, and his father stopped paying child support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Today, Danielle works 40 hours a week and still receives SNAP benefits. Marcus, who is neurodivergent, lives at home while he takes classes at a community college and works about 15 hours a week. Yet, despite having two working adults in the house, Danielle and Marcus don’t earn enough to feed themselves adequately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Danielle’s SNAP benefits help, but they are still struggling. Marcus stopped receiving benefits when he turned 18 because he was in school full-time and wasn’t working enough hours to qualify for SNAP. Now, Danielle has to feed herself and her son with SNAP benefits meant for one adult. “I understand the rules,” Danielle tells Yahoo. However, she emphasizes that she’s unwilling to let her son go hungry or drop out of school and have a chance at a more financially stable life. “That means I skip meals so he doesn’t have to,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Danielle usually buys foods like dry pasta, rice and canned vegetables to stretch her grocery budget. Eggs are a rare luxury, and she relies on a nonprofit food bank for fresh produce. Most of Danielle and Marcus’s diet is “Heavy. Salty,” Marcus says. “You feel full, then you crash. I get foggy. Slow. Food’s supposed to be medicine,” Marcus tells Yahoo. However, his limited diet often makes him feel worse. “We’re both trying. But we’re still hungry,” Danielle says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Danielle wants people to know that “this isn’t about laziness. It’s not about people gaming the system. It’s about working families, caregiving parents, students trying to get out and still falling short.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="snap-is-not-charity-its-a-stabilizing-force"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'SNAP is not charity. It’s a stabilizing force.'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Like Danielle, Jessica is also a single mother living in Missouri. She’s been on and off SNAP since 2012. She typically buys items like flour, cereal, cheese and salmon with her SNAP benefits. Occasionally, she buys fresh fruit and vegetables and treats like ice cream or chicken nuggets for her son. However, due to the higher cost of fruit and vegetables, Jessica often finds that her benefits aren’t enough to support a healthy diet. To fill the gap, Jessica relies on nonprofits like A Red Circle. “The biggest challenge of being on SNAP is finding affordable quality food,” Jessica tells Yahoo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Even though Jessica would like to feed her son a healthy diet, she laments that her SNAP benefits are often just enough to cover “pantry fillers.” Another challenge to staying healthy on SNAP is that "you can’t buy vitamins, medicine or supplements,” she says. That makes it harder to stay healthy in the long run, she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Nevertheless, SNAP is a lifeline for Jessica. “Without SNAP, feeding my family would be incredibly hard. With the cost of living so high and wages so low, it would be a serious struggle,” she explains. “SNAP is not charity. It’s a stabilizing force,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="i-literally-wouldnt-be-surviving-without-snap"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'I literally wouldn't be surviving without SNAP'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Megan, who lives alone and has chronic Lyme disease and other tick-borne illnesses, worked as a public servant in New York for 24 years. For her entire career, she helped others in need, including people struggling with mental illness and families whose loved ones were placed in child or adult protective services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Although Megan wanted to continue working, her health worsened, and she had to leave her job. Once Megan’s savings ran out, she relied on local food pantries for food. When that wasn’t enough, she applied for SNAP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Megan still visits food pantries. However, she uses her SNAP benefits to “round out meals from the ingredients the food pantry provides,” she says. Since Megan usually gets canned and boxed goods from the food pantry, she usually uses her SNAP benefits to buy meat and produce. However, she notes that because of the high price of fresh fruit, produce “feels like a luxury.” Moreover, although Megan tries to cook everything from scratch to save money, she keeps one or two pre-prepared meals on hand to eat when her illness flares and she’s too fatigued to cook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“I literally wouldn't be surviving without SNAP,” Megan tells Yahoo. “Having SNAP has given me some peace of mind regarding access to food.” However, Megan is concerned because SNAP benefits don’t automatically increase when &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:8;pos:1" class="link " href="https://www.pbs.org/newshour/show/why-snap-benefits-arent-keeping-up-with-the-rising-cost-of-food" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:grocery prices;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:8;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;grocery prices&lt;/a&gt; go up. Due to rising grocery prices, “the SNAP benefits don't stretch as far in covering what's needed for a month,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Megan is doing what she can to help with her recovery, but doesn’t know when or if she will be able to return to work. “Every fiber of me just wants to have my prior level of functioning back,” she says. “I loved the work that I did. I loved my clients.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She adds: “I'm hopeful that I will medically improve enough to be able to return to work and discontinue SNAP, but it will realistically be a few years, at best.” Until then, “SNAP is a lifeline for me,” Megan says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="i-would-have-had-a-hard-time-paying-for-my-essentials"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'I would have had a hard time paying for my essentials.'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Ryan Wilson, a disabled videographer from Colorado, was on SNAP for seven years. Like &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:9;pos:1" href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/why-including-people-disabilities-workforce-133700705.html" data-ylk="slk:many people with disabilities;cpos:9;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;" class="link  yahoo-link"&gt;many people with disabilities&lt;/a&gt;, he had a hard time finding a job that paid him a living wage. “The job market was and is tough,” Wilson tells Yahoo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When he wasn’t earning enough to cover his basic expenses, SNAP helped him get by. He told Yahoo that without SNAP, “I would have had a hard time paying for my essentials” like food and medical care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, Wilson emphasizes that SNAP helped him survive but not thrive. When he was on SNAP, he couldn’t use his benefits to buy necessities other than food. Additionally, he could only use his benefits at select locations like big box stores, even though smaller grocery stores were often closer. “That is an inconvenience, especially for someone with a disability that impacts their mobility,” Wilson says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Now Wilson runs a video production company called &lt;a data-i13n="elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:10;pos:1" class="link " href="https://teamtrustproductions.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Team Trust Productions;elm:context_link;elmt:doNotAffiliate;cpos:10;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Team Trust Productions&lt;/a&gt;. His income has increased, and he no longer needs SNAP to ensure he can access enough food. Wilson is grateful he received SNAP when he needed it, but he never expected to receive SNAP benefits forever. “It's a temporary option. It does not have to be a permanent solution to financial uncertainty,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl" data-jump-link-target="" id="i-would-definitely-not-be-eating-three-meals-a-day"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;'I would definitely not be eating three meals a day'&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Although Laura, a single woman from Pennsylvania, worked full-time, her income wasn’t enough to support herself. For three years, Laura received SNAP benefits to help her get by. Eventually, she started earning a higher salary and no longer needed SNAP to buy food. However, in early 2025, Laura lost her job. Once her unemployment benefits ran out, she started receiving SNAP benefits again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Without SNAP, “I would definitely not be eating three meals a day,” Laura tells Yahoo. She usually uses her SNAP benefits to buy frozen fruits and vegetables, chicken thighs and seasonal fruit and vegetables, which she finds more affordable than out-of-season produce. When she can afford it, Laura buys cheese and coffee. She also goes to her local food pantry to supplement her groceries. However, she emphasizes that food pantries are “meant to be just that — supplemental, not a source of regular groceries.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Laura is grateful for the SNAP benefits she receives, but thinks some aspects of the program need to be changed. “I wish we could buy paper products,” she says. “Toilet paper is just as necessary as apples, and I wish I could just get everything at once.” She also wishes that restrictions on what SNAP recipients can buy, such as candy and hot foods, would be removed. Plus, Laura finds it difficult to figure out which foods she can buy with her benefits and which are excluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“No one should be told what food they're allowed to buy. Food is a human right,” Laura says. “By making laws that just blindly eliminate whole sections of foods, that just makes it harder on people with specific diets. Or, it makes it impossible to give a little kid a birthday party,” she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Most importantly, Laura wishes she could rely on SNAP being around for those who need it. She’s still looking for a full-time job that pays enough for her to support herself. Until then, however, "it’s always in the back of my mind that my access to food could be taken away at any time. Depending on a program that's outside of your control, just to feed yourself, is terrifying,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 09:00:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxQcGhTRlMtYXFtZUlSRFpSdzQzcmxMSGxkMml0ZUxMZWFNVlRES0liZUNIakFQSTl5TEdOUEtxY3ZDNElfeHpLUVIzREptcDcwQkN1NUhzYXh0U3JUbFg1eFphb25JbnU3LXI4NHB3T3FZQjM0ak0xNFdqYU95cGg5RGEwb0ZiWHpRWUtwR280SzlJZGx4SHU4M3RSQVAzanpxcUR4OXNLX19nbXlrTTJZTW5fdWg3bGxKVGVZNC1DU1hfdEQycmJHakc1WHE</guid></item><item><title>轮式肺癌筛查-《纽约时报》 | Lung Cancer Screening on Wheels - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxQVXlIOEJHMm5uMkRtZHJHMzBfd3R4ZXRLTmM1b05YQVZzZFQwdFBDT3BPQjh3MDRWYUZFOHNBNDBGaW5PUDRNaDllamNnNVNfOTFfV2Z4TkMzWE80bXhIQXNXRjJlMTBUWklPczJnWFBPQ0VuQTI0R0M2UkJWa0VBMS1CLXdDQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 07:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQVXlIOEJHMm5uMkRtZHJHMzBfd3R4ZXRLTmM1b05YQVZzZFQwdFBDT3BPQjh3MDRWYUZFOHNBNDBGaW5PUDRNaDllamNnNVNfOTFfV2Z4TkMzWE80bXhIQXNXRjJlMTBUWklPczJnWFBPQ0VuQTI0R0M2UkJWa0VBMS1CLXdDQQ</guid></item><item><title>轮式肺癌筛查-《纽约时报》 | Lung Cancer Screening on Wheels - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihwFBVV95cUxOT1hZM3VUaEJ0bm03UXhOcWxpbjRsVnJWYWRuMEpHT01rRlZ5WFgweV9lMEw1STlhRnFkNkpFOHdZXzNvSWpZemZnTllRQi1BOGtKUlVNRndfZEVEdlZZdHhoaEJ1VnEtam5XUzBKbGxhaUowcHAxeVplOTBNaTdiUzNEZ0hIaDQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 07:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxOT1hZM3VUaEJ0bm03UXhOcWxpbjRsVnJWYWRuMEpHT01rRlZ5WFgweV9lMEw1STlhRnFkNkpFOHdZXzNvSWpZemZnTllRQi1BOGtKUlVNRndfZEVEdlZZdHhoaEJ1VnEtam5XUzBKbGxhaUowcHAxeVplOTBNaTdiUzNEZ0hIaDQ</guid></item><item><title>蛋白质对抗：动物与植物-您的身体真正需要什么-印度时报 | Protein face-off: Animal vs. plant—what your body really needs - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi7wFBVV95cUxOSDRYRmdEWWMtU2N1eUYtUWIzZ19XTHdva2hySUxScDVQeTRBZEhBRnY1MFNhckRzVDE1ajdiakR0ZkhaUGw1TklOZTNWUkZIR2VFUVlTcVNPMzhNRWFGQjh2OFhZTWlUZldHX1A1WWJQNVotVDVJN1FHajRIc2xBVXVlREtQZHRFdEwzTnVyOURVcWYwTlVvNWtHX3pkbHNPVkJpcFR6QzVxSnRyYlhHUGZRSXYzTHA3eGtVTGs0N3AtNktwZDlPVnBmRlRrd2JwclRfbUVwTFlMd1cybkVfOWc1VkRHNnBsM0czRWpvNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Plant proteins are the food sources that come from plants, including legumes such as lentils and chickpeas, beans, whole grains including seeds, nuts, quinoa, white rice, wheat, and vegetables. Plant-based sources are often considered incomplete food sources as they lack essential amino acids. But consuming it with the right food choices, such as rice with beans or hummus with whole-grain bread, can provide you with all the essential amino acids. “Plant proteins offer additional health benefits—fiber, antioxidants, and lower fat content—making them excellent for heart health, diabetes, and weight management." They are more environmentally sustainable and can be easily produced with few resources and are the best choice for those looking to be environmentally conscious. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 04:01:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7wFBVV95cUxOSDRYRmdEWWMtU2N1eUYtUWIzZ19XTHdva2hySUxScDVQeTRBZEhBRnY1MFNhckRzVDE1ajdiakR0ZkhaUGw1TklOZTNWUkZIR2VFUVlTcVNPMzhNRWFGQjh2OFhZTWlUZldHX1A1WWJQNVotVDVJN1FHajRIc2xBVXVlREtQZHRFdEwzTnVyOURVcWYwTlVvNWtHX3pkbHNPVkJpcFR6QzVxSnRyYlhHUGZRSXYzTHA3eGtVTGs0N3AtNktwZDlPVnBmRlRrd2JwclRfbUVwTFlMd1cybkVfOWc1VkRHNnBsM0czRWpvNA</guid></item><item><title>使您的锻炼与您的个性相匹配可以使锻炼更愉快，并给出更好的结果- CNN | Matching your workouts to your personality could make exercise more enjoyable and give better results - CNN</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxPTld0SjZ6TWlRZGdDbHdjeDZ5anBxWEVCOEt5T1Y4UW80dVVKWktTUE5HcV95cDlCTXVuT2Z2dEYwVWE5TkhUNlotbldzVlVqY3dwNGZWak52SktEZm02alJqQnlPYjkteml6NGRibkFlT1dXc2lRV010bkVCUHpvS25sdlRiY3JRQnozRGJzbTlOQdIBlwFBVV95cUxQV1RiWFplSHZDUlY2ZUplSUQwRmxGTGhYV0FqaDAybU82Z05mbmxiR3o0aEwzaEhPS3BmYmh1OTVtVXd5UDJWcmF6QVZFdlliNGREU0pfRjU3NFZTWndfT0Rqd0E4MXNSVXNWbmV3bFFLY0ljbzVjMkkxTlFMTmpDSG84Yzk4V01naUpPVVc3WUEtTHU0ZHBn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/action-bar/instances/cmct68azg00ei27nj32uwb4o2@published" data-label-id-prefix="action-bar-start-of-article" class="action-bar" data-dynamic-breakpoint-placement='{"extraLarge":{"placement":".layout-article-elevate__left"}}' data-expand-conditions='{"follow":{"extraLarge":{"alwaysExpand":true}},"shareOptions":{"large":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"medium":{"maxNumOfActions":1},"extraLarge":{"withAction":"follow","maxNumOfActions":2}}}'&gt;
    &lt;p class="action-bar__overlay"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet" tabindex="-1"&gt;
        
            
            &lt;div class="action-bar__action-sheet--action" data-title="share options"&gt;
                  &lt;div data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/social-share/instances/cmct68azg00el27nj3t240kdw@published" class="social-share_labelled-list"&gt;
    &lt;div class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links vossi-social-share_labelled-list" data-type="share-links"&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.facebook.com/dialog/share?app_id=80401312489&amp;amp;href=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F07%2F08%2Fhealth%2Fpersonality-type-enjoy-exercise-intl-scli-wellness&amp;amp;display=popup" data-type="facebook" aria-label="share with facebook" title="Share with Facebook"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-facebook-circle" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.04139 1.33301C11.7458 1.33301 14.7488 4.33601 14.7488 8.04042C14.7488 11.3884 12.296 14.1632 9.08943 14.6663V9.97928H10.6523L10.9497 8.04042H9.08943V6.78225C9.08943 6.25182 9.34934 5.73475 10.1825 5.73475H11.0283V4.08409C11.0283 4.08409 10.2607 3.95309 9.52685 3.95309C7.99476 3.95309 6.99336 4.88165 6.99336 6.56269V8.04042H5.29031V9.97928H6.99336V14.6663C3.78677 14.1632 1.33398 11.3882 1.33398 8.04042C1.33398 4.33601 4.33699 1.33301 8.04139 1.33301Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Facebook&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://twitter.com/intent/tweet?text=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F07%2F08%2Fhealth%2Fpersonality-type-enjoy-exercise-intl-scli-wellness" data-type="x" aria-label="share with x" title="Share with X"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-x-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.99386 8.11503L0 0.666992H4.74756L8.44753 5.27039L12.4004 0.687719H15.0151L9.71175 6.84331L16 14.667H11.2666L7.2603 9.6887L2.98317 14.6532H0.354296L5.99386 8.11503ZM11.9565 13.287L2.91105 2.04698H4.0571L13.0912 13.287H11.9565Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Tweet&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        &lt;a class="social-share_labelled-list__share" href="mailto:?subject=CNN%20content%20share&amp;amp;body=Check%20out%20this%20article%3A%0Ahttps%3A%2F%2Fwww.cnn.com%2F2025%2F07%2F08%2Fhealth%2Fpersonality-type-enjoy-exercise-intl-scli-wellness" data-type="email" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" aria-label="share with email" title="Share with email"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-email-share" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 24 24" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M2 6C2 4.89543 2.89543 4 4 4H20C21.1046 4 22 4.89543 22 6V18C22 19.1046 21.1046 20 20 20H4C2.89543 20 2 19.1046 2 18V6ZM4 6H20V9.11604L12 11.9396L4 9.11604V6ZM4 11.237V18H20V11.237L12.3328 13.943C12.1174 14.019 11.8825 14.019 11.6672 13.943L4 11.237Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Email&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/a&gt;
        &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__share" data-url="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/08/health/personality-type-enjoy-exercise-intl-scli-wellness" data-type="copy" aria-label="copy link to clipboard" title="Copy link to clipboard"&gt;
                &lt;svg class="icon-hyperlink" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none"&gt;
&lt;path fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M5.64373 10.3574C5.38338 10.0971 5.38338 9.67496 5.64373 9.41461L9.88637 5.17197C10.1467 4.91162 10.5688 4.91162 10.8292 5.17197C11.0895 5.43232 11.0895 5.85443 10.8292 6.11478L6.58654 10.3574C6.32619 10.6178 5.90408 10.6178 5.64373 10.3574Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M4.22952 8.94321L5.64373 7.52899C5.90408 7.26865 5.90408 6.84654 5.64373 6.58619C5.38338 6.32584 4.96127 6.32584 4.70092 6.58619L3.28671 8.0004C1.98496 9.30215 1.98496 11.4127 3.28671 12.7144C4.58846 14.0162 6.69901 14.0162 8.00075 12.7144L9.41497 11.3002C9.67532 11.0399 9.67532 10.6178 9.41497 10.3574C9.15462 10.0971 8.73251 10.0971 8.47216 10.3574L7.05795 11.7716C6.2769 12.5527 5.01057 12.5527 4.22952 11.7716C3.44847 10.9906 3.44847 9.72426 4.22952 8.94321Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;path d="M8.94356 4.22916L7.52935 5.64338C7.269 5.90373 6.84689 5.90373 6.58654 5.64338C6.32619 5.38303 6.32619 4.96092 6.58654 4.70057L8.00075 3.28635C9.3025 1.98461 11.4131 1.98461 12.7148 3.28635C14.0165 4.5881 14.0165 6.69865 12.7148 8.0004L11.3006 9.41461C11.0402 9.67496 10.6181 9.67496 10.3578 9.41461C10.0974 9.15426 10.0974 8.73215 10.3578 8.4718L11.772 7.05759C12.553 6.27654 12.553 5.01021 11.772 4.22916C10.9909 3.44812 9.72461 3.44811 8.94356 4.22916Z" fill="#0C0C0C"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;
&lt;/svg&gt;

                &lt;span class="social-share_labelled-list__share-links--label"&gt;Link&lt;/span&gt;
        &lt;/button&gt;
        
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__open" data-type="open" aria-label="open social share" title="Open social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-share-os" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19 12c.394 0 .714.32.714.714v8.572c0 .394-.32.714-.714.714H4.714A.715.715 0 014 21.286v-8.572a.715.715 0 011.429 0v7.857h12.857v-7.857c0-.394.32-.714.714-.714zm-7.664-9.79a.73.73 0 011.024 0l.076.075 4.916 4.854c.183.18.27.449.188.69a.734.734 0 01-1.216.314L12.57 4.5v11.786c0 .357-.357.714-.714.714s-.714-.359-.714-.714V4.5L7.372 8.143a.73.73 0 01-1.102-.091c-.21-.289-.149-.694.106-.946l4.884-4.821z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button class="social-share_labelled-list__close" data-type="close" aria-label="close social share" title="Close social share"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="icon-ui-close" viewbox="0 0 24 24" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;path d="M19.787 18.758l-6.792-6.781 6.746-6.735a.728.728 0 00-1.028-1.03l-6.747 6.737-6.711-6.7a.728.728 0 00-1.028 1.03l6.71 6.698-6.723 6.712a.727.727 0 101.027 1.03l6.725-6.714 6.793 6.782a.725.725 0 001.028 0 .727.727 0 000-1.03"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;

    &lt;/button&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct68azg00ek27njfsa92a3m@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Making &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/interactive/exercise-recommendations-workout-quiz-wellness/"&gt;exercise&lt;/a&gt; fun is the holy grail for many people who can’t quite find the &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/04/26/sport/london-marathon-running-spt-intl"&gt;motivation&lt;/a&gt; to work out.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct68fcv0000356mqqowwdbc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But rather than forcing yourself to enjoy running or that gym class you once attended, the solution may lie in something more straightforward — simply matching a workout to your personality type, according to a study published Tuesday in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/psychology/articles/10.3389/fpsyg.2025.1587472/abstract" target="_blank"&gt;Frontiers in Psychology&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6bbjs0006356mwfvvl1gl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            That’s because people with different personality traits enjoy different types of exercise, the study found.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6dmd90009356mau78elt2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            More extroverted people, for example, prefer high-intensity training sessions with others, such as team sports, while people who scored highly on “neuroticism,” a metric that measures someone’s emotional instability, preferred private workouts without people watching them and punctuated by short breaks.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6dtzl000c356m6spz1fdv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As for those who scored highly on conscientiousness, they “were more likely to have a well-rounded fitness … and we think that’s because conscientious individuals are more likely to be driven by the fact that exercise is good for them,” said the study’s co-lead author, Flaminia Ronca, an associate professor in exercise science at University College London.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6e0e0000f356mhyrknkc7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Personality determines which intensities and forms of exercises we’re attracted to. … If we can understand that, then we can make that first step in engagement and exercise in sedentary individuals,” she told CNN.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6f4mc000i356mh58fc80x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            These findings have important implications for encouraging more people to exercise, especially since just 22.5% of adults and 19% of adolescents worldwide manage the &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/physical-activity" target="_blank"&gt;World Health Organization-recommended&lt;/a&gt; 150 minutes of physical activity per week, according to the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6ffx3000n356m3fbozy1p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            By focusing on personality types, health care providers may be able to offer a “more personalized approach to exercise,” said Angelina Sutin, a professor at Florida State University who specializes in investigating links between personality and health, and who wasn’t involved in the study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6fqzh000q356mwsth2b0n@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Typically … we tell people to exercise and just say: ‘We know high-intensity interval training is good for you, so you should do it,’” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6g7k8000t356m08kzz03z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “But for people high in neuroticism, they’re not going to do it, and we also know that low-intensity exercise can be beneficial too. Knowing that somebody is high in neuroticism, recommending that kind of exercise, maybe people will be more likely to engage in it.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6gcfx000w356mmea0y3vf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It is also important to note that personality traits interact with each other, Ronca added. Some people score highly on both neuroticism and conscientiousness, meaning that although they may find exercise anxiety-inducing, they are much more likely to do it since they know it is good for them, she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6hakc000z356m9zdq8vpm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            To reach their findings, Ronca and her colleagues in London first directed the 132 study participants, aged between 25 and 51 years old, to complete a questionnaire revealing their personality traits.
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6henz0012356m3zrwjy1d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study employed a commonly used model that conceptualizes someone’s personality through five traits — extroversion, neuroticism, agreeableness, openness and conscientiousness.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6j1lm0017356mtat7iplm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Personality traits … they’re just descriptions of the way people behave in certain situations,” Paul Burgess, a professor of neuroscience at UCL who co-led the study, told CNN.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6jqqm001a356mf5s98lgi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “And the way that people behave in certain situations is determined to a large degree by their brain capabilities, what they notice, what they pay attention to, what they can remember, how fast they can react.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6jvca001d356me5yr0fm1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The researchers then ran fitness tests on the participants and randomly sorted them into two groups. One group was given an eight-week cycling and strength plan, while the control group&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;did 10 minutes a week of stretching exercises. Of the original 132 participants, 86 completed both pre- and post-testing either side of these eight weeks.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6lcmn001g356murskf0jw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The study team found that, although fitness improved across all personality types for those who completed the cycling and strength program, there was a marked difference in enjoyment of the exercises. More extroverted people enjoyed the higher-intensity lab fitness tests, while more “neurotic” people enjoyed the home-based light-intensity sessions.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6lidg001j356migml94oo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Personality traits also informed how exercise influenced someone’s stress levels. People who scored highly in neuroticism had a significant reduction in self-reported stress, much more than in any other group, the study found.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6lv9m001m356mvq32ltzm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Those who would benefit the most from a stress reduction are the ones who actually showed a decrease in stress following those eight weeks of exercise,” Ronca said. “And I think that’s quite a powerful message to give.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6lzqt001p356mxlzskehv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Given the many benefits of exercise, including stress reduction, both Ronca and Burgess hope their findings encourage people to find alternative ways of exercise outside the more traditional workouts they might dislike.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6m6j3001s356m4nsv2p91@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There’s a danger, perhaps, that the focus becomes … competitive sports and serious engagement at a time when young people are starting to have lots more demands on them,” Burgess said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmct6mdlu001v356mkg2tdlv3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There are a lot of personalities that don’t respond well to that kind of situation, that find it quite stressful.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmcttl7og00073b6nvdyhc1o8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    &lt;em&gt;Sign up for &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/newsletters/fitness-life-but-better?source=nl-acq_article"&gt;&lt;em&gt;CNN’s Fitness, But Better newsletter series&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;. Our seven-part guide will help you ease into a healthy routine, backed by experts.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 04:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPTld0SjZ6TWlRZGdDbHdjeDZ5anBxWEVCOEt5T1Y4UW80dVVKWktTUE5HcV95cDlCTXVuT2Z2dEYwVWE5TkhUNlotbldzVlVqY3dwNGZWak52SktEZm02alJqQnlPYjkteml6NGRibkFlT1dXc2lRV010bkVCUHpvS25sdlRiY3JRQnozRGJzbTlOQdIBlwFBVV95cUxQV1RiWFplSHZDUlY2ZUplSUQwRmxGTGhYV0FqaDAybU82Z05mbmxiR3o0aEwzaEhPS3BmYmh1OTVtVXd5UDJWcmF6QVZFdlliNGREU0pfRjU3NFZTWndfT0Rqd0E4MXNSVXNWbmV3bFFLY0ljbzVjMkkxTlFMTmpDSG84Yzk4V01naUpPVVc3WUEtTHU0ZHBn</guid></item><item><title>高血压到糖尿病：根据美国顶级医生的说法，常见健康问题的最佳食物-印度时报 | High blood pressure to diabetes: Best foods for common health issues, according to a top US doctor - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogJBVV95cUxOaGFxSHRpMldTZ20yQThHbVliTWx2OE1VMFM3cmFob2U3ZmZUNU5aMzctWUU3d3VTcDBlU1EwNk04UXhOZFU1Zk5ubk8zYTFkLUc1QzdlNnV1ejlqZW9MSjk3M3NER1NiYng0WmhZWUlhNWNNS0t5aGgtcFFraVRSR3BjeTZIZWpzcFRHMkRWcjNlQlVMcmxYSHRUVEVsS2hIX0tjUHY2UjFrY1B6RmFvY1pON001T1I4NnBfdkNtTndsekd1a0JvSy1LX2UyczJfNlJuY1AwQnBueDc1a0ptZmxnb0VGRmZfNnBkaGdxWWV5NVczREVUNjVmQlZ4RGgwemtWUWhwTFRmM0FjRHRTZU5Hd0d0Mm9vQ3I5WEhLMnRlZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;We all know that food has a huge impact on health. What we eat has profound effects on our bodies, minds, and overall well-being. But have you ever heard of food being medicine?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr. Saurabh Sethi, a California-based gastroenterologist trained at Harvard and Stanford, the right foods not only nourish us but also heal. “You’d be surprised how much your food choices affect not just your energy, but also your blood pressure, blood sugar, mood, and pain,” he said in a video shared on Instagram.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;5 Simple ways to bring down high BP&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The doctor has revealed foods that can improve 6 common health conditions. “These aren’t trendy ‘superfoods.’ They’re supported by research and can make a real difference when used consistently,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-type="in_view" class="  "&gt;&lt;div class="EEW3_ timeline_pollWrapper_as " data-scrollga="scroll#poll_view"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="hLnAH"&gt;Poll&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="KEEGr"&gt;Do you believe that food can be used as medicine?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Beets for blood pressure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Millions of people across the globe have high blood pressure, or hypertension. This condition, though common is one of the leading causes of chronic illnesses, including heart disease, stroke, and kidney failure, worldwide. It is essential to manage hypertension effectively. Dr. Sethi says beetroot is good for managing high blood pressure. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rich in nitrates, beets help dilate blood vessels, improve blood flow, and reduce blood pressure. A 2017 meta-analysis has shown that &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5683004/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;beetroot juice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; can lower systolic blood pressure by 4-5 mmHg. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Oats for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;diabetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="oats" msid="122286912" title="(Pic courtesy: iStock)" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/thumb/imgsize-23456,msid-122286912,width-600,resizemode-4/oats.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;(Pic courtesy: iStock)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sethi recommends oats to manage diabetes. Oats are rich in soluble fiber, particularly beta-glucan, which slows down glucose absorption and helps stabilize blood sugar levels. A 2022 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9438016/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that regular oat consumption improved insulin sensitivity in type 2 diabetes patients. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Foods to treat anxiety and depression&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gastroenterologist also spoke about foods that can improve mental health. To ease anxiety, he recommends sipping chamomile tea. This tea is known for its calming properties. Chamomile contains apigenin, a compound that promotes relaxation by binding to brain receptors. A 2024 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11109927/#sec9" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; has confirmed that regular consumption of chamomile tea can improve anxiety symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Blueberries are Dr. Sethi’s go-to option for combating depression. This fruit is packed with antioxidants like flavonoids, which help reduce oxidative stress and inflammation linked to mood disorders. A 2024 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11139700/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that supplementation with blueberry juice for 20 days significantly reduced depression and anxiety symptoms in healthy adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Red meat for iron deficiency anemia &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sethi has recommended red meat to reverse iron deficiency anemia. Red meat is the best source of heme iron, which the body absorbs efficiently. A 3-ounce serving of red meat provides about 2.7 mg of iron, which almost completes the required daily value. He suggests eating lentils for people on a plant-based diet. Lentils offer non-heme iron and are enhanced when paired with vitamin C-rich foods like tomatoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Turmeric for back pain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are struggling with back pain, keep turmeric handy. Turmeric can alleviate back pain, thanks to its active compound, curcumin, which has potent anti-inflammatory properties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8572027/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; have consistently shown that curcumin reduces chronic pain and inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 03:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogJBVV95cUxOaGFxSHRpMldTZ20yQThHbVliTWx2OE1VMFM3cmFob2U3ZmZUNU5aMzctWUU3d3VTcDBlU1EwNk04UXhOZFU1Zk5ubk8zYTFkLUc1QzdlNnV1ejlqZW9MSjk3M3NER1NiYng0WmhZWUlhNWNNS0t5aGgtcFFraVRSR3BjeTZIZWpzcFRHMkRWcjNlQlVMcmxYSHRUVEVsS2hIX0tjUHY2UjFrY1B6RmFvY1pON001T1I4NnBfdkNtTndsekd1a0JvSy1LX2UyczJfNlJuY1AwQnBueDc1a0ptZmxnb0VGRmZfNnBkaGdxWWV5NVczREVUNjVmQlZ4RGgwemtWUWhwTFRmM0FjRHRTZU5Hd0d0Mm9vQ3I5WEhLMnRlZw</guid></item><item><title>心脏病专家分享了伤害心脏的10个日常习惯：盐过多导致睡眠不足-薄荷 | Cardiologists share 10 daily habits that hurt your heart: Too much salt to lack of sleep - Mint</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi4AFBVV95cUxNRng2RGJtWm9zMW4xeS1reGtJNmxhanB5UEJ6QXVRbkpZdEl2dnV2dng4T0hhNzQ0UzZWM3Rtb3VWVm91OHVkaEVUVDlVSU9MRksxMENQNHlYRURMek5kc0l3VmliMW5MODMxaVQ1NlIxdU04MmprWTFvbEFlWnZ0TDlsTVNhdGNUb1dTRlRoVTNKU1RyS3N1SU42NFBROEpycy1oOVFwLUtWYjNSeS0yclpPb3pyak5zZll4WmxZWVZyZndQV2FUMlhaTExCeUZTWkR6YWgtTndfamR0SDZaRg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="storyPage_storyContent__3xuFc"&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-0" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we think of heart disease, we often imagine it as a jolt — a heart attack, a stroke, or a medical emergency that arrives without warning. But according to cardiologists, the real danger to your heart could be hiding in the patterns of your everyday life. From late-night snacking to endless screen time, skipped meals to excess salt, it’s our daily routines that may be damaging our cardiovascular health, regardless of age, gender, or body size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-1" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is commonly believed that heart disease occurs only in older or obviously unfit individuals. Actually, cardiovascular disease can accumulate over years, maybe in young, thin, or 'healthy-looking' people. Heritability, stress, and lifestyle are factors, and prevention is the way to go," Dr Vikrant Khese, Cardiologist, Apollo Clinic, Kharadi, tells Health Shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-2" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, the incidence of heart-related conditions in individuals below 50 years of age, has seen a rise. This busts the myth that heart disease is only for older people or men, says Dr Nitin Bote, Interventional Cardiologist, K.J. Somaiya Hospital and Research Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-3" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are actually seeing an increasing number of young patients, including women, presenting with early symptoms of heart disease, caused by stress, lifestyle, and hormonal changes. Another myth is that if you take medication, lifestyle modifications are not required. This is very much not the case. Medication controls risk but long-term cardiac health relies on habit changes," adds Dr Bote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-4" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Daily habits that affect heart health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the daily lifestyle habits that may silently raise cardiovascular risk:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-5" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Chronic sleep deprivation&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inadequate rest increases stress hormone levels and blood pressure, straining the heart. According to a 2010 study about sleep duration as a risk factor for cardiovascular disease, there was an increased risk of Congenital Heart Disease in subjects with sustained 5 or fewer, 6, 7, and 9 hours or more, compared with those with 8 hours of sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-6" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Excess screen time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you spend hours on phones or in front of the TV, be mindful. Studies have found a correlation between excessive use of mobile phones and TV screens, and an increased risk of coronary artery disease, heart failure, and ischaemic heart disease. This is because these activities promote a sedentary lifestyle, affecting circulation and movement, and thereby raising the risk of obesity, which is not good for the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-7" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. Constant late-night snacking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Making a habit of late-night snacking can disrupt metabolism, impact insulin levels, and even add to weight and cholesterol issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-8" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Skipping meals or eating irregularly&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Bote, missing meals or consuming huge, irregular portions, can raise insulin levels and disrupt metabolic balance, indirectly impact &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.livemint.com/web-stories/5-simple-ways-to-boost-your-cardiovascular-health-visual-story-11733739591540.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="cardiovascular health"&gt;cardiovascular health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-9" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Excess salt intake&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most overlooked threats for your heart? Salt. Both Dr Khese and Dr Bote, agree that excessive salt is one of the biggest risks for heart damage. "Through processed snack foods, restaurant meals, or what may be perceived as benign condiments, most individuals take in twice the daily recommended amount of sodium," says Dr Bote. Explaining the risks, Dr Khese adds, "Consuming salt in excess on a regular basis increases blood sodium concentrations that attract fluid into the blood vessels, causing them to swell. This is what increases blood pressure and causes the heart to work more forcefully, which can lead to hypertension, left ventricular hypertrophy (thickening of heart muscle), and eventually heart failure. Too much salt consumption also hardens arteries in the long term."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-11" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;6. High sugar and trans-fat consumption&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to take care of your heart? Give up or reduce sugary drinks, packaged snacks, and fried foods, which tend to increase inflammation and unhealthy cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-12" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;7. Low intake of fibre, fruits, and vegetables&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lack of nutrient-dense foods means the body misses out on key antioxidants and heart-protective fibre. Your diet plays a key role in protecting your heart, so if you consume a high-trans fat diet with added sugar and red meat, with low fibre, fruit, and vegetable consumption, you may be inviting a cardiovascular risk, says Dr Khese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-13" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;8. Physical inactivity&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even normal-weight individuals are at risk for unfavourable lipid profiles, hypertension, and insulin resistance if they are sedentary. Sedentary life affects circulation, causes inflammation, and promotes the development of plaque in the arteries, independent of body size. "Everyday physical movement, even just walking, can dramatically lower cardiovascular risk," asserts Dr Bote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-14" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;9. Unmanaged chronic stress&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-term emotional stress can elevate blood pressure and contribute to hormonal imbalances that affect heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-15" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;10. Skipping routine medical check-ups&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missing preventive screenings can delay diagnosis of high blood pressure, cholesterol, or early-stage heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-16" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to improve your heart health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prevention is the best cure! So, making simple, sustainable shifts like eating more fibre, avoiding sugary beverages, sleeping well, managing stress, and even simply &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.livemint.com/web-stories/how-walking-daily-improves-your-health-visual-story-11740563987461.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="walking"&gt;walking&lt;/a&gt; for 30 minutes daily — can dramatically reduce long-term heart disease risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-17" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regular health check-ups, especially after the age of 30, are crucial to catch warning signs before they turn critical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="article-index-18" class="storyParagraph"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Heart disease is preventable in most cases. By being mindful of what we eat, staying physically active, managing stress, and getting enough sleep, we can protect our hearts from damage that builds silently over time," says Dr Bote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="end-of-story-0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Mint</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 03:30:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4AFBVV95cUxNRng2RGJtWm9zMW4xeS1reGtJNmxhanB5UEJ6QXVRbkpZdEl2dnV2dng4T0hhNzQ0UzZWM3Rtb3VWVm91OHVkaEVUVDlVSU9MRksxMENQNHlYRURMek5kc0l3VmliMW5MODMxaVQ1NlIxdU04MmprWTFvbEFlWnZ0TDlsTVNhdGNUb1dTRlRoVTNKU1RyS3N1SU42NFBROEpycy1oOVFwLUtWYjNSeS0yclpPb3pyak5zZll4WmxZWVZyZndQV2FUMlhaTExCeUZTWkR6YWgtTndfamR0SDZaRg</guid></item><item><title>研究警告说，常见的肠道细菌将导致数百万例胃癌病例-印度时报 | Common gut bacteria set to cause millions of stomach cancer cases, study warns - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwJBVV95cUxQOTQ4RldWR09jUHRGX2VfMWtGajVrUDNCeW55WnFhNlJObjZjNmR2dXR3V2FZYzRGcVFtLUxfaU5Na0RSREJ2NWJpVGgyNU1rbVhySmE0NkJpdkduR0J2VG5LT3V4ZW8yMTBEdjhGQVg3eWZUY0Ftdm5Cd25EMU5uYVI0Tkxjcm1fU1B1TlVadHJqS0pvTFhkckZoSkpBWi1MUmE1eEpuc2hweTk1aThKb0QyMnZoRE9CRV9NZFpKUXkyRDN1QUFfNjVvdW5DVUsxM0JHclFONDIwWGhNa3FqRlpDbjQwUklGMmJVemgycmRabnpsNVgyUXJtUjZ0YlRHeUhCbU4zYm9CSWFiWm9KYTJMbVpxYVNNZHhyWEpNdTZFeVZkWVVLUzI3bTJBaWp6TV90QWtsWUtFWUnSAcACQVVfeXFMT3JQSlg5YUZkOW1ZVWp4WmFKZVU0Y2xudXVrU0NjSVotMm5hajM2QnJEVmFjVVJyQ2FwdzJ2cVVueXdYNHBnQ1AyX3BxVnBNT3lvTnFPNDZscmdnWWZxa3IwLXlsckthNGN5SUVVVm51VHNYS0hJVFdLbE54M3BfMG1LQjN2VVg0QWM2S3FpbDJqdTlEaXRqWHRNNHVnNzNKVGdmVVZNWXN3TlRzQ2lSRG1uNlg1cnRaelpBakdseFI2bTh6OG9idUJiWTR5SnYxUE9BUTZxSmo5SUxmRUlQUzAzVF96TzBVdlZvcW5ualpUaWZhNVVXWVM4bTRnMWFqdnY2czRTWTNHamZVdnVrc09LR3FuYnZDeUpiNzZLNldvU1VkSFBEMVpudi1jMTB2MzZzZ2VoRVZ6Q1RyOGpTNXU?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A common bacteria found in the stomach could be fuelling millions of stomach cancer cases globally. A new study suggests this bacterial infection could cause nearly 12 million cancers among people born over a single decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists from the International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC), part of the World Health Organisation, project that if current trends continue, around 15.6 million people born between 2008 and 2017 will be diagnosed with stomach (gastric) cancer in their lifetime. Of all those cases – 76%, i.e., a staggering 11.9 million, may be caused by the Helicobacter pylori bacteria (H. pylori), according to a study published in the journal &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41591-025-03793-6#:~:text=Among%20the%20expected%20gastric%20cancer,the%20Americas%20and%20Africa%2C%20respectively." rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Nature Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Early Detection Saves Lives: Watch for These Ovarian Cancer Symptoms&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is H. pylori?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stomach cancer, often called a “silent killer,” is grabbing global attention following the striking new warning – thanks to the world’s most under-the-radar risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Helicobacter pylori, previously known as Campylobacter pylori, is a gram-negative, flagellated, helical bacterium. Mutants can have a rod or curved rod shape that exhibits less virulence. This easily transmissible bacterium often shows no symptoms – which makes it more invincible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let’s explore more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;A common but concealed inhabitant:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Half the world’s population hosts H. pylori in their stomach lining, often without visible symptoms. It's &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2999139/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;classified&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; as a class I carcinogen by IARC and the US Carcinogens Report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Transmission vectors:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The bacterium spreads through contaminated food or water and close contact, like saliva or fecal-oral routes. It’s more prevalent in regions with poor sanitation and crowded living conditions, especially in Asia, Africa, and parts of Latin America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Silent but damaging:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Though only &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC2999139/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;10–20%&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; may show mild symptoms like indigestion or bloating, H. pylori &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10376897/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;quietly triggers chronic inflammation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; – setting the stage for ulcers, atrophic gastritis, and eventually cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What does the study underline?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the study, scientists examined the incidence of stomach cancer in 185 countries in 2022 and combined it with projections of future deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;They looked at the potential impact of screen-and-treat strategies for H. pylori and found the number of stomach cancers could be cut by up to 75% overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asia accounts for two-thirds of projected future cases, with 10.6 million cases (68% of the total), followed by the Americas (2 million or 13%), Africa (1.7 million or 11%), Europe (1.2 million or 8%), and Oceania (0.07 million or 0.4%).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study projected that under current trends, 11.9 million people could be diagnosed with stomach cancer attributable to H. pylori infection by 2101, which is the year someone born in 2017 would turn 84.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Jin Young Park, one of the study’s co-authors and head of the gastric cancer prevention team at the WHO’s International Agency for Research on Cancer (IARC), said: “It is essential that health authorities make gastric cancer prevention a priority and accelerate efforts to control it by planning pilot and feasibility projects, including H. pylori screen-and-treat programmes,” adding, “With demographic changes set to increase the gastric cancer burden in many parts of the world, there is an urgent need for coordinated prevention strategies and for regional health systems to be prepared to manage the growing burden.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;H. pylori and stomach cancer: A deadly connection&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stomach cancer is largely preventable, but the prognosis is poor once a patient is diagnosed. It is the fifth most common form of cancer worldwide, killing an estimated 770,000 people per year. As per the study, chronic infection with H. pylori is a major cause, and it helps explain the rise in stomach cancers among young people in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The link between H. pylori and gastric adenocarcinoma is solid: infected individuals have a 2–6-fold greater risk. According to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK590949/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, around 90% of stomach cancers are linked to this infection, and up to 89% of non-cardia gastric cancers may be due to H. pylori. Its &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/about-cancer/causes-prevention/risk/infectious-agents/h-pylori-fact-sheet" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;presence is also tied&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; to MALT lymphoma, with tumor regression observed after eradication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;But how does a bug become a carcinogen?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bacterium’s virulence, especially strains containing the cagA gene and the cag pathogenicity island, intensifies inflammation and damages DNA repair mechanisms. Persistent inflammation produces reactive oxygen and nitrogen species, leading to DNA damage in gastric cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Genetic susceptibility and co-factors:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Not all infected individuals develop cancer. A study showed that certain genetic variants prompt immune-suppressive environments via IFNα, increasing cancer risk. Environmental risk factors – smoking, high salt intake, low fruit/vegetable diets, obesity, and genetic predispositions – can aggravate the damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="75"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is stomach cancer?&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gastric cancer, also known as stomach cancer, is a disease where malignant (cancerous) cells form in the lining of the stomach. It's a growth of cells that starts in the stomach, a muscular, sac-like organ in the upper abdomen that plays a key role in digesting food. Most stomach cancers are adenocarcinomas, which develop from the gland cells in the stomach's inner lining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="81"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While stomach cancer rates have declined in many parts of the world, it's still a significant health concern, particularly in East Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Symptoms:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Early-stage stomach cancer often doesn't cause noticeable symptoms, but later stages can include pain or discomfort in the upper abdomen, heartburn, feeling full after small meals, nausea, vomiting, and weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Risk Factors:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Risk factors include Helicobacter pylori infection, diet (especially high salt and smoked/preserved foods), obesity, smoking, and family history of stomach cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="91"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Preventing the invisible threat&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="92"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Screen-and-treat programs:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The study highlights that national initiatives to screen for and eradicate H. pylori could reduce new stomach cancer cases by up to 75%. Eradication has already reduced gastric cancer risk by roughly 75% in treated populations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Effective treatment protocols:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Current treatment involves two weeks of quadruple therapy: two antibiotics, a PPI, plus possibly bismuth. However, rising antibiotic resistance often requires multiple courses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="99"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Early detection boosts survival:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; In the US, early cancer diagnosis rates rose by 53% (2004–2021), improving survival to around 75% – compared to just 7% for late-stage detection. In regions with high H. pylori prevalence, targeted screening via endoscopy and breath/stool tests starting from age 40–50 is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="102"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="103"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 02:59:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwJBVV95cUxQOTQ4RldWR09jUHRGX2VfMWtGajVrUDNCeW55WnFhNlJObjZjNmR2dXR3V2FZYzRGcVFtLUxfaU5Na0RSREJ2NWJpVGgyNU1rbVhySmE0NkJpdkduR0J2VG5LT3V4ZW8yMTBEdjhGQVg3eWZUY0Ftdm5Cd25EMU5uYVI0Tkxjcm1fU1B1TlVadHJqS0pvTFhkckZoSkpBWi1MUmE1eEpuc2hweTk1aThKb0QyMnZoRE9CRV9NZFpKUXkyRDN1QUFfNjVvdW5DVUsxM0JHclFONDIwWGhNa3FqRlpDbjQwUklGMmJVemgycmRabnpsNVgyUXJtUjZ0YlRHeUhCbU4zYm9CSWFiWm9KYTJMbVpxYVNNZHhyWEpNdTZFeVZkWVVLUzI3bTJBaWp6TV90QWtsWUtFWUnSAcACQVVfeXFMT3JQSlg5YUZkOW1ZVWp4WmFKZVU0Y2xudXVrU0NjSVotMm5hajM2QnJEVmFjVVJyQ2FwdzJ2cVVueXdYNHBnQ1AyX3BxVnBNT3lvTnFPNDZscmdnWWZxa3IwLXlsckthNGN5SUVVVm51VHNYS0hJVFdLbE54M3BfMG1LQjN2VVg0QWM2S3FpbDJqdTlEaXRqWHRNNHVnNzNKVGdmVVZNWXN3TlRzQ2lSRG1uNlg1cnRaelpBakdseFI2bTh6OG9idUJiWTR5SnYxUE9BUTZxSmo5SUxmRUlQUzAzVF96TzBVdlZvcW5ualpUaWZhNVVXWVM4bTRnMWFqdnY2czRTWTNHamZVdnVrc09LR3FuYnZDeUpiNzZLNldvU1VkSFBEMVpudi1jMTB2MzZzZ2VoRVZ6Q1RyOGpTNXU</guid></item><item><title>咳嗽药物可以预防一些帕金森最严重的症状- ScienceAlert | Cough Medicine May Protect Against Some of Parkinson's Worst Symptoms - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMingFBVV95cUxObENJalNnXzlaZnRWaWcwdl9mVFEyNHdWSnRpVHlWMHBBVk5JM21kaVJvemJjTXRWNEZUUnY4MzcxUWZfcUdXeUF1WUx4WXR4ZE1yWEhybUk0WFBScllTMWRJSVdfcC01UGtBc3dyOXZEVU1hUXA2QlpON3UzSnVwTVJKWVV3dEt2MU5pUjduQ2pWM2YxSXM0TlUxYnFKQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;An active ingredient in cough medicines since 1979 has shown promise as a treatment for neuropsychiatric symptoms in  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IYl" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73029" data-postid="166748" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt; disease-related dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drug, &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ambroxol"&gt;ambroxol&lt;/a&gt;, isn't approved for use in the US, Canada, or Australia, but it is commonly found in cough syrups and tablets from Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a gold-standard phase 2  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="166748" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt;, 22 participants with Parkinson's dementia who received a high daily dose of ambroxol for a year showed no worsening of key &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1212/WNL.44.12.2308"&gt;neuropsychiatric symptoms&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, 25 patients who received the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-a-placebo" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="102371" data-postid="166748" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;placebo&lt;/a&gt; displayed worsening symptoms, gaining an average of 3.73 points on an &lt;a href="https://www.apa.org/pi/about/publications/caregivers/practice-settings/assessment/tools/neuropsychiatric-inventory"&gt;established neuropsychiatric score&lt;/a&gt;. Patients on ambroxol dropped an average of 2.45 points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/parkinsons-disease-might-not-start-in-the-brain-study-finds?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Parkinson's Disease Might Not Start in The Brain, Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both groups shared similar cognitive scores related to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3233/JAD-170991"&gt;memory and language&lt;/a&gt;. But those taking ambroxol showed stabilization in symptoms like delusions, hallucinations, anxiety, irritability, apathy, and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/brainsci12020130"&gt;aberrant motor activity&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants on ambroxol also experienced fewer falls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though ambroxol was found to be safe, no clinically meaningful improvements in cognition were recorded. Yet there are reasons to remain optimistic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our goal was to change the course of Parkinson's dementia," &lt;a href="https://news.westernu.ca/2025/06/cough-syrup-parkinsons-dementia/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; neurologist Stephen Pasternak from Western University in Canada.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This early trial offers hope and provides a strong foundation for larger studies."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_166759" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-166759" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Neuropsychiatric-symptoms-of-Parkinsons-disease-Modified-from-Fredericks-et-al-30-642x641.png" alt="Parkinson's Neuropsychiatric Symptoms" class="size-medium wp-image-166759" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Neuropsychiatric-symptoms-of-Parkinsons-disease-Modified-from-Fredericks-et-al-30-642x641.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Neuropsychiatric-symptoms-of-Parkinsons-disease-Modified-from-Fredericks-et-al-30-416x415.png 416w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Neuropsychiatric-symptoms-of-Parkinsons-disease-Modified-from-Fredericks-et-al-30-600x599.png 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/07/Neuropsychiatric-symptoms-of-Parkinsons-disease-Modified-from-Fredericks-et-al-30.png 727w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-166759" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Neuropsychiatric symptoms of Parkinson's disease. (Desai et al., &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.4103/jmedsci.jmedsci_277_23"&gt;&lt;em&gt;J. Med. Sci. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, 2024)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the team's analysis, some participants carrying a high-risk &lt;em&gt;GBA1&lt;/em&gt; gene for Parkinson's showed improved cognitive performance on ambroxol. With a small sample size and no control group to compare outcomes to, the authors caution these results need to be followed up before drawing any conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, high-risk &lt;a href="https://www.genecards.org/cgi-bin/carddisp.pl?gene=GBA1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;GBA1&lt;/em&gt; gene&lt;/a&gt; variants tend to result in lower activity of the enzyme &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glucocerebrosidase"&gt;Glucocerebrosidase&lt;/a&gt; (GCase), and this, in turn, is linked to more protein clumps in the brain, like Lewy bodies, which are &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-isnt-the-only-form-of-dementia-an-expert-explains-the-differences"&gt;associated with Parkinson's dementia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.parkreldis.2021.02.003"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; have found that ambroxol can significantly increase GCase activity. In the current trial, those taking the drug showed 1.5 times the amount of GCase activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No serious adverse effects were reported by those taking ambroxol, although mild to moderate gastrointestinal issues were common and caused a few participants to drop out of the trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings suggest that some of the more serious symptoms of Parkinson's disease may be managed by ambroxol if taken regularly at high doses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because ambroxol can easily &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.hsr.2023.100096"&gt;cross the blood-brain barrier&lt;/a&gt;, some scientists suspect the cough medicine &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/drug-used-in-cough-syrup-for-decades-offers-new-hope-as-parkinson-s-treatment"&gt;can treat neurodegenerative conditions&lt;/a&gt;, like Parkinson's, Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS), Gaucher disease, neuroinflammation, or spinal cord injury.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether that hypothesis proves to be true requires more clinical research. But the recent phase 2 trial on Parkinson's dementia gives scientists good reason to keep digging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These findings suggest ambroxol may protect brain function, especially in those genetically at risk," &lt;a href="https://news.westernu.ca/2025/06/cough-syrup-parkinsons-dementia/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Pasternak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It offers a promising new treatment avenue where few currently exist. If a drug like Ambroxol can help, it could offer real hope and improve lives."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamaneurol.2025.1687"&gt;&lt;i&gt;JAMA Neurology&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 02:46:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxObENJalNnXzlaZnRWaWcwdl9mVFEyNHdWSnRpVHlWMHBBVk5JM21kaVJvemJjTXRWNEZUUnY4MzcxUWZfcUdXeUF1WUx4WXR4ZE1yWEhybUk0WFBScllTMWRJSVdfcC01UGtBc3dyOXZEVU1hUXA2QlpON3UzSnVwTVJKWVV3dEt2MU5pUjduQ2pWM2YxSXM0TlUxYnFKQQ</guid></item><item><title>大峡谷国家公园近十年来首次出现汉坦病毒病例--SFGATE | Grand Canyon National Park sees its first hantavirus case in nearly a decade - SFGATE</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxPN3o3TllDRXZuc3AwaUpwRmdvanp4YjFFTHhpQnJSYVQtTjZwOXRYQ3IwZVVCUGhrb2dMTTJFUG81MFlHdkIzTlhwaENVWlJhcm11R1RGRkdBUmdtQ1pLU2l5T2JUR2duM2pzWlZnUGVSU1RDYkJ0UENKMDZXNF9sN3RBdS1IX0dMbEtWdGozRmMxWDBsX1lpMGwzc2RqLTFWdWc0?oc=5</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:01:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPN3o3TllDRXZuc3AwaUpwRmdvanp4YjFFTHhpQnJSYVQtTjZwOXRYQ3IwZVVCUGhrb2dMTTJFUG81MFlHdkIzTlhwaENVWlJhcm11R1RGRkdBUmdtQ1pLU2l5T2JUR2duM2pzWlZnUGVSU1RDYkJ0UENKMDZXNF9sN3RBdS1IX0dMbEtWdGozRmMxWDBsX1lpMGwzc2RqLTFWdWc0</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法，如果您有高血压，应避免的首要事项- EatingWell | The #1 Thing to Avoid If You Have High Blood Pressure, According to Dietitians - EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQbXNMQ1BZMVFraUdGdjg5MnU1TnRscmlBdDNYVl9aY2FvODNfbjZSbkpXN0ZSbTVRSlFrclMzbWVDVjBoZk5SSGROVTM4cTgwM0JuRUdSQWRZMVcyM0tJdXV1dDZhc1FCWmJnTW5aQzFlRFZIX1JETWYwWWQ3ZzE4RnRmTzRYRUVD?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Understanding the importance of a healthy diet is crucial for managing high blood pressure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eat more potassium-rich fruits and vegetables and cut back on sodium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cook more of your meals at home and consider following a DASH or Mediterranean diet.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you know you have high blood pressure, you’re already a step ahead. Although high blood pressure (hypertension) affects nearly half of American adults, it doesn’t cause symptoms at first—so many people don't even know they have it.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Read on to learn more about what high blood pressure means, the biggest thing to avoid doing if you have it and proven strategies you can take to improve it. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-is-high-blood-pressure"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Is High Blood Pressure? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Your blood pressure is the force of blood pushing through your arteries. Normal blood pressure is below 120/80 mm Hg.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The top number, systolic blood pressure, measures pressure when the heart beats. The bottom number, diastolic blood pressure, is the pressure when the heart is at rest between beats.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; High blood pressure can lead to several health complications, such as stroke, heart attack, kidney disease, vision loss and more.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; “If you are diagnosed with high blood pressure, lifestyle modification is key. Assess your diet, weight and exercise habits,” says &lt;a href="https://www.mountsinaiconciergecare.org/maria-fraga-rd/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Maria Elena Fraga, RD, CDCES&lt;/a&gt;, director of the Diabetes Alliance at the Mount Sinai Health System in New York City.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-the-1-thing-to-avoid"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; The #1 Thing to Avoid &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The No. 1 thing to avoid if you have high blood pressure is underestimating the impact your nutrition habits can have on your levels. Knowing that you can make a big difference in your blood pressure by changing some aspects of your diet is positive and empowering news.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Actionable habits for lowering blood pressure include limiting sodium, eating fruits and vegetables that are rich in potassium, cooking more at home and following blood-pressure-lowering eating plans. “Getting a handle on your blood pressure requires behavior and lifestyle changes, which can take time, effort, consistency and patience,” says &lt;a href="https://physeq.com/personal-trainers-trainer-nyc/sarah-currie-personal-trainer-new-york-ny/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Sarah Currie, M.S., RD&lt;/a&gt;, a personal trainer and co-owner of Physical Equilibrium in New York City. With that said, here are the impactful changes you can start making to your diet.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Cut Back on Sodium &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Over time, eating a high-sodium diet can narrow blood vessels and increase blood pressure. “You’d be surprised how many food items contain hidden sources of sodium,” says Fraga. Packaged foods are often packed with sodium, and some of the top culprits are canned soups, frozen meals and deli meat, adds Currie.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The American Heart Association suggests that cutting out 1,000 milligrams per day of sodium can have a beneficial impact on blood pressure. For people with high blood pressure, the AHA recommends consuming no more than 1,500 milligrams of sodium per day.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To reduce your sodium intake, try replacing a portion of salt in your recipes with garlic, fresh herbs and spices. Read package labels and restaurant menus before buying or ordering to help make lower-sodium choices. When you’re reading labels, look at the Daily Value percentage for sodium and aim for lower-sodium foods when possible. Foods with a sodium DV of 5% or less per serving are considered a low-sodium foods, while those with 20% DV or more of sodium per serving are considered high-sodium and should be limited.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Eat Potassium-Rich Foods &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Potassium counteracts sodium by helping your body excrete it through your urine. (In short, you pee it out.) The mineral also helps relax blood vessel walls, which lowers blood pressure. The AHA recommends consuming 3,500 to 5,000 milligrams of potassium daily to prevent or treat&lt;a href="https://www.health.com/high-blood-pressure-overview-7505223" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;high blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Boost your potassium intake by eating more fruits and vegetables. Aim to eat 4½ cups of fruits and vegetables every day.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Foods rich in potassium include:&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Lentils&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prunes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bananas&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kidney beans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Orange juice&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cantaloupe&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Squash&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Apricots&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Soybeans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Raisins&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Potatoes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Spinach&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chicken breast&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Low-fat dairy products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Cook More Meals at Home &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Restaurant meals are often high in sodium, which can make it difficult to stay within the recommended limits. One study found that the average sodium content in a fast-food meal was about 1,300 milligrams—nearly all of the recommended sodium limit for someone with high blood pressure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Cooking at home gives you control over all the ingredients. Whole foods, like fruits, vegetables, dried legumes, unsalted nuts and seeds and fresh sources of protein contain little to no sodium. When cooking you can flavor foods with fresh and dried herbs and spices, including basil, oregano, cumin, rosemary, turmeric and more.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This doesn’t mean you can’t eat out—it just takes a little planning. If the restaurant provides nutrition information, check it ahead of time to plan out a meal that’s lower in sodium. Avoid or limit fried foods, which tend to be higher in sodium, says Currie, and ask for sauces and dressings on the side. Opt for baked, broiled, grilled or steamed proteins paired with green and other colorful vegetables. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-subheading mntl-sc-block-subheading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-subheading__text"&gt; Consider the DASH or Mediterranean Style of Eating   &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The DASH (Dietary Approaches to Stop Hypertension) diet was created to intentionally treat high blood pressure. This eating style focuses on eating fruits, vegetables, legumes, whole grains, low-fat or fat-free dairy, lean protein and limited saturated fats, red meat, added sugar and sodium. The &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/11624/dash-diet-meal-plan/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;DASH diet&lt;/a&gt; is rich in important nutrients that help lower blood pressure, including potassium, calcium, magnesium, fiber and protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/longform/8046714/a-new-mediterranean-diet/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt; is very similar to the DASH eating plan, as it’s full of fresh fruits and vegetables, fiber-rich beans and whole grains, nuts and seeds. This eating plan also recommends limiting foods that contain higher amounts of saturated fat, such as red meat. One food that’s famously associated with the Mediterranean diet is extra-virgin olive oil, which is rich in polyphenols that can protect the heart.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-strategies-to-improve-blood-pressure"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Strategies to Improve Blood Pressure  &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Improving the quality of your diet is one effective way to manage hypertension. Other lifestyle factors that help bring down blood pressure include:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If lifestyle factors are not enough to keep your blood pressure in a healthy range, you may need medication. Reach out to a health care provider for guidance.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-spotlight--1-2-post mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight--1-2-post mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight mntl-block theme-1-2-post"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight__heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight__heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Recipes to Help Lower Blood Pressure&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; High blood pressure is a common condition affecting many Americans, yet, you can take steps to improve your numbers and prevent hypertension. One of the biggest mistakes people make is not realizing how important nutrition is for managing blood pressure and maintaining a healthy heart.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Small, consistent steps—like reading labels to cut down on sodium, cooking at home more often and eating plenty of fruits and vegetables—can make a big difference. For personalized support and guidance, ask a health care provider about working with a registered dietitian who can create an individualized eating plan and set goals that work for you.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQbXNMQ1BZMVFraUdGdjg5MnU1TnRscmlBdDNYVl9aY2FvODNfbjZSbkpXN0ZSbTVRSlFrclMzbWVDVjBoZk5SSGROVTM4cTgwM0JuRUdSQWRZMVcyM0tJdXV1dDZhc1FCWmJnTW5aQzFlRFZIX1JETWYwWWQ3ZzE4RnRmTzRYRUVD</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心表示，禽流感紧急情况已经结束- Axios | Bird flu emergency is over, CDC says - Axios</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxPZFdObUtxMEtvVk55TmtQUVpxX0lhU1NsdzNDVjZPMm1taWdDMl9WNE5GVTktUWQ0T2Jna0pHZmxYOHV0eHIyWldzNVQ0elQ4bVFVYlpQbG5peGVQa1VKT0xTTWhHVUNOX2t1R2FMalFFTnpjUGZsdFgtV09ZbTdKaDBucnk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 23:08:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxPZFdObUtxMEtvVk55TmtQUVpxX0lhU1NsdzNDVjZPMm1taWdDMl9WNE5GVTktUWQ0T2Jna0pHZmxYOHV0eHIyWldzNVQ0elQ4bVFVYlpQbG5peGVQa1VKT0xTTWhHVUNOX2t1R2FMalFFTnpjUGZsdFgtV09ZbTdKaDBucnk</guid></item><item><title>科学家终于发现了麸质反应的起源- ScienceAlert | Scientists Finally Uncovered Where Gluten Reactions Start - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxOV0hfMEhsUHp3cUtJOVp5NXdBT2tCZU80LWVmMFVqdmZnTjZqVUY1RDBOUUh6eUtWamhLeDBJSTdidmowNGNWZVBObHBrNDl1V2dTSGsxRVRSbkh0RVZDd2s2V2xmYnptdmVvZFg2YlJua3BiUzFXVzkxZ19yeEFQbVF4R0JxTGZVamJaQjljQQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;For roughly one in every hundred people, food containing even the smallest amounts of gluten can deliver a gutful of hurt and pose severe risks to their health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While a domino effect of immunological reactions can be traced back to their &lt;a href="https://www.massgeneral.org/children/celiac-disease/genetic-testing-for-celiac-disease"&gt;genetic roots&lt;/a&gt;, a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/evidence-emerges-that-a-viral-infection-could-be-behind-celiac-disease"&gt;number of contributing factors&lt;/a&gt; are also involved, making it difficult to map the precise chain of events that causes celiac disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using transgenic mice, an international team led by scientists from McMaster University in Canada has &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BnuKJhhfBT8"&gt;identified a crucial role&lt;/a&gt; played by the very cells making up the gut's lining, describing a major stepping stone that could lead to new therapies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Celiac disease is a lifelong autoimmune disorder triggered by the presence of a group of structural proteins known as gluten in the intestines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/gluten-food-list"&gt;Eating virtually anything&lt;/a&gt; made with wheat, barley, or rye – meaning most baked goods, breads, and pastas – puts &lt;a href="https://celiac.org/about-celiac-disease/symptoms-of-celiac-disease/"&gt;people with the condition&lt;/a&gt; at risk of transient symptoms like bloating, pain, diarrhea, constipation, and sometimes reflux and vomiting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/gluten-intolerance-vs-celiac-disease-experts-reveal-the-key-differences?utm_source=SA_article&amp;amp;utm_campaign=related_link"&gt;Gluten Intolerance vs Celiac Disease: Experts Reveal The Key Differences&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Currently the only way to avoid the symptoms is to avoid the foods that trigger them. Over the longer term, immune attacks triggered by gluten can &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/nutrition/articles/10.3389/fnut.2020.00006/full" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" navigationtraceid="T02Q5MRL9-to-Thread:thread" href="https://www.frontiersin.org/journals/nutrition/articles/10.3389/fnut.2020.00006/full" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;damage the small intestine's villi&lt;/a&gt;. These &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Intestinal_villus" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" navigationtraceid="T02Q5MRL9-to-Thread:thread" href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Intestinal_villus" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;tiny structures&lt;/a&gt; increase the internal surface area of the intestinal walls, which  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/hiv" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73049" data-postid="166991" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;aids&lt;/a&gt; absorption of nutrients from food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span aria-label="" data-stringify-type="paragraph-break"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;People with celiac disease – particularly if it's untreated – face serious health risks, such as being more likely to &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://www.cureus.com/articles/144351-increased-risk-of-colorectal-cancer-in-patients-with-celiac-disease-a-population-based-study" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" navigationtraceid="T02Q5MRL9-to-Thread:thread" href="https://www.cureus.com/articles/144351-increased-risk-of-colorectal-cancer-in-patients-with-celiac-disease-a-population-based-study" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;develop colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://bmjmedicine.bmj.com/content/2/1/e000371" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" navigationtraceid="T02Q5MRL9-to-Thread:thread" href="https://bmjmedicine.bmj.com/content/2/1/e000371" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt;. The disease is associated with a myriad of conditions, with just some examples including &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://doi.org/10.3109/00365521.2012.706828" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" navigationtraceid="T02Q5MRL9-to-Thread:thread" href="https://doi.org/10.3109/00365521.2012.706828" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;anemia&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu15051089" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" navigationtraceid="T02Q5MRL9-to-Thread:thread" href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu15051089" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;osteoporosis&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://www.wjgnet.com/2219-2808/full/v10/i4/53.htm" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" navigationtraceid="T02Q5MRL9-to-Thread:thread" href="https://www.wjgnet.com/2219-2808/full/v10/i4/53.htm" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;growth delays&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://doi.org/10.1093/humrep/dey214" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" navigationtraceid="T02Q5MRL9-to-Thread:thread" href="https://doi.org/10.1093/humrep/dey214" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;reproductive issues&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a target="_blank" data-stringify-link="https://doi.org/10.1212/WNL.0b013e3182544728" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" navigationtraceid="T02Q5MRL9-to-Thread:thread" href="https://doi.org/10.1212/WNL.0b013e3182544728" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;neurological disorders&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_145308" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-145308" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/VariousKindsOfBreads642.jpg" alt="Various kinds of bread" class="size-full wp-image-145308" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/VariousKindsOfBreads642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/VariousKindsOfBreads642-621x415.jpg 621w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/VariousKindsOfBreads642-600x401.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-145308" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;For roughly one in every hundred people, food containing gluten can deliver a gutful of hurt. (&lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/photos/bread-candy-pies-2864703/"&gt;aureliofoxrj/Pixabay&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The only way we can treat celiac disease today is by fully eliminating gluten from the diet," &lt;a href="https://brighterworld.mcmaster.ca/articles/celiac-origin-of-gluten-immune-reaction/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; McMasters gastroenterologist Elena Verdu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is difficult to do, and experts agree that a gluten-free diet is insufficient."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 90 percent of people diagnosed with the condition carry a pair of genes that encode for a protein called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HLA-DQ2"&gt;HLA-DQ2.5&lt;/a&gt;. Of the remaining 10 percent, most have a similar protein called HLA-DQ8.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like other kinds of 'HLA' (or &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Human_leukocyte_antigen"&gt;human leukocyte antigen&lt;/a&gt;) proteins, the proteins hold pieces of fallen invaders aloft like macabre trophies on a &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Antigen-presenting_cell"&gt;class of immune cells&lt;/a&gt;, warning other defensive tissues to be on the lookout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the specific case of HLA-DQ2.5 and HLA-DQ8, the proteins are shaped to hold chunks of gluten peptide that are resistant to digestion, instructing murderous T cells to go on the hunt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, these instructions aren't the clearest at distinguishing between a threat and similar-looking materials in our body, meaning those with the genes are at risk of a variety of autoimmune conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_145310" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-145310" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PastaInBowlAndOnAFork642.jpg" alt="Eating pasta" class="size-full wp-image-145310" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PastaInBowlAndOnAFork642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PastaInBowlAndOnAFork642-621x415.jpg 621w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PastaInBowlAndOnAFork642-600x401.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-145310" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;HLA-DQ2.5 and HLA-DQ8 proteins are shaped to hold chunks of gluten peptide that are resistant to digestion. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAD-UOJuJkI/"&gt;pixelshot/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.coeliac.org.uk/information-and-support/coeliac-disease/about-coeliac-disease/causes/genetics/"&gt;Not everybody&lt;/a&gt; who expresses either HLA-DQ2.5 or HLA-DQ8 will develop an immune disorder like celiac disease, however.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For that to happen, those torn-up pieces of gluten first need to be carried across the gut wall by a &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tissue_transglutaminase"&gt;transporting enzyme&lt;/a&gt; that binds with the peptide and alters it in ways to make it even more recognizable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cells in the intestinal wall are responsible for releasing this transporting enzyme into the gut, so they clearly have a critical role in the early stages of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are also known to &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/MHC_class_II"&gt;express the family of proteins&lt;/a&gt; to which HLA-DQ2.5 and HLA-DQ8 belong, which are typically regulated by inflammatory responses in the gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What hasn't been clear is how this staging ground for people with celiac disease actually functions within the pathology itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_145312" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-145312" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PersonHoldingWheatAndStomach642.jpg" alt="Hands on a stomach, with one holding wheat" class="size-full wp-image-145312" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PersonHoldingWheatAndStomach642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PersonHoldingWheatAndStomach642-621x415.jpg 621w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/PersonHoldingWheatAndStomach642-600x401.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-145312" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Currently the only way to avoid the symptoms is to avoid the foods that trigger them. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEpNqvTdV0/"&gt;AndreyPopov/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To focus on this important link in the chain, the research team double-checked the expression of the major immune complex in the cells lining the intestines of people with treated and untreated celiac disease, and in mice with the human genes for HLA-DQ2.5.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They then created functional living models of the gut, called an &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-an-organoid"&gt;organoid&lt;/a&gt;, using the mouse intestinal cells, to study the expression of their immune proteins up close, subjecting them to inflammatory triggers as well as predigested and intact gluten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This allowed us to narrow down the specific cause and effect and prove exactly whether and how the reaction takes place," &lt;a href="https://brighterworld.mcmaster.ca/articles/celiac-origin-of-gluten-immune-reaction/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; McMasters biomedical engineer Tohid Didar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From this it became evident the cells lining the gut weren't just passive bystanders suffering collateral damage in a misguided effort to rid the body of gluten – they were key agents, presenting a mash-up of gluten fragments broken down by gut bacteria and transporting enzymes to gluten-specific immune cells firsthand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knowing the types of tissue involved and their enhancement by the presence of inflammatory microbes gives researchers a new list of targets for future treatments, potentially allowing millions of people worldwide to enjoy a gluten-filled pastry or two without the risk of discomfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.gastrojournal.org/article/S0016-5085(24)05211-9/abstract"&gt;Gastroenterology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in August 2024. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 22:40:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOV0hfMEhsUHp3cUtJOVp5NXdBT2tCZU80LWVmMFVqdmZnTjZqVUY1RDBOUUh6eUtWamhLeDBJSTdidmowNGNWZVBObHBrNDl1V2dTSGsxRVRSbkh0RVZDd2s2V2xmYnptdmVvZFg2YlJua3BiUzFXVzkxZ19yeEFQbVF4R0JxTGZVamJaQjljQQ</guid></item><item><title>益生菌有望减少自闭症和多动症幼儿的多动症- PsyPost | Probiotics show promise for reducing hyperactivity in young children with autism and ADHD - PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitAFBVV95cUxPVUhtZWt6Rk1famIta3pGaDBsWWhnb2pNNHJ3aWE1cm1nTXNHUnN2Y3VMdWhiV2NRRERHanBNOTVDQVRZdGF4b2t3UFRubFNIRG1MNHlveUVNZWpTLWJSMldHVEVVLTFXamE0dU5IX0J6c2ZqSy02a0tycTdWSFp5V0tneUZvWUR1N2lZTHI5MlNidl9nSXpZTlFyUmxaaHJ2a0RwYnJUa0FpUE5WTUo1dGZKcVM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists continue to hunt for safe ways to ease the day-to-day challenges faced by children with autism spectrum disorder and attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder. A new randomized, placebo-controlled trial published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10802-024-01278-7" target="_blank"&gt;Research on Child and Adolescent Psychopathology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; reports that a 12-week course of two probiotic strains was linked to lower hyperactivity-impulsivity ratings in children aged five to nine and to modest gains in comfort-related quality-of-life scores among children with autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autism spectrum disorder describes a set of lifelong developmental differences marked by persistent social-communication difficulties and a preference for repetitive or highly focused behaviours. Attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder (ADHD), in contrast, is characterized by age-inappropriate levels of inattention, motor restlessness, and impulsive actions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both conditions emerge early in life, show high rates of overlap, and often involve delays in executive functions that help a child plan, inhibit urges, and regulate emotions. Over recent years, researchers have turned their attention to the community of microbes that lives inside the gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some intestinal bacteria can manufacture or modulate neurotransmitters such as dopamine and gamma-aminobutyric acid, chemicals that also shape reward, movement, and self-control within the brain. If the mix of microbes differs in children with neurodevelopmental conditions, supplying strains that boost those messenger molecules could conceivably ease everyday symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To examine this possibility, a team of researchers in Spain conducted a randomized, double-blind, placebo-controlled clinical trial involving 80 children aged 5 to 16 years. The study included 38 children diagnosed with ADHD and 42 children diagnosed with autism, some of whom had both diagnoses. Participants were randomly assigned to receive either a daily probiotic supplement or a placebo for 12 weeks. The probiotic mixture contained two strains of bacteria—&lt;em&gt;Lactiplantibacillus plantarum&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Levilactobacillus brevis&lt;/em&gt;—which are known to promote the synthesis of dopamine and GABA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the first dose and again after twelve weeks, parents completed standard rating scales that capture inattentive behaviours, hyperactivity-impulsivity, peer relations, and other challenges. For children with autism, parents also filled out the Social Responsiveness Scale, which gauges social awareness, communication, and repetitive patterns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each child took a computerized continuous-performance task that records omission errors (a sign of inattention) and commission errors (a sign of impulsivity). Parents answered questionnaires about executive function in everyday life, recorded their child’s sleep patterns, and judged five domains of health-related quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Statistical analyses included every child who started the trial, whether or not the family missed a few doses, reflecting real-world use. Across the whole sample, average scores on parent checklists and performance tasks shifted only slightly and did so to a similar degree in the probiotic and placebo groups. When the team separated the data by age, a clearer pattern emerged. Among children aged five to nine, parent ratings of hyperactivity-impulsivity fell more sharply in the probiotic condition than in the placebo condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The difference equaled a very large effect size in the autism group and a moderate-to-large effect size in the attention-deficit group. Within-group comparisons told a similar story: young recipients of the probiotic moved from the “elevated” into the “high-average” range on that subscale, while their peers on placebo showed no reliable change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Performance on the continuous-performance task largely mirrored those parent reports. Children with autism who swallowed the probiotic made fewer commission errors—an index of hurried responses—by the end of the study, whereas the placebo group showed a smaller drop. Detectability scores, which reflect how well a child can distinguish target from non-target stimuli, nudged upward only in the placebo arm. Reaction-time variability, a hallmark of attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder, was unchanged in both arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the researchers looked beyond core symptoms, they found one additional glimmer of benefit. On the Child Health and Illness Profile, a broad inventory of perceived well-being, children with autism in the probiotic arm reported a higher sense of physical comfort—covering aches, energy, and stomach complaints—than they had at baseline, and the effect size again reached the large range. Sleep ratings, executive-function scores, and social-communication scales stayed level for most participants, regardless of the supplement they received.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How might a bacterial drink calm hyperactivity in younger children yet leave inattention untouched? One possibility is that the strains used in the trial release gamma-aminobutyric acid, an inhibitory neurotransmitter that tempers motor activity. Earlier work shows lower gamma-aminobutyric acid levels in parts of the brain that coordinate movement and impulse control in both neurodevelopmental conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a probiotic raises the supply of that transmitter—either directly or by stimulating host cells to produce more—it could dampen fidgety behaviour without necessarily sharpening focus. Alternatively, the microbes could influence dopamine signalling, which plays out differently in circuits that support controlled attention versus those that regulate action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The modest scope of the changes tempers enthusiasm. The trial lasted only three months, a brief window in the long developmental arc of these conditions. The participating families were, on average, socially advantaged and reported few severe behaviour challenges, limiting room for improvement. The sample size—just over eighty—was sufficient to detect large effects but not the nuanced gains that might unfold in smaller subgroups, such as children with pronounced gastrointestinal complaints or those who do not respond well to medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most importantly, the investigators did not profile each child’s gut microbiome before and after treatment, so it remains unclear whether the probiotic actually took hold and shifted microbial balance in a way that mattered to the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future studies could address those gaps by enrolling larger cohorts across multiple clinics, extending the intervention to six months or a year, and adding stool sequencing to confirm bacterial colonisation and neurotransmitter output. Researchers might also explore whether combining probiotics with traditional behavioural therapies or with dietary fibre that feeds beneficial microbes produces a stronger signal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trials that begin during infancy, before hyperactivity or social-communication problems are fully established, may reveal whether microbial support can alter developmental trajectories rather than merely quiet symptoms that have already appeared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the current findings are preliminary, they add weight to the idea that the gut-brain connection offers a promising, low-risk target for supporting children with neurodevelopmental differences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10802-024-01278-7" target="_blank"&gt;Effect of Probiotics on the Symptomatology of Autism Spectrum Disorder and/or Attention Deficit/Hyperactivity Disorder in Children and Adolescents: Pilot Study&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Meritxell Rojo-Marticella, Victoria Arija, and Josefa Canals-Sans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 22:04:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxPVUhtZWt6Rk1famIta3pGaDBsWWhnb2pNNHJ3aWE1cm1nTXNHUnN2Y3VMdWhiV2NRRERHanBNOTVDQVRZdGF4b2t3UFRubFNIRG1MNHlveUVNZWpTLWJSMldHVEVVLTFXamE0dU5IX0J6c2ZqSy02a0tycTdWSFp5V0tneUZvWUR1N2lZTHI5MlNidl9nSXpZTlFyUmxaaHJ2a0RwYnJUa0FpUE5WTUo1dGZKcVM</guid></item><item><title>遵循这种饮食可以降低您患阿尔茨海默氏症的风险，无论您的年龄如何- SciTechDaily | Following This Diet Can Reduce Your Risk of Alzheimer’s, No Matter Your Age - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMioAFBVV95cUxOeXNaa2RybE5GSUdUQUFzM2llUUFvRGwzenZfSUZSeGpsSHNRTlNIYkFJWjgyS0tGZHI4Vl9QaUt3VWduZ3BTQ3U2aDFpelNhX29wNmxUNFFGbzJkUXFGTGp0c0J1Y19BNlQyRlBsU3RDS1VlYXBDT0Q2Z3hRU2R0bHVDb09QOHlaLUt5d1MyQWJETDZNZWEyTDItRzdJMWlJ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 21:54:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOeXNaa2RybE5GSUdUQUFzM2llUUFvRGwzenZfSUZSeGpsSHNRTlNIYkFJWjgyS0tGZHI4Vl9QaUt3VWduZ3BTQ3U2aDFpelNhX29wNmxUNFFGbzJkUXFGTGp0c0J1Y19BNlQyRlBsU3RDS1VlYXBDT0Q2Z3hRU2R0bHVDb09QOHlaLUt5d1MyQWJETDZNZWEyTDItRzdJMWlJ</guid></item><item><title>专家为何关注RFK Jr. - NPR引用的疫苗研究 | Why experts are concerned about the vaccine study cited by RFK Jr. - NPR</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirwFBVV95cUxNaWlHMXVSX3VOQm9xZEozZ0VuYzF2QkM4ZGZHb1hlT2VKUzhtN1kwdk96Z0d4X0VQOTE4TzJxeVRWUm11VVJPVmZheTZieFFvd1hTNnhnRXdHMHlZaHIwYUJaSktlZy1QckI0bDN2Tm9tcEc5SGpSX1NRVW5xSlQ4OVE2VDRSbjNJMkFNanBTQnhDaXA3YTg0dl9iYl9udi1NcDJ5em03LURUZWNGOXRn?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;p&gt;RFK Jr. stunned the global health world when he said the U.S. would halt funding the group that helps provide vaccines to many low-income countries. The study he cited is seen by others as dubious.&lt;/p&gt;   
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="transcript storytext" aria-label="Transcript"&gt;
    &lt;b class="icn-story-transcript-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;b class="icn-story-transcript"&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/b&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARI SHAPIRO, HOST: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; The Trump administration has cut many global health programs. One cut stands out to some experts. Gavi, the Vaccine Alliance provides immunizations for some of the world's poorest children. It won't be getting over a billion dollars in promised U.S. funding. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. says Gavi doesn't consider vaccine safety. NPR's Gabrielle Emanuel reports this stunned the global health world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GABRIELLE EMANUEL, BYLINE: And what angered many of them was the reason he gave for attacking the organization's safety record. RFK Jr. singled out a study from 2017. He called it a landmark study that he says proves one of the world's most common vaccines could be dangerous. He delivered his remarks in a video to the organization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(SOUNDBITE OF ARCHIVED RECORDING)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ROBERT F KENNEDY JR: The authors of this study were five internationally revered deities of vaccine research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: One of those authors is a researcher named Christine Stabell Benn. She looked at the DTP vaccine that's given to the vast majority of the world's children. It protects them against diphtheria, tetanus and pertussis. Stabell Benn says it's good at protecting them against these three deadly diseases, but...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(SOUNDBITE OF ARCHIVED RECORDING)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHRISTINE STABELL BENN: We started doing what nobody else had done before us. We evaluated the effect of vaccines on overall health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: Overall health, meaning, could this vaccine maybe make you more likely to die of other causes? To find out, Stabell Benn and her team looked through health records for about a thousand kids. The records came from the early '80s in the West African country of Guinea-Bissau. Stabell Benn didn't respond to interview requests, but here she is speaking at a TEDx Talk from 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(SOUNDBITE OF ARCHIVED RECORDING)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;STABELL BENN: And the results were scary. Children who received DTP vaccine had five times higher risk of dying than those who didn't.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: A scary thought, yes, but outside researchers like Beate Kampmann aren't buying it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEATE KAMPMANN: It's just false news, right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: She's at the London School of Hygiene &amp;amp; Tropical Medicine. She has a long list of concerns about the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAMPMANN: That study is based on ancient data. It is an observation study. Statistics are dodgy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: And, Kampmann says, a few years later, those same researchers themselves repeated the study and found totally different results. The kids who got the DTP vaccine this time were not more likely to die. Kampmann says, on top of all this, that original study isn't even relevant because the DTP vaccines given today are different than the shots given in the '80s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;KAMPMANN: The recipe has changed, and the whole production of the process is different as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: Kampmann's not the only one who is skeptical. The World Health Organization has brought together independent panels of experts to investigate this issue. As a result, new studies were commissioned, and multiple times over the past 20 years the panels have concluded the current recommendation - that everyone gets a DTP vaccine - is the right one. Kate O'Brien is the WHO's top vaccine expert. She says billions of people have received the DTP vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;KATE O'BRIEN: This vaccine has been used for over 50 years. We have decades and decades of safety information on DTP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: If this vaccine is not given, she says...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;O'BRIEN: We will cause harm. It will result in deaths.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: NPR sent HHS a list of concerns raised by outside vaccinologists. The HHS spokesperson did not respond to the concerns but said Gavi must re-earn public trust. Many in the medical establishment have condemned the U.S. for pulling its funding for global vaccination efforts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAUL OFFIT: It's just a travesty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: Paul Offit directs the Vaccine Education Center at the Children's Hospital of Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OFFIT: There is probably no better public health organization, and, frankly, more economical public health organization, than Gavi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMANUEL: He says RFK Jr. used shoddy evidence to make a big decision. Gabrielle Emanuel, NPR News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="disclaimer"&gt;Copyright © 2025 NPR.  All rights reserved.  Visit our website &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/about-npr/179876898/terms-of-use"&gt;terms of use&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/about-npr/179881519/rights-and-permissions-information"&gt;permissions&lt;/a&gt; pages at &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org"&gt;www.npr.org&lt;/a&gt; for further information.&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="disclaimer"&gt;
        Accuracy and availability of NPR transcripts may vary. Transcript text may be revised to correct errors or match updates to audio. Audio on npr.org may be edited after its original broadcast or publication. The authoritative record of NPR’s programming is the audio record.
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jul 2025 21:47:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNaWlHMXVSX3VOQm9xZEozZ0VuYzF2QkM4ZGZHb1hlT2VKUzhtN1kwdk96Z0d4X0VQOTE4TzJxeVRWUm11VVJPVmZheTZieFFvd1hTNnhnRXdHMHlZaHIwYUJaSktlZy1QckI0bDN2Tm9tcEc5SGpSX1NRVW5xSlQ4OVE2VDRSbjNJMkFNanBTQnhDaXA3YTg0dl9iYl9udi1NcDJ5em03LURUZWNGOXRn</guid></item></channel></rss>