<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>纽约证实美国6年来首例本地感染基孔肯雅病毒病例-美国广播公司新闻-突发新闻、最新新闻和视频</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/new-york-confirms-1st-locally-acquired-case-chikungunya/story?id=126539403</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;The New York State Department of Health has confirmed a case of locally acquired chikungunya on Long Island, marking the first case of the virus reported to be locally acquired in New York and the first locally acquired case to be reported in the United States since 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Laboratory testing at the department’s Wadsworth Center confirmed the case in Nassau County on Long Island, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“An investigation suggests that the individual likely contracted the virus following a bite from an infected mosquito,” officials said. “While the case is classified as locally acquired based on current information, the precise source of exposure is not known.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Chikungunya is a mosquito-borne disease most common in tropical and subtropical regions and symptoms include fever and joint pain, headache, muscle pain, joint swelling, or rash, officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The disease cannot be spread directly from one person to another, authorities said, and the risk to the public is low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The illness is rarely fatal, and most patients recover within a week, though some may experience persistent joint pain, authorities continued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;A worker attends a mosquito control sequence ordered by the Provence Alpes Cote d'Azur Regional Health Agency to prevent the spread of chikungunya in Nice, southern France, on October 10, 2025.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Valery Hache/AFP via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“People at higher risk for severe disease include newborns infected around the time of birth, adults aged 65 and older, and individuals with chronic conditions such as high blood pressure, diabetes or heart disease,” according to the New York State Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The Aedes albopictus mosquito, which is known to transmit chikungunya, is present in parts of downstate New York and local transmission can occur when an A. albopictus mosquito bites an infected traveler, becomes infected and bites another person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“Our Wadsworth Center has confirmed this test result, which is the first known case of locally acquired Chikungunya in New York State. Given the much colder nighttime temperatures, the current risk in New York is very low.” State Health Commissioner Dr. James McDonald said. “We urge everyone to take simple precautions to protect themselves and their families from mosquito bites.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In 2025, there have been three additional chikungunya cases outside New York City that were all linked to international travel to regions with active chikungunya infections, according to health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;“Routine mosquito testing conducted by the Department’s Wadsworth Center and the New York City Department of Health and Mental Hygiene (DOHMH) has not detected chikungunya virus in any New York mosquito samples to date,” said the New York State Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Health officials said that all New Yorkers should take precautions to reduce the risk of mosquito bites by using EPA-registered insect repellents, wearing long sleeves, long pants and socks outdoors when possible, removing standing water around homes, such as in flowerpots, buckets and gutters, and by repairing or patching holes in window and door screens to keep mosquitoes out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News - Breaking News, Latest News and Videos</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:51:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxNdG16djB0M1M2enczaEZMRU1CcHZPUk9wNWJnbWszYzRRNnJDZVY2WTVtZ0pfekdJS2V4Q29MZ3dxYXNadkNrVEVJNzZ0YmdUYk9BU2Q3LTBGZXBqMGpGUm9nSXNKM3hyYS1GTEhVOG9WVXlVUlBLR0RMYVczY0lUMzY1NmU0NXl2dkJ0aDJqTW54Um9OOHYwbnlBM1lSalpVRlhFb2JHNNIBrAFBVV95cUxQbFNEMi01WDVhRDhKOVpScVYxTWlJTWpuc1dHc1hsWTVOdGFmd2xub1hBZ1dmLWJfWkJCNVBUNGk1RmRackpwWEhTQjZRNVJTeDRCajdvcm1tOTJ4SXN3Rm9BS2IxMjBSUEw2RU5jX3o4Z3FzV3F2OWlyTE85NFhESlhSd01HcDh1OWw1d204Tk5vbmtmSXVLbk9aMzAxT29Jel9VV04zVzRzSFNQ</guid></item><item><title>Ozempic可能会从字面上改变我们的身体处理酒的方式，研究发现- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/ozempic-might-literally-change-how-our-bodies-handle-booze-study-finds-2000672609</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl "&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Scientists are learning more about the strange effects of Ozempic and similar GLP-1 drugs on alcohol use. New research shows that these obesity and diabetes medications might actually change how our bodies handle booze.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Virginia Tech researchers conducted the study, which tracked how GLP-1 users processed alcohol immediately after downing several drinks. Compared to non–GLP-1 users, the researchers found that those taking GLP-1s saw their blood alcohol levels rise more slowly and reported feeling less intoxicated overall. The findings appear to provide some insight into why GLP-1 drugs have shown promise as a treatment for alcohol use disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“These data provide preliminary evidence that GLP-1RAs could act through peripheral mechanisms to suppress alcohol intake,” the authors wrote in their paper, &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-025-17927-w"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Wednesday in Scientific Reports.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;A surprising loss of craving&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Semaglutide (the active ingredient in Ozempic and Wegovy) and other GLP-1 drugs have changed the field of obesity treatment in recent years. They’ve proven to be &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/semaglutide-tirzepatide-weight-loss-drugs-future-uses-1851116318"&gt;far more effective&lt;/a&gt; at helping people lose weight than diet and exercise alone. Some doctors and GLP-1 users have also reported that these drugs seem to reduce cravings for things besides food as well, including potentially addictive drugs like opioids, cocaine, and alcohol. &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/glp-1-drugs-like-ozempic-reduce-cocaine-cravings-case-study-finds-2000565524"&gt;Several&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/the-case-for-ozempic-as-a-addiction-treatment-keeps-getting-better-2000513096"&gt;early&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/glp-1-drugs-like-ozempic-reduce-cocaine-cravings-case-study-finds-2000565524"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; have begun to support these observations, too.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Intriguing as all this is, there’s still a lot we don’t know about how and why these drugs may actually work to reduce people’s cravings for substances like alcohol. So researchers at Virginia Tech’s Fralin Biomedical Research Institute (FBRI) were interested in studying the immediate effects of alcohol on people taking GLP-1s.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;They recruited 20 participants living with obesity (a body mass index over 30) for their small study. Half of the volunteers were taking one of three GLP-1 medications—semaglutide, tirzepatide, or liraglutide—while the other half weren’t on any of these drugs. Then the researchers got them drunk—in a controlled setting, of course.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The volunteers were asked to drink three alcoholic beverages over the course of an hour, and then they were monitored for up to four hours in a recovery room. Throughout this experiment, the volunteers had their blood alcohol, glucose, and vital signs, such as blood pressure, measured regularly.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The researchers gave the volunteers enough alcohol to raise their blood alcohol concentration to 0.08% by the end of the drinking period—the legal limit for driving in most of the U.S. But though both groups did roughly reach that same endpoint, the GLP-1 users saw their blood alcohol level rise more slowly on average, the researchers found. What’s more, the GLP-1 users also reported feeling less drunk subjectively during the experiment and reported having less of a craving for alcohol in general before and after the trial.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The findings suggest that GLP-1s can change the speed at which alcohol enters the bloodstream, the researchers say, possibly through slowed gastric emptying from the stomach, a known GLP-1 effect. This slower introduction can then make alcohol less potentially addictive.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Why would this matter? Faster-acting drugs have a higher abuse potential,” said study author Alex DiFeliceantonio, assistant professor and interim co-director of the FBRI’s Center for Health Behaviors Research, in a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-glp-drugs-delay-alcohol-effects.html"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; from the university. “They have a different impact on the brain. So if GLP-1s slow alcohol entering the bloodstream, they could reduce the effects of alcohol and help people drink less.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;More to learn&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The researchers do note their work should be viewed as a pilot study, meaning more studies are needed to confirm the team’s findings. Some research has also &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3796262/#:~:text=In%20parallel%2C%20emerging%20evidence%20suggests%20that%20the%20range%20of%20action%20of%20GLP%2D1%20on%20reward%20behavior%20is%20not%20limited%20to%20food%2Dderived%20reward%20but%20extends%20to%20cocaine%2C%20amphetamine%2C%20and%20alcohol%20reward."&gt;indicated&lt;/a&gt; that GLP-1s can also directly affect the brain’s reward system linked to alcohol and other drug use, possibly providing another way these medications can temper our cravings.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;However these drugs work, the most important tests of their potential are yet to come. There are now several clinical trials of GLP-1 therapy for substance use disorders, including &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT06015893?cond=Alcohol%20Use%20Disorder&amp;amp;intr=semaglutide&amp;amp;rank=4"&gt;alcohol use disorder&lt;/a&gt;, underway. Should these trials pan out, GLP-1 drugs could become a tantalizing option for treating these difficult-to-manage disorders.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:20:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPMzA2UmlYbFRXYnMyaTdYN2t4clRqcHhqdy03WnY0SEE4U1ZvWm84eDNIR0VfMWx3MEdlUDFQU2l6QkgxNTRWNlc5VEFPWENwaWRFdmpPR0ljU2lKY1lnZVZEdExRVjRQQmJrQ0ZqcTVCUmJEcTBsNmpGaDBxYVh2T1QxYnpGeENKOS0wZ1RFOFZnLU5wRlNHRXZMUnNUZ19sLVFj</guid></item><item><title>我的不寻常的阴茎从未在出生时得到矫正。现在，它在床上造成了一个令人生气的问题。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/10/sex-advice-birth-defect-penis.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgqwt4xo000gpkm917o4vv0n@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Jessica and Rich here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgqz6rgz002b3b79dna1xak4@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It, &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="10" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgqyy6cj00183b79gvijf19j@published"&gt;I’m a 41-year-old man and have an uncorrected birth defect…&lt;/p&gt;




  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgs4d0vc000c3b794k876it0@published"&gt;I have &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/hypospadias/symptoms-causes/syc-20355148"&gt;hypospadias&lt;/a&gt; (an unformed urethra basically), which causes my penis to bend at a near 90-degree angle when erect. Functionally, it is fine (have to pee sitting down … whatever). I have, however, struggled with body image issues over this and have never been in a relationship or had sex (as of yet). Any advice for discussing this with a potential partner or positions to try if the day ever comes?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgqyy6eq00193b79kxnxqv2o@published"&gt;—Curved and Curious&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgqyy6gn001a3b79ry7rcg3n@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Curved and Curious,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="60" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgqyy6ih001b3b791ez3l1u5@published"&gt;A nearly 90-degree bend is significant. I emailed a few questions to Prof. Dr. Ahmed T. Hadidi of Germany’s &lt;a href="https://www.hypospadias.net/en/"&gt;Hypospadias Center,&lt;/a&gt; and he clarified that while “it is rather impossible to have traditional penetrative sex with a 90-degree curvature”—in fact, anything more than 20 degrees may interfere with penetrative sex—”the doggy position may reduce the negative effects of penile curvature.”&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="92" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgs6ka16001c3b793pzdxgtz@published"&gt;There’s no guarantee, of course, because your particular anatomy, combined with the anatomy of any individual partner, is going to dictate how the two of you fit together. Something like Tetris, but more fleshy and with fewer sharp angles. Generally speaking, penetrative sex is a question of getting tab A into slot B—try as many possibilities as you can think of, and keep track of the ones that feel good. It could be useful to experiment on your own with a “male masturbator” style toy, which you can insert your penis into.&lt;/p&gt;

  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="174" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgqyy6kd001c3b79be035vas@published"&gt;As for how to broach the discussion with romantic and sexual interests, the more matter-of-fact and direct you are, the more likely they are to take it well. Again, no promises, but it’s the main thing you can control in these conversations, and people do tend to base part of their reaction on the tone of the person delivering information. You’ll want to express your attraction, and follow it up with the basic details of your situation—namely, that you’ve got a significant bend in your penis that’s part of a condition you’ve had since birth, you’ve decided not to pursue surgery to reduce it, and you’ll need to work together to figure out what positions are possible for the two of you. You may find that practicing your phrasing in the mirror or with a friend reduces anxiety. Line up a friend you can lean on in case the potential partner behaves like a jerk, who will also be happy to celebrate with you if your new partner responds with the compassion you deserve.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgqz68gl001h3b796zpo3172@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Jessica&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmgqz6ern001t3b79r1kk7t95@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="60" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmgqz6c5w001n3b79te8ys7uh@published"&gt;I’m a straight man in my late 30s, and my wife of 10 years recently came out as bisexual. She says that nothing about herself has changed, she’s just acknowledging an attraction to women that’s always been there, and that our relationship will stay entirely the same, which is mostly great! &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/01/bisexual-wife-relationship-sex-advice.html"&gt;The thing is, part of me WANTS a change.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmgqwt4xo000jpkm99iknruow@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;The latest sex, parenting, and money advice from our columnists delivered to your inbox three times a week.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 16:04:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE1lWHBvQ3dUbE4yN3Y0dmNReDQ4cXg3eWVRWHhHLWpkeTF6MXltemtueXJhUnR4RU96aG8tekJfSmRpTjN2aXFHOV8wZkhyX1UyNHltRk1pNFBnRHdRbk41M0NaNGpsMnRxRzVNQVFRa1ZnSEItYkE</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，根据新的定义，近70%的美国成年人将被视为肥胖-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/oct/15/almost-70-of-us-adults-would-be-deemed-obese-based-on-new-definition-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Almost 70% of adults in the US would be deemed to have obesity based on a new definition, research suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The traditional definition of obesity, typically based on having a body mass index (BMI) of 30 or greater, has long been contentious, not least as it does not differentiate between fat and muscle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In an effort to tackle the issue, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/jan/14/call-to-overhaul-obesity-diagnoses-amid-fears-of-over-reliance-on-bmi" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;in January medical experts from around the world called for&lt;/a&gt; a new definition to be adopted. This would encompass people either with a BMI greater than 40; or those with a high BMI and at least one raised figure for measures such as waist circumference, waist-to-hip ratio, or waist-to-height ratio; or those with two such raised figures regardless of BMI; or those with direct measures of excess body fat based on scans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In addition, they said obesity should be split into two categories: clinical obesity – where there are signs of illness – and pre-clinical obesity, where there are not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Now research suggests the revamped definition could result in a dramatic rise in the prevalence of obesity among adults in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Lindsay Fourman, the first author of the study, from Mass General Brigham in the US, said the increase in obesity prevalence based on the new definition was striking, and was largely driven by people who would not have been considered to have obesity based on their BMI alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Recognising people with [this type of] obesity can lead to more accurate health risk stratification,” she said. “For example, someone with BMI 23 but excess abdominal fat could benefit from lifestyle interventions such as improving diet and increasing physical activity, even though their BMI is in the “normal” range. Their physician might also more closely monitor for obesity-related complications such as pre-diabetes or fatty liver.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2025.37619" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Writing in the journal Jama Network Open&lt;/a&gt;, Fourman and colleagues describe how they applied the traditional and new definitions of obesity to a nationally representative group of 301,026 participants, aged 18 to 80, who had enrolled in a US-based health study between the end of May 2017 and the end of September 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While traditional BMI-based criteria would mean 128,992, or 43%, of the participants were deemed to have obesity, the team found this increased by nearly 60% using the new definition, encompassing 206,361, or 69%, of participants. For those aged 70 years or older, prevalence under the new definition was 78%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Almost all those with obesity under the traditional definition also had obesity under the new definition, with only 678 participants no longer considered to have obesity. However, the new definition meant 78,047 participants who would not previously have been considered to have obesity based on BMI alone would be deemed to have the condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Our data show that these individuals have a heightened risk of organ dysfunction and long-term health complications, suggesting that their classification as having obesity is clinically appropriate,” said Fourman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Of those deemed to have obesity without a high BMI, 48% had clinical obesity. For those who had obesity based on their BMI together with other measures, this figure was 56%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The researchers noted that while the prevalence of obesity under the new definition was similar between men and women, men showed a greater increase upon the use of the new definition, adding that while prevalence increased by a similar number of percentage points across racial groups, the greatest relative rise was among Asian individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Naveed Sattar, a professor of metabolic medicine at the University of Glasgow, who was not involved in the study, described it as thought-provoking and said further research was now needed, but noted that the newly proposed definition of obesity had yet to be adopted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Regardless of definitions, it’s clear that current obesity levels pose major challenges especially in high-income countries like the UK, with rising weight levels underscoring the urgent need for more effective strategies to support healthier living,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixwFBVV95cUxNdllMMEJET0J0anphX0lGaUVEOC10bzNqQ1pFLS1xNVozMHU3TzV2SkRUSDZuRWl3aG5SOXVqN3ZhMWtVUmdUR0ZlS3BuV25BeE9ETFFmWTQ2MTNMYzA1bU9IekM0aXpYVjZ5enJLeEhWY29kaklxSUtoTDhKeWpMSEJrWG0wck03X3BIVFJrVU5wT2ZLNVhaM0czMmc5MkN0NVphbWhnWE1VOHNqZkZ2TzZBNTdOVHJyWTBfWGIyQW8zNXhIV1Yw</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，符合肥胖新定义的美国成年人百分比急剧增加- Mass General Brigham</title><link>https://www.massgeneralbrigham.org/en/about/newsroom/press-releases/dramatic-increase-in-adults-who-meet-new-definition-of-obesity</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-cmp-data-layer="{&amp;quot;text-d86e812d13&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;@type&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;aem-mgb/components/text&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;repo:modifyDate&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;2025-10-15T15:01:03Z&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;xdm:text&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;amp;nbsp;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;ul&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Mass General Brigham researchers studied a new definition of obesity that moves beyond BMI to include measures of body fat distribution&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;li&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;Applying the updated criteria to a national study population revealed a nearly 60 percent rise in obesity prevalence, affecting up to 80 percent of older adults&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/li&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;/ul&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;&amp;lt;br&amp;gt;\r\nThe prevalence of obesity in the United States could rise sharply under a new definition of obesity released earlier this year by the&amp;lt;a href=\&amp;quot;https://www.thelancet.com/commissions-do/clinical-obesity\&amp;quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;i&amp;gt;Lancet Diabetes and Endocrinology Commission&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;. Researchers from Mass General Brigham found that when applying the new criteria, which expands upon the traditional use of body mass index (BMI) to include measures of body fat distribution, the prevalence of obesity increased from about 40 percent to about 70 percent among over 300,000 people included in their study. The rise was even more pronounced among older adults. Additionally, the researchers found that those newly added individuals also had a higher risk of adverse health outcomes. Their results are published in &amp;lt;a href=\&amp;quot;http://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2025.37619?utm_source=For_The_Media&amp;amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;amp;utm_term=101525\&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;i&amp;gt;JAMA Network Open&amp;lt;/i&amp;gt;.&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“We already thought we had an obesity epidemic, but this is astounding,” said co-first author Lindsay Fourman, MD, an endocrinologist in the Metabolism Unit in the Endocrinology Division of the Mass General Brigham Department of Medicine. “With potentially 70 percent of the adult population now considered to have excess fat, we need to better understand what treatment approaches to prioritize.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Traditionally, obesity has been defined by BMI, which estimates body fat based on a person’s weight and height. But other anthropomorphic measures—such as waist circumference, waist-to-height ratio, or waist-to-hip ratio—may further account for fat distribution and aid in differentiation between muscle and fat mass.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Under the new framework, a person is classified as having obesity if they have a high BMI plus at least one elevated anthropometric measure (a condition the authors term “BMI-plus-anthropometric obesity”), or if they have a normal BMI and at least two elevated anthropometric measures (a condition termed “anthropometric-only obesity”). The new definition also distinguishes between preclinical and clinical obesity with clinical obesity defined as the presence of obesity-related physical impairment or organ dysfunction. At least 76 organizations have endorsed the new guidelines, including the American Heart Association and The Obesity Society.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The study analyzed participants in the National Institutes of Health All of Us Research Program’s cohort of over 300,000 Americans. Obesity prevalence was 68.6 percent with the new definition, versus 42.9 percent under the traditional BMI-based definition. This increase was entirely driven by inclusion of individuals with anthropometric-only obesity. Obesity rates varied by sex, race, and especially by age—affecting nearly 80 percent of adults over 70.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Importantly, the study found that those with anthropometric-only obesity – who would not have been classified as having obesity by the traditional definition – had a higher risk of diabetes, cardiovascular disease, and mortality than people without obesity. About half of all individuals who met the new obesity criteria had clinical obesity, and this proportion was only slightly lower in the anthropometric-only obesity group compared with the BMI-plus-anthropometric obesity group.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“We have always recognized the limitations of BMI as a single marker for obesity because it doesn't take into account body fat distribution,” said senior author Steven Grinspoon, MD, Chief of the Metabolism Unit in the Endocrinology Division of the Mass General Brigham Department of Medicine. “Seeing an increased risk of cardiovascular disease and diabetes in this new group of people with obesity, who were not considered to have obesity before, brings up interesting questions about obesity medications and other therapeutics.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;The researchers emphasize that further studies are needed to better understand the causes of and optimal treatments for anthropometric-only obesity. The research team previously developed a therapeutic that reduces waist circumference and plans to explore the utility of different treatment strategies in this newly defined population.&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;“Identifying excess body fat is very important as we’re finding that even people with a normal BMI but with abdominal fat accumulation are at increased health risk,” Fourman said. “Body composition matters – it’s not just pounds on a scale.”&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;\r\n&amp;quot;}}" id="text-d86e812d13" class="cmp-text"&gt;
 &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mass General Brigham researchers studied a new definition of obesity that moves beyond BMI to include measures of body fat distribution&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Applying the updated criteria to a national study population revealed a nearly 60 percent rise in obesity prevalence, affecting up to 80 percent of older adults&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;
The prevalence of obesity in the United States could rise sharply under a new definition of obesity released earlier this year by the&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/commissions-do/clinical-obesity"&gt; &lt;i&gt;Lancet Diabetes and Endocrinology Commission&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Researchers from Mass General Brigham found that when applying the new criteria, which expands upon the traditional use of body mass index (BMI) to include measures of body fat distribution, the prevalence of obesity increased from about 40 percent to about 70 percent among over 300,000 people included in their study. The rise was even more pronounced among older adults. Additionally, the researchers found that those newly added individuals also had a higher risk of adverse health outcomes. Their results are published in &lt;a href="http://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2025.37619?utm_source=For_The_Media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_term=101525"&gt;&lt;i&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We already thought we had an obesity epidemic, but this is astounding,” said co-first author Lindsay Fourman, MD, an endocrinologist in the Metabolism Unit in the Endocrinology Division of the Mass General Brigham Department of Medicine. “With potentially 70 percent of the adult population now considered to have excess fat, we need to better understand what treatment approaches to prioritize.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Traditionally, obesity has been defined by BMI, which estimates body fat based on a person’s weight and height. But other anthropomorphic measures—such as waist circumference, waist-to-height ratio, or waist-to-hip ratio—may further account for fat distribution and aid in differentiation between muscle and fat mass.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Under the new framework, a person is classified as having obesity if they have a high BMI plus at least one elevated anthropometric measure (a condition the authors term “BMI-plus-anthropometric obesity”), or if they have a normal BMI and at least two elevated anthropometric measures (a condition termed “anthropometric-only obesity”). The new definition also distinguishes between preclinical and clinical obesity with clinical obesity defined as the presence of obesity-related physical impairment or organ dysfunction. At least 76 organizations have endorsed the new guidelines, including the American Heart Association and The Obesity Society.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study analyzed participants in the National Institutes of Health All of Us Research Program’s cohort of over 300,000 Americans. Obesity prevalence was 68.6 percent with the new definition, versus 42.9 percent under the traditional BMI-based definition. This increase was entirely driven by inclusion of individuals with anthropometric-only obesity. Obesity rates varied by sex, race, and especially by age—affecting nearly 80 percent of adults over 70.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Importantly, the study found that those with anthropometric-only obesity – who would not have been classified as having obesity by the traditional definition – had a higher risk of diabetes, cardiovascular disease, and mortality than people without obesity. About half of all individuals who met the new obesity criteria had clinical obesity, and this proportion was only slightly lower in the anthropometric-only obesity group compared with the BMI-plus-anthropometric obesity group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We have always recognized the limitations of BMI as a single marker for obesity because it doesn't take into account body fat distribution,” said senior author Steven Grinspoon, MD, Chief of the Metabolism Unit in the Endocrinology Division of the Mass General Brigham Department of Medicine. “Seeing an increased risk of cardiovascular disease and diabetes in this new group of people with obesity, who were not considered to have obesity before, brings up interesting questions about obesity medications and other therapeutics.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers emphasize that further studies are needed to better understand the causes of and optimal treatments for anthropometric-only obesity. The research team previously developed a therapeutic that reduces waist circumference and plans to explore the utility of different treatment strategies in this newly defined population.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Identifying excess body fat is very important as we’re finding that even people with a normal BMI but with abdominal fat accumulation are at increased health risk,” Fourman said. “Body composition matters – it’s not just pounds on a scale.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;

    

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Mass General Brigham</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:07:43 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiygFBVV95cUxOZTFzYjVYYnJGN3Y4ZTV1eExNclBYM0llQVhfSVZmQkk0UUptX1VWZFBxby1oQmo2UkNIR2V1M2JIYUZOY0hVZzFzenNHbkNjVlBQVWhia3pjNV9kbktHY18xQWM5ZHY0dWVqVnE2S1dMQ0hQdTNTMGxSMTA4WUxLZHNLWExYdDF2ZkNYME5hRjFwc1F1bHR3U3NnRWhQd1ByZGhOQkJZQndMUGZjajJNYXU0STRPLWZPNlNEVXEtdF82TDdWN3FwZlRB</guid></item><item><title>想为行程接种疫苗？旅行诊所须知。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/travel/2025/10/15/travel-clinics-insurance-prices/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RVNDQW3Y3RH6TKBSGMJFA2YPLQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;During Courtney Gardner’s first visit to a travel clinic, she learned about all the diseases she could catch on an upcoming trip to India: typhoid, Japanese encephalitis, hepatitis A, chikungunya, cholera, malaria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 15:01:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxOeE5rcERKOHFENEUxWmtocFlZZXpaSndGSURJRExmNWZ2TWZvR3F0TFA5WVJ1RVlKX0VsQUh0eU5kZWwwdTBUdXRGajdUTUtETlZ6a1diX0wzb1FrcjBHdXNoWktuLVRRUUQ2VkZsLXh1NzQ2UFhpZTJrUWNmRnZWV1Q3RnhNVnRU</guid></item><item><title>特朗普喋喋不休地谈论铝制疫苗专家--《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/15/health/vaccines-aluminum-trump.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:43:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTFBiZzlMNlhRTUZyR2k3VXNRMUFEaHM1YmhwZFdreVNQeTdnZFhlLUNSWWtHV0xBOXJLRktKUWpZQnYwSWxYcXY5ZEtQeXY3TWFkTktJanFuYzZGSEN0TXVmajh2THNwTi1BdXdGSnRncTdRSWpkaUxLMU9B</guid></item><item><title>“对不起，太奇怪了！《：爸爸让女儿担心他对她家的奇怪评论-无聊的熊猫》</title><link>https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;  &lt;p&gt;When you know a person for a long time, you get a sense of how they communicate. You understand why they chose one word instead of another and what emotion that subtle shift in tone is giving away. Our parents often fall into this category. However, Reddit user &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TwoXChromosomes/comments/1kcry6f/dad_hates_my_house_and_apparently_expects_me_to/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;SlenderSelkie&lt;/a&gt; recently ended up in a situation with her father that she just couldn’t wrap her head around. While visiting her home, he not only started criticizing its renovations for being “too weird,” but also tried to see if he could tear them down. And when he was confronted about it, he dropped a dubious line about his grandsons—the woman’s nephews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;This woman invited her dad for a visit, but his comments and actions made little sense&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Worried woman holding her head, reacting to dad upset about daughter’s home and saying something weird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-6" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-6.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-6" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-6.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502656" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-6.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Worried woman holding her head, reacting to dad upset about daughter’s home and saying something weird." title="Worried woman holding her head, reacting to dad upset about daughter’s home and saying something weird." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="post-tablet-ad-within-content post-ads"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad" data-source="primis"&gt;&lt;span id="desktop-widget-loaded"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/stressed-woman-working-from-home-coronavirus-quarantine_19008864.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=4&amp;amp;position=13&amp;amp;uuid=6c9ca5d2-d45a-452f-94e3-82777bcd93c8&amp;amp;query=stressed+woman" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;rawpixel / freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;She wasn’t sure if it was manipulation or a sign of cognitive decline&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt about a dad upset about his daughter’s home and her reaction to his concerns about the house being too weird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fcfb529c6-0a31-45ed-ad49-dea5bc9865a5" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fcfb529c6-0a31-45ed-ad49-dea5bc9865a5.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fcfb529c6-0a31-45ed-ad49-dea5bc9865a5" data-image="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fcfb529c6-0a31-45ed-ad49-dea5bc9865a5.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fcfb529c6-0a31-45ed-ad49-dea5bc9865a5.jpg" alt="Text excerpt about a dad upset about his daughter’s home and her reaction to his concerns about the house being too weird." title="Text excerpt about a dad upset about his daughter’s home and her reaction to his concerns about the house being too weird." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fdaa3cb2b-9f59-4e47-ac75-2eb5c7e19b29" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fdaa3cb2b-9f59-4e47-ac75-2eb5c7e19b29.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fdaa3cb2b-9f59-4e47-ac75-2eb5c7e19b29" data-image="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fdaa3cb2b-9f59-4e47-ac75-2eb5c7e19b29.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fdaa3cb2b-9f59-4e47-ac75-2eb5c7e19b29.jpg" alt="Man Tries To Undo Daughter's Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter's Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt about managing a condition and home accommodations made by husband and wife with disabilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_9d4e5f85dc40824d7f50741a15da7018" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_9d4e5f85dc40824d7f50741a15da7018.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_9d4e5f85dc40824d7f50741a15da7018.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text excerpt about managing a condition and home accommodations made by husband and wife with disabilities." title="Text excerpt about managing a condition and home accommodations made by husband and wife with disabilities." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text on a white background describing satisfaction with accommodating renovations that improve energy and functionality after changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_00badc6bb2d5f900cdde4c57c678d8d0" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_00badc6bb2d5f900cdde4c57c678d8d0.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_00badc6bb2d5f900cdde4c57c678d8d0.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text on a white background describing satisfaction with accommodating renovations that improve energy and functionality after changes." title="Text on a white background describing satisfaction with accommodating renovations that improve energy and functionality after changes." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_2" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Man installing tiles on floor in daughter’s home renovation with dad upset about the unusual changes and worries expressed&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-7" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-7.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-7" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-7.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502657" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-7.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Man installing tiles on floor in daughter’s home renovation with dad upset about the unusual changes and worries expressed" title="Man installing tiles on floor in daughter’s home renovation with dad upset about the unusual changes and worries expressed" loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/tiler-working-renovation-apartment_22698690.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=2&amp;amp;position=21&amp;amp;uuid=2e94c936-284d-4066-83e6-61111fa06c9f&amp;amp;query=renovating" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text showing a dad upset about daughter’s home, worried it’s too weird and concerned about resale value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_a0cf6b28116ccec3146a087d81c08438" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_a0cf6b28116ccec3146a087d81c08438.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_a0cf6b28116ccec3146a087d81c08438.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text showing a dad upset about daughter’s home, worried it’s too weird and concerned about resale value." title="Text showing a dad upset about daughter’s home, worried it’s too weird and concerned about resale value." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt describing a dad upset about his daughter’s home, causing worry due to his unusual reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_e8d6519514913f75580838ed136e4d67" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_e8d6519514913f75580838ed136e4d67.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_e8d6519514913f75580838ed136e4d67.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text excerpt describing a dad upset about his daughter’s home, causing worry due to his unusual reaction." title="Text excerpt describing a dad upset about his daughter’s home, causing worry due to his unusual reaction." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excerpt from a story about a dad upset about daughter's home and his strange behavior in the kitchen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_4e3bc64bbd705c3ae5218d5abefe7155" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_4e3bc64bbd705c3ae5218d5abefe7155.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_4e3bc64bbd705c3ae5218d5abefe7155.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Excerpt from a story about a dad upset about daughter's home and his strange behavior in the kitchen." title="Excerpt from a story about a dad upset about daughter's home and his strange behavior in the kitchen." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_3" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text discussing damage to a home, highlighting dad upset about daughter’s home causing worry over aesthetic issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_cfc649890d373bcb59c54bae3c63b57c" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_cfc649890d373bcb59c54bae3c63b57c.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_cfc649890d373bcb59c54bae3c63b57c.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text discussing damage to a home, highlighting dad upset about daughter’s home causing worry over aesthetic issues." title="Text discussing damage to a home, highlighting dad upset about daughter’s home causing worry over aesthetic issues." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt showing a dad upset about daughter’s home, saying it’s too weird and causing her to worry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_b02b09bb833a7622194fce81b2351c89" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_b02b09bb833a7622194fce81b2351c89.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_b02b09bb833a7622194fce81b2351c89.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text excerpt showing a dad upset about daughter’s home, saying it’s too weird and causing her to worry." title="Text excerpt showing a dad upset about daughter’s home, saying it’s too weird and causing her to worry." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elderly man looking upset and worried at home, illustrating a dad upset about daughter’s home and concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-8" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-8.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-8" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-8.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502658" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-8.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Elderly man looking upset and worried at home, illustrating a dad upset about daughter’s home and concern." title="Elderly man looking upset and worried at home, illustrating a dad upset about daughter’s home and concern." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/thoughtful-senior-man-living-room_13187187.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;position=1&amp;amp;uuid=3f27269c-d46e-4411-8db6-5fe8698da946&amp;amp;query=stressed+elderly+man" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;gpointstudio / freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt from a family discussion where a dad expresses being upset about daughter’s home and moving in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_ed5122ccf67e850434e0b57009e4fd42" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_ed5122ccf67e850434e0b57009e4fd42.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_ed5122ccf67e850434e0b57009e4fd42.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text excerpt from a family discussion where a dad expresses being upset about daughter’s home and moving in." title="Text excerpt from a family discussion where a dad expresses being upset about daughter’s home and moving in." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_4" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dad upset about daughter’s home expresses frustration and worry over unexpected situation involving Billy and Bobby moving in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_7a83cce8f0a3693405cf952e5519f0eb" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_7a83cce8f0a3693405cf952e5519f0eb.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_7a83cce8f0a3693405cf952e5519f0eb.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Dad upset about daughter’s home expresses frustration and worry over unexpected situation involving Billy and Bobby moving in." title="Dad upset about daughter’s home expresses frustration and worry over unexpected situation involving Billy and Bobby moving in." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text showing a dad upset about his daughter's home saying it’s a massive house with room for two boys, which worries her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F39258965-38e1-4112-bd1e-16970e45ffc5" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F39258965-38e1-4112-bd1e-16970e45ffc5.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F39258965-38e1-4112-bd1e-16970e45ffc5" data-image="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F39258965-38e1-4112-bd1e-16970e45ffc5.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F39258965-38e1-4112-bd1e-16970e45ffc5.jpg" alt="Text showing a dad upset about his daughter's home saying it’s a massive house with room for two boys, which worries her." title="Text showing a dad upset about his daughter's home saying it’s a massive house with room for two boys, which worries her." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt showing a dad upset about daughter’s home, saying something that makes her worry about the situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fbd7b1c02-274e-485e-9512-cc078ff995d2" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fbd7b1c02-274e-485e-9512-cc078ff995d2.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fbd7b1c02-274e-485e-9512-cc078ff995d2" data-image="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fbd7b1c02-274e-485e-9512-cc078ff995d2.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2Fbd7b1c02-274e-485e-9512-cc078ff995d2.jpg" alt="Text excerpt showing a dad upset about daughter’s home, saying something that makes her worry about the situation." title="Text excerpt showing a dad upset about daughter’s home, saying something that makes her worry about the situation." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text showing an apology for damaging a home, transferring money via Zelle, and taking someone out to lunch as planned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_146fc0f6749e39393c8c110bfce4af01" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_146fc0f6749e39393c8c110bfce4af01.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_146fc0f6749e39393c8c110bfce4af01.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text showing an apology for damaging a home, transferring money via Zelle, and taking someone out to lunch as planned." title="Text showing an apology for damaging a home, transferring money via Zelle, and taking someone out to lunch as planned." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_0" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elderly dad upset about daughter’s home, leaning forward with hands clasped, showing worry and stress indoors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-9" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-9.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-9" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-9.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502659" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-9.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Elderly dad upset about daughter’s home, leaning forward with hands clasped, showing worry and stress indoors." title="Elderly dad upset about daughter’s home, leaning forward with hands clasped, showing worry and stress indoors." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/senior-man-confronting-alzheimer-disease_16518616.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;position=28&amp;amp;uuid=3f27269c-d46e-4411-8db6-5fe8698da946&amp;amp;query=stressed+elderly+man" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt showing a worried daughter reflecting on her dad being upset about her home and feeling annoyed days later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_76a5c6bf6964301f821ca54ebf927192" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_76a5c6bf6964301f821ca54ebf927192.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_76a5c6bf6964301f821ca54ebf927192.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text excerpt showing a worried daughter reflecting on her dad being upset about her home and feeling annoyed days later." title="Text excerpt showing a worried daughter reflecting on her dad being upset about her home and feeling annoyed days later." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text showing frustration about dad being aggressive only towards daughter's home decoration and feeling disrespected for being a woman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_736482ce6d6774501c677b01c255b662" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_736482ce6d6774501c677b01c255b662.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_736482ce6d6774501c677b01c255b662.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text showing frustration about dad being aggressive only towards daughter's home decoration and feeling disrespected for being a woman." title="Text showing frustration about dad being aggressive only towards daughter's home decoration and feeling disrespected for being a woman." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt showing confusion and worry about a dad upset and daughter’s home situation involving family and nephews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_97ff77629a664cfd34566178069ecb3b" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_97ff77629a664cfd34566178069ecb3b.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_97ff77629a664cfd34566178069ecb3b.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text excerpt showing confusion and worry about a dad upset and daughter’s home situation involving family and nephews." title="Text excerpt showing confusion and worry about a dad upset and daughter’s home situation involving family and nephews." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_1" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home and the resulting worry over unusual family expectations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_b67aa1a2452cc35c4769baa6fc459a0c" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_b67aa1a2452cc35c4769baa6fc459a0c.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_b67aa1a2452cc35c4769baa6fc459a0c.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text excerpt discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home and the resulting worry over unusual family expectations." title="Text excerpt discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home and the resulting worry over unusual family expectations." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text saying a daughter feels stuck deciding whether to talk to her upset dad or brother about a weird home situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_4f7a0f1bbcbe44977846e39d44a3094b" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_4f7a0f1bbcbe44977846e39d44a3094b.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_4f7a0f1bbcbe44977846e39d44a3094b.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text saying a daughter feels stuck deciding whether to talk to her upset dad or brother about a weird home situation." title="Text saying a daughter feels stuck deciding whether to talk to her upset dad or brother about a weird home situation." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TwoXChromosomes/comments/1kcry6f/dad_hates_my_house_and_apparently_expects_me_to/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;SlenderSelkie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Parental disapproval doesn’t mean a lack of love&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1-1" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1-1" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9507333" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1-1.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Man Tries To Undo Daughter's Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter's Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/mother-being-upset-daughter-worried_6319115.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;position=3&amp;amp;uuid=bf782cac-6065-486e-92a5-5ac0a6729caf&amp;amp;query=elderly+mom" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“From your vantage point, your parents’ overreactions and stubborn disapproval probably look unfounded and irrational. To be fair, some may be. What is almost certain, though, is that underneath those behaviors lies their zealous love for you,” &lt;a href="https://hbr.org/2020/09/dont-let-your-parents-disapproval-derail-your-dreams" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Ron Carucci, co-founder and managing partner at &lt;a href="https://www.navalent.com/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;Navalent&lt;/a&gt;, which works with CEOs and executives pursuing transformational change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Carucci is the author of &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Be-Honest-Power-Justice-Purpose/dp/1398600660?tag=vilofjoy-20" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;&lt;em&gt;To Be Honest: Lead with the Power of Truth, Justice and Purpose&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and says that, “at some point, all parents fail to show that love in ways their children need. Trust me, as parents, we remember those moments too, with regret. But moments of poorly expressed love don’t mean that love isn’t there.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_2" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;So while negative comments about your house, for example, can really sting, the concern for its resale value might imply they come from a caring place. (Whether or not they’re warranted is another discussion, though.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The relationship between parents and children is a lifelong study of what is most important in human connections,” Carucci adds. “Through this relationship, we learn so much about how we relate to friends, colleagues, and life partners.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“More than any other formative experience, this relationship shapes the best, and sometimes the worst, of who we become as adults. It’s messy, complicated, and sacred. And it deserves all the effort it takes to keep it strong, especially in the moments where that’s hard.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;As people reacted to the woman’s story, she provided them with more information on her dad and their argument&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a Reddit conversation discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home, raising concerns about his mental state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forum discussion about dad upset over daughter’s home and concerns about unusual family expectations and boundaries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit conversation about dad upset and daughter’s home concerns, discussing safety and family worries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_3" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit discussion about dad upset and worried daughter’s home with concerns about dad’s mental state and behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dad upset about daughter’s home shares concerning views causing her to worry about his denial and attitude toward her disability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text conversation showing a daughter discussing her dad’s covert narcissistic traits and family cluster B behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dad upset about daughter’s home discussing jealousy and concerns over house and yard size in family conflict conversation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_4" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Discussion about dad upset and daughter’s home, with concerns about dementia and family reactions shared in comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a comment discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home and concerns over renovation and family obligations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502272" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-1.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Screenshot of a comment discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home and concerns over renovation and family obligations." title="Screenshot of a comment discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home and concerns over renovation and family obligations." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text post discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home, expressing concern over his strange behavior and boundaries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502273" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text post discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home, expressing concern over his strange behavior and boundaries." title="Text post discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home, expressing concern over his strange behavior and boundaries." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home and his behavior causing worry about their relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-3" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-3" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-3.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502274" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-3.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Comment discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home and his behavior causing worry about their relationship." title="Comment discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home and his behavior causing worry about their relationship." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_5" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home and concerns about his unusual behavior possibly linked to dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-4" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-4.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-4" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-4.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502587" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-4.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Comment discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home and concerns about his unusual behavior possibly linked to dementia." title="Comment discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home and concerns about his unusual behavior possibly linked to dementia." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text conversation discussing concerns about dad’s mental well-being and unusual behavior suggesting possible cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-5" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-5.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-5" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-5.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502588" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-5.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text conversation discussing concerns about dad’s mental well-being and unusual behavior suggesting possible cognitive decline." title="Text conversation discussing concerns about dad’s mental well-being and unusual behavior suggesting possible cognitive decline." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dad upset about daughter’s home talks with her, causing worry over the unusual situation and family concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forum conversation about a dad upset about daughter’s home causing worry and concerns over his mental health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_6" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comment discussion about dad upset over daughter’s home and concerns about kids being left behind or abandoned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Forum conversation about dad upset with daughter’s home and its impact on family dynamics and worries&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reddit user discussing dad upset about daughter’s home and concerns over his unusual, worrying behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a text conversation discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home causing worry due to something weird said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_7" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dad upset about daughter’s home discusses unusual concerns causing her to worry and feel uneasy about the situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Screenshot of a Reddit conversation showing a user concerned about updating a post with a dad upset about daughter’s home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Eventually, the woman got in touch with her brother—the dad of the boys her own father had mentioned&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dad upset about daughter’s home, holding phone and covering face with hand, showing worry and frustration indoors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-10" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-10.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-10" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-10.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502661" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-10.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Dad upset about daughter’s home, holding phone and covering face with hand, showing worry and frustration indoors." title="Dad upset about daughter’s home, holding phone and covering face with hand, showing worry and frustration indoors." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/disappointed-young-blonde-handsome-man-sits-armchair-putting-hand-face-holding-phone_13468176.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=1&amp;amp;position=20&amp;amp;uuid=c07e1bfb-92ef-4944-bed1-c8bc8ef91f11&amp;amp;query=stressed+man+phone" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;stockking / freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home situation, causing confusion and worry about his true intentions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_264f6134fc743d8ff23f3abfb4a46ed7" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_264f6134fc743d8ff23f3abfb4a46ed7.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_264f6134fc743d8ff23f3abfb4a46ed7.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home situation, causing confusion and worry about his true intentions." title="Text discussing a dad upset about daughter’s home situation, causing confusion and worry about his true intentions." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_8" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home, raising concerns that make her worry about his intentions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_eafb886b4ee90b7fc8174bf03a89fdc0" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_eafb886b4ee90b7fc8174bf03a89fdc0.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_eafb886b4ee90b7fc8174bf03a89fdc0.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home, raising concerns that make her worry about his intentions." title="Text discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home, raising concerns that make her worry about his intentions." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text discussing dad upset about daughter’s home situation causing worry and feeling it’s just too weird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_5505e5682ac712e3f16381eb96df3855" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_5505e5682ac712e3f16381eb96df3855.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_5505e5682ac712e3f16381eb96df3855.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text discussing dad upset about daughter’s home situation causing worry and feeling it’s just too weird." title="Text discussing dad upset about daughter’s home situation causing worry and feeling it’s just too weird." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two boys focused on building a wooden train set at home, capturing a dad upset about daughter’s home scene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-11" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-11.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-11" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-11.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502662" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-11.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Two boys focused on building a wooden train set at home, capturing a dad upset about daughter’s home scene." title="Two boys focused on building a wooden train set at home, capturing a dad upset about daughter’s home scene." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/kids-playing-their-room_20546540.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=2&amp;amp;position=27&amp;amp;uuid=114b69f5-1cba-48e5-bb3c-c8d7b4c7c759&amp;amp;query=kids+boys+playing" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home with concerns over strange behavior and earliest signs of decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_014e36a0f53a25709c4ced087a6bc76c" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_014e36a0f53a25709c4ced087a6bc76c.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_014e36a0f53a25709c4ced087a6bc76c.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home with concerns over strange behavior and earliest signs of decline." title="Text discussing a dad upset about his daughter’s home with concerns over strange behavior and earliest signs of decline." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_9" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text message about brother talking to dad regarding daughter’s home causing dad to feel upset and worried.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_0ecf29a3f01ad7faf21d6edb077a2db5" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_0ecf29a3f01ad7faf21d6edb077a2db5.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_0ecf29a3f01ad7faf21d6edb077a2db5.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text message about brother talking to dad regarding daughter’s home causing dad to feel upset and worried." title="Text message about brother talking to dad regarding daughter’s home causing dad to feel upset and worried." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt describing a dad upset about daughter’s home, showing signs of manipulation and OCD fixation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_03ff68973385268c0fbbf042c8a14a7f" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_03ff68973385268c0fbbf042c8a14a7f.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_03ff68973385268c0fbbf042c8a14a7f.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text excerpt describing a dad upset about daughter’s home, showing signs of manipulation and OCD fixation." title="Text excerpt describing a dad upset about daughter’s home, showing signs of manipulation and OCD fixation." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text excerpt showing a dad upset about his daughter’s home with strange agendas causing worry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_64587fdfd40a4d83db85e71d64f50575" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_64587fdfd40a4d83db85e71d64f50575.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_64587fdfd40a4d83db85e71d64f50575.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text excerpt showing a dad upset about his daughter’s home with strange agendas causing worry." title="Text excerpt showing a dad upset about his daughter’s home with strange agendas causing worry." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older dad looking upset while talking to his adult son about daughter’s home, expressing worry about it being too weird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-12" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-12.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-12" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-12.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9502670" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-12.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Older dad looking upset while talking to his adult son about daughter’s home, expressing worry about it being too weird." title="Older dad looking upset while talking to his adult son about daughter’s home, expressing worry about it being too weird." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/free-photo/senior-man-celebrating-his-birthday_25624991.htm#fromView=search&amp;amp;page=2&amp;amp;position=28&amp;amp;uuid=847a8a73-751f-4a68-9af1-adfcf3f3f247&amp;amp;query=elderly+father" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_10" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text message discussing confronting dad about honesty and manipulation, reflecting daughter’s home worries and dad upset situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_2ed2d748837b2c76e0a604ad8d91d2a7" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_2ed2d748837b2c76e0a604ad8d91d2a7.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_2ed2d748837b2c76e0a604ad8d91d2a7.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text message discussing confronting dad about honesty and manipulation, reflecting daughter’s home worries and dad upset situation." title="Text message discussing confronting dad about honesty and manipulation, reflecting daughter’s home worries and dad upset situation." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text thanking everyone for feedback and addressing a dad upset about daughter’s home and calling it weird.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F04a0a995-ab3e-48be-8403-c7a9f1ada0e2" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F04a0a995-ab3e-48be-8403-c7a9f1ada0e2.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F04a0a995-ab3e-48be-8403-c7a9f1ada0e2" data-image="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F04a0a995-ab3e-48be-8403-c7a9f1ada0e2.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://slack-imgs.com/?c=1&amp;amp;o1=ro&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fhtmltoimage-s3bucket-1lw6aoyde4nz5.s3.us-east-1.amazonaws.com%2F04a0a995-ab3e-48be-8403-c7a9f1ada0e2.jpg" alt="Text thanking everyone for feedback and addressing a dad upset about daughter’s home and calling it weird." title="Text thanking everyone for feedback and addressing a dad upset about daughter’s home and calling it weird." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Text image with a message about updating plans, relating to dad upset about daughter’s home causing worry with unusual comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="author_f0c7f8b0cec7a2cc5a6119af31f47cb6" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=author_f0c7f8b0cec7a2cc5a6119af31f47cb6.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/author_f0c7f8b0cec7a2cc5a6119af31f47cb6.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Text image with a message about updating plans, relating to dad upset about daughter’s home causing worry with unusual comments." title="Text image with a message about updating plans, relating to dad upset about daughter’s home causing worry with unusual comments." loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/TwoXChromosomes/comments/1kcry6f/dad_hates_my_house_and_apparently_expects_me_to/" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;SlenderSelkie&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The woman’s concerns are understandable&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="attachment-link-container shareable-image-block" id="dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2-1" data-href="http://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?image_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;a class="web-share-button list-item-share new-share-experiment" data-location="single-post-image" data-title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter\'s Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" data-share-url="https://www.boredpanda.com/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house/?media_id=dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2-1" data-image="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2-1.jpg"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;svg class="svg-icon icon-share-icon" role="img" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;title&gt;Share icon&lt;/title&gt;&lt;path d="M0 15C0 10.8824 5.22292 10.0588 8.79817 10.0588V14.1765L15.7006 8.23061C15.7941 8.15345 15.8695 8.05559 15.9213 7.94441C15.9731 7.83323 16 7.71155 16 7.58824C16 7.46492 15.9731 7.34314 15.9213 7.23196C15.8695 7.12078 15.7941 7.02302 15.7006 6.94586L8.79817 1V5.11765C2.3995 5.11765 0 9.76235 0 15Z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-9507341" src="https://www.boredpanda.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/dad-expects-daughter-take-nephews-big-house-2-1.jpg?utm_campaign=rebelboost_true" alt="Man Tries To Undo Daughter's Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" title="Man Tries To Undo Daughter's Disability-Friendly Home Renovations, Gets Caught Red-Handed" loading="lazy" fetchpriority="low"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Image credits: &lt;a href="https://www.freepik.com/premium-photo/senior-retired-man-sitting-home-alone-while-quarantine_9201997.htm#from_element=cross_selling__photo" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;natusm / freepik (not the actual photo)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="post-desktop-ad-within-content post-ads margin-left"&gt;&lt;span class="dfp-ad"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="pg-ad-label"&gt;ADVERTISEMENT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p id="boredpandacom_desktop_post_infinite_11" align="center" data-freestar-ad="__728x90"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mild cognitive impairment (MCI) is the in-between stage between typical thinking and dementia. It may affect your judgment, like spotting a scam on the internet, or it could affect your ability to plan and remember appointments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/17990-mild-cognitive-impairment" target="_blank" class=" staff-link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;two types&lt;/a&gt; of MCI:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Amnestic MCI (aMCI): This type mostly affects memory. People might forget important information that they used to be able to remember.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Non-amnestic MCI (naMCI): This type mostly affects thinking. You may have trouble with judgment, making decisions, or completing complex tasks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;MCI happens when parts of the brain that help with memory and thinking are damaged or undergo structural changes. These include your hippocampus, temporal lobes, parietal lobe, and other connected regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MCI may be an early stage of certain neurodegenerative conditions&lt;/strong&gt;, such as:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Frontotemporal dementia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Lewy body dementia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Parkinson’s disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vascular dementia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone can develop MCI, but &lt;strong&gt;you are more at risk if you&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone can develop mild cognitive impairment. But you may be more at risk if you:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are above age 65&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have a biological family history of dementia&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have the APOE-ε4 (APOE4) gene variant (a gene that increases your risk of Alzheimer’s disease)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The following factors may also increase your risk&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Brain injuries or disorders, like traumatic brain injury and normal pressure hydrocephalus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Chronic conditions, like diabetes, COPD, and osteoarthritis&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heart and blood vessel issues, like high blood pressure, high cholesterol, and stroke&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Infections, like urinary tract infections (UTIs) and HIV&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mental health conditions, like anxiety and depression&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Metabolic and nutritional issues, like hypothyroidism, vitamin B12 deficiency, and dehydration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sleep conditions, like obstructive sleep apnea&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can also appear as a side effect of taking: antihistamines, antidepressants, blood pressure medications, antiseizure medications, benzodiazepines, muscle relaxants, and opiates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, it’s important to note that MCI looks different for each person and not all cases lead to dementia. According to &lt;a class="text-brandBlue-500 underline underline-offset-[5px] decoration-1 break-words hover:text-blue-800 transition staff-link" href="https://www.alzheimers.gov/alzheimers-dementias/mild-cognitive-impairment" target="_blank" data-identity="link" rel="noopener nofollow"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt;, about 2 in 10 people over age 65 with this condition will develop dementia within a year.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div id="postPoll-9501865" class="post-poll poll-wrapper single-post" data-poll-viewed="false" data-post-id="9501865" data-main-post-id="" data-poll-id="17749"&gt; &lt;input class="post-9501865-poll-value" type="hidden" value="eyJwb2xsSWQiOjE3NzQ5LCJwb3N0SWQiOjk1MDE4NjUsImhpZGVDb21tZW50cyI6ZmFsc2UsInF1ZXN0aW9ucyI6W3siaWQiOjE3NzQ5LCJwb2xsSWQiOjE3NzQ5LCJ0ZXh0IjoiSG93IGRvIHlvdSBpbnRlcnByZXQgdGhlIGRhZCdzIGNvbW1lbnQgYWJvdXQgbmVwaGV3cyBtb3ZpbmcgaW4gd2hlbiBubyBwbGFucyB3ZXJlIG1hZGU/Iiwib3JkZXIiOm51bGwsImFuc3dlcnMiOlt7ImlkIjo2NzY2NiwicXVlc3Rpb25JZCI6MTc3NDksInRleHQiOiJBIHNpZ24gb2YgY29nbml0aXZlIGRlY2xpbmUiLCJ2b3RlcyI6ODd9LHsiaWQiOjY3NjY3LCJxdWVzdGlvbklkIjoxNzc0OSwidGV4dCI6IkF0dGVtcHQgdG8gbWFuaXB1bGF0ZSB0aGUgc2l0dWF0aW9uIiwidm90ZXMiOjE1NH0seyJpZCI6Njc2NjgsInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE3NzQ5LCJ0ZXh0IjoiQSBtaXN1bmRlcnN0b29kIGpva2Ugb3IgY29tbWVudCIsInZvdGVzIjoxMX0seyJpZCI6Njc2NjksInF1ZXN0aW9uSWQiOjE3NzQ5LCJ0ZXh0IjoiQ29uY2VybiBhYm91dCBmYW1pbHkgZHluYW1pY3MiLCJ2b3RlcyI6MzJ9XX1dLCJwb3N0VGl0bGUiOm51bGwsInBvc3RVcmwiOiJodHRwczpcL1wvd3d3LmJvcmVkcGFuZGEuY29tXC9kYWQtZXhwZWN0cy1kYXVnaHRlci10YWtlLW5lcGhld3MtYmlnLWhvdXNlXC8ifQ=="&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: isInitialised()"&gt;    &lt;div data-bind="if: !isLoading() &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults"&gt; &lt;div class="poll-content"&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-title"&gt;Thanks! Check out the results:&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;h3 class="answered-content-question" data-bind="text: currentQuestionText()"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;  &lt;p class="total-votes" data-bind="visible: totalVotes() &amp;gt; 10 &amp;amp;&amp;amp; isShowingResults &amp;amp;&amp;amp; totalVotesDisplayMode !== 0"&gt; &lt;span class="text"&gt;Total votes · &lt;/span&gt; &lt;span data-bind="text: totalVotesFormatted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block-wrapper"&gt; &lt;p class="badge"&gt;Newsletter&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="subscribe-to-newsletter-block"&gt; &lt;p class="left"&gt; &lt;h3 class="title"&gt;Subscribe to Access &lt;br&gt; Exclusive Polls&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;div class="disclaimer"&gt; &lt;p&gt;By entering your email and clicking Subscribe, you're agreeing to let us send you customized marketing messages about us and our advertising partners. You are also agreeing to our &lt;a href="https://www.boredpanda.com/privacy-policy/"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;div data-bind="if: newsletterSubscribed" class="thank-you"&gt; &lt;div class="wrapper"&gt;  &lt;p class="right"&gt;Thank you! You've successfully subscribed to newsletters!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;  &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;     &lt;p class="clearfix"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bored Panda</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 14:39:38 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMie0FVX3lxTE5uYmYwdzktazZub1JfcTFfSEdhTFVGX0JfVW52YXJFM3E4Vks0YVFTMTcxczdxMnE5WWJqVkRWelVDbFd3UlZudkNKckdOUVBKejQxNGgySHU3eTlCRXFERDNHY3pFMmxEVXZlVGlpdGtiTk5WelpQTVJQVQ</guid></item><item><title>专家精确定位简单的力量测试可以预测您患肝病和其他疾病的风险-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15194203/simple-strength-test-grip-liver-disease-longevity.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People who are overweight but have good muscle strength may be less likely to develop obesity-related heart, liver or kidney damage, new research has suggested. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite a growing body of evidence that excess body fat can directly cause illnesses, from heart disease to &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-40bdf8b0-a9b2-11f0-93ac-c9db3c873251"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, experts now say obese people with good grip strength may be less likely to die early, and are better protected against disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Grip strength—which measures the force with which someone can squeeze an object—has long been considered a good indicator of physical health, with higher scores indicating a reduced risk of heart disease, arthritis and even certain cancers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now researchers, from Pennington Biomedical Research Center, say it's a 'powerful, early sign of who is most at risk' of developing obesity-related diseases among people with excess body fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Whilst obesity is defined as a body mass index (BMI) of 30 or higher, using an individual's height and weight to assess their potential health risks, excess body fat refers to an abnormal build-up of fatty tissue that has an adverse affect on our health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/jcem"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;researchers looked at 93,275 participants from the UK Biobank with excess body fat—also known as preclinical obesity—to determine the link between grip strength and the development of obesity-related health issues or death. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They found that participants with a stronger hand-grip were significantly less likely to develop obesity and die during a follow-up period of just over 13 years.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Yun Shen, an expert in metabolic disease and study lead author, said: 'This protective link was consistent in multiple checks using other muscle metrics, including the muscle-to-weight and lean-to weight ratios. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-module-version="1.16.1" data-dataset-id="2057" data-mol-fe-xpmodule-newsletter-sign-up data-newsletter="configurable" data-form-action-url="https://link.news.dailymail.co.uk/s/Health" data-environment="production" data-newsletter-id="Health" data-newsletter-channel-colour="health" data-watermark="uk" data-image="https://i.dailymail.co.uk/i/pix/2025/10/10/health_newsletter.png" data-title="Sign up for our free Health newsletter" data-subtitle="Transform your health every Tuesday with expert guides, real-life stories and advice from top doctors"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;People with excess body fat but more muscle may be less likely to develop organ damage or die from obesity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Because grip strength is easy to measure and strength can be improved with weight training, the research points to a practical, low-cost way to identify at-risk individuals and to act early,' he added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To test your grip strength at home, experts suggest attempting to grip a heavy weight or object—around three quarters of your bodyweight, for one minute straight without any interruptions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For the average man, this means selecting a weight that is around 85kg, while form women its 54kg. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For men, 60 seconds should be easy enough, whilst 30 seconds is a reasonable target for women—with anything less than this indicating an increased risk of premature mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Grip strength has long been used by doctors to identify patients at risk of developing various health problems early on, including cardiovascular disease and even dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2016, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14530873/Simple-DIY-test-die-early-health-expert-warns.html"&gt;research &lt;/a&gt;involving nearly 7,000 people by University College London found that those who had weaker grip strength at the start of the 17-year study had a higher-than-average rate of premature death from all causes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another analysis of previous research, with nearly 140,000 people, found that weak grip strength is a more accurate predictor for early death than high blood pressure, reported The Lancet in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And according to one study published in the Journal of Strength and Conditioning last year, those with the least muscle strength were almost 150 per cent more likely to die early.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;A hand dynamometer is used to measure isometric grip force (hand grip strength)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To improve grip strength, the NHS advises performing muscle-strengthening activities that work all major muscle groups—including legs, hips, back,. abdomen, chest, shoulders and arms—at least twice a week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;No specific amount of time is recommended, but exercises should be performed to the point at which another repetition would be difficult without help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These may include push ups, bicep curls, glute bridges, squats and tricep dips. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It comes as new research has suggested that just five minutes of exercise twice a day can help boost heart health—especially for those who lead sedentary lifestyles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists found that brief bursts of activity can significantly improve cardiovascular fitness, a key measure of how the heart, lungs and blood vessels deliver oxygen to the muscles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This effect was also true for obese people, suggesting that improving muscle strength could help protect against a number of obesity-related diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It comes as the British Liver Trust has estimated that metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD) may affect up to 40 per cent of people in the UK. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Known medically as metabolic dysfunction-associated steatotic liver disease (MASLD), the condition is not linked to heavy drinking—the more commonly known cause of liver problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People with MASLD have excess fat in their liver and one or more metabolic risk factors, which can include obesity, high blood sugar and high blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Roughly one in four patients has a more advanced form called metabolic dysfunction-associated steatohepatitis, or MASH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In this condition, fat buildup has led to inflammation, cell damage and, in some cases, liver scarring.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Up to 1 in 5 people with MASH will progress to cirrhosis — advanced, irreversible scarring of the liver — which can lead to liver failure and increase the risk of liver cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When liver function starts to decline, though, patients can accumulate fluid in the abdomen, develop jaundice or experience confusion caused by a buildup of toxins in the bloodstream.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 13:00:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPT1g2OWEzTjVfWGM4YWhqR1pOX3Bhb3hadjBMdFJlcThpcnRtZzRzU0ZuSzJ3LTBRZnhNUWNJbGhLclpQd3M1STA2N3BPYWFycFotWGtBdTg3eXo5YVJQNjRSUWhQaVgyUEhqeUF6Zlh3emhjc1BNU3BEVmc3SVFRbks2LW9zTTBPZFpLek1UQ1NESzNnWjVNMGRONENFSFpUUVREand2dTVJUdIBrwFBVV95cUxNVVdMMnlncTdUTDdhN3otajVFOTl4YkM0RFR6cVk3LVBlMGlpUXFyUVlhYnR3eWR4ckxXZTEtUWZwYUxsdHJsaVB5WGl3cGFTU3JDcW9JWVZnNFc3OUlKTUdTaE8xYjdJS1VDdWptZmx5MUlYSWdQTHpKUFRoZUdYRjFjZUVXNllpVEZObEhTenlldHQ5LXV3dTRmWUdydDI0d3lmU1dPck45S0s3Rk8w</guid></item><item><title>研究：我们正在以比想象更快的速度输掉对抗耐药性感染的战争- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/10/15/g-s1-93449/antibiotic-resistance-bacteria</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-93462" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                This micrograph image depicts a gastrointestinal bacteria that can become pathogenic after trauma, surgery or other disruptions.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Smith Collection/Gado/via Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Smith Collection/Gado/via Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;One of the pillars of modern medicine is showing its cracks, according to a new report from the World Health Organization.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Antibiotics have turned once deadly infections into minor inconveniences. They make lifesaving interventions, from surgery to chemotherapy, safer. But every time this powerful tool gets used, there's a risk — antibiotic resistance.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Out of the billions of bacteria causing an infection in an individual, some small fraction may be naturally resistant to a given drug. Taking an antibiotic can clear the field for those resistant bacteria to spread.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Antimicrobial resistance is just basic evolution," says &lt;a href="https://profiles.ucla.edu/kevin.ikuta" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Kevin Ikuta&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, an infectious disease physician and researcher at UCLA. He says we need antibiotics, but "we are in this battle we're trying to lose as slowly as possible anytime we treat an infection."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Humans are losing that battle faster than previously thought. In 2023, roughly &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/i/item/B09585" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;1 in 6 infections&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tested by labs worldwide were resistant to antibiotic treatment, according to WHO. The report says nearly 40% of antibiotics used to treat common urinary, gut, blood and sexually-transmitted infections have lost effectiveness over the past five years.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Frankly, it's quite concerning," says &lt;a href="https://onehealthtrust.org/researchers/ramanan_laxminarayan/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Ramanan Laxminarayan&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, president of One Health Trust, a non-profit. "We do see increases in resistance every year, but here we see a pretty sharp increase."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Antimicrobial resistance is already directly responsible for about &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/antimicrobial-resistance" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;1.2 million deaths&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a year and contributes to nearly 5 million, according to WHO. That toll could grow, says Laxminarayan.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We're sleepwalking into a disaster," he says. "I shouldn't say we are — we already have sleepwalked into a disaster."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hot spots of resistance &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The jump in resistance was sharpest in low- and middle-income countries with weaker health systems, the report found. Countries with less robust systems to track &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2020/05/14/853984869/antibiotic-resistance-is-still-a-top-health-worry-its-a-pandemic-worry-too" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;antibiotic resistance&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; tended to report higher levels, too.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"For some of the most common infections that afflict tropical countries, nearly 50 to 60% of the infections are now drug resistant," says Laxminarayan.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;These higher numbers could reflect biased data, where weak surveillance systems only pick up the worst infections that are more likely to be resistant to antibiotics. But they could also reflect genuinely higher levels of resistance.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"It's probably both," says Laxminarayan.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Weak surveillance systems tend to be coupled with weaker health systems. That means "you probably have less infection prevention and control, less vaccination, weaker water and sanitation system," he says, which can breed resistance.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Easier access to basic antibiotics could be playing a role too.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"You don't necessarily need a prescription to get an antibiotic in a lot of countries," says Ikuta. That can lead to misuse, for instance &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2024/05/29/g-s1-1647/covid-pandemic-superbugs-antibiotic-resistance" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;treating a viral infection with antibiotics&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which could give resistant bacteria a leg up without providing any therapeutic benefit.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Less access, more resistance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;While misuse is a problem in lower-income countries, the bigger problem is that effective antibiotics — especially those that wealthier countries use when more basic ones fail — are often out of reach for those who need them most.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"In the U.S., if the first two drugs didn't work for you, likely you could afford the third drug," says Laxminarayan. "That option is not available to someone living in Cote d'Ivoire or The Gambia." That can leave infections insufficiently treated, ultimately fueling the fire of resistance.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Those dynamics are part of what's driving &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2023/11/07/1209109088/antibiotics-that-fight-deadly-infections-in-babies-are-losing-their-power" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;increased resistance&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; among the most commonly prescribed antibiotics — especially carbapenems and fluoroquinolones — that target a wide range of bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;As resistance to those first-choice antibiotics grows, physicians are left with older and more potentially toxic medications, or newer drugs that aren't widely available, especially in lower-income countries, says Ikuta. "So we're either left with an untreatable infection or with a treatment where the side effects may be as toxic as the infection itself," he says. "It's quite the pickle, clinically."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Getting out of that pickle won't be easy.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For one, it'll require a clearer global picture of resistance. While more countries are submitting data to WHO to help track global resistance levels, there are still major gaps.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Last year, 48% of countries didn't report any resistance data to WHO. Among the countries that did, nearly half still lack robust surveillance systems, the WHO says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Better surveillance data can help physicians narrow down which antibiotics to use, ensuring more effective treatments that minimize resistance.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Physicians also need newer, better antibiotics. Developing drugs that target bacteria in novel ways can help humans get ahead of resistance, but &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/02-10-2025-who-releases-new-reports-on-new-tests-and-treatments-in-development-for-bacterial-infections" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;WHO says&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the global pipeline of new treatments isn't flowing fast enough to meet the need.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The clock is ticking, says Ikuta. If progress isn't made and resistance continues to grow, medical care we take for granted could be at risk.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's not just the treatment of acute infections and sepsis, it's making sure surgery is safe and effective, and chemotherapy is available," he says "These advancements in medicine are on the back of antibiotics, so when we lose antibiotics, we risk losing those."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 12:13:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxOSWM5TFRPODBEVjZnTlR5U25SU1pYTFJWZWQ2akVESHNPOE02RGh0T1J3bGxvSVBpYjNkX29UVFJ0aVZMcnVjWEVZazVhbkdxQzZ5RF90TXBHQUpLSVZlQ09wUzdrT2JXMEo0SnhCX1VMcXFUTE5lUnloZkFIU2RLLWM4ZDZHUXl2OE0taWJwV3lrRDlXU0JqM0YySjY</guid></item><item><title>纽约卫生官员确认该州首例本地获得的基孔肯雅病毒病例- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/new-york-health-officials-confirm-states-first-locally-acquired-case-c-rcna237734</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c64121" class="body-graf"&gt;MINEOLA, N.Y. — A person living in New York has tested positive for the &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/china-mosquitoes-chikungunya-explainer-050e53750c8c041fc72b7cf62c01b92f"&gt;chikungunya virus&lt;/a&gt; in what state health officials say is the first reported transmission of the mosquito-borne illness within the United States in six years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-76977e" class="body-graf"&gt;The state Department of Health said Tuesday that the virus, which has been &lt;a href="https://apnews.com/article/china-chikungunya-virus-outbreak-control-measures-3ee97c21152b05ed0912af646594eafd"&gt;spreading in China&lt;/a&gt; and elsewhere, was identified in a person living in Nassau County on Long Island.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-34a7a9" class="body-graf"&gt;The county’s health department, in a separate statement, said the person began experiencing symptoms in August after having traveled outside of the region, but not out of the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-1496e1" class="body-graf"&gt;It’s not clear how exactly the person, whom authorities have not named, contracted the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-0c4f72" class="body-graf"&gt;Health officials say the person was likely bit by an infected mosquito, but they also say the virus has not been detected in local mosquito pools and there is no evidence of ongoing transmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-45621c" class="body-graf"&gt;The type of mosquito known to carry chikungunya is present in parts of the New York City metropolitan area, including suburban Long Island. The disease cannot be spread directly from one person to another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-92bd15" class="body-graf"&gt;Since mosquitoes are less active during the fall’s cooler temperatures, the current risk of transmission is “very low,” said state Health Commissioner James McDonald.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-fc74c6" class="body-graf"&gt;Chikungunya is found mostly in tropical and subtropical regions, according to the state health department. Its symptoms include fever and joint pain, headache, muscle pain, joint swelling and rashes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-8db843" class="body-graf"&gt;The illness is rarely fatal and most patients recover within a week, though newborns, older adults and people with chronic health conditions such as high blood pressure and diabetes are at higher risk, the agency said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-275e3a" class="body-graf"&gt;The U.S. and its territories have not seen a locally acquired case of the virus since 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3606f8" class="body-graf"&gt;New York state has had three other cases of the virus this year, though all were linked to international travel to regions where the virus is prevalent, state health officials said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7d50ea" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;Local mosquitoes can transmit other dangerous viruses, such as West Nile, Eastern Equine Encephalitis and Jamestown Canyon viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:50:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxOODh4d2RkQmhqVUR1ZW5WTUdxTlk2amhvLVZwTlphbV9hZE04N0lxQ1pHblVtMFpEODZDOTFaT1BWbTlMb2VhZDhRZEpHcFJHaUxtaVpWNmdOWS1YM0RTZkxheUVQTlNUaXpTOWhXMnhmZEljaHVZZV9iWTI3d2FUNmkxSWJHYXcwN2lFQnE1bER3U2VfNS1mYU8yeVRyLXl2TWlJOXU5UlZTUThxV29QdldNRVIwYU9SZHfSAVZBVV95cUxPMmFjdVZwS2R2cnROejZOZjBGWGNtYnRwVmFvRVBnc2pFT3hnNTRSVGFXM3dGemNKQUlfYjZ1TzNRR1BmelBMeHBiSm9jaDNsTGJ2NURrUQ</guid></item><item><title>您可能无法发现的心脏病异常症状-《每日电讯报》</title><link>https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/heart-health/unusual-signs-of-heart-disease/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="component article-body-text    " data-test="article-body-text"&gt;
  
  

	

	
	

	
	



  
  
    &lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Dizziness&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudden dizziness or light-headedness could be because the heart isn’t pumping enough blood to the brain, usually a result of an arrhythmia (abnormal heart rhythm), a heart valve condition or even a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Feeling sick&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A lot of the time, being nauseous isn’t related to your heart, but if you’re experiencing it, along with the other symptoms like radiating chest pain, it’s because your heart is unhappy and is trying to work on the blood flow. Your body senses something’s not quite right, and then that can affect your stomach, so you feel a bit sick because your body’s struggling,” says Goss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Swollen ankles&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This can be a marker that your heart is not pumping as effectively, says Goss. “Fluid can build because it’s not able to pump blood around properly, and it is common to experience it in your lower limbs. It can sometimes be medication-related or someone might have a problem with their heart like valvular heart disease or heart failure, which can cause fluid to build up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Obviously if you get off a plane, and your ankles are swollen, it doesn’t mean you’ve got a heart problem,” agrees Dr Segal, “but it can be an indicator of heart failure and other conditions such as renal failure and liver failure. So get it checked out if it persists.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Indigestion&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="ck-custom-link" href="https://www.telegraph.co.uk/health-fitness/conditions/cancer/tummy-ache-serious-crohns-colitis-ibs-stomach-cancer/"&gt;Stomach pain&lt;/a&gt; which comes in waves can be a sign of a heart attack, and the difficulty is distinguishing between heart pain and indigestion. “It can be quite difficult to tell the difference because the heart, stomach, gullet all lie really close to one another,” says Goss. ‘If you’re having indigestion-type pain and are unsure what is causing it, speak to your doctor as it’s always better to be checked out.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Grey pallor&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with heart failure can get a bad colour across their face – their skin becomes pasty and grey. Loved ones may look at you and say: “Your colour’s not right.” In some extreme cases, people’s lips go white or bluish. “There are many reasons why that can be benign, but on the other hand, going clammy and pale and grey can be a sign of a heart problem,” says Dr Segal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Sleeping upright or in a chair&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some elderly people don’t like lying flat because it makes them breathless, which is a sign of fluid building up in the lungs. “Obviously, we all occasionally get up because we can’t sleep,” says Dr Segal. “But if there’s been a persistent change, and the person is now having to prop themselves up, that’s a classic sign the heart is struggling, and they’re unable to lie flat at night comfortably.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-normal"&gt;Other ways to keep track of your heart health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-colour"&gt;Have a health check&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adults between 40 and 74 can have a free NHS Health Check every five years, which helps assess your risk of heart disease, type 2 diabetes, kidney disease, stroke, and certain types of dementia. You will typically be invited by your GP, but if you are not invited, contact your GP practice or local pharmacy to book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="u-heading-size-medium u-heading-style-colour"&gt;Get a blood pressure monitor&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;These usually start from £30. Normal blood pressure is considered to be between 90/60mmHg and 120/80mmHg.&lt;/p&gt;
  
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Telegraph</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:08:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPT0Y1LXgtejZuQVJlS1ZBVEhoRGZod2lValVYZEh6dEVPUVh5MUk2eEpIeG05ZEtJYjMxQlRWY1pfT0kzUU84U0U5akRIM1p0ckd1NU4tQ3pzYWplSWJ5M2lpN3BYcVVNYzg5dzcyV2RqX09tRGJzY1FOc1NwNm1Bc1FlSlpYZHVjQU9SMXZVTmJKd0lTVTBQUFcwTVRCNEE</guid></item><item><title>佛罗里达州野生动物官员在州内发现第二例“僵尸鹿病” -卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/oct/15/florida-zombie-deer-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Wildlife officials in Florida have discovered only the second case in the state of a deadly infection known colloquially as “zombie deer disease”, and are enforcing emergency measures to try to prevent a spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The highly contagious chronic wasting disease (CWD) was found during routine screening in the carcass of a young white-tailed doe that was struck by a vehicle in Holmes county, close to the Alabama border, early last month. The only previous recorded instance in &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/florida" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Florida&lt;/a&gt; was in a four-year-old doe killed about a mile away in June 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Experts are warning of a domino effect on wildlife management if the neurodegenerative disease, more prevalent in western and north-eastern states, is not contained. Although not harmful to humans, it has no vaccine or cure, and spreads easily through animal to animal contact, environmental contamination, and ticks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="7dec8a41-62ec-4751-8a57-1735f45109e6" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":3,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"‘Kissing bug’ disease should be treated as endemic in US, scientists say","elementId":"7dec8a41-62ec-4751-8a57-1735f45109e6","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/sep/13/kissing-bug-chagas-disease"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This disease right now is probably the greatest threat to deer and deer hunting in North America,” said wildlife biologist &lt;a href="https://sheawildlife.com/deer" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Steven Shea&lt;/a&gt;, an expert in deer populations who manages more than half a million acres of species habitat in central Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Based on everything we know, CWD is going to continue to spread. Every instance where it’s been tried to be contained and eradicated has been unsuccessful. So really what agencies are trying to do is basically slow down the spread, keep it in a relatively small area.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Florida Fish and Wildlife Conservation Commission (FWC) has implemented a special management zone and program of enhanced surveillance and monitoring in Holmes and neighboring Jackson and Washington counties. &lt;a href="https://myfwc.com/research/wildlife/health/white-tail-deer/cwd/monitoring/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Test results are pending&lt;/a&gt; on 90 animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The disease is a so-called silent killer because an infected deer can live for several years without exhibiting symptoms. It will eventually succumb to brain tissue damage and experience a range of symptoms including weight loss, behavioral abnormalities, loss of coordination, excessive salivation, and eventually death, according to the University of Florida’s &lt;a href="https://nwdistrict.ifas.ufl.edu/phag/2023/09/08/deadly-deer-disease-found-in-holmes-county-implications-for-deer-hunting-and-management/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;department of wildlife ecology and conservation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The state’s white-tailed deer population is estimated at up to 700,000, with about 100,000 hunted each year, making it Florida’s most popular game animal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;FWC implemented &lt;a href="https://myfwc.com/research/wildlife/health/white-tail-deer/cwd/regulations/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;special rules&lt;/a&gt; in the CWD management zone for the deer hunting season beginning later this month, including mandatory checking of all carcasses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Florida’s early detection puts us in a best-case scenario for CWD management, as a smaller outbreak is more realistic to contain,” James Kelly, the commission’s CWD surveillance coordinator, said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Hunters are our first line of defense in managing this disease. Each sample helps us track the spread of the disease and informs our strategies to manage it effectively.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Shea said he feared a “domino effect” if CWD took hold in Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Hunters have to send a head in for testing, they’re waiting on the meat, and if it comes back positive they have to discard the meat,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“So we’re fearful the number of hunters of white-tailed deer will drop. Hunters are the major way we control deer populations in many areas of the country and if that goes away you’re still going to have high numbers of deer, [but] there’s going to be bigger impacts on vehicle strikes, and crop depredation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Hunters provide one of the largest revenue sources that supports all fish and wildlife management in North America and if fewer hunters are hunting there’s less money that comes in to seed programs that help all wildlife, not just white-tailed deer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxOdGMzNU9qeGMtNTRVNV9LaldrMTlZWnZIZ2ZSYU16TGtQTGlMZG1qMEswZ2MwQWVhaFRsb0lMVGh4WFZGVFJUVUtENHh0bDFfMW5tUkdCeDZyX3owamozd0JjU1FNQ3BtejRLeVIweVZaSW9WQVB1UGZJYnJLSEVESQ</guid></item><item><title>呼吸道病毒季节已经到来。今年接种疫苗的注意事项- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/15/health/flu-covid-season-vaccine-tips-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl9l3ty003u3b6nf7w1v1gb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It’s that time of year when the leaves are turning golden, there’s a chill in the air and the threat of respiratory viruses like Covid-19, influenza or RSV looms across the country.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000a3b6nkhif38ry@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention expects the 2025-26 fall and winter respiratory disease season to have a similar number of peak hospitalizations due to Covid-19, flu and respiratory syncytial virus as there were last season.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl9njk900433b6nm6zkg8n0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But there are some steps you can take to reduce your risk of getting seriously ill with any of those circulating viruses this year – and vaccination plays a key role.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000b3b6nf0zieqeo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “One question or comment I get all the time from my own patients is, ‘Dr. Ren, I got the flu vaccine last year, or I got the Covid vaccine last year, but I still got Covid, or I still got the flu. What gives?’” said Dr. Mike Ren, an assistant professor of &lt;a href="https://nam11.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Flink.mediaoutreach.meltwater.com%2Fls%2Fclick%3Fupn%3Du001.rS6AFLs2KX-2FUfTmhUDQFOA50cagcI56HAvnRKrweh1IRC0ivJtGUIRQbGfaxNKF25I3C9oZjVVuBGm8YN0INaMPGkiVEywVn6RfQcC2CR2w-3D4_Zs_-2BfvDFm8rLlMG3DiFVwLpkkmQZ5tK1QI-2Bs-2FpJe6gRjYIK1XFj6zR1wY-2F1FgAYynw6UBk8Y7NcVJyGS0c5nHy9Y5PTJ0djCZZ5RXOaizvrcI6PZPb9G7M-2Bed4Vtc2WmnW92rOmh41TsdHxu-2BhstQFhezutmgGLl4ZGFTWax9eGF5TtHfHto8b8sKtzcQ4sZ662jPhK-2FuZk-2BxwcJxYbOdz3bOEhZHqS0e-2BNYCYMi0Yn2sydPhL36nEvnI7Rb0H-2FWzqd6Fe9N6wjadivEJCu2izqQmNsDHOaLjpLaIM75G6c4-2BnRN8bDu5BHPZ6ocaUpFmHcExU7JrTPlmEgPvRo9B0naGzOmCoav4izHEuZrwekHY2niR8HbERq2iyKYgO-2FO5TxERzYIKxF92zNWYsqEjNAXw-3D-3D&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7Cjacqueline.howard%40cnn.com%7C735d35e1b3504200029808de073d941d%7C0eb48825e8714459bc72d0ecd68f1f39%7C0%7C0%7C638956158217132134%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=PpEKJ3LbaWH%2FPnqPnXMwiZNVijD4RiEs1u7cbpzkLVg%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank"&gt;family and community medicine&lt;/a&gt; at the Baylor College of Medicine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000c3b6nahnklqsu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “What I tell them is, if I get the flu shot and someone with the flu sneezes on me and I’m in direct contact, I may still get sick, but it would be a much lighter version of illness,” he said. “Vaccines are not just disease prevention, but it’s to prevent you from getting a severe form of the disease that sends you to the hospital or worse. Flu every year and Covid every year still cause significant mortality in the country.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000d3b6n7514il12@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC estimates that about 1 million people were hospitalized with the flu last season, and there were up to 130,000 flu deaths, based on &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu-burden/php/data-vis/2024-2025.html" target="_blank"&gt;preliminary data&lt;/a&gt; from October 2024 through May 2025. Similar &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/php/surveillance/burden-estimates.html" target="_blank"&gt;CDC estimates&lt;/a&gt; suggest that from October 2024 through September 2025, there have been almost 540,000 Covid-19 hospitalizations and up to 63,000 Covid-19 deaths.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000e3b6n5xqk6f61@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Here’s what to know about getting this season’s Covid-19, flu and RSV vaccinations.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000g3b6naa395hje@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC says people 6 months and older - including pregnant people - should consult a health care provider to get an updated Covid-19 vaccine this season. It’s a shift away from the broader push in previous years for most people to get a Covid-19 shot.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000j3b6nt8uns5yc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The difference this year is that there’s not an explicit recommendation by the federal government to get the booster,” said Dr. Dan Barouch, director of the Center for Virology and Vaccine Research at Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000k3b6nf1jnz2xn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This fall, the CDC has not explicitly recommended the Covid-19 vaccine but has made it available to everybody 6 months and older in a process called shared-decision making, which means that people are supposed to talk to a health care provider about the risks and benefits,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgld2jcb00003b6n069lgtyp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Types of &lt;a href="https://medlineplus.gov/ency/article/001933.htm" target="_blank"&gt;health care providers&lt;/a&gt; may include people like physicians, nurse practitioners, pharmacists and physician assistants.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000l3b6nqxyskqhf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There are three types of Covid-19 vaccines available in the US: Pfizer for ages 5 and older, Moderna for 6 months and older, and Novavax for 12 and older. Pfizer and Moderna’s shots use mRNA technology, and Novavax’s version is a protein-based vaccine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl99n1r001z3b6n74p073bp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            This year’s vaccines have been updated to target coronavirus strains circulating more recently, and they are available at most pharmacies, some doctors offices and certain public health departments.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000n3b6nfsubspc4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Many pharmaceutical places like your Walgreens or CVS should carry it,” said Dr. Panagis Galiatsatos, pulmonary and critical care medicine physician at Johns Hopkins and a spokesperson with the American Lung Association, who is author of the book “&lt;a href="https://www.press.jhu.edu/books/title/33262/medicine-greater-good?c" target="_blank"&gt;Medicine for the Greater Good&lt;/a&gt;.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000o3b6n3cc88o2a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Before the CDC finalized the new recommendation this year, access to Covid-19 shots had differed from state to state as pharmacies and providers navigated new federal vaccine policies. CVS, which had previously limited access to Covid-19 shots in some places, said last week that it was “updating our systems to be able to offer the updated COVID-19 vaccines to patients nationwide” and that “prescriptions from outside prescribers will no longer be required in any states.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000q3b6ndtkw85sh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For people who may have questions about where to find updated Covid-19 vaccines in their area or how to get their children vaccinated, Galiatsatos suggested directing questions to their local city or county health department or finding a large academic medical center in their area where they may be able to receive the vaccine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000r3b6niyp72gvg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “And what we usually say is to get the updated vaccine that usually comes out in the fall, get it once it’s available, and then talk with your doctor if you should consider getting boosted in about six months,” Galiatsatos said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000s3b6nnrcdocix@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Sarah Dupont, a family medicine physician at Emory Healthcare and assistant professor at Emory University School of Medicine, recommends getting the Covid shot in October or early November.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000t3b6nm89bttbv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “At least a few weeks before Thanksgiving, to be sure you are protected over the holidays. If you have had a COVID-19 infection recently, however, you probably want to delay your booster as you already have a boost in immunity,” Dupont said in an email.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000u3b6nktyk4wft@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For most eligible people with insurance, vaccinations may be covered, but “a COVID booster at a retail pharmacy is about $220 without insurance,” Dupont added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgnx1p0000003b6njflxze5n@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The nation’s largest trade association for health insurers said its members – which cover more than 200 million Americans – indicated that the new CDC recommendations would not have an impact on policyholders’ coverage through the end of 2026.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgny57z300053b6n987f42ki@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            AHIP, formerly America’s Health Insurance Plans, said in a statement in September that its members would continue to cover all immunizations that the CDC’s advisory committee recommended as of September 1 at no cost to patients. This includes the updated Covid-19 vaccine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000v3b6n7lxqwcmi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Last year’s updated Covid-19 vaccines were found to be about 39% effective against Covid-19 hospitalizations and about 64% against Covid-19 deaths, according to a study of US veterans published Wednesday in the &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2510226" target="_blank"&gt;New England Journal of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000w3b6n7ni4ie90@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The Covid-19 vaccines do a better job at preventing severe disease than they do preventing mild infection, and so people at higher risk of severe disease benefit the most from the boosters,” Barouch said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h4 class="subheader inline-placeholder subheader-elevate vossi-subheader vossi-subheader--size-h4" data-editable="text" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/subheader/instances/cmgl9bqth002b3b6n78dxi0j2@published" data-component-name="subheader" id="can-you-get-a-covid-vaccine-and-flu-shot-at-the-same-time" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
        Can you get a Covid vaccine and flu shot at the same time?
&lt;/h4&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl9bo6200293b6nyireglii@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The Covid-19 vaccines can be given at the same time as a seasonal flu shot, if people prefer to get both at once.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000x3b6n7o9ip1v0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “There’s no recommendations against it other than just personal preference,” Ren said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7000y3b6n5ot10d0x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “With a lot of the vaccines, a lot of people may say they feel a little bit of fatigue,” he said of some of the side effects. “So if you’re getting multiple shots all at the same time, that effect could kind of compound.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro700103b6ntkajnr5e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Most people 6 months and older &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;should get a flu vaccine&lt;/a&gt; every season, according to the CDC.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro700113b6nsotsl26b@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For flu, there is no change from prior years in terms of guidelines,” Barouch said. “And according to the CDC, the annual seasonal flu vaccine is recommended universally for everybody 6 months and older.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro700123b6nk6f5cmir@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Most people need only one dose of the flu vaccine each year. But some children who are getting the vaccine for the first time should get two doses, spaced four weeks apart.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro700143b6n9i03gf38@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It won’t be clear how effective this season’s flu vaccine is until after the season has ended. The &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu-vaccines-work/php/effectiveness-studies/2024-2025.html" target="_blank"&gt;CDC estimates&lt;/a&gt; that the vaccine was about 42% to 56% effective in adults during the 2024-25 respiratory virus season.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro700153b6nysfbcb54@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Flu has a seasonality. That’s why we update it every year,” Galiatsatos said. “I usually recommend trying to get the vaccine at least two weeks before Thanksgiving, just so you can build up the immunity, because flu really kicks in in November and December and sometimes lingers into January, February, March.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro700163b6nc07hohfy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            September and October are considered generally &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/vaccines/vaccinations.html" target="_blank"&gt;good times to get the flu vaccine&lt;/a&gt;, according to the CDC, and ideally eligible people should be vaccinated by the end of October.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro700173b6nswxe44mc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “So get the flu vaccine now, if you haven’t already,” Galiatsatos said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro700193b6nark1k7ic@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some public health experts describe this as “&lt;a href="https://emscimprovement.center/news/flu-boo/" target="_blank"&gt;flu before boo&lt;/a&gt;,” an effort to encourage people to get their flu shots by Halloween.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001a3b6n4wvpchb8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It is still okay to get it later than that (you will still get protection),” Dupont wrote in the email. “But it is better to get it before the winter holidays to avoid spreading illness among your loved ones.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgny55cy00033b6nrmwlzxb3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Most people may be able to access flu vaccines at their local pharmacy, doctors office or even through certain public health departments.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgo276k0000c3b6njhsvi9sg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But for the first time, many people in the United States who want to protect themselves against the flu can order a &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/08/15/health/first-us-home-flu-vaccine-launch-flumist-astrazeneca"&gt;nasal spray vaccine to give themselves at home&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgo26brn000a3b6n81saf8g1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            AstraZeneca’s FluMist, the only nasal spray flu vaccine in the US that has been approved by the US Food and Drug Administration, is now available for home delivery in 34 states under the brand name FluMist Home. It can be self-administered by adults under 50 and to children as young as 2 with the help of a parent or caregiver.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgo2byol000k3b6nacuqm10p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            FluMist has been on the market for more than two decades, receiving initial FDA approval in 2003. In September 2024, the FDA gave the green light for the nasal spray vaccine to be self-administered, but it wasn’t ready to reach the public in time for last respiratory virus season. However, the product is available for this season.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001b3b6nnf3qoyp1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For eligible patients, the flu shot should be covered by almost all insurance programs, but without insurance, “a flu shot at a retail pharmacy may be as low as $30 for a regular dose and up to $130 for a high dose (which is recommended for those over 65),” Dupont said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgo1ryg600003b6nov98dipd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The at-home nasal spray flu vaccine option is covered by most commercial insurance, with an $8.99 fee for shipping and handling. The online ordering platform includes a brief medical screening questionnaire to be reviewed by a licensed health-care provider before prescribing the vaccine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001d3b6ntweso055@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            RSV vaccines are recommended for adults 75 and older as well as those ages 50 to 74 who are at &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;increased risk of severe illness&lt;/a&gt;, according to the CDC. It’s estimated that one dose of RSV vaccine &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/vaccines/adults.html" target="_blank"&gt;provides protection against disease&lt;/a&gt; in older adults for at least two years.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001g3b6n578e71vr@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Separately, to protect infants from severe RSV, immunizations can be given to mothers during pregnancy or to babies after birth as an antibody shot.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001h3b6nizgg8atc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “If you’re someone who is pregnant, between 32 and 36 weeks, consider getting it – because when you get that RSV vaccine, you’re going to pass those antibodies to your newborn, and they’ll be protected,” Galiatsatos said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001e3b6nx02zzjhf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The RSV vaccine is available for eligible adults at any time, but the best time to get it is typically late summer and early fall, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/media/images/2025/08/RSV-vaccine-chart-3272025_lc_08.15.2025_edit.png" target="_blank"&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001i3b6nxlugjwcb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For mothers, the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/rsv/media/images/2025/08/RSV-vaccine-chart-3272025_lc_08.15.2025_edit.png" target="_blank"&gt;RSV vaccine is usually available&lt;/a&gt; from September through January, according to the CDC. For infants, the antibody shot is typically recommended from October through March.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001j3b6nze2l3ar7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “They should start getting it now,” Dupont said. “It is just a one time shot currently.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001k3b6n5m3zsx5a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For eligible people with insurance, the RSV vaccine may be covered.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001l3b6nvt6ko97s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Without insurance, “an RSV vaccine may cost $350,” Dupont said. “But there are patient assistance programs that can significantly lower the price if you are paying out of pocket.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001n3b6nwz25jooc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Outside of respiratory viruses, other seasonal vaccines may help reduce the risk of getting sick this fall and winter, Galiatsatos said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001o3b6nrznzx1xv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Pneumococcal vaccines help protect against bacterial pneumococcal infections – including pneumonia – in older adults, infants and certain younger adults with underlying health conditions.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001q3b6nnicozwq0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In addition to vaccination, people should stay home when they’re sick to avoid spreading diseases, and if people want to protect themselves further, then they can avoid crowded indoor locations during the wintertime,” Barouch said. “People also always have the option to wear a mask if they wish to do so, both to protect themselves and to protect others.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001r3b6nzsr749x8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Flu, Covid-19 and RSV can spread through respiratory droplets, Ren said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001s3b6n9dh66ye3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Good hand hygiene – so frequent handwashing and hand sanitizing – is really important because if somebody might have sneezed and then touched a door handle or touched that carton of milk that you were going to grab, as gross as it sounds, that’s how illnesses can spread,” Ren said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmgl96ro7001t3b6nc9jeno5i@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It’s also important to cover your mouth when you cough, “get plenty of sleep, eat colorful fruits and vegetables and/or consider a multivitamin to keep your immune system up,” Dupont said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:00:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPQk5mUUJxcjZaSFJpVHF0bGRxRTJMU0tlNXV2Tkp5NUpNOWNheDFqOS1DM1JRaG56ZmhfTjI5MDFlblowQldJM052dzhCcVNJaDRkdWZCT0N2MUh3SVdsZTFfNXFNcFpManA0c04yVkxQUFBVbnVCcHBaQ2x3VFZpX3pR</guid></item><item><title>没有任何数量的酒精是安全的，至少对于痴呆症风险而言-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/10/15/alcohol-dementia-risk/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DZQEVGDCZVBOZLOBK7BJPSMS4E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;For years, the common wisdom and science was that a little bit of alcohol wasn’t bad — and even beneficial — for your health: A toast to moderation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LFL6OUMXUJEKRIXYCQM2ISASDQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But &lt;a href="https://ebm.bmj.com/content/early/2025/09/16/bmjebm-2025-113913" target="_blank"&gt;new research&lt;/a&gt; published in BMJ Evidence-Based Medicine suggests that even light alcohol consumption can increase &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/09/30/dementia-prevention-questions-answers/" target="_blank"&gt;dementia risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:01:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5Ec0c1ckR3Q2xRb25zdk8tV1l0QXRxSl9EYVY2RXM4S1JFM0RjdXRmVmNTMnQ5MXZkV3NrTURVQW1PWFJSWXVXbWJNN2tkRUVsekUwdTRLN0xSTDlWTkl0cGZDX0sxdjNZVC1KNGxmRFlCQVFYZVdsQVA2QmFZUQ</guid></item><item><title>诊断困境：一名女性的恶心是由她胃中的巨大肿块引发的—医生用无糖汽水溶解了这种肿块- Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/diagnostic-dilemma-a-womans-nausea-was-triggered-by-a-huge-mass-in-her-stomach-which-doctors-dissolved-with-diet-soda</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;
&lt;p id="6f60af83-da61-4b1d-9ea2-4ad2fdf30566"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The patient: &lt;/strong&gt;A 63-year-old woman in Massachusetts&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The symptoms: &lt;/strong&gt;The patient went to the emergency department after experiencing nausea and vomiting for about a month, along with decreased appetite. She told doctors that she'd also experienced a burning pain in her upper abdomen and right side of her torso, which wrapped around to her back. She'd tried treating these symptoms with two common over-the-counter medications for acid reflux, but the treatments didn't help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="6f60af83-da61-4b1d-9ea2-4ad2fdf30566-2"&gt;In the year prior, the patient had started taking semaglutide, a type of drug known as a GLP-1 receptor agonist — the same class of drug as Ozempic. These injected drugs are used to treat &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/40894-type-2-diabetes.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/40894-type-2-diabetes.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and assist in chronic weight management; in this case, the woman had a history of type 2 diabetes and obesity. Since starting the medication, she'd lost about 40 pounds (18 kilograms), but notably, that weight loss had accelerated over the previous month, she noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="783cb3af-5bd8-45ec-b346-df6eebf25ac8"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happened next: &lt;/strong&gt;Doctors took a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/64093-ct-scan.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/64093-ct-scan.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;CT scan&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of the patient's abdomen and pelvis. This revealed that the bile ducts, which move bile from the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/44859-liver.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/44859-liver.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;liver&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to the gallbladder and small intestine, were slightly dilated. The woman also had "heavy stool burden" but no signs of obstructions in her bowels, and her stomach was slightly stretched out due to carrying "semisolid material."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To take a closer look, the medical team then used magnetic resonance cholangiopancreatography, a noninvasive scan that examines the bile ducts, gallbladder, pancreas and pancreatic ducts. The scan confirmed that the bile ducts were dilated and revealed a mass in the stomach that appeared to be trapped air. The doctors then examined the upper digestive tract, from the esophagus to the top of the small intestine, with an endoscope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The diagnosis: &lt;/strong&gt;The endoscopy revealed a large mass in the woman's stomach, known as a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.merckmanuals.com/professional/gastrointestinal-disorders/bezoars-and-foreign-bodies/bezoars#Etiology_v892633" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.merckmanuals.com/professional/gastrointestinal-disorders/bezoars-and-foreign-bodies/bezoars#Etiology_v892633" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;gastric bezoar&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. These masses are tightly packed blobs of partially digested or undigested materials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The treatment: &lt;/strong&gt;Semaglutide and other GLP-1 agonists typically cause delayed gastric emptying, which means they slow the rate at which the stomach empties its contents into the intestines. The woman was taken off that medication upon hospital admission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-MxBm3tCDYG8sNnQcHo7UH5" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-MxBm3tCDYG8sNnQcHo7UH5 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next step with a bezoar is to try and dissolve the mass while it's still in the stomach — and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3966177/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3966177/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;evidence suggests&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a good way to do this is to give the patient soda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Existing evidence, largely from case series and anecdotal experiences, supports the administration of 3 liters [0.8 gallons] of cola, either orally or through a nasogastric tube, within a 12-hour window," doctors noted in a &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMimc2502450" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMimc2502450" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;report of the case&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. "It is not well understood whether acidity, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/32492-why-does-soda-fizz.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/32492-why-does-soda-fizz.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;carbonation&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, or another mechanism accounts for dissolution of the bezoar."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Due to the patient's history of diabetes, she was given diet cola. She also didn't enjoy carbonated beverages, so the typical prescription of 3 liters of soda was cut down to 1.5 liters (0.4 gallons). On the second day after starting this treatment, the patient noted a "tugging" sensation in her abdomen followed by relief of her nausea and abdominal discomfort. An endoscopic exam revealed that the bezoar was no longer stuck in her stomach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman then transitioned to a typical diet in the hospital, and by the time she was discharged, she had no nausea, vomiting or abdominal pain. She did not restart semaglutide but was prescribed acid reflux medication to take daily. She reported that her appetite increased after hospital discharge and her weight rebounded a bit over the following months. Her abdominal symptoms had not returned within a few months of discharge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What makes the case unique: &lt;/strong&gt;Gastric bezoars are fairly rare, the report noted. They are found in less than 0.5% of endoscopies of the upper digestive tract. Common symptoms of the condition, such as pain, nausea, vomiting and abdominal discomfort, also appear in many more-common disorders, so they don't necessarily point to the presence of a bezoar in all cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common type of gastric bezoar is formed of plant fibers and called a "phytobezoar." Eating lots of certain foods, such as persimmons, pineapples, raisins or celery, can raise the risk of phytobezoars because the plants contain a high concentration of indigestible components, such as cellulose, lignins and certain tannins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, various medical conditions, procedures and drugs can also raise the risk of bezoars. These include anatomical changes related to bariatric or other gastric surgeries, autonomic nerve damage, and medications that cause delayed gastric emptying, such as GLP-1s. In the woman's case, semaglutide was likely to blame for her bezoar, and discontinuing the treatment helped resolve the problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="dcfdf2a6-e002-4624-9242-248abef99c13"&gt;The cola she consumed also helped. Although that course of treatment sounds strange on paper, it is the preferred first-line treatment over using a scope to physically break up the bezoar in the patient's stomach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Bezoars formed from food material may be initially managed with oral administration of cola in patients in a clinically stable condition," the report said. "This intervention is generally cost-effective and is associated with a lower risk of complications than invasive procedures."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For more intriguing medical cases, check out our &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/tag/diagnostic-dilemma" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/tag/diagnostic-dilemma"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;Diagnostic Dilemma archives&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="mb-6" id="380d4c1f-60b7-4d9e-98db-fa02984ba128"&gt;
&lt;div class="[&amp;amp;_a]:text-[#2f6e91] [&amp;amp;_a]:visited:text-[#09c] p-5 bg-[#F5F5F5] text-sm text-[#333]"&gt;

&lt;p class="infoDisclaimer tracking-[.02em] pt-2 font-normal"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and is not meant to offer medical advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5wFBVV95cUxOdG92dGM4VkpBYW1ucnNaM0NCYkdLZTBOTW5PWG14ZnRSelFnSVY5STBkYTlLaWZBSnRidWZIVjZkWVJDY0pweURsVk5hUEluTHY1cnhEQzFBQXpxRklyc01JYXZBOG9sejRNT2Qta29PQ0JmVEhYN1R1VUpHckowcHFiQTROY1FlbzhxX1hvU2IyVUZkSWpodlZ1TlRKakRiSjRlUlBmMnlueXN1OVcyS1l1T1VCUWZKcG9QTXMtd2tHYmNtV21keWo1WHBJLWhENUhIUWF6cFE1MDJLZkx1ZUZPMllzcms</guid></item><item><title>新的阿尔茨海默氏症治疗方法可在数小时内清除小鼠大脑中的斑块- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/new-alzheimers-treatment-clears-plaques-from-brains-of-mice-within-hours</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Scientists have repaired a natural gateway into the brains of mice, allowing the clumps and tangles associated with  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="176770" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease to be swept away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After just three drug injections, mice with certain genes that mimic Alzheimer's showed a reversal of several key pathological features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within hours of the first injection, the animal brains showed a nearly 45 percent reduction in clumps of amyloid-beta plaques, a hallmark of Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mice had previously shown signs of cognitive decline, but after all three doses, the animals performed on par with their healthy peers in spatial learning and memory tasks. The benefits lasted at least six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clearing-brain-waste-dramatically-improves-memory-in-aging-mice"&gt;Clearing Brain Waste Dramatically Improves Memory in Aging Mice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These preclinical results don't guarantee success in humans, but they're an encouraging start, which the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-025-02426-1"&gt;say&lt;/a&gt; "heralds a new era" in drug research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The therapeutic implications are profound," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-025-02426-1"&gt;claim&lt;/a&gt; the international team of researchers, co-led by scientists at the Institute for Bioengineering of Catalonia (IBEC) and the West China Hospital Sichuan University (WCHSU).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176794" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176794" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Imagen-horizontal-3-1-642x361.jpg" alt="BBB IBEC" class="size-medium wp-image-176794" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Imagen-horizontal-3-1-642x361.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Imagen-horizontal-3-1-738x415.jpg 738w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Imagen-horizontal-3-1-768x432.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Imagen-horizontal-3-1-1536x864.jpg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Imagen-horizontal-3-1-600x338.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Imagen-horizontal-3-1.jpg 1920w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176794" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Amyloid-beta plaques (red) were cleared from the brains of treated mice (left) but not untreated controls (right). Vessels of the blood-brain barrier are shown in green. (&lt;a href="https://ibecbarcelona.eu/consiguen-revertir-el-alzheimer-en-ratones-con-el-uso-de-nanoparticulas"&gt;IBEC&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their approach to treating Alzheimer's reframes the blood-brain barrier as &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41392-023-01481-w"&gt;more than a hurdle&lt;/a&gt; to be leapt over, but a gate in need of repair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blood-brain barrier separates the blood system of the brain from the rest of the body, keeping dangerous toxins and pathogens away from our seat of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/consciousness" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73104" data-postid="176770" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;consciousness&lt;/a&gt;. It also keeps out much of our medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years now, drug researchers &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-think-theyre-on-the-verge-of-breaching-the-blood-brain-barrier"&gt;have tried&lt;/a&gt; to use nanoscopic packages, called nanoparticles, to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-think-theyre-on-the-verge-of-breaching-the-blood-brain-barrier"&gt;smuggle&lt;/a&gt; Alzheimer's drugs across the blood-brain barrier. They've also &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ultrasound-with-immunotherapy-could-be-used-to-treat-alzheimer-s"&gt;used sound waves&lt;/a&gt; (ultrasound) to momentarily open the barrier, to allow drugs to pass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But these approaches treat the barrier "merely as a gate to cross rather than as a dysfunctional tissue to repair," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-025-02426-1"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; lead authors Junyang Chen and Pan Xiang from Sichuan University and their colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of trying to sneak drugs into the brain, researchers in China and Spain are trying to make it easier for amyloid-beta to get &lt;em&gt;out&lt;/em&gt; of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177534" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177534" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/AmyloidPlaquesBloodBrainBarrier-642x357.png" alt="Protein clumps are cleared from the vessel wall of the blood-brain barrier. " class="wp-image-177534 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/AmyloidPlaquesBloodBrainBarrier-642x357.png 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/AmyloidPlaquesBloodBrainBarrier-600x334.png 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/AmyloidPlaquesBloodBrainBarrier.png 748w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177534" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;After treatment with nanoparticles (white), amyloid-beta deposits (red) were cleared from the brain side of the blood-brain barrier (green) and carried away in the blood. (Chen et al., &lt;em&gt;STTT&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their novel approach supports an &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/blood-brain-barrier-guardian-shows-promise-against-alzheimers"&gt;emerging hypothesis&lt;/a&gt; that the blood-brain barrier is weakened or impaired in Alzheimer's cases, leading to waste products piling up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In Alzheimer's disease, the problem extends beyond access; the very transport machinery itself is pathologically biased," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-025-02426-1"&gt;argues&lt;/a&gt; the international team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using nanoparticles, not as passive carriers of medicine but as active agents of change, the researchers have altered traffic flow across the blood-brain barrier, restoring clearance of amyloid plaques in mice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Mid Article Promo Astro" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nanoparticles act as tiny engineers of cellular behavior, the researchers explain, orchestrating repair at the molecular scale. Their ultimate target is 'endothelial LRP1', which helps remove amyloid-beta plaques at the blood-brain barrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The long-term effect comes from restoring the brain's vasculature," &lt;a href="https://ibecbarcelona.eu/consiguen-revertir-el-alzheimer-en-ratones-con-el-uso-de-nanoparticulas"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt; bioengineer Giuseppe Battaglia from IBEC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We think it works like a cascade: when toxic species such as amyloid-beta  accumulate, disease progresses. But once the vasculature is able to function again, it starts clearing amyloid-beta and other harmful molecules, allowing the whole system to recover its balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What's remarkable is that our nanoparticles act as a drug and seem to activate a feedback mechanism that brings this clearance pathway back to normal levels."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, effective treatments for Alzheimer's disease are proving tricky to find. The &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/latest-alzheimers-drugs-can-add-years-of-independence-to-patient-lives"&gt;latest drugs&lt;/a&gt;, which target abnormal clumps and tangles in the brain, have &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/men-and-women-may-respond-differently-to-latest-alzheimers-drugs"&gt;produced mixed results&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While drugs like lecanemab and donanemab can &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-lifes-purpose-could-be-keeping-dementia-at-bay-study-finds"&gt;somewhat&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://sciencealert.com/this-fda-approved-drug-slows-down-alzheimers-we-finally-know-why"&gt;slow down&lt;/a&gt; Alzheimer's symptoms, they can't reverse the disease or stop its progression, no matter how scientists try.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some researchers &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-might-not-actually-be-a-brain-disease-says-expert"&gt;think&lt;/a&gt; we've gotten ourselves into a bit of a rut. They argue we've been too focused on clearing plaques and tangles inside the brain, when Alzheimer's may actually &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-may-start-at-the-brains-borders-scientists-discover"&gt;start at the brain's borders&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Julia Dudley, head of research at Alzheimer's Research UK, who was not involved in the current study, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencemediacentre.org/expert-reaction-to-study-of-amyloid-%CE%B2-clearance-in-a-mouse-model-of-alzheimers-disease/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; it's too early to say if this strategy will work in people. Mice don't have the same brain vasculature as humans, and the current study only examined a very specific subtype of dementia in a small number of rodents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, Dudley says the results add to growing evidence that "repairing the blood-brain barrier itself could offer a new way to treat Alzheimer's."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This type of research – while still early – is crucial for taking us closer to finding a cure," she &lt;a href="https://www.sciencemediacentre.org/expert-reaction-to-study-of-amyloid-%CE%B2-clearance-in-a-mouse-model-of-alzheimers-disease/"&gt;writes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-025-02426-1"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Signal Transduction and Targeted Therapy&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 02:51:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxQek1RMG41UlE3QzZtNHNhYkpwaXE5TUJVX09fWU5MM3lGUWh4Wk5ZYTZiQVBIRy05amlueE45VFc2Y2NLSEZyZ1lxN1laSkdYeGl2UzdYT2RPRldlNGhhSWxWM1ZWWnA1UzJGNHdLcm9sZmhnZlZuREZqRmt4X0dRb3hyWXJsMEJSdzh4Nm1CUTlLZHh3ajljNEFmRS1WcGo2czU4</guid></item><item><title>纽约卫生官员确认该州首例本地获得的基孔肯雅病毒病例-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/chikungunya-virus-case-new-york-long-island-24beff9662b5070e28a471a61602e051</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;MINEOLA, N.Y. (AP) — A person living in New York has tested positive for the &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/china-mosquitoes-chikungunya-explainer-050e53750c8c041fc72b7cf62c01b92f"&gt;chikungunya virus&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in what state health officials say is the first reported transmission of the mosquito-borne illness within the United States in six years&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The state Department of Health said Tuesday that the virus, which has been &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/china-chikungunya-virus-outbreak-control-measures-3ee97c21152b05ed0912af646594eafd"&gt;spreading in China&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and elsewhere, was identified in a person living in Nassau County on Long Island.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The county’s health department, in a separate statement, said the person began experiencing symptoms in August after having traveled outside of the region, but not out of the country. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not clear how exactly the person, whom authorities have not named, contracted the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Health officials say the person was likely bit by an infected mosquito, but they also say the virus has not been detected in local mosquito pools and there is no evidence of ongoing transmission.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;The type of mosquito known to carry chikungunya is present in parts of the New York City metropolitan area, including suburban Long Island. The disease cannot be spread directly from one person to another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since mosquitoes are less active during the fall’s cooler temperatures, the current risk of transmission is “very low,” said state Health Commissioner James McDonald.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Chikungunya is found mostly in tropical and subtropical regions, according to the state health department. Its symptoms include fever and joint pain, headache, muscle pain, joint swelling and rashes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The illness is rarely fatal and most patients recover within a week, though newborns, older adults and people with chronic health conditions such as high blood pressure and diabetes are at higher risk, the agency said. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;The U.S. and its territories have not seen a locally acquired case of the virus since 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York state has had three other cases of the virus this year, though all were linked to international travel to regions where the virus is prevalent, state health officials said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Local mosquitoes can transmit other dangerous viruses, such as West Nile, Eastern Equine Encephalitis and Jamestown Canyon viruses.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:47:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPNzVDd3R5ZERkTWl1SHRWa3dJVVJrUG5aOXR0SGUzaXgtU0hoTEktTllkeE9qUldnSTVJRTZqb1ktZ3ZqOW96NjFJRHVIcUMwMnQ5ZzR2OFFtcWlHc3RYa204LTBiZFdYemp6RUFtc3g2clowSWVTQ1NIczdUYjQ0ZWZuS3dRNFBrbXNYUUtRRkVPNTN3SWEteGptaEtJdTJXSGdwOVd3</guid></item><item><title>维生素D毒性：隐藏的危险、体征和症状，以及如何安全自然地逆转--印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/vitamin-d-toxicity-hidden-dangers-signs-and-symptoms-and-how-to-reverse-it-safely-and-naturally/photostory/124565147.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because symptoms are largely from elevated calcium, they can affect many body systems. Some early signs may be subtle; others may be more severe as toxicity worsens. Common signs of toxicity include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digestive and appetite symptoms:&lt;/strong&gt; Starting from nausea, vomiting, loss of appetite (anorexia), abdominal pain, the signs can range up to constipation, sometimes even pancreatitis in extreme cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Urinary, kidney, and hydration issues:&lt;/strong&gt; Frequent urination (polyuria) and excessive thirst (polydipsia) are the most prominent symptoms of this kind of toxicity. Additionally, dehydration (as your body loses water trying to flush excess calcium), kidney stones, kidney calcification, and impaired kidney function can occur in severe or prolonged cases &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Muscles, bones, and fatigue:&lt;/strong&gt; While muscle weakness and fatigue are very common, bone pain or discomfort, possibly from abnormal calcium handling, is also indicative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neurological and mental effects:&lt;/strong&gt; Apart from confusion, irritability, apathy, depression, and mental fog, stupor, coma, and altered mental status can also happen in severe cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because many symptoms mimic other conditions (kidney disease, gastrointestinal issues, etc.), vitamin D toxicity is often misrecognized – especially in early stages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:30:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwJBVV95cUxQaFdBTm1jci1hR3dwZGJrTmRTTkphRTFuR2lWSUV2RDVKWkZRdnhqSHE2Rjg1YWxIRkxtczZMUndpc1IyYXBscHcxSEd0TGtvaHdaWnlZMWp5cExPQlRhWEp1OTV1ajBLX0tUQmFvcGYtcXMtUE5QdjdKUnl0dk1KMUt2Vl92X0JXRlZaRmVvaTRfMmRKd2pCUW1NVWpSQ1NiT2c0RXdCVnBVbDFSdVZvWTNXRlYtNmdkYWdmMThhRllvbHVXRWk5SDh0VkhaU0N2cjhEWU1zcWhWZG5kVXNzeTF1eEgtakQzVHhEWmNhSVNNRUo5bjhMWWxOQzNnalJxb3diLWpMNEZ6SWVmQlBvaTNjeWo4NEswZTN0MzJHQdIBpwJBVV95cUxPTWRQTkJJNC1FTzNEaWVwR05vSmJsQXRpSkFtWXJrS1Bud1g2UjNZRk5tOEZqVlAtbU1sczlVTUV1RkUxcEltMlFsM0s2TVlRS0VXS182V0tRVm5zZ24wNEZiOGhvN1NOVUhBdFR3WlpKdjlzM2haX1VpVm1XOGpXRDJyYXQzSFhYSzE5Y1owc2tBaktLY3BMbWt0OHVFMHRQNkVmdjhhMDJSVWtTck1HcjNIVnRrWjRBNEl3U3dMLWJRVG5KU2JlOE9CWHMzTXJzWVZTemdoaHNBS0lwdUlOMWtOZGZvUUoxLVZ2UWJJcl9HMEJONDlIRHNvT0dFLXo4c1BNbS1WQXZMaEhNVDhwYVYxUHRGYWY5QUtpYzh5VnExNmVTN2Zr</guid></item><item><title>州警告生病的马诺阿鸭可能有禽流感病例-檀香山Star-Advertiser</title><link>https://www.staradvertiser.com/2025/10/14/breaking-news/state-warns-of-possible-bird-flu-case-in-sick-manoa-duck/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hsa-paywall"&gt;&lt;p&gt;State officials are urging caution after a presumptive case of avian influenza has been identified in an ailing duck at the University of Hawaii at Manoa.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A student found the duck earlier in the week, according to the Hawaii Department of Health. Laboratory testing confirmed the duck carried the H5 subtype of influenza A virus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Confirmation of avian influenza, or H5N1, is pending from the National Veterinary Services Laboratories in Iowa, in the next week or two.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At this time, officials said, the risk of infection to humans is considered low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Human infections remain rare and are primarily linked to direct animal exposure,” said health officials in the release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://health.hawaii.gov/docd/disease_listing/avian-influenza/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Avian influenza&lt;/a&gt; has been circulating worldwide, and is highly infectious among wild birds and poultry, with outbreaks on the U.S. continent affecting hundreds of dairy cattle herds in 18 states, including California.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;div id="breaking-news-signup-form" class="email-form rounded my-3 px-4 py-3"&gt;
                &lt;div class="row"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="col-12 col-md-6 mb-2 mb-md-0 text-center text-md-start"&gt;
                        &lt;h6 class="fs-4 mt-0 mb-1"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don't miss out on what's happening!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
                        &lt;p class="email-form-blurb m-0"&gt;Stay in touch with breaking news, as it happens, conveniently in your email inbox. It's FREE!&lt;/p&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    
                    
                &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The spread of highly pathogenic avian influenza, so far, has been limited in Hawaii, which has had no human cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hawaii’s first outbreak of avian influenza was &lt;a href="https://808ne.ws/3V1duhd" target="_self" rel="noopener"&gt;confirmed at Susie’s duck sanctuary &lt;/a&gt;in Wahiawa last November.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Hawaii Department of Agriculture &amp;amp; Biosecurity confirmed that at least 10 birds on the property, including ducks, geese, and a wild zebra dove, died from avian influenza.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More than 70 waterfowl, including some ducks adopted by a family at Pearl Harbor, either died or were euthanized in relation to that outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last November, officials also confirmed avian influenza in a &lt;a href="https://808ne.ws/3WCxRBP" target="_self" rel="noopener"&gt;wild duck&lt;/a&gt; tested at James Campbell National Wildlife Refuge in Kahuku.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That duck showed no signs of infection when tested, and was swabbed and released by the U.S. Fish and Wildlife Service during an ongoing project on genetics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since then, no new avian influenza detections had been reported in the Hawaiian islands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DOH, DAB, and the state Department of Land and Natural Resources are monitoring health reports, poultry farms and wild bird populations for any signs the virus has spread.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The student had reported the sick duck to the Hawaii Wildlife Center, a nonprofit that saves and rehabilitates wild birds, including seabirds disoriented by artificial lights during fallout season.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fallout season began in mid-September and lasts through mid-December.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;”As Hawaiʻi enters migratory bird season, this latest case is a reminder that wild birds may carry diseases to the islands and the public should remain vigilant,” said officials in the release.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Officials remind anyone who encounters sick or dead birds to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Avoid touching or handling wild birds, especially waterfowl or shorebirds. Upon finding a wild bird, follow &lt;a href="https://808ne.ws/4om9aFH" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;these instructions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Report multiple or unusual illnesses in poultry, livestock, or other wild birds to the DAB Animal Industry Division at 808-483-7100, Monday to Friday from 7:45 a.m. to 4:30 p.m., 808-837-8092 during non-business hours and holidays; or via email at &lt;a href="mailto:dabic@hawaii.gov" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;dabic@hawaii.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Honolulu Star-Advertiser</author><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 23:24:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxOWlFTaWQwX3lDUXpLMzhsdk8zbjdZZEFldm40TVdUekdIaGQyVGRKSFlreFdRUk5jczhMTVRFcnNnc3ZncGpjc1cwNTRyUXljTnpPNDVFSFluaXRXRUdCdDJXUGtEZ0J5TDJUZHE2aFRTS2NrenR1dFRiM2MzQUozdVBxbUhvcDNILXdGbEsxU2tpal9rYkR2MnljdTV4SFdUN2FIVlFWa05odjlKTDY0Qy1JMA</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，这种互换可以帮助您在不减少卡路里的情况下减肥- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/red-meat-beans-weight-loss-study-11829661</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Men who swapped beans for meat lost weight without cutting calories, a study found.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Replacing red meat with legumes also lowered LDL cholesterol in just six weeks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Easy swaps like bean tacos or mixed burgers can improve health without overhauling your diet.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re a fan of &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/gallery/7887628/healthy-taco-recipes-30-minutes/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;delicious taco nights&lt;/a&gt;, your routine is probably down pat—chop some veggies, grab the salsa, brown the ground beef, warm the tortillas and call everyone to the table. But as one recent study suggests, there’s a very easy swap you can make in that meal that could help you reach or maintain a healthy weight, according to a new study. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Just swap in a hearty scoop of seasoned beans for some of that meat. You’ll still enjoy the same tacos and the same full plate, but making that substitution may help you &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7835958/habits-you-should-break-if-you-re-trying-to-lose-weight/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;lose weight without needing to count your calories&lt;/a&gt;. In a six-week randomized trial, men who made that kind of trade—beans instead of part of their red and processed meat—lost more weight without cutting calories, and their LDL cholesterol improved too.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; That’s the takeaway for the rest of us: you don’t have to eat less to make progress. Tweaking what’s on the plate—more &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8061834/healthiest-beans-to-eat/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;fiber-rich beans&lt;/a&gt;, a little less meat—can quietly move the needle on weight and heart health while dinner still tastes like dinner. Let’s break down this study, which was recently published in the &lt;em&gt;European Journal of Nutrition&lt;/em&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-was-this-study-conducted"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Was This Study Conducted? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This was a six-week randomized controlled trial in Finland with 102 healthy men. Participants’ average age was 38. The were assigned to one of two diets:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Meat group: This group ate about 760 grams per week of red and processed meat. That’s roughly the average intake for Finnish men, and that meat supplied about 25% of their diet’s total protein.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Legume group: This group ate about 200 grams per week of red and processed meat, which is the amount aligned with a planetary health diet recommendation. They also ate legume-based foods that matched the protein from about 560 grams of red meat. So, in their diets, legumes accounted for 20% of their diet’s total protein, while red and processed meat made up 5%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Apart from these provided study foods, participants kept eating their normal diets. Researchers collected food records and measured blood and urine markers at the start and end of the study. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-did-the-study-find"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; What Did the Study Find? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; By the end of six weeks, the legume group lost more weight (around 2 pounds) than the meat group (around 0.5 pounds), though participants weren't told to restrict calories. In fact, the legume group ate around 240 more calories per day. &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/weight-loss-heart-health-study-11757537" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Body mass index&lt;/a&gt; (BMI) also decreased more in the legume group, but the difference may not be clinically significant. Total and LDL ("bad") cholesterol also fell more in the legume group than in the meat group, which makes sense since legumes offer more fiber and healthy fats. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Finally, researchers found that the legume group’s &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/foods-with-more-vitamin-b12-than-beef-11776277" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;vitamin B12 intake&lt;/a&gt; and blood levels dipped but remained adequate. Iron intake actually increased overall for the bean group—though this form is less bioavailable than animal-based iron, leading to equal iron levels in both groups—while iodine status stayed the same between groups in the short term. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Like all studies, this one has its limitations. The trial was relatively short at only six weeks. It also included only men. Participants self-reported food intake, which can introduce errors. Also, those in the legume group reported exercising more, which likely affected the results. Although participants in the legume group lost around 1.5 pounds more—consisting of small reductions in fat and muscle mass—compared to the meat group, there were no significant differences in body composition between groups, suggesting the observed weight change may reflect transient factors like hydration or bowel contents. While the design allows stronger conclusions than observational studies, longer trials in more diverse groups would help confirm the benefits researchers observed. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-does-this-apply-to-real-life"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; How Does This Apply to Real Life? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; You don’t need a full dietary overhaul to see benefits—just make space for beans. Try these easy swaps a few times a week:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For tacos and taco salads&lt;/strong&gt;, use spiced black beans or lentils for half (or all) of the ground beef.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When you’re grilling&lt;/strong&gt;, make a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/7886300/chickpea-beef-burgers-with-whipped-feta/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;half-and-half burger&lt;/a&gt; with some mashed beans mixed into lean beef (or go for &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/8046362/best-vegan-burgers/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;a hearty bean patty&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For a &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/sheet-pan-dinner-recipes-to-make-forever-8606756" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="3"&gt;weeknight sheet-pan dinner&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, roast chickpeas with veggies and toss with a lemon-olive oil vinaigrette; serve alongside a smaller portion of steak or pork.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upgrade your pasta&lt;/strong&gt; and stir white beans into marinara for extra protein and fiber. Top each bowl with a sprinkle of Parmesan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For simple meal prep&lt;/strong&gt;, build a grain-and-greens bowl with a big scoop of beans, crunchy veggies and a simple dressing. Recipes like our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/chickpea-grain-bowl-with-feta-tomatoes-11742803" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="4"&gt;Chickpea Grain Bowl with Feta &amp;amp; Tomatoes&lt;/a&gt; are perfect for this.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Make beans the easy choice: stash a few cans in the pantry and cook a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/8047812/how-to-cook-lentils/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;pot of lentils&lt;/a&gt; over the weekend so they’re ready for you in the fridge all week. Beans play well with all kinds of big flavors, so let them bring out your culinary creativity. Add lemon and olive oil, a little garlic, herbs and maybe some spicy peppers. Bean-based dishes can quickly become something you look forward to each week. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In a six-week randomized trial, men who swapped part of their red and processed meat for &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8060938/live-longer-fight-climate-change-eat-more-plants/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;bean-based foods&lt;/a&gt; lost more weight and improved their cholesterol—without being told to eat fewer calories. Building more beans into your week is a simple, budget-friendly move that can support &lt;a class="recommendation-inline-link-ai" href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8045323/new-study-best-worst-behavior-patterns-weight-loss/" link-destination-recommendation-ai="true" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;weight management and heart health&lt;/a&gt; while keeping your diet nutritionally balanced.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 22:09:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTFAtZ2gxVUNJU0JiVnNOZzdyTkNWTEpvTU1xajFoTlFVbzYtR2Fid2k0MjAyeWlEZ3VvVXRGRy02U2ZyQ0h1MTRtQUItbmh2b3RyUVdfX3RzbmJSQ1dmZTFaNTRkVzAwTXVxcmJneE5FVmhqN0ZvTTBv</guid></item><item><title>飞机、直升机在阿拉巴马州为浣熊投掷装有狂犬病疫苗的诱饵包- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/10/planes-helicopters-dropping-bait-packets-with-rabies-vaccine-for-raccoons-across-alabama.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3AW4JABFIRBMDLUR6M2UNNR7AQ"&gt;The U.S. Department of Agriculture is distributing bait packets containing an oral rabies vaccine across 14 central and north Alabama counites to try to reduce rabies in raccoons and the related public health risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VGRFH54XCZEANCTYERSQVIMP5M"&gt;The Alabama Department of Public Health announced that &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/national-wildlife-programs/rabies" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/national-wildlife-programs/rabies"&gt;the USDA Wildlife Services &lt;/a&gt;is using low-flying planes and helicopters to drop coated sachet baits with the RABORAL V-RG® vaccine over a zone of about 14,000 square kilometers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QSTM5IIBWVGDFJAKFELJZG3G2U"&gt;The area includes parts of Autauga, Blount, Calhoun, Cherokee, Chilton, Coosa, DeKalb, Etowah, Jackson, Jefferson, Marshall, St. Clair, Shelby, and Talladega counties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6PU63KJXCRFO3DFVEZPVJ3XFJQ"&gt;More than 30,000 of the oral rabies vaccine baits are being distributed from ground vehicles in the Birmingham metro area through Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="I37OIDMEVVG6HDSWY6FTQCPMSM"&gt;The bait packets used in the urban and suburban areas are square blocks made of fishmeal and fish oil that attract raccoons. When raccoons bite into the packets, their gums are exposed to the vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="XFD6KAPXJJBC7PYQ4WF43RQ6CI"&gt;The baits aerially distributed over most of the zone are plastic packets of vaccine coated with an oily, fish-scented substance to attract raccoons and other animals that carry rabies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QN7W5VHLHRAZHNIZLERYTT2KVE"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Read more:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.al.com/news/2025/09/horse-tests-positive-for-rabies-alabama-health-officials-advise-caution.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.al.com/news/2025/09/horse-tests-positive-for-rabies-alabama-health-officials-advise-caution.html"&gt;Horse tests positive for rabies: Alabama health officials advise caution&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RFPTOOX6FRBE5CCIXRFREXGTTA"&gt;The oral vaccine packets pose no risk of rabies to humans or animals if exposed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="C3OIUNBCOZEJZOWH4GGQFYSZDM"&gt;People who see one of the packets are advised to leave it for wildlife. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DTZ32VVWWJHQ3ICX2JFFSDJGPQ"&gt;If they do handle a packet, they are advised to wear gloves, place it in an area where a raccoon may find it, or dispose of it in the trash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="V2VV77FU5NHF3E2JNTH7E3TY5Q"&gt;Occasionally, skin reactions occur in humans. It is best to avoid direct contact with the skin, eyes or mucous membranes with the vaccine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OVDKAHJDWJAXVGNLHNDGBB4MYY"&gt;If exposure occurs accidentally, then it is recommended that the person wash hands with warm water and soap. Should more serious reactions occur, there is a telephone number on the vaccine packet to call the office of State Public Health Veterinarian Dr. Dee W. Jones for more information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WOYCV6NFLNDMNKMQZGMC5VNLVI"&gt; “I understand the concern from citizens and owners when an ORV packet is found in an unintended place or when there is an unintended exposure, but I am hopeful that people keep the big picture in mind, and that is actually reducing the risk of rabies exposures in Alabama by vaccinating raccoons,” Jones said in a news release.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="3PMUDX7OYNGVLGDZXCLRPJTFGU"&gt; “The vaccine packets have been proven to be very safe by historical data collected from incidental exposures. I believe the ORV program benefits public health, animal welfare and wildlife.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RV6OYF5NHBFFJA5UWJ2SDVBXC4"&gt;For more information, call the USDA at 1-866-487-3297. For more information about rabies exposures or animal or human exposures to the oral rabies vaccines, please call the Alabama Department of Public Health at 1-800-338-8374. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HQDDX2SYFNFDLOCMETB75B6RV4"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/national-wildlife-programs/rabies" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/national-wildlife-programs/rabies"&gt;More information is available here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 22:09:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwwFBVV95cUxQeWZSYTlpTnFwOS0wQ0dsWGs4T0IzQTNrNlk1dGEtM055c1NLZG1nNVNIc0RVTmUzMFNvcERfMGZGMUxCUnhBZ3RfcjNlb18yT29ScVJham5wT29MdU5pN1pYSWE1VzZ0SWE0WWdKd2MyX2dPUXZPalNNMFpWanpOS2ZYSWgwVm4waHhjUUdlMDVFMFNQcmtSUmw3LW4wUVNwSF9RS0Rrc1JoRW52c0xvZGhZYUJ1QUJrNDV3M3lDYm9PaDjSAdcBQVVfeXFMUGJmUmt4Y29jSW9tVjBhTWxLNGQ0bjYwZ0dPTjJaUkdQeXliRjNqWnozUHZUcTlaRGlMNTNIUmRCbVVUYVpNMktjd2dQLTlqOUpKcFdicFZSVkgtWmx4NjBCRmU1blhtVkwza2V6UEhDNWlEMDNxem1LMHdzd3FReVNhVkpFNDVNZW5ZaWhqdTVSQmU5NkZET3k5QXhBejEyVVdGUEpMSDR0bXJkd19sTG90MnFzeXlwZ3pCNWtFV2I1TmJ2V0xkenhzaHk1dUxlc3hCR1VrM3c</guid></item><item><title>科学家警告说，人类的思想不应该在午夜后醒来- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/the-human-mind-isnt-meant-to-be-awake-past-midnight-scientists-warn</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;In the middle of the night, the world can sometimes feel like a dark place. Under the cover of darkness, negative thoughts have a way of drifting through your mind, and as you lie awake, staring at the ceiling, you might start craving guilty pleasures, like a cigarette or a carb-heavy meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plenty of evidence suggests the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41386-020-00879-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;human mind functions differently&lt;/a&gt; if awake at nighttime. Past midnight, negative emotions tend to draw our attention more than positive ones, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.smrv.2015.10.003" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;dangerous ideas grow&lt;/a&gt; in appeal, and inhibitions fall away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some researchers think the human &lt;a href="https://www.nigms.nih.gov/education/fact-sheets/Pages/circadian-rhythms.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;circadian rhythm&lt;/a&gt; is heavily involved in these critical changes in function, as they outline in a &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fnetp.2021.830338/full" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;2022 paper&lt;/a&gt; summarizing the evidence of how brain systems function differently after dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/there-are-5-profiles-of-sleep-heres-what-yours-says-about-your-health"&gt;There Are 5 Profiles of Sleep – Here's What Yours Says About Your Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their hypothesis, called 'Mind After Midnight', suggests the human body and the human mind follow a natural 24-hour cycle of activity that influences our emotions and behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, at certain hours, our species is inclined to feel and act in certain ways. In the daytime, for instance, molecular levels and brain activity are tuned to wakefulness. But at night, our usual behavior is put to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_141228" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-141228" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/AlarmClockWithPersonSleepingInBackgroundBlurry_R_U_642.jpg" alt="An alarm clock in the foreground with a blurred person in bed " class="size-full wp-image-141228" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/AlarmClockWithPersonSleepingInBackgroundBlurry_R_U_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/AlarmClockWithPersonSleepingInBackgroundBlurry_R_U_642-600x337.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-141228" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Our species is inclined to sleep at night. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADEbULOUn4/"&gt;Motortion/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;From an evolutionary standpoint, this, of course, makes sense. Humans are much more effective at hunting and gathering in the daylight, and while nighttime is great for rest, humans were once at greater risk of becoming the hunted at this time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the researchers, to cope with this increased risk, our attention to negative stimuli is unusually heightened at night. Where it might once have helped us jump at invisible threats, this hyper-focus on the negative can then feed into an altered reward/motivation system, making a person particularly prone to risky behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add sleep loss to the equation, and this state of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/consciousness" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73104" data-postid="177488" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;consciousness&lt;/a&gt; only becomes more problematic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There are millions of people who are awake in the middle of the night, and there's fairly good evidence that their brain is not functioning as well as it does during the day," &lt;a href="https://mgriblog.org/2022/07/28/researchers-call-for-new-studies-to-learn-how-our-brains-change-when-were-awake-after-midnight/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; neurologist Elizabeth Klerman from Harvard University in 2022 when the study was published.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"My plea is for more research to look at that, because their health and safety, as well as that of others, is affected."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors of the hypothesis use two examples to illustrate their point. The first example is of a heroin user who successfully manages their cravings in the day but succumbs to their desires at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second is of a college student struggling with insomnia, who begins to feel a sense of hopelessness, loneliness, and despair as the sleepless nights stack up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_141230" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-141230" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/PerspnStudyingLateAtNightLookingExhausted_R_U_642.jpg" alt="A person sitting at a desk while it's dark outside, looking tired and trying to study " class="size-full wp-image-141230" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/PerspnStudyingLateAtNightLookingExhausted_R_U_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/PerspnStudyingLateAtNightLookingExhausted_R_U_642-600x337.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-141230" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;At night, our attention to negative stimuli is unusually heightened. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAB-v4tyCrs/"&gt;Diego Cervo/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both scenarios can ultimately prove fatal. Suicide and self-harm are very common at night. In fact, &lt;a href="https://www.psychiatrist.com/jcp/neurologic/neurology/nocturnal-wakefulness-and-suicide/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;some research&lt;/a&gt; reports a threefold higher risk of suicide between midnight and 6:00 am compared to any other time of day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7953996/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; in 2020 concluded that nocturnal wakefulness is a suicide risk factor, "possibly through misalignment of circadian rhythms."&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp?utm_source=promo_astro"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Astronaut in space, with text overlay" class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-177074" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;"Suicide, previously inconceivable, emerges as an escape from loneliness and pain, and before the costs of suicide are considered the student has acquired the means and is prepared to act at a time when no one is awake to stop them," the authors of the 'Mind After Midnight' hypothesis &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fnetp.2021.830338/full" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;explain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Illicit or dangerous substances are also taken more by people at night. In 2020, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0955395920301134" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;research&lt;/a&gt; at a supervised drug consumption center in Brazil revealed a 4.7-fold greater risk of opioid overdose at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of these behaviors could be explained by sleep debt or the cover that darkness offers, but there are probably nighttime neurological changes at play, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers like Klerman and her colleagues think we need to investigate these factors further to make sure we are protecting those most at risk from nighttime wakefulness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To date, the authors said no studies have examined how sleep deprivation and circadian timing impact a person's reward processing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As such, we don't really know how shift workers, such as pilots or doctors, are coping with their unusual sleep routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For six hours or so a day, we know surprisingly little about how the human brain works. Whether asleep or awake, the mind after midnight is a mystery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was published in &lt;a href="https://www.frontiersin.org/articles/10.3389/fnetp.2021.830338/full" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Frontiers in Network Psychology&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If this story has raised concerns or you need to talk to someone, &lt;a href="http://www.suicidestop.com/call_a_hotline.html"&gt;please consult this list to find a 24/7 crisis hotline in your country, and reach out for help.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in August 2022.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 22:06:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQdk5QZU53bXhRNFpyeS1Bb0R0RktxQzh1MTVxMkxGclc4VkM3NHZ0blJMSkZaUnB2a3hJcDVVcUk2R0JPRVZ1dkhEdzNJY0NjeF9WNnd4bGZCUnp5SWxGX2haMW11OGhCWDV1MHk3WDdscjRwX0U3X1pEdlRoSDc3ZjkxTlQtR29sdlBqTkl3UUhKVXpKdGdlYXhSY2I</guid></item><item><title>牙医希望您在预约时停止做的8件事-非常简单</title><link>https://www.realsimple.com/things-not-to-do-at-the-dentist-11824527</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-article-intro_1-0" class="comp mntl-article-intro mntl-block article-content__description"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’ve ever fibbed about &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/things-no-one-tells-you-about-flossing-11717317" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;how much you floss&lt;/a&gt; or found yourself trying to talk mid-cleaning, you’re not alone. Many of us head to the dentist with good intentions, but some of the things we do (often without realizing it) actually end up slowing down or disrupting the care we’re there to get. We spoke with several dentists to find out which habits they’d love their patients to stop, and what to do instead, so your next checkup is easier and more comfortable for everyone.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--meetourexpert mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-meetourexpert callout--bordered" data-text="Meet the Expert" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.aspendental.com/providers/whitney-white/1821606674/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1" rel="nofollow"&gt;Whitney White&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; DDS, DMD, dentist and practice owner at Aspen Dental&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.smilebar.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2" rel="nofollow"&gt;Nayson Niaraki&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; DMD, MS, orthodontist and the cofounder of Smilebar &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://vipsmiles.com/meet-dr-catrise-austin/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="3" rel="nofollow"&gt;Catrise Austin&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/strong&gt; DDS, celebrity cosmetic dentist and the host of the Let’s Talk Smiles podcast &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://veneerslongisland.com/veneers-cosmetic-dentist-long-island/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="4" rel="nofollow"&gt;Jenna Chimon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;/strong&gt;DDS, lead cosmetic dentist at Long Island Veneers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc__content_1-0" class="comp list-sc__content realsimple-sc-page mntl-sc-page mntl-block" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 3, 6, 9, 12, 15, 18]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="list-sc-item_1-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-lying-about-brushing-or-flossing"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Lying About Brushing or Flossing &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Perhaps the most common slip-up at the dentist’s office is patients stretching the truth about their oral hygiene habits. “I notice that patients often exaggerate about how frequently they brush and floss,” says Whitney White, DDS/DMD, a dentist and practice owner at Aspen Dental. “We always ask about oral hygiene during routine visits, and I think some patients feel like they have to say they floss daily and brush twice a day—whether it’s true or not. But their gums usually tell the real story!” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; White says many patients feel embarrassed to admit they’re not flossing or brushing as much as they should, but she emphasized that honesty with your dentist is always best. “We make it a priority to create a judgment-free space where patients feel comfortable being honest about their habits. The goal is always to &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/tips-to-brush-your-teeth-better-11778280" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;help them improve their oral health&lt;/a&gt;—not to make them feel bad about it.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@6813b928" data-item-index="1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_2-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-saying-you-wear-a-device-more-often-than-you-do"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Saying You Wear a Device More Often Than You Do &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; As far as any orthodontic treatment, honesty (again) is just as important as consistency. “I frequently encounter patients who don't share that they haven’t been diligent in wearing their aligners or following directions,” says Nayson Niaraki, DMD, MS, an orthodontist and the cofounder of Smilebar. “It makes it much harder to help them achieve their goal when they are not giving us the whole story. We are in this together! Helping us understand what is happening when you leave the office ultimately will help you, the patient, to achieve the smile you’ve always wanted.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@7b858c27" data-item-index="2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_3-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-showing-up-late"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Showing Up Late &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One of the simplest ways to practice good dental etiquette is actually the most obvious: Respect everyone’s schedule. “Dental etiquette is really a win-win: It protects your health, saves you money in the long run, and allows your dentist to deliver their very best work,” says Catrise Austin, DDS, celebrity cosmetic dentist and the host of the Let’s Talk Smiles podcast. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Make sure you arrive on time, and do not head to the bathroom right as the office is ready for you. “Dental schedules run on precision,” says Austin. “Running late without notice or delaying once called in disrupts care for everyone. A quick call ahead makes all the difference.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@38f5de63" data-item-index="3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_4-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-skipping-the-appointment-altogether"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Skipping the Appointment Altogether &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Skipping a visit without notice is one habit dentists say impacts both patients and providers. “By far the number one thing is patients not showing up for their appointments without letting us know,” says Jenna Chimon, DDS, lead cosmetic dentist at Long Island Veneers. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “It might seem like no big deal to skip an appointment, but that time slot that was reserved for the no-show could have gone to someone else instead of leaving us with an empty chair.” She notes that while they understand that unexpected things come up, a simple call or text allows the office to adjust the schedule and offer the spot to another patient.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@6f4699ee" data-item-index="4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_5-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-walk-ins-and-last-minute-drop-by-visits"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Walk-Ins and Last-Minute Drop-By Visits &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Another common misstep is showing up without an appointment and hoping to be squeezed in. “Dental care isn’t like grabbing a latte—our schedules are carefully structured around time-intensive procedures,” says Austin. “Every time a patient pops in unannounced, it can push back the whole day and compromise care.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Her advice: Always schedule ahead, and if you have a dental emergency, call first to see how they can fit you in safely. In true emergencies, most offices will make every effort to prioritize your care without disrupting the treatment of other patients.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@3b94744f" data-item-index="5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_6-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-trying-to-talk"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Trying to Talk &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Another habit that frustrates professionals is when patients talk on the phone during an appointment. “Imagine working with tiny instruments in someone’s mouth while they’re chatting on speakerphone—it’s stressful and unsafe,” says Austin. “Appointments are short; it’s best to silence your phone and use that time for your health.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Chimon points out that a smaller, though still noticeable, issue is when patients attempt to talk to her while she’s working in their mouth. “Instead, I always tell patients to give me a thumbs up if they need a break or feel uncomfortable.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@60c6033a" data-item-index="6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_7-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-being-negative"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Being Negative &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; One dentist shared that there’s one phrase they hear far too often at the start of an appointment: “I hate the dentist.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “We understand dental fear, but leading with negativity sets the wrong tone,” says Austin. “Instead, share what [about the process] makes you anxious so we can help make your visit more comfortable.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Also, it’s one thing to have concerns about the cost of treatment, but turning that concern into a complaint, such as “this is way too expensive,” can make the discussion less productive. “High-quality dental care reflects advanced training, materials, and safety,” says Austin. “Instead of complaining about fees, ask about financing options or preventive care to lower future costs. Investing in your oral health is like investing in your smile’s retirement plan.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@74be1a58" data-item-index="7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="list-sc-item_8-0" class="comp list-sc-item mntl-block mntl-sc-list-item"&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-taking-your-shoes-off"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block realsimple-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-list-item-title"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text text-title-300"&gt; Taking Your Shoes Off &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Believe it or not, some patients treat the dental chair like a living room recliner and kick off their shoes. “It happens more than you’d think!” says Austin. “It’s unsanitary and makes the environment less professional for everyone. &lt;a href="https://www.realsimple.com/home-organizing/cleaning/shoes-inside-house" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Keep shoes on&lt;/a&gt; and remember: A dental chair is not a recliner—it’s a medical environment.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block-adslot_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block" item="freemarker.template.DefaultMapAdapter@7cb8ebe4" data-item-index="8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Real Simple</author><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 21:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE5zb3ZtdnlRNkxsSGJuZ2RPUXBvam1oeThjYU5rNnpCUW93U2hnQ3lUYUJ3LW9GN2F4Wm1JRTJTNTRobk5Edno0NWxmWEFjM0g4SFNMcWN5RmNRS1huUi1yM2N2UTNic0I3ZEtQcWhBUGJjU3ptanc</guid></item></channel></rss>