<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>“即将离职”的9岁儿童将“一夜之间”变成了父母不认识的愤怒的人。然后得到令人震惊的诊断（独家） - AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/outgoing-9-old-changes-overnight-103000223.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos' daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2023, Crystal Loos noticed that her daughter was acting differently — the once bubbly child became reserved and angry, pulling back from friends, school and the world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It was utter terror, like she wasn't herself," the mother tells PEOPLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;After searching for answers, Loos' daughter finally got a diagnosis that changed everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the spring of 2023, Crystal Loos began noticing that her daughter wasn’t acting like her normal self. Her once bubbly elementary schooler seemed distracted and pulled away from school, her friends and the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Illinois mother of three tells PEOPLE that her daughter, Lacy Mae, stopped eating foods that she used to enjoy, and, at the time, Loos thought it was depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Before this, she was the happiest, funniest, most outgoing child ever. She never had any issues," Loos, 30, shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, in July 2024, there was a "complete overnight change," and the then-9-year-old was no longer “herself."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Lacy Mae was diagnosed with anxiety and depression, Loos knew deep down it was something else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They tried to put her on SSRIs, they tried to get her into a psychiatrist, psychologist, everything," she says. "But I just felt that there was something deeper going on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos' daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The night in July came, and it was like she had a psychotic break that night, and she was banging on my door. She was begging to go to the hospital," Loos continues. "She knew something was wrong, but she didn't know what, because she couldn't even explain to me what was going on. It was just like she didn't have control over her brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos describes a period of time where her young daughter wouldn't sleep, felt paranoid and constantly begged to be taken to the hospital to figure out what was wrong with her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It was utter terror, like she wasn't herself. She had dilated pupils. You looked at her, and she just wasn't the same kid, like, it was like something took over her," Loos says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although they "had gone to multiple hospitals," nearly everyone agreed that it was just depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At that point, Loos’ daughter begged to be admitted to a psych ward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She's 10 years old, so that's crazy, obviously, but she just wanted her health to get fixed," Loos says. "She begged, begged, begged to be admitted. She was, at this point, suicidal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We had to sometimes hold her down because she was trying to hurt herself or us. Sometimes we would have to lock her and us in a room together so that she wouldn't. She was more of a danger to herself than us," she shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos, who was recently postpartum when Lacy Mae's health took a turn, says her parents then stepped in to help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos' daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eventually, she did have to move in with my parents because I had a newborn baby, and then I also have a 5-year-old, and my 5-year-old was just terrified of her," she says. "He was just absolutely terrified because she was screaming. Rage is what I could describe her. She had so much rage in her.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos’ daughter refused to eat, refused to go to school, and ended up missing most of fourth grade. While many people believed the new baby could have caused Lacy Mae's personality change, Loos noted that it was much deeper than that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I'm like, ‘You guys don't get it. She was running away from home. She was trying to jump out of moving cars, like just complete psychosis.’ It was nothing like I've ever seen before. Especially as a child and in my childhood, I never had any issues before this," she shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, Lacy Mae was admitted to a behavioral health unit. During that time, Loos turned to various Facebook mom groups for support, asking if anyone else had ever experienced something similar. A few people mentioned that it could be PANS/PANDAS, so Loos got to work researching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I went to the psychiatrist at the children's hospital, and I literally begged. I was bawling at him. I said, 'She has something wrong with her. I think this is what it is: PANS /PANDAS. Can we do any further workup?' They refused to do that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/pans.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stanford University School of Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Stanford University School of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, Pediatric Acute-onset Neuropsychiatric Syndrome (PANS) is a clinical diagnosis for children who "have a dramatic – sometimes overnight – onset of neuropsychiatric symptoms" characterized by the sudden onset of obsessive-compulsive symptoms (OCD) or eating restrictions. They may also have symptoms of depression, behavioral regression, irritability, anxiety, sleep issues, and difficulty with schoolwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Pediatric Autoimmune Neuropsychiatric Disorders Associated with Streptococcal Infections (PANDAS) is a subset of PANS, and has five distinct criteria for diagnosis, including "abrupt 'overnight' OCD or dramatic, disabling tics; a relapsing-remitting, episodic symptom course; young age at onset (average of 6–7 years); presence of neurologic abnormalities;" and a recent streptococcal infection, such as strep throat, peri-anal strep or scarlet fever, per the &lt;a href="https://www.pandasppn.org/what-are-pans-pandas/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PANDAS Physicains Network.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PANDAS Physicains Network. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There isn’t an official test to diagnose PANS/PANDAS, making it hard for medical professionals to determine it as the root cause of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, Loos took her daughter out of the psych ward and searched for a doctor who specialized in PANS/PANDAS. They eventually contacted Indiana-based specialist Dr. Antoine, and in September 2024, after in-depth blood work, Lacy Mae was officially diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was put on antibiotics and received IVIG (Intravenous Immunoglobulin) to help her immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos and her daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She had different infections in her body that were mistakenly attacking her brain. She had several different infections," Loos shares. "She had a tick-borne illness. She had mycoplasma, plasma pneumonia, and these are all things that Dr. Antoine checked for. That's how we figured out what was going on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He put her on antibiotics to kill these infections, and then he put her on antibiotics to regulate her immune system, and then the IVIG, that's also to regulate the immune system, and then different supplements just to get her immune system back to normal so that it attacks the infection rather than attacking her brain,” Loos adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slowly, treatment began to work, and by December of 2024, Loos says they started to “see her again.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Loos admits the tween "still had a lot of episodes after that,” the severity of those episodes decreased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I was having just so much anxiety through all this because I was like, I don't know what to do," she shares. "I can't even describe how bad it was. It was literally like a living hell.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lacy Mae was also put on an anti-psychotic to help calm her down, and now, just over one year after her diagnosis, Loos says the 10-year-old is "99%" herself again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She does have some setbacks and a little bit of anxiety here and there, but for the most part, ever since we found Dr. Antoine and got on the right medication, she has been thriving, and life is pretty much back to normal for the most part," Loos says. "She goes to school. She plays sports. She plays with her friends, which she hasn't done for a while. Now she's completely back to living life and enjoying life again.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos recently shared a &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@crysrenae/video/7580132165707451662" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:TikTok video;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;TikTok video&lt;/a&gt; showing the difference in her daughter to raise awareness of PANS/PANDAS. The video went viral, amassing over 45 million views.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She says that parents have since reached out to share their own stories about how their children changed seemingly without cause. She’s been able to connect them with resources and talk them through what they’re feeling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I want parents to get answers. I want them to know that this is a thing and something to look into if your child has similar symptoms. I wish I would have found it sooner, before our life got really hard with it," she tells PEOPLE. "It's really amazing, because I've gotten so many messages and people, saying the kindest things and that they've been through it, and they know how it feels, and they're so grateful that I'm spreading awareness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we were going through this, I was really struggling because I didn't feel like I could find other parents that were dealing with this," she continues. "It’s very, very lonely, and you want to find any information you can, and there's just not a lot out there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos wants to educate people on PANS/PANDAS since it's a diagnosis that "is not widely known."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although I think it's honestly not a rare diagnosis. It’s more common than we think," she adds. "I think it's just often misdiagnosed as other things. I just want people to be aware of what everyone's going through when they have PANS/PANDAs.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you or someone you know is struggling with mental health challenges, emotional distress, substance use problems, or just needs to talk, call or text 988, or chat at &lt;a href="http://988lifeline.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:988lifeline.org;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;988lifeline.org&lt;/a&gt; 24/7.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/girl-diagnosed-with-pandas-after-extreme-behavior-changes-exclusive-11871633" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 08:12:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE5kdmJ3bXRvX0pENjJFNlRFMlFtdjNSTThqejBqQ1U3Qm1xdFV6NVd4cEVORXlEc0dMRVMxMW4tdnhvYk51WDhadEljMWdnejkwMS0wSTFHRGExM2hPRXE5Sk9feTZHT0NDTjRaYkVxdEFGWkw3ckE</guid></item><item><title>减肥刺拳：停止服用时会发生什么？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cn98pdpyjz5o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Weight-loss jabs: What happens when you stop?&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/688b/live/b6ff6480-dcfe-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/688b/live/b6ff6480-dcfe-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/688b/live/b6ff6480-dcfe-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/688b/live/b6ff6480-dcfe-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/688b/live/b6ff6480-dcfe-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/688b/live/b6ff6480-dcfe-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/688b/live/b6ff6480-dcfe-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/688b/live/b6ff6480-dcfe-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC Two women are smiling at the camera, the one on the left, Ellen, has long blonde hair. The one on the right, Tanya, has long red hair" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Ellen and Tanya have both lost weight using GLP-1s but have had very different experiences when it comes to stopping the medication&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="subByline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 ciiGlA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 kdBCdE"&gt;Ruth Clegg,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 eDNgSC"&gt;Health and wellbeing reporter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-9 keGieE"&gt;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-1" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 ciiGlA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 kdBCdE"&gt;Holly Jennings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's like a switch that goes on and you're instantly starving."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Tanya Hall has tried to stop taking weight loss medication multiple times. But every time she stops the injections, the food noise comes back. Loudly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Weight loss jabs, or GLP-1s, have done for many what diets could never do. That constant background hum, telling them to eat even when they are full, has been turned off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The drugs have given those who never thought they could lose weight a new body shape, a new outlook and in many cases, a completely different life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But you can't continue taking them forever, can you? Or can you? Well, that's one of the issues, no-one quite knows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;They are new drugs - which mimic GLP-1, a natural hormone that regulates hunger - and the potential side effects from using them in the long term are only just beginning to emerge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;And with an estimated 1.5 million people in the UK paying for the injections privately, staying on them for a long time is not a cheap endeavour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;So what happens when you try to stop? Two women, with two very different stories but the same goal - to lose weight and keep it off - tell us what it's been like for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c4dc/live/57ed5810-dc42-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c4dc/live/57ed5810-dc42-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c4dc/live/57ed5810-dc42-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c4dc/live/57ed5810-dc42-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c4dc/live/57ed5810-dc42-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c4dc/live/57ed5810-dc42-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c4dc/live/57ed5810-dc42-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c4dc/live/57ed5810-dc42-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Tanya Hall Three pictures of Tanya at different stages in her weight loss. In the first pic on the left she is wearing a grey top, in the middle pic she is at the gym, and in the third pic she has lost weight and is wearing a white corset top and smiling at the camera" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Tanya Hall&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Tanya says her hair "came out in clumps" when she first started taking the medication &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It was like something opened up in my mind and said: 'Eat everything, go on, you deserve it because you haven't eaten anything for so long'."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Tanya, a sales manager for a large fitness company, first started taking Wegovy to prove a point. She was overweight, felt like an "imposter" and thought her opinion was not valued by her industry because of her size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Would she be taken more seriously if she were slimmer?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ultimately, she says her suspicions were proved right. After she started using the jabs, people would come up to her and congratulate her on her weight loss. She felt she was treated with more respect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;However, during the first few months of the treatment, Tanya struggled to sleep, felt sick all the time, had headaches and even started to lose her hair, which might not be directly due to the drug but is a potential side effect of rapid weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"My hair was falling out in clumps," she recalls. But in terms of weight, she was getting the results she'd hoped for. "I'd lost about three and a half stone."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now, more than 18 months down the line, what started as a bit of an experiment has turned into a complete life change. She's lost six stone (38kg) and she's tried to come off Wegovy several times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But each time, within just a few days, she says she eats so much food she's left "completely horrified".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Should she stay on the medication, and live with all the side effects that come with it, or jump into the unknown?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Wegovy's manufacturer, Novo Nordisk, said that treatment decisions should be made together with a healthcare provider and that "side effects should be taken into account as part of this".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Stopping weight loss drugs can feel like "jumping off a cliff", observes lifestyle GP Dr Hussain Al-Zubaidi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I often see patients who will come off it when they're on the highest dose because they've reached their target and then they stop."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;According to Dr Al-Zubaidi, that can be like being hit by an "avalanche or a tsunami". The food noise comes back as quickly as the next day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He says the evidence so far suggests that, between one and three years after stopping the medication, people will see a "significant proportion of weight" go back on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Somewhere in the region of 60 to 80% of the weight that you lost will return."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ellen Ogley is determined not to let that happen. She decided to start taking weight-loss medication because she had reached a "key turning point" in her life. She was so overweight she had to sign a waiver to say she might not make it through a vital operation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Starting on Mounjaro was her "final shot to get it right", she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I was an emotional binge eater," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"If I was happy, I would binge. If I was sad, I was binging. It didn't really matter, I had no filter whatsoever."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But when she started using the jabs, "all that switched off".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Ellen says she changed her whole relationship with food while she was on weight-loss drugs&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Life without food noise gave Ellen the space to redesign her relationship with eating. She started to read up on nutrition and create a healthy diet that helped fuel her body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She was on the medication for 16 weeks before she began to taper, cutting down over a period of six weeks. She lost 3st 7lb (22kg).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As she lost more weight, she found she could exercise more and when she was feeling "low", instead of "going to to the cupboards and filling my face", she would go for a run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But when Ellen stopped taking Mounjaro, she began to see her weight creep up, which she says "messed my head up a little bit".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This is why the right support is crucial, Dr Al-Zubaidi says. &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nice.org.uk/news/articles/people-need-support-to-keep-weight-off-after-treatment-ends" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;The UK's medicine watchdog, Nice, has recommended that patients&lt;/a&gt; receive at least a year of ongoing advice and tailored action plans after they've stopped treatment, helping them to make practical changes to their lives so they can keep the weight off and most importantly, stay healthy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But for those who pay for the drugs privately, like Tanya and Ellen, this kind of support is not always guaranteed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;For the past few months, Tanya's weight has stayed the same, and she feels the medication is having little impact. But she's not going to come off it, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She's finally at a weight she feels comfortable with and each time she's tried to stop, the fear of putting the weight back on quickly becomes too great and she finds a reason to go back on the medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"For the first 38 years of my life, I was overweight - now I'm six stone (38kg) lighter," says Tanya.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Therefore, there's part of me that feels like there's an addiction to keep it going because it makes me feel the way that I feel, it makes me feel in control."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She stops for a second. Maybe it's the other way round, she muses, maybe it's the drug that controls her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5afb/live/90c49540-dc42-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5afb/live/90c49540-dc42-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5afb/live/90c49540-dc42-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5afb/live/90c49540-dc42-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5afb/live/90c49540-dc42-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5afb/live/90c49540-dc42-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5afb/live/90c49540-dc42-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5afb/live/90c49540-dc42-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Ellen Three pics side by side of Ellen at different stages of her weight loss. In the far left pic she is bigger, with a green dress on, in the middle pic she is at the gym and in the final pic she is slim with a pair of blue jeans and a black top on" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Ellen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Ellen has continuned to lose weight since she stopped taking weight-loss drugs&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's all about having an exit strategy," Dr Al-Zubaidi explains. "The question is: what are these people's experiences once they come off the injection?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He is worried that without additional support for people making the transition, society's unhealthy relationship with food means little will change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The environment that people live in needs to be one that promotes health, not weight gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Obesity is not a GLP-1 deficiency," he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In some respects, many people enter a game of weight-loss roulette when it comes to stopping their weight-loss medication. Factors like lifestyle, support, mindset and timing all play into how futures post-GLP-1s unfold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Tanya is staying on the medication and is fully aware of the pros and cons of this decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ellen feels that chapter has now closed. She's lost more than eight stone (51kg) now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I want people to know that life after Mounjaro can be sustainable as well," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Eli Lilly, the company which makes Mounjaro, says "patient safety is Lilly's top priority", and that it "actively engages" in monitoring, evaluating and reporting information to regulators and prescribers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2025 01:01:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1JanRvendjcC0zQmtiYWxBSTMzVC1tVk1nLURHM3ItQjJPYlBxdElwRDBfLVNDa3BkTXlkODFUWnVaclE1UEMwazcxVS0xMHdKU0paMld3LTFhZ9IBX0FVX3lxTE53N3JXbG1YOEZGellZaVkxUHpoOWE3LVV5WGNhSFo3QVBRYnZITWFEWnhUd2NFX1RackI0dk9nVGcwY1NCMDJESWgzVkFYN2NINmR4ZjhvUGUwem1peFRV</guid></item><item><title>在RFK Jr.取消在美国采用丹麦疫苗接种计划的内部-Politico</title><link>https://www.politico.com/news/2025/12/20/rfk-kennedy-danish-vaccine-schedule-denmark-00701999</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Politico</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 22:12:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPQUJ4aWhGc2tqY0NVTHdxaXo2cnJJc3JfNDhuQ2ZfMTNzVXJBN2pGWGVWZmVCMzVyb2FnNGl2RXhfb21TWGcxbHNER3Z5emZiX01WaGF2T2VRR1hOLUhQUkJjYkw2dVYwRklvTVB2XzF2d2RiQUhXbzVKTVVQbHVtTzFiYVNnMXVlcXlVM3U1LWUzYl9xY2p2UQ</guid></item><item><title>研究表明， “Forever Chemicals”与另一种健康状况有关- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/forever-chemicals-linked-another-health-203558512.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt; Non-stick pans (stock image)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers have found a new link between exposure to “forever chemicals” and one lifelong health condition&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study found that people exposed to two major environmental toxins are more likely to be diagnosed with multiple sclerosis&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Forever chemicals” are synthetic compounds found in products like non-stick pans, waterproof clothing and dental floss&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers have found a new link between exposure to “forever chemicals” — synthetic compounds found in non-stick pans, waterproof clothing, dental floss and more items — and one lifelong health condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study, published in the scientific journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0160412025007445?via%3Dihub" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Environment International;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Environment International&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;/em&gt;found that people exposed to two major environmental toxins — known as perfluorooctane sulfonic acid (PFOS) and polychlorinated biphenyls (PCBs) — are more likely to be diagnosed with multiple sclerosis, or MS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We saw that several individual substances, such as PFOS and two hydroxylated PCBs [substances that arise when PCBs are broken down in the body], were linked to increased odds for MS," Kim Kultima, who led the Sweden-based study, said in a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-exposure-pfas-pcbs-linked-higher.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:press release;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"People with the highest concentrations of PFOS and PCBs had approximately twice as high odds of being diagnosed with MS, compared with those with the lowest concentrations," she added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt; Brain scan (stock image)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/multiple-sclerosis/symptoms-causes/syc-20350269" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mayo Clinic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;, multiple sclerosis is a chronic autoimmune disease that causes a breakdown of the protective covering of nerves, causing numbness, weakness, trouble walking, vision changes and other symptoms.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MS causes an interruption in communication between the brain and the rest of the body, and can eventually lead to permanent damage of the nerve fibers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study, researchers analyzed blood samples from 900 people who had been recently diagnosed with MS, and compared them to samples from people who do not have MS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kultima and her team then measured the toxin levels in each group's blood samples, using statistical models see how chemical exposure corresponded with the odds of developing MS. According to the study, people are often exposed to a mixture chemicals at the same time, so researchers also investigated how exposure to more than one toxin affected them.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"We could then see that an increase in total exposure was linked to higher odds of MS, even after adjusting for previously known lifestyle and genetic risk factors," said Aina Vaivade, the first author of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getty&lt;/p&gt; A non-stick pan (stock image)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final phase of the study also explored the relationship between genetics, chemical exposure and the odds of being diagnosed with MS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers found that people who carry a certain gene variant have a reduced risk of MS. People who carry the gene and participated in the study saw "unexpected increased odds" of being diagnosed with MS when they had higher PFOS exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This indicates that there is a complex interaction between inheritance and environmental exposure linked to the odds of MS," Kultima added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://people.com/people-news-daily-newsletter-sign-up-8692701" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer​​, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Forever chemicals” can last for years in the body without breaking down and are linked to cancer, fetal complications, liver disease, kidney disease, thyroid disease, fertility problems, autoimmune disorders and other serious health issues, &lt;a href="https://people.com/cancer-causing-forever-chemicals-found-in-nearly-half-of-u-s-tap-water-7557908" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:previous research has found;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;previous research has found&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest study's authors believe that there is still more to research when it comes to “forever chemicals” — including what happens when people are exposed to several chemicals at once.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The results show that when attempting to understand the effects of PFAS and other chemicals on human beings, we need to take mixtures of chemicals into account, not just individual substances, as people are generally exposed to several substances at the same time," Vaivade said.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although PCBs were banned in the U.S. in 1979 by the Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) under the Toxic Substances Control Act, they are still found in the environment today — and PFAS are still used today in products ranging from fast food wrappers to &lt;a href="https://people.com/smart-watch-bands-very-high-concentrations-pfas-forever-chemicals-8776525" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:smart watch bands;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;smart watch bands&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We ... think it is important to understand how environmental contaminants interact with hereditary factors, as this can provide new knowledge about the genesis of MS and could also be relevant for other diseases," Kultima added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/forever-chemicals-linked-to-another-health-condition-multiple-sclerosis-study-says-11873993" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 20:46:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOSlNIX2pCS0djbGEyYjA3S0lQcld2X2NLa0ozdng4NzRXZU13ak1zUnI3WlJKLUw2Y24zRW05ZzlIZnQ1MVZFNWNlZE9sWTlWTGIyZV93YXFORTdOZ1FUbGVYRG1GdHRfdnFMdzRXaEpFMGJnSWxvZkRtc0RoZ0pObUt2WmRpMDVFY0NF</guid></item><item><title>读者写道：马哈运动，乙肝，家庭保护，清雪，老年智慧-星论坛报</title><link>https://www.startribune.com/readers-write-the-maha-movement-hepatitis-b-family-preservation-clearing-snow-elderly-wisdom/601546619</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;Vercel Security Checkpoint&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="hide-mobile" data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;|&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p data-astro-cid-nbv56vs3&gt;sfo1::1766299575-XVSHsTUh6llrQp5ad5IvIQhzM0IN0ruX&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Star Tribune</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 19:30:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiygFBVV95cUxQV0F4Vmx4eThLZERBN3pFT0xqVndfbjFoOEtueFFIUGY3cnpNc2NIb1lRWGdUeXRFdy11VVA4dUZyQ0Q1VGdteDRzZVBLeUl2b1Y0Qll1Zk9XcXAwVDFueGk1QlFtempWN2NCSHhPZXc3OG52Ulc0VWZIb2xQaWtRVTdXMjd0WE1Bd0hRdEVDeVNwMXNPSlRxbi1SSjlidWtlaUZZVmJudnFWRWc4bTNUQkhzc3V2V1gzVXhqZGdoUnowX01VR0cyVWh3</guid></item><item><title>“超级流感”对这些州的打击最大：以下是症状- AL.com</title><link>https://www.al.com/news/2025/12/super-flu-hitting-these-states-the-hardest-here-are-the-symptoms.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MZA3V3C355GXHEAV6LBJBB4YTY"&gt;The super flu strain is spreading widely around the country and to make matters worse, it is not included in the &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/nexstar_media_wire/5657502-map-influenza-hitting-these-states-hardest-as-super-flu-continues-to-spread/?tbref=hp" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;flu vaccine this year, experts say. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EYQLJPCANFCPFCTYQEAL7CUPEI"&gt;The nation’s hospitalization rate went up by 14.3 % as of Friday, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VUEWR67TBVAOJDLYJ2NP57NC6I"&gt;Public health officials say the flu is spreading especially quickly in &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/nexstar_media_wire/5657502-map-influenza-hitting-these-states-hardest-as-super-flu-continues-to-spread/?tbref=hp" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;New York, Louisiana and Colorado, The Hill reported Friday.&lt;/a&gt; New Jersey and Rhode Island are also seeing high rates of the flu, as of the latest data from Dec. 13. Georgia, New Mexico, Idaho, Michigan, North Carolina, South Carolina, Massachusetts, Connecticut, Maryland and Washington, D.C. have elevated hospital visits for flu symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6OP3NXRBPBC5VCBSANOM6O5YYE"&gt;Between now and the end of flu season in February, the disease will be spreading in every state to varying degrees, experts say. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BLIMGIKHMVEAFEWE2UVX3DVRBM"&gt;The super flu strain is called subclade K. Early sampling of flu cases show that 90% of influenza A viruses were positive for the strain. The flu shot does not cover influenza A this year, the strain that leads to the most deaths among the &lt;a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/nexstar_media_wire/5657502-map-influenza-hitting-these-states-hardest-as-super-flu-continues-to-spread/?tbref=hp" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;elderly, The Hill reported.&lt;/a&gt; Still, experts say it is worthwhile to get the shot to lessen symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="L325W7XRX5CGZPHPKKEHPYNY6Y"&gt;Symptoms of the flu include fever, chills, cough, sore throat, runny nose, muscle aches, headaches, fatigue and occasionally vomiting or diarrhea, according to the CDC. While most people get better in a few days or a couple of weeks, some complications, like pneumonia, can be deadly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:OOL7FCLWZNB5XODNA6OCHUMJDQ" data-fusion-component="OOL7FCLWZNB5XODNA6OCHUMJDQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:OOL7FCLWZNB5XODNA6OCHUMJDQ" data-fusion-component="OOL7FCLWZNB5XODNA6OCHUMJDQ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 19:04:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxOUmFjM0ktOElLNjVoYlI5Qk5UdzlOZ0RBSVliUmV4M2YtQ3ZqTUZzRktjenp5aFlOTFdlOTJqRVBUUHlGYjZ0eFN3VXFUY0hLVkd3aHRfQlZGRXl6TkwzanRueGVSVXNSVmxlNmliMTNaYWdrUUQ4eFNiVm1RQjRkMUg1WUZqVi1UbTc3S0dMaGZ2c25UMjJBLU9CS2xxNFY1a2JN0gG3AUFVX3lxTE12cFpJV2NjMDVlS1ppSG9HaDZmLXVLUENRbDNZUlVHNUlyVzltYlk1bFJkOXpYZzdfOGJGbzQ3Rm00MVp2UmJHbTNiRExSZ1B0bjI3NlVHd2ZJeV83WmFhTFFKRHFFNHhtTENCb01GSkVaWXpHV0U5V280LVY5RlR3a0Z1cHB1RDc2dTRLZTVhaG1BdkJwa29kby11dXh4U3dsOVFrSHhpOXVzWl9jQ0pKUjlVSms5dw</guid></item><item><title>纽约州罗克兰县新增20例麻疹病例，卫生部门负责人敦促民众接种疫苗——哥伦比亚广播公司新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/measles-cases-rockland-county-ny-health-warning/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;New York health leaders are urging families in Rockland County to get vaccinated for measles amid a recent spike in cases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rockland's health department said Friday that 20 new cases of the highly contagious disease &lt;a href="https://www.rocklandcountyny.gov/Home/Components/News/News/1042/?utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=govdelivery" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;have been confirmed since October&lt;/a&gt; in people who were unvaccinated, including many children under 5 years old. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;County health officials said four children were hospitalized for &lt;a href="https://www.rocklandcountyny.gov/departments/health/communicable-diseases/measles" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;measles&lt;/a&gt;, including one who was critically ill, and that they have since recovered. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Measles and the potential complications are preventable. We can all do our part to protect our most vulnerable community members — such as young children and individuals with weakened immune systems — by ensuring our immunity to measles. Anyone who is unsure of their immunity should seek vaccination as soon as possible," Rockland County Department of Health Commissioner Dr. Mary Leahy said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new measles cases brought the county's total for the year to 21, according to the health department.   &lt;/p&gt;

    
    &lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It comes a week after Connecticut reported its &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/connecticut-measles-case/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;first measles case since 2021&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. So far this year, there have also been 15 confirmed cases &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/nyc-measles-cases/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;in New York City&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and 11 in &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/newark-liberty-international-airport-measles-exposure/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What Rockland County residents should do&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rockland County advised residents to check their measles vaccination status and to also verify their family members' immunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Check your records, ask your doctor, or consider a titer (a blood test that measures immunity) check, which can be done at a health clinic or your health care provider," the county said. "If you are not immune or unsure about your immune status, it is best to seek MMR vaccination, unless you are pregnant or have a weakened immune system." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free vaccines are available by calling the Rockland County Department of Health at 845-364-2497 or 845-364-2520, officials said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Measles symptoms&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.health.ny.gov/diseases/communicable/measles/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;Measles&lt;/a&gt; becomes airborne and spreads when a sick person coughs or sneezes. The virus can remain in the air for two hours after an infected person was present, according to county health officials.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms include fever, rash, cough, red or watery eyes, and a runny nose. They usually appear 10-12 days after exposure, but can occur within a week or up to three weeks later, the county health department said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first symptoms are followed by a rash that starts on the face and moves downward, according to officials. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles can lead to serious conditions such as pneumonia, brain swelling, or even death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who are unvaccinated, young children, pregnant women and people with weak immune systems are at the highest risk, officials said. &lt;/p&gt;

    

                  
        
    
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 17:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNSzhmZzRzUGFRbWVsV0JDLVJhSnN4b25VekRLWXAyeHpHZDV2eVplbjBydHlwV3YyMkxVamhRWHVoOUdOeEhEWWRfZURacmxZcHB4MVpVZGsyTlZkUDNjVUlTV0hOT2h2bmRxZGVHUWR4UVQ2aVhncnVyYWN4RURod3dtWDVHMDdqa25Md0ln</guid></item><item><title>肯尼迪可能会彻底改革儿童疫苗接种计划，建议美国儿童少接种疫苗- WRAL</title><link>https://www.wral.com/news/local/health-kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;
					&lt;p id="font-resize" class="font-resize-container"&gt;
						&lt;button id="small-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa small-buttom-font-svg" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="medium-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;button id="large-font-button"&gt;
							&lt;svg aria-hidden="true" focusable="false" data-prefix="fas" data-icon="text-height" class="fa-text-height fa-w-18 svg-inline--fa" role="img" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 576 512"&gt;
								&lt;use href="#i-text-height"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
							&lt;/svg&gt;
						&lt;/button&gt;
						
					&lt;/p&gt;

					
						&lt;p&gt;Over the last year, Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and his appointees have taken tentative steps toward his goal of remaking the childhood vaccination schedule.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;But emboldened by a directive from President Donald Trump, Kennedy is now poised to make a seismic shift. He is expected to announce in the new year that American children should be immunized according to a different schedule with fewer vaccines, used by the much smaller, largely homogenous country of Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
								
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;A wholesale revision of the schedule would bypass the evidence-based, committee-led process that has underpinned vaccine recommendations in the country for decades, and could affect whether private insurance and government assistance programs will cover the shots.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;And many medical experts worry that losing strong endorsements of some vaccines will create financial and logistical hurdles to obtaining them, further erode Americans’ confidence in immunizations and increase the chances of disease outbreaks. Measles and whooping cough are already resurgent in multiple states because of dropping vaccination rates.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;It is unclear whether any changes will still protect vaccine manufacturers from being sued for claims of harm. Without that guarantee, companies might face “frivolous” lawsuits and flee the American market as they did before such protections were instituted in the 1980s, some vaccine experts warned.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Trump directed Kennedy to align recommendations for childhood vaccines with “best practices from peer, developed countries,” calling the United States “a high outlier in the number of vaccinations recommended for all children.” He pointed to Denmark, Germany and Japan as examples of nations that immunize against fewer diseases.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The directive said that health officials should make the changes “while preserving access to vaccines currently available to Americans,” suggesting to some public health experts that those who wish to get them may still be able to do so in consultation with a health care provider.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
								&lt;p class="opscoad-Mobile_In_Content" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/health-kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark"&gt;
								&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;p class="opscoad-article_in_read" data-unit="wral-v4/news/local/health-kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark/"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;Still, even if only some Americans follow a reshaped schedule that includes fewer immunizations, medical experts said, it is almost certain to lead to more cases of infectious disease.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;“They’re going to bring back suffering and death,” said Dr. Sean O’Leary, chair of the infectious disease committee for the American Academy of Pediatrics. “I don’t say that with any hyperbole. That’s exactly what’s going to happen.”&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health and Human Services did not immediately respond to a request for comment.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
						&lt;p&gt;This article originally appeared in &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/19/health/kennedy-childhood-vaccine-schedule-denmark.html"&gt;The New York Times&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
						
							
							
							
						
					
					
				&lt;/div&gt;


				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WRAL</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:55:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNMWRmWXVZMzJnQmt1VGFfY1E5ZUhhclVjbVByelFhVDdWT1pNME1vMExRN1JHYnh2c0JKWjJqNC1FZm1aQ2xyS085c2Jjcl81OVJCT1V3WkRuLTdXS0c3cnUzLUJPR2d3VDdpR2lJVTBDM3pMY1FzYTktcU1mR0x4ZXV0V2dLVUZVNlE</guid></item><item><title>8种有助于控制糖尿病患者血糖水平的食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/8-foods-that-can-help-manage-blood-sugar-levels-in-diabetes/photostory/126094819.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Winter is the season, when most underlying health issues tend to increase and this is majorly because of the sedeantray lifestyle and unmindful eating habits. Most people tend to over indulge in unhealthy foods, which is one of the biggest reasons why people suffering from Diabetes often experince spike in their insulin levels and suffer with discomfort associted with high sugar. In fact, managing blood sugar levels is crucial for diabetes control, and by adding certain foods to the diet, one can that directly include soluble fiber to slow down glucose absorption, and ensure low glycemic index (GI) that helps in a steady energy release, and the presence of antioxidants in these foods helps combat inflammation, and the healthy fats or proteins enhance insulin sensitivity. According to the books of Ayurveda, there are many foods that are loaded with nutrients and can help prevent spikes, support gut health, and promote satiety without refined carbs. It is also believed that adding these foods to the regular diet can help balancing prana and metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2AFBVV95cUxQb3RHQ2dob3UtNHNBNzBzaEZwRHcxN2pBVDl2T3NRak9NaWtuWVphYjRxejNkX1FLdFZPZW9FUUJnaFhJM1JuMTlkeERxXzJiVDM3dXpUcGRnVmJRQlVqRm94akZPbE1HU0pWdmJFeTkzT0NpZkpsbmlNV181WGFGaXFScWNVMDFpSHY5U2VZM0Myak5UTzU4SnN3UjZRb2Y5UHc5YXZFWEtTeG1UNmpGSGlFdnhtOVFjWVhaakpoU0JucHczdUNZSl9NMXk4ZXZnaV9TbDM5RU3SAeABQVVfeXFMT2pxaVh2OXNiTXBTbjdpNXVtTWlqdUhBMVFDRi1ETTNLb0IzRGY5cUVnRTk2YUJTLThKVlNQbGFZMXZPajRpX0Zyb29hdFRhOFNHS1RaZFY2aXRTZVNTTDdadWZkaDkyQUh1MW9kUkY1clZtT0t3Nmx2MUw4dmFKV2tGVVA2YlI3dWpiakxuaFUzRS1aNHNrNXNUSkxfZFVKMUFDNkl1VTVGRTRwYTRfQzFDd042VG5ORkZRR01hTTJ2bzNpcHBjZlNXb0stZThkUkVQNXpicGxPSTRad09veDc</guid></item><item><title>受欢迎的圣诞晚餐会导致癌症并增加心脏病发作的风险-雅虎英国新闻</title><link>https://uk.news.yahoo.com/popular-christmas-dinner-item-causes-145540188.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With Christmas Day just days away, millions of us are getting in the last of the food needed for the festive period. But what you might not know is there is a direct link between cancer and one of the most popular items on your plate on &lt;a href="https://www.walesonline.co.uk/all-about/christmas" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Christmas;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Christmas&lt;/a&gt; Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Many people believe sugar causes cancer, &lt;a href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/only-two-foods-major-cancer-36227881" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:but this is not the case;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;but this is not the case&lt;/a&gt;. Only two foods are known to have a direct link to cancer. They are alcohol and processed meats. And, given this Christmas favourite is made up of bacon and sausages, the beloved pigs in blankets fall firmly into the processed meats category.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Of course, no one is suggesting that you are going to get cancer because you ate some pigs in blankets on Christmas Day, just as no one is suggesting you will be diagnosed with cancer as a result of a glass of wine or sherry. That said, recent scientific studies say there is no safe amount of alcohol to drink and that even a small amount increases your chance of getting cancer. &lt;a href="https://www.getsurrey.co.uk/news/health/risk-seven-types-cancer-increased-30983764" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:In a recent report;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;In a recent report&lt;/a&gt;, Vivek Murthy, the former surgeon general of the US Public Health Service, warned that alcohol use had been &lt;a href="https://www.getsurrey.co.uk/news/health/risk-seven-types-cancer-increased-30983764" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:directly linked with at least seven types of cancers;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;directly linked with at least seven types of cancers&lt;/a&gt;. He also warned that even light or moderate alcohol consumption can increase a person’s risk of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Processed meat and alcohol are classified as Group 1 carcinogens by the World Health Organisation, meaning they are carcinogenic to humans. The WHO says: "There is convincing evidence that the agent causes cancer." Tobacco smoking and asbestos are also Group 1 carcinogens, though the WHO stresses that this does not mean that alcohol and processed meat are equally as dangerous as smoking and asbestos. Cancer Research UK says unequivocally: "We know for definite that processed meat is a cause of cancer. We are sure about this link like we are for other proven causes of cancer, like tobacco and alcohol."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What is processed meat?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The World Health Organisation says processed meat refers to "meat that has been transformed through salting, curing, fermentation, smoking, or other processes to enhance flavour or improve preservation". Sausages and bacon are among the examples of processed meats given by the WHO and Cancer Research UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Cancer Research UK explains that chemicals found in processed meat, added during processing or produced when cooking it, include nitrates and nitrites, which are used to keep processed meat fresher for longer. It adds: "When we eat them, nitrates and nitrites can become N-nitroso chemicals (NOCs) that can damage the cells that line our bowel. This damage can lead to bowel cancer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why does processed meat cause cancer?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/30376922" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research has linked three meat-related chemicals to increased bowel cancer risk.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Research has linked three meat-related chemicals to increased bowel cancer risk.&lt;/a&gt; These chemicals are either naturally found in meat, added during processing or produced when cooking:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Haem, a red pigment found mostly in red meat&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Nitrates and nitrites, which are used to keep processed meat fresher for longer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Heterocyclic amines (HCAs) and polycyclic amines (PCAs), which are produced when meat is cooked at high temperatures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.cancerresearchuk.org/2024/08/01/bacon-ham-hot-dogs-salami-how-does-processed-meat-cause-cancer-and-how-much-matters/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Cancer Research UK;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Cancer Research UK&lt;/a&gt; explains that all three can damage the cells in our bowel, and it’s the accumulation of this damage over time that increases cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why does alcohol cause cancer?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Alcohol causes cancer through biological mechanisms as the compound breaks down in the body. This means that any drink containing alcohol, regardless of its price, quality or strength, poses a risk of developing cancer and that there is no "safe" amount of alcohol to drink. The WHO says the risk of developing cancer "increases substantially the more alcohol is consumed" but that "latest available data indicate that half of all alcohol-attributable cancers... are caused by 'light' and 'moderate' alcohol consumption – less than 1.5 litres of wine or less than 3.5 litres of beer or less than 450 millilitres of spirits per week".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Does processed meat increase risk of heart disease?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In 2021, &lt;a href="https://www.ox.ac.uk/news/2021-07-21-red-and-processed-meat-linked-increased-risk-heart-disease-oxford-study-shows" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Oxford University said;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Oxford University said&lt;/a&gt; the "largest review of all large-scale studies to date finds red and processed meat increase the risk of heart disease".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Across the world, coronary heart disease claims nearly nine million lives a year, the largest of any disease. Researchers at the University of Oxford’s Nuffield Department of Population Health said evidence from its analysis "indicated that each 50g/day higher intake of processed meat (eg bacon, ham, and sausages) increased the risk of coronary heart disease by 18%".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News UK</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 15:13:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOaU90VjQ3Uk1DYWJDZkhKWmZvbkVURVgza09zc0xEWVNERS14RGRmNDNJUVZVRDdrVVdrWkNkZzBJWnlCNC05bHZibjFoQV9teW1rTVR2Zzg4a3h4VkRCVU9JVmtraW1WcHNGZTdDdTlKXzJ0anJ0RW12MzlERVlsX2FIOA</guid></item><item><title>“永远的化学物质”与另一种毁灭性的终身疾病有关：研究-纽约邮报</title><link>https://nypost.com/2025/12/20/health/forever-chemicals-linked-to-devastating-lifelong-condition/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="single__content entry-content m-bottom"&gt;
							


&lt;p&gt;The news just keeps getting worse for “forever chemicals.” &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;These man-made substances — designed to repel oil, water and stains — can be found in &lt;a href="https://www.niehs.nih.gov/health/topics/agents/pfc" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;thousands of everyday items&lt;/a&gt;, from nonstick pans and fast-food wrappers to waterproof jackets. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Scientists have already linked them to a laundry list of health problems, including &lt;a href="https://keck.usc.edu/news/usc-study-shows-how-pfas-disrupt-healthy-function-in-human-liver-cells/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;liver damage&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://hsph.harvard.edu/news/exposure-to-pfas-associated-with-increased-blood-lipids-possible-cvd-risk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;high cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2023/03/21/inescapable-forever-chemicals-hurt-pregnancy-odds-warning-to-women/"&gt;fertility troubles&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/12/09/health/forever-chemicals-may-triple-risk-of-infant-death-new-study/"&gt;birth defects&lt;/a&gt; and several types of &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2022/08/09/forever-chemicals-linked-to-liver-cancer-in-first-human-study/"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Forever chemicals don’t break down easily, accumulating in the environment and the human body over time.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;luchschenF – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Now, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0160412025007445?via%3Dihub" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;new research&lt;/a&gt; suggests that people exposed to two major environmental toxins — perfluorooctane sulfonic acid (PFOS) and polychlorinated biphenyls (PCBs) — are more likely to be diagnosed with multiple sclerosis, or MS. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p id="connatix-outstream-video"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The chronic autoimmune disease attacks the central nervous system, disrupting communication between the brain and the rest of the body. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;It can lead to a wide range of symptoms, including numbness, muscle weakness, trouble walking, vision problems, extreme fatigue, pain and cognitive difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;


	



&lt;p&gt;“People with the highest concentrations of PFOS and PCBs had approximately twice as high odds of being diagnosed with MS, compared with those with the lowest concentrations,” Kim Kultima, who led the study, said in a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-exposure-pfas-pcbs-linked-higher.html#goog_rewarded" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Previous research has shown that forever chemicals can &lt;a href="https://www.pnas.org/doi/10.1073/pnas.2105018118" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;interfere with the immune system&lt;/a&gt;, either weakening it or sending it into overdrive. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That immune disruption has been tied to autoimmune diseases beyond MS, including &lt;a href="https://www.jrheum.org/content/52/Suppl_1/123" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;lupus&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC12170615/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;rheumatoid arthritis&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11209830/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;inflammatory bowel disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Difficulty walking is one of the most common and debilitating symptoms of multiple sclerosis. &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Halfpoint – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In the new study, Kultima and her team analyzed blood samples from 900 people in Sweden recently diagnosed with MS and compared them with samples from people without the disease.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The researchers measured toxin levels in each group, then used statistical models to see how strongly chemical exposure lined up with the odds of developing MS. &lt;/p&gt;





&lt;p&gt;Because people are typically exposed to multiple chemicals at once, the team also looked at how combined exposure affected their risk.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We could then see that an increase in total exposure was linked to higher odds of MS, even after adjusting for previously known lifestyle and genetic risk factors,” said Aina Vaivade, the study’s first author. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The team also dug into genetics, looking at how inherited traits might interact with chemical exposure.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;In earlier studies, people carrying a certain gene variant were thought to have a lower risk of developing MS. However, the new research found that those same people had higher odds of MS if they were also exposed to elevated levels of PFOS. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“This indicates that there is a complex interaction between inheritance and environmental exposure linked to the odds of MS,” Kultima said. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;“We therefore think it is important to understand how environmental contaminants interact with hereditary factors, as this can provide new knowledge about the genesis of MS and could also be relevant for other diseases,” she added. &lt;/p&gt;



&lt;figure class="nyp-slideshow-modal-image wp-block-image aligncenter size-large"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Multiple sclerosis affects the brain and spinal chord, disrupting communication with the rest of the body.  &lt;span class="credit"&gt;Valerii Apetroaiei – stock.adobe.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;While the study focused on people with MS, it adds to mounting evidence that these chemicals pose serious long-term health risks.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;They seep into the soil, water and air — and studies show nearly all Americans have &lt;a href="https://www.nationalmssociety.org/understanding-ms/what-is-ms/who-gets-ms/how-many-people" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;measurable levels in their blood&lt;/a&gt;, including newborns.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;p&gt;Even more troubling, the toxins don’t break down easily, allowing them to linger in the environment, and inside the human body, for an unknown amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;That’s why PCBs, despite being &lt;a href="https://ecology.wa.gov/blog/january-2024/polychlorinated-biphenyls-pcbs-were-banned-45-years-ago-why-are-they-still-a-problem" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;banned in the US since 1979&lt;/a&gt;, are still found in the environment and older products. PFAS, meanwhile, remain widely used today.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p class="comments-inline-cta" data-comment-count data-prompt="What do you think?"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Experts say there are steps you can take to reduce your exposure, such as &lt;a href="https://nypost.com/2025/07/26/health/new-tool-can-remove-99-of-a-forever-chemical-from-water/"&gt;filtering drinking water&lt;/a&gt; and steering clear of nonstick cookware and grease-resistant food packaging.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Looking for “PFAS-free” labels and choosing fresh, unpackaged foods can further help cut down contact with these chemicals both at home and in your everyday diet.&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;/div&gt;

												&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>New York Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 15:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxNOE9nb0dqV0RXVERHdUhCSHhjdUQ4Z3E5b04xQlNwbktDN3V3MGstZzNXaFUwUDdlbjMwbUhRc1hER0xleWw3QUFlUl9VWXZLVmdybjBuY24xaFNyazkxeVFyZkdxS0MtRm5JZk9VTkgtallob0RPWWhUd2VrLW5iLVBtcUJsX2d5T05mYWJOTFl1cTluUHNjSWhvazE</guid></item><item><title>微小的眼睛植入物可以逆转黄斑变性吗？ - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/could-a-tiny-eye-implant-reverse-macular-degeneration/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:55:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNdko5SmlySlh3dENvaDlkc0tKOW1xRWstZmRlMFNocTlVaUFFVFNYeVZVUl9zbTJVNUxneEl1dVQ0eVg4eUhUcWd0YVU2VWFxSUhwRENwSlNGRDBvTGRUb1g2WUtoeVBPanNCelNsWGdlMnRhQnd5R2Z5aXctMExjMUl5c3E0dw</guid></item><item><title>胃肠病学家揭示了7种阻止减肥的日常习惯，解释了少吃是一种不好的策略|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/gastroenterologist-reveals-7-daily-habits-that-block-weight-loss-explains-how-eating-less-is-a-bad-strategy-101766241077720.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/gastroenterologist-reveals-7-daily-habits-that-block-weight-loss-explains-how-eating-less-is-a-bad-strategy-101766241077720.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;With 2026 less than two weeks away, it is time to start planning our &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/start-the-new-year-right-heart-surgeon-shares-7-simple-habits-that-can-transform-your-health-in-2026-101765870390705.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="New Year"&gt;New Year&lt;/a&gt;’s resolutions. And one of the more popular ones every year, since time immemorial, is &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/new-year-weight-loss-tips-fitness-coach-shares-5-realistic-resolutions-for-losing-weight-in-january-without-crash-diets-101766221275620.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="losing weight"&gt;losing weight&lt;/a&gt; and hitting fitness goals.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/20/550x309/pexels-photo-1172019_1766241534835_1766241561143.jpeg" alt="Sustainable weight loss is facilitated by daily habits, shares Dr Manickam.(Pexel)" title="Sustainable weight loss is facilitated by daily habits, shares Dr Manickam.(Pexel)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/20/550x309/pexels-photo-1172019_1766241534835_1766241561143.jpeg" alt="Sustainable weight loss is facilitated by daily habits, shares Dr Manickam.(Pexel)" title="Sustainable weight loss is facilitated by daily habits, shares Dr Manickam.(Pexel)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Sustainable weight loss is facilitated by daily habits, shares Dr Manickam.(Pexel)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fitness/yoga-trainer-shares-easy-exercises-and-hacks-to-strengthen-spine-and-improve-posture-101766229553448.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Yoga trainer shares easy exercises and hacks to strengthen spine and improve posture"&gt;Yoga trainer shares easy exercises and hacks to strengthen spine and improve posture&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;However, as many of us have painstakingly discovered, it is easier said than done. While we often blame a lack of motivation and willpower, American board-certified gastroenterologist Dr Palaniappan Manickam disagrees.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In an Instagram post on 18 December, he observed, “It’s the daily habits silently blocking your fat loss.” He went on to highlight the habits that stand in our way.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Under-eating to lose weight&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While reaching &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/chennai-fitness-coach-simplifies-weight-loss-in-3-easy-steps-and-calorie-deficit-is-the-name-of-the-game-101764916324612.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="calorie deficit"&gt;calorie deficit&lt;/a&gt; is important for losing weight, not eating enough is the wrong path to follow. “Chronic calorie restriction slows metabolism, raises cortisol, and trains the body to store fat,” stated Dr Manickam.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Snacking all day&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Snacking, or eating in between meals, is also detrimental to achieving weight-loss goals. Eating frequently keeps our insulin levels elevated, explained Dr Manickam. This blocks the burning of fat and metabolic flexibility.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Skipping strength training&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strength training, also known as resistance training, is exercising muscles against an external force to help grow and build strength and endurance. “Muscle drives metabolism,” noted the gastroenterologist. Working on cardio alone to hasten weight loss leads to muscle loss and failure to lose fat in the long term.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Ignoring sleep quality&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our body needs to rest well in order to function properly. Lack of quality sleep disrupts the hunger hormones, which increases craving and reduces the oxidation of fat, thereby obstructing weight loss.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Low protein intake&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lack of protein in the diet “reduces satiety, accelerates muscle loss, and slows down metabolic rate,” warned Dr Manickam.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Normalising chronic stress&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chronic stress is harmful to both mental and physical health. In terms of weight loss, it keeps cortisol levels persistently high, which triggers the storage of fat, especially around the abdomen.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Poor hydration&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Low water intake impairs fat metabolism, digestion, and appetite regulation,” shared Dr Manickam. This results in a false sensation of hunger, which is detrimental to weight loss.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:47:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwJBVV95cUxOT1BCemt1cUlIdTdDVjNIa3RtYmZLaGlncElSM21fNTZUODVjNjc0b2lUUF8yZ0RLVmxPeURUVWxpQ0FBYUI1dmVTT09FZ0k0V2RwMkhMcXNkN2VWdTJoY2Z6M2lhNE4zdjRCRlQxZ0dzLUhsX3BVQ29jOVR1MXBleHBwSHpBZi1adjFvaS0tcEE2R3FrZUFQVkppb3hEejZOc20xVFJXcUp6Z3JBMUhIa1BHTjZ1d1ZJU0ZOekRLYkRxWmQxbXVEZFFGZkFtVVFyemwzcEZETWdXZjlLR3hjdF90LVliTFdwYUtZVi1uV0RnX09Nd1Fpc1NybkRrWFh3MGJzTjI1Y9IBjAJBVV95cUxOSmRrQjVKMHU0Vk5CS2RXM0pFZnNnUjQ4REQ5cEFaSHY4MU5jbWRMWDZCR2JzNGlQbmZ3X0VmQ2tvOFFGbnVjbzRTekJZQWkwUUQ1UTBUYnNHOFJOUUEzZ2VVcldYZ3ZKZXc0LWNIVlRlX0tMSVpGeHRBVWthOURISlJMSUlyR2RpYXRySGMtWXItZGY4SVpaczcyVEFFRldzWGdVQ2lhbWpMT1pCcVNQai1ndEZ6THNxaGJhRVlyLUFiUHhHWjR6V3AyV2dnN3JmNGJvalZMQzRSSndsRl85a045clV3U29zOS1WWl9Hc3Buai11T0hlR3VVWWdEckQtaWVHMVFFa3RHeUNt</guid></item><item><title>即将崩溃的女性通常会开始为自己购买这11样东西- YourTango</title><link>https://www.yourtango.com/self/women-verge-breaking-down-usually-start-buying-these-things-for-themselves</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every day, many people struggle to keep it together. No matter what life throws their way, they do their best to push those ugly feelings aside and push forward. Unfortunately, stress and overwhelm eventually catch up, which can create a desire to purchase certain items to bring calm and relaxation. And whether it's candles or loads of takeout, women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of women, in particular, feel pressure to juggle everything and maintain their composure. From landing their dream career to being the perfect mother, womanhood is exhausting, to say the least. When a woman begins buying certain things, it could be a strong indicator that she's spiraling mentally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these 11 things for themselves&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h3&gt;1. Comfy weighted blankets&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-comfy-blankets.png" alt="woman enjoying tea wrapped in a weighted blanket" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves comfy weighted blankets" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;dekazigzag | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a woman finds it comfortable and they're going through it, expect them to add a weighted blanket to their online cart immediately. Sure, she may have a few blankets in her bed already, but another one never hurts. And for many, something is grounding about sleeping with a weighted blanket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/279846113_Positive_effects_of_a_weighted_blanket_on_insomnia" rel="nofollow"&gt;study published in the Journal of Sleep Medicine and Disorders&lt;/a&gt;, weighted blankets actually have a positive effect on sleep. People report feeling more comfortable and safe while sleeping with a weighted blanket. So, if a woman is close to experiencing a mental break of sorts, having weight on top of her might be just what she needs to feel good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/small-signs-woman-who-deeply-unhappy-with-her-life"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Small Signs Of A Woman Who Is Deeply Unhappy With Her Life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;2. Self-improvement journals&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-self-improvement-journals.png" alt="woman on the verge of breaking down writing in a journal" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves self improvement journals" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everyone wants to &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/ways-become-better-version-yourself"&gt;be the best version of themselves&lt;/a&gt;, growing and learning throughout life. But as things become harder and pressure builds, we abandon these goals entirely. And sometimes, it takes something drastic to make a woman snap out of it and focus on herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying self-improvement journals for themselves as a way to feel grounded with nowhere else to turn to. They invest in journaling and engage in it religiously. While they might not be able to afford a therapist, they know that healthy venting of their emotions is crucial to keeping them from breaking down completely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/signs-youre-not-lazy-youre-just-emotionally-done"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Signs You're Not Lazy — You're Just Emotionally Done&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;3. Skincare products&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-skincare-products.png" alt="woman with towel wrapped around hair applying skincare products" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves skincare products" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Gorgev | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For women who are running themselves dry, it's probably been a while since they prioritized their skincare. So busy with everything and everyone else around them, they barely have enough time to properly take care of themselves, let alone their body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sure, she might have a lot of products, from the newest Korean skincare mask all the way to an overpriced lip balm. However, it never hurts to buy one more thing if it's going to help with self-care. And as &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/a-deeper-wellness/202302/understanding-the-mental-health-and-self-care-connection"&gt;clinical psychologist Monica Vermani&lt;/a&gt; pointed out, "Quality &lt;a href="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/topics/caring-for-your-mental-health" rel="nofollow"&gt;self-care is linked to improved mental health&lt;/a&gt;, with benefits like enhanced self-esteem and self-worth, increased optimism, a positive outlook on life, and lower levels of anxiety and depression."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/love/wives-stay-quiet-during-arguments-usually-feel-these-things-theyll-never-admit"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wives Who Stay Quiet During Arguments Usually Feel These 11 Things They'll Never Admit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4. Assortments of tea&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-tea.png" alt="smiling woman in cardigan drinking tea " title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves tea" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Drazen Zigic | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coffee is amazing, especially on tough days when people don't feel like getting up for work. But coffee isn't as calming as tea and can make a woman's mental breakdown worse. For a woman like this, she may end up buying lots of different teas to try, often drinking it for comfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/live-long-and-prosper/202207/taking-time-for-tea-comforting-rituals-in-stressful-times"&gt;well-being researcher Jasmin Tahmaseb-McConatha&lt;/a&gt; said, rituals like drinking tea can "soothe difficult times, relieve anxiety and stress, and connect us to others." So, the next time a woman feels anxious, a nice &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health/affordable-ways-to-calm-your-nerves"&gt;hot cup of tea will calm her nerves&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-signs-woman-who-has-been-through-lot-life-according-research"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Subtle Signs Of A Woman Who Has Been Through A Lot In Life, According To Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;5. Comfort clothes&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-comfort-clothes.png" alt="woman in comfort clothes standing outside with tea" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves comfort clothes" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Aleksandra Suzi | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobody likes wearing overly tight clothes. Whether it's at work or with the in-laws, these restrictive clothes can make a woman's mental state worse. Filled with anxiety, she might feel more trapped than ever before. And while she may be at her wits' end right now, slipping into comfortable clothing can do wonders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From wearing sweatpants to baggy shirts, women who are having a breakdown make sure they're comfortable. While they can't control what's happening around them, they can change small things to make themselves feel just a little less anxious.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/health-wellness/subtle-signs-not-just-stressed-completely-exhausted-emotionally"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;15 Subtle Signs You're Not Just Stressed, You're Completely Exhausted Emotionally&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;6. Candles&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-candles.png" alt="woman smelling candles at the store" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves candles" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Vladeep | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying candles for themselves. And while it might not make much sense, candles have a bigger impact on people than most realize. Besides the warmth it provides, candles can play a part in improving mental health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.kacadas.com/blogs/default-blog/can-candles-have-an-effect-on-your-mental-health" rel="nofollow"&gt;psychotherapist and cognitive behavioral therapist Chryssa Chalkia&lt;/a&gt;, "It is scientifically proven that scented candles can play an essential role in the physiological effects of mood, stress, working capacity, and overall mental health... The smell of scented candles stimulates our limbic system, the part of the brain that is home to our memory and emotions. Hormones like serotonin and dopamine can be produced to help regulate mood."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/little-things-deeply-unhappy-people-have-homes-anyone-else-never-buy"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Little Things Deeply Unhappy People Have In Their Homes That No One Else Would Ever Buy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;7. Takeout&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-takeout.png" alt="woman in suit eating takeout" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves takeout" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;PeopleImages | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life can get exhausting, whether it's juggling work, family, or other responsibilities. For women experiencing burnout and exhaustion, cooking is the last thing they're worried about, so they'll often order takeout. It might not be the healthiest option, but takeout in moderation isn't necessarily a bad thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only is it convenient, but it can bring a ton of comfort too. In fact, &lt;a href="https://www.upi.com/Health_News/2011/03/27/Meatloaf-mashed-potatoes-fight-loneliness/UPI-79641301252021/" rel="nofollow"&gt;one study published in Psychological Science&lt;/a&gt; found that comfort foods can improve our mood. So, women shouldn't be afraid to eat takeout, as there's a small sense of joy in enjoying a comforting meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/things-emotionally-exhausted-people-start-avoiding-completely"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Things Emotionally Exhausted People Start Avoiding Completely&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;8. Supplements and wellness products&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-supplement-and-wellness-products.png" alt="woman taking daily supplements with water" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves supplement and wellness products" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;insta_photos | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life can get busy, especially for women who are mothers and working full-time. They don't always have the time to care about their health. But whether it's supplements to improve their fiber intake or strengthen their gut, ​​women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many women who are worn down find themselves worrying about every little thing. Especially with so many health scares, to keep their sanity in check, they'll purchase wellness products for peace of mind and sanity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/money/grew-up-broke-made-it-still-probably-cant-bring-yourself-buy-simple-things"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If You Grew Up Broke But Made It, You Still Probably Can't Bring Yourself To Buy These 11 Simple Things&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;9. New hobbies&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-new-hobbies.png" alt="woman painting enjoying new hobby" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves new hobbies" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;GBJSTOCK | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When a woman is stressed and looking for an escape, there are a ton of things she can do. She may not be great at painting or fishing, but because she's been feeling overwhelmed, with no other option, she's finding a great way to escape from reality by buying new hobbies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Engaging in new hobbies is actually a good thing. According to &lt;a href="https://www.psychologytoday.com/us/blog/social-instincts/202502/3-kinds-of-hobbies-that-can-help-us-thrive"&gt;psychologist Mark Travers&lt;/a&gt;, "While physical and creative hobbies nurture your body and soul, &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/special-interests-women-who-are-more-intelligent-than-everyone-else"&gt;intellectual hobbies keep your mind sharp&lt;/a&gt;, curious, and engaged with the world around you... In this way, finding a hobby that challenges your intellect can feel like rediscovering a part of yourself you didn't realize was missing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/signs-woman-emotionally-drained-but-keeps-pushing-through"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Signs A Woman Is Emotionally Drained But Keeps Pushing Through&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;10. Organizing items&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-organization-items.png" alt="woman doing laundry " title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves organization items" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Evgeny Atamanenko | Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once a woman is going through it, her environment will show it. From clothes on the floor to dishes on the countertop, her surroundings look disastrous. But by purchasing items intended for organizing her home, she's on a mission to improve herself from the outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because &lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/balance/ss/slideshow-clutter-affects-health"&gt;clutter can negatively affect a person's mental health&lt;/a&gt;, she's prepared to spend hours &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/quick-organizing-tips-declutter-your-home"&gt;dusting, organizing, and cleaning her home&lt;/a&gt; until it's spotless. Not only does it feel good, but it keeps her distracted from the negative thoughts she has swirling around in her head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/subtle-signs-woman-been-misunderstood-her-whole-life-according-research"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Subtle Signs Of A Woman Who Has Been Misunderstood Her Whole Life, According To Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;11. Plants&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="media media--type-image media--view-mode-default"&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-media-image field--type-image field--label-hidden field__item"&gt; &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://www.yourtango.com/sites/default/files/image_blog/2025-12/women-verge-breaking-down-start-buying-things-plants.png" alt="woman smiling holding plants" title="women on the verge of breaking down usually start buying these things for themselves plants" class="img-fluid" typeof="foaf:Image" decoding="async"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="field field--name-field-credit field--type-string field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;ShotPrime Studio | Shutterstock &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plants are a huge upkeep, and it's not always fun to keep them alive. But there's no denying that they improve a woman's environment and make her more excited. Whether it's learning new tips and tricks or spending hours digging in the backyard, there's &lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/art-green-living-hidden-perks-filling-home-with-plants"&gt;something calming about plants&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s40101-015-0060-8" rel="nofollow"&gt;study published in the Journal of Physiological Anthropology&lt;/a&gt; found, "active interaction with indoor plants can reduce physiological and psychological stress compared with mental work." For women on the verge of breaking down, plants are a great tool to keep her calm and engaged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article-body-related-links"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RELATED: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.yourtango.com/self/small-ways-take-better-care-yourself-nothing-do-diet-exercise"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;11 Small Ways To Take Better Care Of Yourself That Have Nothing To Do With Diet And Exercise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Marielisa Reyes is a writer with a bachelor's degree in psychology who covers self-help, relationships, career, family, and astrology topics.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="midcat-most-popular"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Related Stories From YourTango:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="rc-widget-c743d1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>YourTango</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:31:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxNSF9MRUx5d0ttWHJwV0czOUVBM3p4TFBqcVhHZU5tVlVhNEJ3a0M4aEthN1F2N3VMNFBwTi1vUExNSFVkNm5EdkRETUVFVkQ3amJOZWRlb1FrM25Fc0tZU21aQVFDcDhoTUFlZGxIWWZ1RXlBZTJJc0IzaHRDRkcyVDhfSFdCdG8ydndQUEhrOVlidjNkTEVFbmx3OU9kMmxPODdxTC1tUGs</guid></item><item><title>科学家警告流行的止痛药可能弊大于利- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-warn-popular-painkiller-may-do-more-harm-than-good/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:15:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxONU1DbTRud0NUUVM3am1hNTRMV0VpaXQ4OW80Ml81SUtpQWRENDhVN090aVlPNzctak82ckF2dnV6NVVKR1cyWmMwU08wQ0o4SnREZ1EyR05ZSEFQREZfaTJORzFKZjdYaEdXLWdCS2RQMXYzLXh6UHJlTG9Ed0dCOUpJNnl0bXhkcDZIemt6dGU</guid></item><item><title>人民药店：从合法的加拿大在线药店购买一些药物可以节省您的包裹- OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2025/12/peoples-pharmacy-purchasing-some-medicines-from-a-legitimate-online-canadian-pharmacy-can-save-you-bundles.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BWVOY24CQBDELDXQ6NXPISPPEE"&gt;Q. I’ve been taking a low-dose Jardiance pill for two years. The endocrinologist at the hospital put me on it after my heart attack and triple bypass. My blood sugar is under control, and I have experienced no noticeable side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7ZQ3S4DY2NEJVMVAT6ZJQOP5KM"&gt;I purchase the drug from a Canadian pharmacy. It costs me about $400/year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LSWL7FBDSRC33OAMQ6MWSZZSMI"&gt;A. If you were buying Jardiance (empagliflozin) without insurance in the U.S., the monthly price tag could run more than $600. Purchasing your medicine from a legitimate online Canadian pharmacy would bring the price down substantially.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5YE7POEXDZA4FBJJA5FOE426DU"&gt;You can learn more about the pros and cons of using Jardiance to treat Type 2 diabetes in our “eGuide to Preventing and Treating Diabetes.” We also discuss how to safely purchase medications from Canada in our “eGuide to Saving Money on Medicines.” These online resources may be found under the Health eGuides tab at www.PeoplesPharmacy.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AW27S6DSHFCL3LRTWJSJCAN7NU"&gt;Q. Guaifenesin is a miracle drug for me. For most of my life, I’ve had sinus problems. Even with a big sinus infection, guaifenesin clears the congestion within a day or two. Nothing a doctor has prescribed has ever been better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TOC5ASTRH5CBXLH6M7H5EWGKSI"&gt;A. Guaifenesin is sold over the counter as an expectorant. That means it is supposed to loosen mucus and ease congestion. We’re glad you get such great relief from this very old drug. Researchers have recently raised questions about its effectiveness, though (Otolaryngology-Head and Neck Surgery, May 28, 2024). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV6MCHOH2VEWXPLJQLBNMTAT4M"&gt;&lt;i&gt;In their column, Joe and Teresa Graedon answer letters from readers. Write to them in care of King Features, 628 Virginia Drive, Orlando, FL 32803, or email them via their website: www.PeoplesPharmacy.com. Their newest book is “Top Screwups Doctors Make and How to Avoid Them.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxNbFdoWUZpUzUwNVo1LVZDN3lraWJCamU1NzJYUTk3dm1QcXdybVU3d0FGRDdCWjR5SUpnam5vX0JKZWppR2JldU4zem9rZ0RsdWJYdVB4RkRhTERsaGlpWnF6SVRfME1meXNsQUtPTndpV1k2Rk1JQVB0N3NlbFZMS2R2SlExaDBoa0xvWVlDQWN0dVpfTDhjTDVzMmxINEZWZklhb0R4UXhQTzVhc0VUYVk2SzlaQ20tUHhIb2RxSGlwMVQyakdsdWxoQUNFcmViWllPcWdrRjZRTDdjMWw1QWlZYnFGaXpH0gH8AUFVX3lxTE91NFNEcEdiMVlKTUJfLWRTTUQzWjh6QkFSQ1NHdWFQMFJ5RUFhQzJ1LVN0cWNRLWZMV0YwUkpqVUtWRHFwOFVGQmphWjlLVmZLd2N3NVZrcUs2eFlvY2U4dTdIeVVpTDVtTm5uc253NlBkb0R5ekM0YkM3QUNDQ0tDR0N3czBqMzZuN2JWb1VHOUVNd21ZZ3dya1EyblEzTVZnSnZTX2thOEpoN1ZRV2NoOW12cGFvM2l4S3RkNm9TZHNFMFNrLVZzZzlFYXctT1Y3ekxwNnVSdlB6VGdmb3VVcUpmMTcwV1lITVBNdWVrWllTaW1pYXRDanJqMA</guid></item><item><title>18名在家庭中处理过阿尔茨海默氏症的人分享了他们注意到的早期迹象- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/scarymouse/what-its-like-alzheimers-family-signs-wish-knew-earlier</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-20
  
  
  
  
  " data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139743837" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;So, what do you think? If you've dealt with something similar, I'd love to hear about your experience in the comments below. You never know — your story might be helpful to others going through something similar! If you want to write in but prefer to stay anonymous, you can utilize this anonymous form. Your story could be included in a future BuzzFeed article!&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Please note: some comments have been edited for length and/or clarity.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:16:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxPbUlpVTBlNDJCZVYxSXBtei1WdEpkREVPX1E2WTNWY2JPMEpsYjVVaUFxMm11ZTJudkFVd2otOFk2YlhOUDdVM3UwdWp4aWxzQzVCbmo1aU1KRTJMNVVEMWRuZmlPTldVMXg2NkVyODhkSEhOSUpGRVF5OElHal9hSjA2dzNoZkxVTGVCR1JwWnhINUk2cnc</guid></item><item><title>你终于去看医生了。以下是如何充分利用它-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/doctor-visits-checkup-questions-primary-care-3fcde5b5c927734429818bd0ed1c6680</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;WASHINGTON (AP) — It’s not unusual for a 20-something to text Mom in a panic from the doctor’s office, seeking help answering a question. And patients of any age can struggle to recall all their medicines — or forget to mention a concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting the most out of a doctor’s visit requires some advance preparation. Even the professionals plan ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is really hard — even for me as a doctor going to see my own family doctor — to remember the things that I wanted to bring up,” said Dr. Sarah Nosal, president of the American Academy of Family Physicians. “The worst is when you’ve had that moment with your doctor” only to recall another problem after walking out, she said. “You’ve lost that time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her top tip: Bring a list of symptoms and questions to show at the start of the visit. The first item should be your top concern, but seeing the full list helps your doctor prioritize what’s most medically urgent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’m actually going to be able to see, is there a red flag?” explained Nosal, who has some advice about prepping for a typical primary care visit.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;h2&gt;Your primary care doctor monitors your overall health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some illnesses require specialists like a cardiologist or rheumatologist. But regardless of your age or how healthy you are, research has long shown that a relationship with a primary care provider is important for overall health. It might be a family physician like Nosal, who cares for all ages, or an internist. Some patients choose gynecologists, geriatricians, or have a primary care team that includes nurse practitioners or physician assistants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Primary care is more than preventive checkups to help avoid illness, such as vaccinations, cancer screenings or health advice. It also includes detecting and treating common problems like high blood pressure, and helping to find and coordinate specialty care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“That ongoing relationship also helps me know your ‘normal,’” Nosal explained. “If something’s different or changes or you feel off, when you tell me that information and I also have known you over time, we can really figure out together what’s going on.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Quiz your family before the appointment&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young adults navigating health care on their own for the first time may need help filling out forms with their personal medical history. Have you ever had general anesthesia? Is your tetanus shot up to date?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you still have access to the patient portal at your former pediatrician’s office, you can see records of vaccinations and prior illnesses, or you may have to request them or quiz parents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all ages, family medical history is critical — and needs regular updating. Ask what diseases your close relatives have had and how they fared. For example, if Type 2 diabetes runs in the family, or Grandma had a stroke, or someone had cancer at a young age, that information could help tailor your preventive care, Nosal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fill out your paperwork ahead of the visit&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Filling out paperwork from home makes it easier to check medicine bottles for the name and dose. Include both prescription and over-the-counter medicines, pills or creams — and don’t forget vitamins and supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why are the latter important? Some can interact with prescription medicines. Nosal cited some patients whose longtime treatments quit working after they started taking turmeric, a spice also sold as a supplement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also before your visit, check if the doctor received records of recent lab tests, hospitalizations or visits to other health providers, since electronic medical records aren’t always automatically shared.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Keep a running list of questions before a doctor visit&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some symptoms are bad enough to prompt an urgent visit. But if you’ve got a checkup coming, whether it’s routine or to follow up on health problems, start a list of questions in advance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notice a pain when you move a certain way? Or chatting with a friend who just got a colonoscopy and wonder if you’re due? Pop those on your list right away, before you forget — and be specific in describing symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nosal keeps a running list on her phone and, ahead of visits with her own doctor, sends it as a heads-up through her patient portal. Patients also can include their list on visit check-in forms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea is to address the most urgent questions first, rather than patients running out of time before raising a key concern. Nosal said questions about mental or sexual health and wellness especially tend to come up at the last minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the medium, “please bring that list,” she said. “That’s the most critical of all pieces.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;It’s OK to ask again&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;People may know to ask questions about treatments, such as how well they work and what side effects to expect. But it’s also important to understand why a doctor makes a particular diagnosis or, conversely, isn’t as worried about a symptom as you might be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don’t hesitate to say, “Explain to me what else could be going on,” Nosal advised. “What would be the next step? How would you evaluate that for me, to know if it’s this or that?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most health advocacy groups also advise bringing along a friend or relative, especially if you have serious or multiple health problems. They can help ask questions and take notes.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;“Whether you are 20 or you are 85, you will not remember everything from your medical visit,” Nosal said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 13:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOc0xFRDltbnNnU05Lb2ZJSDFSZ2EwOS12bElONk1PNi00OGNhem81cEF0LUpodkxGbkc4bV9fMExsa2d3SWFSUlBqOUxqUXdTTDlCdktjMUNPcDlXYXZxNVU4WWdyS0RHRE9hbUdyQ0RJRzFBNHhVaUgtaDFObWdzWHFBWHYwYnE4R1RuLWdMZk1BNDFTWkpkckdyRE5TMWZDSmltX1JBZw</guid></item><item><title>“现在不是拍三张照片的时候” ：专家说， Ozempic上的数百万人面临着新的假期危险-旧金山纪事报</title><link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/article/ozempic-weight-drug-food-21244442.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxQNWNiRlJ2UFZLRWxRVWFqenRYQ0dScmZkb1pOZm1OT1k0QWNRSkppUk1TZFR5LTE5Z3FJckhLbnFBN2lBMklyM0FwXzJfZ2dmOUlkbDdpQ012NDhkaUJvNndEVGNQcWtXYWh6cElGbjNPMUFwS3MzYjNhNGI3NHJ3eHdQZEdlRnM</guid></item><item><title>我们需要停止在假期周围说话的有毒短语- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/toxic-phrase-holidays-goog_l_6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Just 12 hours after the last Halloween trick-or-treater left and my sugared-up kids were tucked into bed, I started my typical Monday morning fitness class. But mid-plank, the instructor’s comment caught me off guard, and didn’t sit well with me the rest of the day. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Let’s work off all that Halloween candy!” she shouted into her mic. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The nonchalant phrase of “let’s work off ___,” while surely intended as a lighthearted joke, is seriously problematic, according to experts. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;The idea that you need to out-exercise food or earn any treats isn’t just prevalent during Halloween ― it’s also extremely common to hear during the holiday season. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s why this mentality needs to stop, and how you can feel good in your body instead.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: SCIENCE PHOTO LIBRARY via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;SCIENCE PHOTO LIBRARY via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Experts explain why it's important to overcome the damaging notion that you have to work out in order to eat holiday meals or treats.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It discredits the more important benefits of exercise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;I definitely wasn’t at the gym that morning to burn off Sugar Daddys and Dots. I was there to strengthen my postpartum abs, to visit my friends and to move my body so it felt limber and strong.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a href="https://healthyemmie.org/pages/about-me" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Emmie Keefe" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://healthyemmie.org/pages/about-me" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Emmie Keefe&lt;/a&gt;, a Boston-based nutritionist, said whenever instructors focus on this calorie-based “motivation,” it backfires. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“We should never exercise for the sake of burning calories. ... We should exercise for cardiovascular health, for mental health, for emotional health. It gives structure to your day. You can create social relationships through classes together,” she explained. “There are &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;so many reasons to exercise. B&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;urning calories shouldn’t be one of them.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent research shows that &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/weight-loss-may-not-make-you-healthier_l_61638056e4b0cc44c50dcbfe" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="focusing on regular exercise improves your longevity" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="61638056e4b0cc44c50dcbfe" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;focusing on regular exercise improves your longevity&lt;/a&gt; ― even more than focusing on weight loss. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/reasons-exercise-nothing-to-do-losing-weight_l_5f0873bdc5b63a72c340c2e5" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="Exercise also" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="5f0873bdc5b63a72c340c2e5" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Exercise also&lt;/a&gt; alleviates symptoms of anxiety and depression, enhances creativity, and helps you sleep better. Meanwhile, &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/phrase-think-about-exercise_l_60e59fe3e4b08ebff5e4b9db" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="looking at exercise as punishment rather than a beneficial activity" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="60e59fe3e4b08ebff5e4b9db" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;looking at exercise as punishment rather than a beneficial activity&lt;/a&gt; makes you less likely to engage in the healthy behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Keefe added that the “mental gymnastics” of trying to count calories in and out with food and exercise isn’t always realistic or helpful. Instead, regular exercise can help you feel more motivated in other areas of your life and that you’ve started the day off in a productive way. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;What that walk and that workout class is not going to do is burn off what you ate right before,” she said. “That way of thinking is big, big trouble.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“There are so many reasons to exercise. Burning calories shouldn’t be one of them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__attribution caption-cli"&gt;- Emmie Keefe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It promotes harmful eating mindsets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;How do you feel when you are about to dig into a pumpkin pie you only encounter once or twice per year? Hopefully simply excited, and not anything else. According to Alyssa Royse, owner of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rocketcommunityfitness.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Rocket Community Fitness" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.rocketcommunityfitness.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Rocket Community Fitness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in Seattle, the mindset that you have to deserve that pie or undo the damage is “really dangerous.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It links us to this idea that we have to earn the right to eat and have to earn the right to have pleasure. Both of those things are innate in simply having a body ... by virtue of being alive, you are allowed [both],” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“When we moralize food, we trigger all sorts of dangerous thoughts and behavior patterns in people,” she continued. &lt;/span&gt;This includes eating disorders, which can lead to &lt;a href="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/publications/eating-disorders" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="major long-term health complications" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nimh.nih.gov/health/publications/eating-disorders" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;major long-term health complications&lt;/a&gt; like heart damage, hair growth issues, brain damage, lethargy and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; Instead of creating these negative connections, trainers in her gym don’t mention food. If the holidays do come up, they try to focus on positive aspects like, “go have fun and enjoy the bounty, go feel the joy ... that’s the primary purpose of your body ― to experience joy,” Royse said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Royse added that people already have these damaging thoughts on their own around the holidays, as a result of years of toxic messaging in media where people are pushed to be thinner. She encourages her clients to challenge these connections they and others have made, and move instead toward body and food neutrality. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Food doesn’t need to be an emotional or moral experience. You are allowed to just have it,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Keefe also noted that shaming yourself for what you ate can have an additional physical consequences. As a result of the stress hormones you release through that thought pattern, you can experience &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/11874-stress" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="stomach pains and digestive problems" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/11874-stress" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;stomach pains and digestive problems&lt;/a&gt; (along with so many other issues like headaches, heart palpitations and more).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt; “You’re really making yourself suffer twice,” she said. Instead, she emphasizes enjoying it and moving on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“Food doesn’t need to be an emotional or moral experience. You are allowed to just have it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__attribution caption-cli"&gt;- Alyssa Royse&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listen to your body instead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Both experts believe it’s necessary to tune in to your body instead of letting outside forces influence how you feel, especially when it comes to the holidays. This process, also known as mindful eating, is where you pay close attention to your food ― mentally noticing how it tastes and how enjoyable it feels to eat it. It also has you listen to your natural hunger and fullness cues. Food is not something you’ve “earned” and there is absolutely no expectation that you need to “work it off.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Royse said she specifically tries to drink more water (one glass per &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/holiday-drink-recipes_n_5a2818d8e4b02d3bfc3774ae" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="holiday cocktail" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="5a2818d8e4b02d3bfc3774ae" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;holiday cocktail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;) and take more walks, not as a penalty but as a way to counteract any physical discomfort she might be feeling.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Keefe enjoys whatever holiday foods she wants, while also prioritizing nutrition. She chooses fruits and vegetables when she can, noting that the holidays don’t necessarily mean you have to only eat rich foods or only stick to the veggie tray. She has also seen clients make themselves sick trying to preemptively offset the holidays’ physical impact.&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“They exhaust themselves with exercise in anticipation or in reaction to how they’ve eaten during the holidays. Their overall health declines ... their bodies are under enormous stress,” she said. “Treat your body kindly.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’re struggling with an eating disorder, call the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/find-help-support" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="National Eating Disorder Association hotline" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="6939aeb8e4b007ac563b48db" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://www.nationaleatingdisorders.org/find-help-support" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;&lt;em&gt;National Eating Disorder Association hotline&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; at 1-800-931-2237.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOeEhWeHNsUVZRY1FnX3BaRm9oZ0M0emJlQmFtbThNVnB0UGpMNUpyMWZrUjk0NmlPNGpoMW1GVzR4YTN2MWJVaktLT1pQcnliVkFXV3JwZy1zVFo4TTlBZF9USzlfdmpmcnk5MnRHT1Y5NVB2ZVNMMTZIOXB0VVNfcFhiSFk4NkJTY0l3MdIBkgFBVV95cUxPTmN5QTh4RHJjTHk2cWRFcmlRVE42ZXUwUlA2RnN1eWtzM3NuSVBBMUVXcTc5b1MwczRRWjVHTGJkS2c0M1pCT19zcjUwRmowYXBQVHBzX25jcXhVVzIzUVpQQVRMbWhJOWdxYUZSRG1RakQ2SFczTWhLSW9qcHVsRE4wdUpLMG1UQUFPQU1taFZyUQ</guid></item><item><title>美国正在经历“国家创伤” —它解释了为什么我们中的许多人感到悲惨- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/us-national-trauma-meaning-goog_l_69405427e4b043da371d0cc1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This year we’ve experienced an onslaught of horrible news. There were multiple high profile deaths and mass shootings, wars, inflation, tariffs, anti-abortion and anti-LGBTQ legislation ― the list goes on and on.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Some people say the United States is in a period of “national trauma,” a psychological phenomenon in which negative events severely impact an entire group (in this case, Americans). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What we are experiencing is unprecedented. “The combination of 24/7 news cycles, social media algorithms designed specifically to keep us engaged, and genuinely challenging global events creates a perfect storm for widespread secondary trauma,” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.losangelesmftherapist.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Saba Lurie" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405427e4b043da371d0cc1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="http://www.losangelesmftherapist.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Saba Lurie&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a therapist and owner of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.losangelesmftherapist.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Take Root Therapy" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405427e4b043da371d0cc1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.losangelesmftherapist.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Take Root Therapy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cntraveler.com/destinations/los-angeles" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Los Angeles" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405427e4b043da371d0cc1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cntraveler.com/destinations/los-angeles" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Los Angeles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, told &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;HuffPost&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s how all this trauma affects us ― and what to do when everything feels like a bit too much.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your body doesn’t know the difference between trauma on a screen versus in real life.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When you see a threat, your body’s stress response — aka the fight or flight system — turns on. Your adrenal glands release stress hormones like cortisol and adrenaline, your heart rate quickens, your blood pressure rises, and blood flow is directed to your muscles to help you either fight the threat or flee, according to Lurie.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;At the same time, the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/24894-amygdala" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="amygdala" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405427e4b043da371d0cc1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/24894-amygdala" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;amygdala&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; — nicknamed the brain’s alarm system — becomes hyperactive and starts scanning your environment for more danger. “All of this is happening because our nervous system is trying to protect us from what it perceives as a real and immediate threat,” said Lurie.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Your body will mount this physiological response regardless of whether you witness the threat in real life or through a screen. As Lurie said, “our brains don’t really distinguish between something happening to us directly versus something we’re watching happen to someone else.” To our brains, a threat is a threat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Humans are also social, empathetic creatures. “The same mechanisms that help us connect ... make us feel as though we are experiencing what we are watching,” Lurie explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It doesn’t help that the news disproportionately focuses on negative events, as a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S245195882400071X?via=ihub" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="study" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405427e4b043da371d0cc1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S245195882400071X?via=ihub" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;study&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; from 2024 described. The media uses compelling imagery, urgent language and nonstop updates to keep us engaged and scrolling, Lurie said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The key issue when consuming media covering traumatic events is that we can’t actually do anything to resolve the threat, she adds. So, we keep watching and thinking about it. “We’re just left activated with nowhere for that energy to go. And our body is convinced that we are in danger, even when we are safe and sitting in a comfortable environment,” Lurie said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Fiordaliso via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Fiordaliso via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Are you feeling the effects of "national trauma"? If you're doomscrolling, the answer is likely "yes."&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This kind of trauma can show up in your body.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Witnessing a trauma — and especially repeated traumas — can tax both your physical and mental health. People commonly feel fatigued and worn down even if they haven’t done anything physically demanding, according to Lurie. Some people develop headaches, muscle tension and digestive problems. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;If your stress response remains activated, your creativity, patience and ability to focus plummet, said Jenny Shields, a clinical health psychologist at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.drjennyshields.com/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Shields Psychology &amp;amp; Consulting" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405427e4b043da371d0cc1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.drjennyshields.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Shields Psychology &amp;amp; Consulting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Mood shifts may become more common, along with irritability and sudden tears, she added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Over time, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S245195882400071X?via=ihub" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="media overload" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405427e4b043da371d0cc1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S245195882400071X?via=ihub" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;media overload&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; can lead to anxiety, depression, hopelessness, and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/full/10.1126/sciadv.aav3502" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="post-traumatic stress symptoms" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405427e4b043da371d0cc1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.science.org/doi/full/10.1126/sciadv.aav3502" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;post-traumatic stress symptoms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, including nightmares, emotional numbness and intrusive thoughts. As a result, people may avoid the news altogether or wind up constantly checking for updates. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“This can make it difficult to complete assignments at work, and relationships suffer because you’re emotionally unavailable or more reactive than usual,” Lurie said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eventually, your worldview might shift. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S245195882400071X?via=ihub" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Research" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="69405427e4b043da371d0cc1" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S245195882400071X?via=ihub" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; shows serious challenges can crush the illusion of predictability and stability, making us question our existence and purpose in life. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“People may begin to see the world as less safe or others as less trustworthy,” Shield said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are ways you can feel more in control when you’re overwhelmed by the news.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Though we can’t control world events, we can control how we respond and engage with them. If you’re watching the news and notice your heart rate or breathing rate speed up, it’s time to ground yourself. Consider doing a quick body scan (focus on how every body part, from your head to your toes, feels) or try a deep breathing exercise (inhale for four counts, hold your breath for another four, then slowly exhale for six counts). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Another trick is the 5-4-3-2-1 technique: Identify five things you can see, four you can touch, three you can hear, two you can smell, and one thing you can taste. “This brings your attention back to the present moment and helps your nervous system recognize that you’re actually safe right now,” Lurie said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Another option is to get outside and move. Walking can quiet an overactive amygdala, lower cortisol and adrenaline levels, and boost the amount of feel-good endorphins in your body, Lurie explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Next, lean on your support system. Call a friend, go out to dinner with a colleague or visit a family member. Spending time with people who feel safe can help your body settle down, Shields said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;When the world feels too overwhelming, shift your focus to the small, meaningful moments in your life. “A morning walk, evening journaling, or a familiar prayer can remind the nervous system that not everything has changed,” Shields said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Finally, set some boundaries on your news consumption. Lurie recommended picking specific times to check the news. Stick to the limits by setting a timer and only looking at one or two sources you know are reliable and trustworthy. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Constantly scrolling — and being constantly activated — will actually impair your ability to respond to the challenges in your life and community, according to Lurie. “At this moment in time, we are tasked with finding the balance between caring engagement and self-preservation, so that we can continue to find connection and find our way through this moment.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 12:00:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOYVBRU181N2Vnemcyc0dGYnNrM1VXWTd2UnM2c3lpdXVEcVJUWUx2VFRxemRCUFdaLWNxd0NMdG9vbmNRYmZfNERZaHhFSWpOTjdSN3RPbWVXNHZveVRsdXJRMGpQUU8tcnh1RDZEb3J0UzNVdlFXOGhDUjJaV1laN2J6NlBISGtQMkt1OFprRXpWQmfSAZgBQVVfeXFMT1g5aTVFcHBpM0R3ZG5uSkZMZkVfcnBiSHZDTkExVnJhRUhsaWRjSjVULWhHZTNZc0xsaEZaM01FWWlxbEp6cVNHVnhEZjNCN0w5aWhZSU5RZ1dQNlU1SlJKaVFTZXB2RWlDSWdvVUJBVHVlcU1LbTZfSF9SbUtWcGpqYXM4QXhRSk5IbzRXd25aUmFIZVRjWWM</guid></item><item><title>“即将离职”的9岁儿童将“一夜之间”变成了父母不认识的愤怒的人。然后得到令人震惊的诊断（独家） - AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/articles/outgoing-9-old-changes-overnight-103000223.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos' daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h3&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2023, Crystal Loos noticed that her daughter was acting differently — the once bubbly child became reserved and angry, pulling back from friends, school and the world&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It was utter terror, like she wasn't herself," the mother tells PEOPLE&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;After searching for answers, Loos' daughter finally got a diagnosis that changed everything&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the spring of 2023, Crystal Loos began noticing that her daughter wasn’t acting like her normal self. Her once bubbly elementary schooler seemed distracted and pulled away from school, her friends and the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Illinois mother of three tells PEOPLE that her daughter, Lacy Mae, stopped eating foods that she used to enjoy, and, at the time, Loos thought it was depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Before this, she was the happiest, funniest, most outgoing child ever. She never had any issues," Loos, 30, shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, in July 2024, there was a "complete overnight change," and the then-9-year-old was no longer “herself."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Lacy Mae was diagnosed with anxiety and depression, Loos knew deep down it was something else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They tried to put her on SSRIs, they tried to get her into a psychiatrist, psychologist, everything," she says. "But I just felt that there was something deeper going on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos' daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The night in July came, and it was like she had a psychotic break that night, and she was banging on my door. She was begging to go to the hospital," Loos continues. "She knew something was wrong, but she didn't know what, because she couldn't even explain to me what was going on. It was just like she didn't have control over her brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos describes a period of time where her young daughter wouldn't sleep, felt paranoid and constantly begged to be taken to the hospital to figure out what was wrong with her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It was utter terror, like she wasn't herself. She had dilated pupils. You looked at her, and she just wasn't the same kid, like, it was like something took over her," Loos says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although they "had gone to multiple hospitals," nearly everyone agreed that it was just depression and anxiety.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At that point, Loos’ daughter begged to be admitted to a psych ward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She's 10 years old, so that's crazy, obviously, but she just wanted her health to get fixed," Loos says. "She begged, begged, begged to be admitted. She was, at this point, suicidal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We had to sometimes hold her down because she was trying to hurt herself or us. Sometimes we would have to lock her and us in a room together so that she wouldn't. She was more of a danger to herself than us," she shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos, who was recently postpartum when Lacy Mae's health took a turn, says her parents then stepped in to help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos' daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Eventually, she did have to move in with my parents because I had a newborn baby, and then I also have a 5-year-old, and my 5-year-old was just terrified of her," she says. "He was just absolutely terrified because she was screaming. Rage is what I could describe her. She had so much rage in her.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos’ daughter refused to eat, refused to go to school, and ended up missing most of fourth grade. While many people believed the new baby could have caused Lacy Mae's personality change, Loos noted that it was much deeper than that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I'm like, ‘You guys don't get it. She was running away from home. She was trying to jump out of moving cars, like just complete psychosis.’ It was nothing like I've ever seen before. Especially as a child and in my childhood, I never had any issues before this," she shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, Lacy Mae was admitted to a behavioral health unit. During that time, Loos turned to various Facebook mom groups for support, asking if anyone else had ever experienced something similar. A few people mentioned that it could be PANS/PANDAS, so Loos got to work researching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I went to the psychiatrist at the children's hospital, and I literally begged. I was bawling at him. I said, 'She has something wrong with her. I think this is what it is: PANS /PANDAS. Can we do any further workup?' They refused to do that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/pans.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Stanford University School of Medicine;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Stanford University School of Medicine&lt;/a&gt;, Pediatric Acute-onset Neuropsychiatric Syndrome (PANS) is a clinical diagnosis for children who "have a dramatic – sometimes overnight – onset of neuropsychiatric symptoms" characterized by the sudden onset of obsessive-compulsive symptoms (OCD) or eating restrictions. They may also have symptoms of depression, behavioral regression, irritability, anxiety, sleep issues, and difficulty with schoolwork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Pediatric Autoimmune Neuropsychiatric Disorders Associated with Streptococcal Infections (PANDAS) is a subset of PANS, and has five distinct criteria for diagnosis, including "abrupt 'overnight' OCD or dramatic, disabling tics; a relapsing-remitting, episodic symptom course; young age at onset (average of 6–7 years); presence of neurologic abnormalities;" and a recent streptococcal infection, such as strep throat, peri-anal strep or scarlet fever, per the &lt;a href="https://www.pandasppn.org/what-are-pans-pandas/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PANDAS Physicains Network.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;PANDAS Physicains Network. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There isn’t an official test to diagnose PANS/PANDAS, making it hard for medical professionals to determine it as the root cause of symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, Loos took her daughter out of the psych ward and searched for a doctor who specialized in PANS/PANDAS. They eventually contacted Indiana-based specialist Dr. Antoine, and in September 2024, after in-depth blood work, Lacy Mae was officially diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was put on antibiotics and received IVIG (Intravenous Immunoglobulin) to help her immune system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Crystal Loos&lt;/p&gt; Crystal Loos and her daughter&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She had different infections in her body that were mistakenly attacking her brain. She had several different infections," Loos shares. "She had a tick-borne illness. She had mycoplasma, plasma pneumonia, and these are all things that Dr. Antoine checked for. That's how we figured out what was going on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He put her on antibiotics to kill these infections, and then he put her on antibiotics to regulate her immune system, and then the IVIG, that's also to regulate the immune system, and then different supplements just to get her immune system back to normal so that it attacks the infection rather than attacking her brain,” Loos adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slowly, treatment began to work, and by December of 2024, Loos says they started to “see her again.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Loos admits the tween "still had a lot of episodes after that,” the severity of those episodes decreased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I was having just so much anxiety through all this because I was like, I don't know what to do," she shares. "I can't even describe how bad it was. It was literally like a living hell.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lacy Mae was also put on an anti-psychotic to help calm her down, and now, just over one year after her diagnosis, Loos says the 10-year-old is "99%" herself again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She does have some setbacks and a little bit of anxiety here and there, but for the most part, ever since we found Dr. Antoine and got on the right medication, she has been thriving, and life is pretty much back to normal for the most part," Loos says. "She goes to school. She plays sports. She plays with her friends, which she hasn't done for a while. Now she's completely back to living life and enjoying life again.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos recently shared a &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@crysrenae/video/7580132165707451662" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:TikTok video;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;TikTok video&lt;/a&gt; showing the difference in her daughter to raise awareness of PANS/PANDAS. The video went viral, amassing over 45 million views.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She says that parents have since reached out to share their own stories about how their children changed seemingly without cause. She’s been able to connect them with resources and talk them through what they’re feeling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I want parents to get answers. I want them to know that this is a thing and something to look into if your child has similar symptoms. I wish I would have found it sooner, before our life got really hard with it," she tells PEOPLE. "It's really amazing, because I've gotten so many messages and people, saying the kindest things and that they've been through it, and they know how it feels, and they're so grateful that I'm spreading awareness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When we were going through this, I was really struggling because I didn't feel like I could find other parents that were dealing with this," she continues. "It’s very, very lonely, and you want to find any information you can, and there's just not a lot out there."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loos wants to educate people on PANS/PANDAS since it's a diagnosis that "is not widely known."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although I think it's honestly not a rare diagnosis. It’s more common than we think," she adds. "I think it's just often misdiagnosed as other things. I just want people to be aware of what everyone's going through when they have PANS/PANDAs.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you or someone you know is struggling with mental health challenges, emotional distress, substance use problems, or just needs to talk, call or text 988, or chat at &lt;a href="http://988lifeline.org/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:988lifeline.org;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;988lifeline.org&lt;/a&gt; 24/7.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/girl-diagnosed-with-pandas-after-extreme-behavior-changes-exclusive-11871633" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:47:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxOM1NJZ2JVRm5YX3RlWWQ4ZC1oOVFPaWVuNmVlOVQxaDRtLTJ0clRpZS1rblpXckdiUVhpTVp0dFIwNWVnQlg4WFg5N0tZQUNZRGVQNUkwcVk0aWRqTlY3MWp3eENiaWVZLXJKSzJBbS1KS1hkdThreHV2bkNnZUtRNzNB</guid></item><item><title>美国疫情激增导致德克萨斯州冬季病毒高传染性飙升- MySA</title><link>https://www.mysanantonio.com/news/local/article/outbreaks-contagious-winter-virus-texas-21234786.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>MySA</author><pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:18:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNVVAzOEFGakVzcnhLcEV5N3Y0a3ctcDBjaG9hVC1BY1Q3X01Qdy1ScGhWeVo3UTIyR3E3UVE2dHE0QUluVVQ4N2c3SURXa1M0cXN1SmdkVHJaajM3WEpxQkROd2JSajV1NThSSzRremRuS3hDZXBSUmlHUWJ1LVZ1MWwzNjdIQ1hzTlJtSXNTc1JtalBzLUJsVHZNSC0zZzZyU3c</guid></item></channel></rss>