<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>“关闭开关”的发现可以帮助我们清除常见的寄生虫- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/off-switch-discovery-could-help-clear-our-brains-of-a-common-parasite</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;There's a parasite living in the brains of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-us-still-doesnt-test-for-this-common-harmful-parasite-during-pregnancy"&gt;40 million Americans&lt;/a&gt;, and most of these human hosts are completely unaware.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors don't usually treat this bug unless it begins wreaking havoc on the bodies of patients with weakened immune systems, but a new discovery may make short work of the invader without the typical risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parasitologist Rajshekhar Gaji runs a lab at the Virginia-Maryland College of Veterinary Medicine, investigating what makes the parasite, &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toxoplasma_gondii"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Toxoplasma gondii&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, tick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cat-parasite-can-seriously-disrupt-brain-function-study-suggests"&gt;Cat Parasite Can Seriously Disrupt Brain Function, Study Suggests&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"The parasite that's sitting in the brain gets reactivated, starts multiplying, and then it's fatal," Gaji &lt;a href="https://news.vt.edu/articles/2025/10/vetmed-research-parasite.html"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt;. "Because of that, the parasite is a dreaded pathogen." &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;T. gondii &lt;/em&gt;is closely associated with cats, which are the only known hosts within which the parasite can reproduce sexually. But once its offspring are shed in the cat's poop, there are very few warm-blooded species &lt;em&gt;T. gondii&lt;/em&gt; won't make a home in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most of us, an infection with &lt;em&gt;T. gondii &lt;/em&gt;will fall &lt;span&gt;completely&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;under the radar. For those with cancer, HIV, or who are on immunosuppressants, the parasite presents significant risks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without a healthy immune system to keep &lt;em&gt;T. gondii &lt;/em&gt;at bay, these patients can quickly develop a disease known as &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Toxoplasmosis"&gt;toxoplasmosis&lt;/a&gt;, which can bring flu-like symptoms, swollen lymph nodes, and brain inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The parasite can also be transmitted to the placenta of a developing fetus during pregnancy. This form of the disease, congenital toxoplasmosis, can cause developmental problems, and even miscarriages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Treatments for acute toxoplasmosis involve medications that target mechanisms in the parasite that are biologically similar to processes in our own bodies. This often puts patients at risk of severe side effects, restricting treatments to situations where infections are considered to be dire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gaji and his team might have found a lead, though: in a new study, they&lt;span&gt; have shown that switching off just a single protein inside the microscopic parasite can kill it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protein, &lt;span&gt;TgAP2X-7, appears to be essential to the parasite's ability to invade a host, form plaques, and self-replicate. To prove this, the team genetically modified some parasites so that their TgAP2X-7 proteins function normally unless &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Auxin"&gt;auxin&lt;/a&gt; (a plant hormone that regulates growth) is added, in which case the proteins would quickly degrade. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Auxin, they established prior, had no impact on &lt;em&gt;T. gondii &lt;/em&gt;growth or plaque formation on its own, so any effect it had on the genetically modified parasites could be attributed to the fact that the TgAP2X-7 proteins had been destroyed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deprived of &lt;span&gt;TgAP2X-7, the parasites couldn't form plaques, and their ability to invade hosts (which, in this lab study, were human foreskin cells) was severely impaired. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Usually, they have a near-100 percent success rate invading these kinds of cells, but without that key protein, success dropped to below 50 percent. They also struggled to replicate.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_178106" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-178106" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/msphere.00438-25.f004-642x256.jpg" alt="Scientists Have Found The Protein Switch That Drives Widespread Brain Parasite" class="wp-image-178106 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/msphere.00438-25.f004-642x256.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/msphere.00438-25.f004-1200x478.jpg 1200w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/msphere.00438-25.f004-768x306.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/msphere.00438-25.f004-1536x612.jpg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/msphere.00438-25.f004-600x239.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/msphere.00438-25.f004.jpg 1877w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-178106" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Strains that had their TgAP2X-7 destroyed (B) were unable to propagate at the same rate as those with the protein intact (A). (Mandadi et al., &lt;em&gt;mSphere&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"These parasites completely stop growing, and they cannot survive," Gaji &lt;a href="https://news.vt.edu/articles/2025/10/vetmed-research-parasite.html"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;. "That shows this particular transcription factor is essential for the parasite to survive within the host."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Best of all, this protein bears no similarities to anything in the human body, which means there's potential to target it without harming patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"T&lt;span&gt;here is a critical need for the identification and development of novel therapeutic options to treat &lt;/span&gt;&lt;i&gt;Toxoplasma&lt;/i&gt;&lt;span&gt; infections," first author parasitologist Padmaja Mandadi and team &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1128/msphere.00438-25"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"U&lt;span&gt;nique transcription factors that regulate the expression of proteins involved in these lytic cycle events could open new opportunities for therapeutic interventions."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given that much of the damage wrought by &lt;em&gt;T. gondii &lt;/em&gt;comes from repeated cycles of cell invasion, replication, and destruction, knowing how to interrupt these cycles could lead to new ways of treating the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1128/msphere.00438-25"&gt;mSphere&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 12:02:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQLTVFWER3dGRBZkx2RUtVM3NmWHdsWEp0dVE1Tk9Md0ZtLWpuRXhkOEY3T05sWG03QldrZ2VWN0pPUnpacjZjR01PZmltaHpXWTBrMUthV2p0UW5mdXdxSzdzc0JvY2YteVVNTVc5QmNqXzl4cXZQbUVvRHpxWFV2dkxRRDlMVWFUb25GTjkxMU9paEtVd2pGcGhrMkQzZzQ</guid></item><item><title>男性正面临睾丸激素危机-这15项修复措施将增强必需激素- BikeRadar</title><link>https://www.bikeradar.com/advice/health/men-are-facing-a-testosterone-crisis-these-15-fixes-will-turbocharge-the-essential-hormone</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div _ngcontent-purplestorefront-c2920483845 class="purple-inner-container purple-content-body-inner"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Testosterone is critical for the health and athletic performance of men (and women). So it is troubling that multiple studies suggest men’s testosterone levels are tanking worldwide. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One study in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of Clinical Endocrinology &amp;amp; Metabolism&lt;/em&gt; traced a “substantial” drop in men’s testosterone levels since 1987, at a rate of 1% each year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another paper in &lt;em&gt;European Urology Focus&lt;/em&gt; found that 20% of younger men now have low testosterone levels. What is happening? And is this cause for mass male panic?  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Modern men – particularly athletes with a keen interest in physical performance – deserve an urgent hormonal health update, beginning with a clarification of why testosterone matters. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Driving growth through early life, in adulthood it supports everything from sperm production to red blood cell creation, muscle strength, bone density, memory performance and energy levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/39/2025/10/GettyImages-1124672639.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt class="wp-image-945056"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Testosterone helps red blood cell production – crucial to endurance athletes such as cyclists. &lt;span&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A worldwide drop, then, is bad news for men’s health, with studies linking it to heart problems, obesity, high cholesterol, diabetes, anaemia, osteoporosis, high blood pressure, erectile dysfunction, infertility and sleep disturbances, plus mental issues such as irritability, low energy, poor self-esteem and weak concentration. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, low testosterone is now associated with a 35-40% higher risk of premature death.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Explanations for this disturbing global decline range from the ageing population to sedentary jobs and the side-effects of drugs such as antidepressants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But almost all experts agree the drop is linked primarily to unhealthy modern lifestyles and the rise in obesity and diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The seminal European Male Ageing study found that 2.1% of men aged 40-79 suffer from medically low testosterone (low enough to require treatment), but another 20% experience sub-optimal testosterone levels (not low enough to require medical treatment, but still likely to impair their everyday health). &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And for most of those men, low testosterone was linked to existing health problems, such as obesity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It fits the narrative that worldwide we are overall less healthy than we were,” explains Dr Channa Jayasena, a specialist in reproductive endocrinology at Imperial College London. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The men with the lowest levels of testosterone tended to be the ones who are the least fit, who have obesity, who are on the most medications or who are most ill.” &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In other words, for most modern men with low testosterone, the issue is the result – not the cause – of their other health problems. “To a certain extent, you can lower your chances of low testosterone by incorporating health promotion into your life.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In medical terms, low testosterone is diagnosed through a combination of blood tests and symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A normal level ranges from around 8-10 nmol/L (nanomoles per litre) of blood to 30-31nmol/L. And symptoms include fatigue, depression, anxiety, irritability, low libido, erectile dysfunction, reduced strength, night sweats and poor memory. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Low testosterone can be caused by genetic conditions, injuries and hormonal disorders. But for most men, lifestyle factors appear to be the primary cause. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is worth noting that men do experience a natural but harmless drop in testosterone as they age, at a rate of 2-3% per year, from the age of 30 onwards. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/39/2025/10/GettyImages-2218546877.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt class="wp-image-945062"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Testosterone declines naturally (and harmlessly) with age, but early and more consequential drops need addressing. &lt;span&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the oft-cited media term ‘male menopause’ is misleading. All menstruating women experience the menopause, which involves a rapid decline in hormone levels. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most men do not suffer from low testosterone, while most age-related hormonal changes are slow and inconsequential. “You shouldn’t expect to be the same man at 80 as you were at 18,” says Dr Jayasena.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are one of the 2.1% of men who have medically low testosterone levels, help is available through the NHS in the form of testosterone injections, gels or patches. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But if you are among the 20% of modern men who have sub-optimal testosterone levels (low but not requiring medical intervention), positive lifestyle changes can help you get back on track. Here are 15 science-backed strategies to get you started.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Blast belly fat&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/39/2025/10/GettyImages-1205492768.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt class="wp-image-945078"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Belly fat increases your chances of low testosterone. &lt;span&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It appears that obesity is a major cause of low testosterone. That is because body fat contains an enzyme that converts testosterone into the female sex hormone, oestrogen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In fact, one American research paper found that every one-point increase in a man’s Body Mass Index (BMI) is associated with a 2% decrease in testosterone. Gynecomastia – the medical term for ‘man boobs’ – is one sign of this hormonal imbalance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That makes the solution pretty simple: from cutting down on saturated fats in your diet, to cranking up your fat-burning workouts, losing body fat can revitalise your testosterone levels. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A reassuring study by the Endocrine Society found that when 900 overweight men shed weight, they slashed their chances of low testosterone by 50%.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Lift dumbbells&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lifting weights will crank up your testosterone, according to a study in the Asian Journal of Sports Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multi-muscle compound movements such as squats and deadlifts are particularly effective, according to Pennsylvania State University. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And lifting heavy weights at 80-85% of your one-rep max also works well, according to the University of Connecticut.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But the good news is that any weight training will help. A study in the journal &lt;em&gt;Human Reproduction&lt;/em&gt; found that even moderate-intensity weight training elevates testosterone levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the results can be fast: a Spanish study found that men who did strength training three days a week enjoyed elevated testosterone levels after just four weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Crank up the cardio&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Routine cardiovascular exercise will elevate your hormonal health and burn off testosterone-wrecking body fat. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One Japanese study found that men who engaged in aerobic exercise for up to 90 minutes per day, three times per week, experienced a rise in testosterone after just 12 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;HIIT your hormones hard&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/39/2025/10/11-02-07CYP414_201123ss7254-scaled.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt class="wp-image-945085"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;High intensity turbo sessions are a recipe for testosterone building. &lt;span&gt;Steve Sayers/Our Media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;High-intensity interval training (HIIT), such as 10x 30-second sprints or sweaty indoor spin classes, will protect your hormones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A paper in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of Clinical Medicine&lt;/em&gt; found that three HIIT sessions a week spiked testosterone by 36% after only eight weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Follow the Mediterranean diet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite wacky claims in dark corners of the internet, there is no magic food ingredient that will boost your testosterone. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But a healthy overall diet will protect your hormonal health. A study in &lt;em&gt;Current Research In Food Science&lt;/em&gt; found that men who adopted a Mediterranean diet significantly increased their testosterone levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Focus on fruit, veg, whole grains, fish, lean meat and healthy fats such as olive oil, avocado and nuts.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Dodge inflammatory food&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/39/2025/10/GettyImages-1391487524.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt class="wp-image-945089"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Regular highly processed food is a testosterone killer. &lt;span&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Protect your testosterone by cutting down on inflammatory foods, such as processed foods, high-glycaemic-index food (such as refined carbohydrates) and saturated fat. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research in the journal &lt;em&gt;Nutrients&lt;/em&gt; linked a high consumption of pastries, desserts and takeaways with low testosterone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Eat more oily fish&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Not all fat is bad. Omega-3 fatty acids, found in salmon, mackerel and sardines, have been shown to help with testosterone synthesis. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These fatty acids support cell membranes in the testes, where testosterone is produced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Don’t get too skinny&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Endurance athletes beware: shifting excess body fat is good for your hormonal health, but turning yourself into a skeleton is not. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Testosterone is produced from cholesterol, and severe calorie restriction will impair its production. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A study by the Universities of Worcester and Warwick found a strong link between low-fat diets and low testosterone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Get some daily vitamin D&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/39/2025/10/CYP_bigride_Guernsey_-100-scaled.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt class="wp-image-945090"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Plenty of sun exposure means cyclists needn't worry about vitamin D levels. &lt;span&gt;Joseph Branston&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good news for cyclists and runners: several studies link outdoor exercise with healthy testosterone levels. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This may be because it boosts vitamin D – the ‘sunshine vitamin’ which is produced when skin is exposed to sunlight. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research in the journal&lt;em&gt; Hormone and Metabolic Research &lt;/em&gt;has linked healthy vitamin D levels to higher testosterone levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Over winter, consider using a supplement: a study in the &lt;em&gt;World Journal of Men’s Health&lt;/em&gt; linked vitamin D supplements with increased testosterone levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Zero in on zinc&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Zinc, an essential mineral found in red meat, poultry, beans, oats, eggs, nuts and grains, supports healthy testosterone production, which is why research in the journal &lt;em&gt;Nutrition&lt;/em&gt; found low zinc levels are linked to a drop in testosterone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most men can get enough zinc from a balanced diet. But consider a supplement if your diet is zinc-deficient: research suggests vegetarians and vegans are most at risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Cut back on booze&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bad news for boozers: testosterone levels can drop within just 30 minutes of consuming alcohol. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Australian research found that heavy drinking disrupts the body’s hypothalamic–pituitary–adrenal axis activity, and causes inflammation and oxidative stress, leading to a decline in testosterone. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stick to the NHS guidelines of no more than 14 units (6 pints of 4% beer) per week. But the less, the better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Eat more green leafy veg&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make your dinner plate greener. Cruciferous vegetables – such as broccoli, cabbage, cauliflower, kale and brussels sprouts – contain the phytonutrient indole-3-carbinol (I3C), which helps the body eliminate estradiol – a testosterone-damaging oestrogen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Get 7-8 hours of sleep&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Testosterone and sleep are intertwined. Most testosterone release occurs during the rapid eye movement (REM) stage. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And a lack of sleep also releases the stress hormone cortisol, which blocks testosterone production. The University of Chicago found that men who got only five hours of sleep suffered a 10-15% drop in testosterone the next day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-large"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://c02.purpledshub.com/uploads/sites/39/2025/10/CYP_PBP_JB_-34-scaled.jpg?webp=1&amp;amp;w=1200" alt class="wp-image-945094"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Clocking up big mileage means cyclists can often fall sleep any time, any place. &lt;span&gt;Joseph Branston&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Improve your sleep by sticking to a regular sleep routine: research in Andrology found that 7-8 hours per night is a healthy target for middle-aged men.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Learn to chill&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is not just a bad night’s kip that will mangle your testosterone levels: research in &lt;em&gt;Frontiers in Molecular Bioscience&lt;/em&gt; found stress also spikes the testosterone-hampering hormone cortisol.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So whether you tune into classical radio or enjoy walks in the park, allocate dedicated time each day to soothing your frazzled mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Don’t overtrain&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exercise supports hormonal health, but don’t overdo it with extreme endurance training or excessive HIIT workouts. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A study in Andrology found that recreational athletes who trained 4-5 hours per week enjoy better hormonal health than elite athletes who train 4-5 days per week. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Always bank plenty of rest days: your hormones depend on it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BikeRadar</author><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiygFBVV95cUxOX2x4TjN5ZzhlaUxUS3paQVVoR2YzeFBUQ0FWbUVuSkRFb0dzU2M2dGZwWFBiY0E4eE4tUDJabFllZEFmU25BN2Z4UlhmN0FBUThtZk9oWmxrS3VleEtadWc1YUxNRXRhVHpHeV84Y2FUZ0VaSTUtSXJKVmhlOHRuZXV2bFF5NjhrREgzT0ZjMG5Bc0VodUFfVmdBTGZPOTZocXMwdjVwTjFBTklfZWJ0MlFQWWN0X2RlTk9uY2hXR3BhZG1nRGM0UnJn</guid></item><item><title>以色列两岁儿童死于麻疹疫情-《耶路撒冷邮报》</title><link>https://www.jpost.com/health-and-wellness/article-871616</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Jerusalem Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 06:03:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTE5BbWtDeHkxcGF4eE95cWpTaEVpMHZLeHZiTFhQWUVSNlFDX0gxS2YwcjhZcVpXdmljRERGZTBMRXRTWEZGR1Jsd3BxOFlXNUtDT1YwWkV2ck42em5XcF9Wc1BQQ184UU0</guid></item><item><title>维生素K ：被遗忘的维生素，让您的骨骼强壮，心脏安全-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/vitamin-k-the-forgotten-vitamin-that-keeps-your-bones-strong-and-heart-safe/articleshow/124815991.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin K rarely makes health headlines, yet it plays a crucial role in keeping both your bones and heart strong. Beyond helping blood clot, it ensures calcium goes where it should, into your bones, not your arteries. Skipping your greens or fermented foods could quietly weaken this vital balance over time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;keyword id="29874155" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="Vitamin-K-benefits" source="keywords"&gt;Vitamin K benefits&lt;/keyword&gt;: The hidden link between blood, bones, and the heart&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people know Vitamin K as the nutrient that stops bleeding when you get a cut. But doctors say it quietly does far more; it activates proteins that help calcium bind to bones instead of sticking to artery walls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminK-HealthProfessional/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;National Institutes of Health (NIH)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, Vitamin K supports both blood clotting and calcium metabolism. Without enough of it, bones lose density while arteries harden, increasing the risk of fractures and heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Types of Vitamin K and how each supports your body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin K exists in two main forms:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="18"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin K₁ (phylloquinone): &lt;/strong&gt;Found in green leafy vegetables; supports normal blood clotting.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vitamin K₂ (menaquinones): &lt;/strong&gt;Found in dairy, eggs, meat, and fermented foods; helps move calcium into bones and teeth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Why modern diets often cause Vitamin K deficiency&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people fall short of Vitamin K not because food is scarce but because daily diets lack greens and fermented foods. Over-frying or overcooking vegetables also destroys much of the vitamin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-term antibiotic use, liver disease, or fat-absorption disorders can further lower Vitamin K levels since it is fat-soluble and requires dietary fat for absorption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Common signs and symptoms of low Vitamin K&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Severe deficiency is rare, but mild insufficiency can appear as:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="31"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Easy bruising or frequent nosebleeds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slow wound healing&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Weak bones or repeated fractures&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Early signs of arterial stiffness in older adults&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infants are especially vulnerable, which is why newborns are given a Vitamin K injection to prevent bleeding disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Best natural food sources of Vitamin K&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="38"&gt;&lt;table class="redcator-table-advance"&gt;&lt;colgroup&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;&lt;colgroup&gt;&lt;col&gt;&lt;col&gt;&lt;col&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Food&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Vitamin K (µg per 100 g)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;Type&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Spinach&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;483 µg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;K₁&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Kale&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;390 µg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;K₁&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Mustard greens (sarson saag)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;260 µg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;K₁&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Broccoli&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;140 µg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;K₁&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Curd / Yogurt&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;12 µg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;K₂&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Paneer / Cheese&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;20–25 µg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;K₂&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Natto (fermented soybeans)&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;1,000 µg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;K₂&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Egg yolk&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;30 µg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;K₂&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adding a small amount of healthy fat, such as mustard or olive oil, to salads or greens improves absorption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Daily Vitamin K requirements for adults&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your vitamin K needs vary based on age and sex. The chart below lists the average recommended daily intake in micrograms (mcg).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;table class="redcator-table-advance"&gt;&lt;colgroup&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;&lt;colgroup&gt;&lt;col&gt;&lt;col&gt;&lt;/colgroup&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Life Stage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Recommended Amount&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Birth to 6 months&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;2.0 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;7–12 months&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;2.5 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;1–3 years&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;30 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;4–8 years&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;55 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;9–13 years&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;60 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;14–18 years&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;75 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Adult men 19 years and older&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;120 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Adult women 19 years and older&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;90 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Pregnant or breastfeeding teens&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;75 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;Pregnant or breastfeeding women&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;90 mcg&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;tbody&gt;&lt;/tbody&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Source: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://ods.od.nih.gov/factsheets/VitaminK-Consumer/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;NIH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because Vitamin K is fat-soluble, deficiency develops slowly, but the body does not store much of it, so consistent intake is important.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Caution for people taking blood-thinning medication&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;People taking blood-thinning medications such as warfarin should be cautious about sudden changes in their vitamin K intake, as this vitamin directly affects how the drug works. According to &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/newsletter_article/ask-the-doctor-do-people-on-warfarin-need-to-avoid-vitamin-supplements-that-contain-vitamin-k" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Harvard Health Publishing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, the goal isn’t to avoid vitamin K-rich foods like spinach, kale, or broccoli, but to keep intake consistent so your blood's clotting level (INR) remains stable. Newer anticoagulants such as apixaban, rivaroxaban, and dabigatran don't interact with vitamin K, but anyone on warfarin should always consult their doctor before making dietary or supplement changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Vitamin K and bone health: The missing link&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin K works with Vitamin D and calcium to strengthen bones. It activates osteocalcin, a protein that helps calcium bind to bone tissue. Low Vitamin K levels reduce osteocalcin activity, weakening bones even when calcium intake is adequate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="64"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nutritionists now consider Vitamin K an essential but often missing piece of most bone-health plans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="66"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;The takeaway on Vitamin K and overall health&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin K quietly keeps two vital systems balanced: blood clotting and calcium regulation. A serving of leafy greens, a bowl of curd, or lightly cooked saag each day can meet your body’s needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of focusing only on calcium or Vitamin D, think of Vitamin K as the nutrient that directs calcium to the right place: into your bones, not your arteries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Disclaimer: This article provides general information for educational purposes and should not be considered medical advice. Please consult a qualified healthcare professional for personalised guidance.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 05:37:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxOY1IzTnVkRFhMa2Nndlc0N1E3b2ZvVFpJb3IyeVdZbW9aN3B0TzB6UnRJSFRlQVF6TFpsWjIwRFVDZkkxTmpicndUSUx1RU5LcVZMcTJXNjJycWZmTHo0VnpmX2NJT2tIT3NOY2dYWjNSbjRQWmViQklEVHhualBKd053V190M1FHbUhiUVVnUDlfOGZoYk1razNOR1F2bG0xUUlKajQwMjIwVnp6d0lxMHJENmh4eWRZQzRtc011Z0dqTm1ZTmVzWDZaWVZrc1VhY21yZjFmd0g2b043TmtlYnUyc0pld25GUDBFUy1Rd3d4RlZtNExjRExmVFlFb1I1LU04c2pn</guid></item><item><title>拥有20年经验的加利福尼亚州心脏病专家说： “你不需要切断每一种不良食物来保护你的心脏” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/california-cardiologist-with-20-years-experience-says-you-dont-need-to-cut-out-every-bad-food-to-protect-your-heart-101761446844493.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/california-cardiologist-with-20-years-experience-says-you-dont-need-to-cut-out-every-bad-food-to-protect-your-heart-101761446844493.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Supplements, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/samantha-ruth-prabhu-beauty-secrets-for-glowing-skin-at-38-revealed-lots-and-lots-of-moisturiser-no-cold-plunges-women-101749963256915.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="cold plunges"&gt;cold plunges&lt;/a&gt;, and eating whole foods have become the holy grail for anyone trying to achieve longevity or protect their heart health. However, these quick fixes are not what ensure that you will stay healthy, including your heart.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/26/550x309/bad_food_heart_health_1761448555575_1761448555736.jpg" alt="You don’t need 15 supplements, cold plunges every morning, or to cut out every ‘bad’ food to protect your heart and stay young. (Freepik )" title="You don’t need 15 supplements, cold plunges every morning, or to cut out every ‘bad’ food to protect your heart and stay young. (Freepik )"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/10/26/550x309/bad_food_heart_health_1761448555575_1761448555736.jpg" alt="You don’t need 15 supplements, cold plunges every morning, or to cut out every ‘bad’ food to protect your heart and stay young. (Freepik )" title="You don’t need 15 supplements, cold plunges every morning, or to cut out every ‘bad’ food to protect your heart and stay young. (Freepik )"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;You don’t need 15 supplements, cold plunges every morning, or to cut out every ‘bad’ food to protect your heart and stay young. (Freepik )&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/neurosurgeon-with-33-years-of-experience-shares-what-happens-in-body-when-you-fast-for-36-hours-you-burn-fat-101761361920563.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Neurosurgeon with 33 years of experience shares what happens in the body when you fast for 36 hours: ‘You burn fat…’"&gt;Neurosurgeon with 33 years of experience shares what happens in the body when you fast for 36 hours: ‘You burn fat…’&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to Dr Sanjay Bhojraj, an interventional &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-says-avoid-these-5-foods-to-reduce-heart-disease-risk-red-meat-high-sodium-diet-sweet-beverages-101761052650721.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="cardiologist"&gt;cardiologist &lt;/a&gt;from California, US, and founder of Laguna Institute of Functional Medicine, it is about recognising the signs your body is giving and finding solutions accordingly.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;‘You don’t need 15 supplements, cold plunges every morning…’&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an Instagram post shared on October 10, the cardiologist highlighted the importance of understanding one's body and identifying the root causes of health problems, rather than resorting to &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/surgeon-warns-against-vitamin-d-supplements-too-much-can-backfire-and-damage-your-arteries-101761291956952.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="supplements"&gt;supplements &lt;/a&gt;and other quick fixes mindlessly.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Sharing the post, Dr Bhojraj wrote, “Let me de-influence you as a 49-year-old doctor and functional cardiologist. You don’t need 15 supplements, cold plunges every morning, or to cut out every ‘bad’ food to protect your heart and stay young. You need to understand your body — and the root causes of why it’s slowing down, inflamed, or running on empty.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;‘Your body isn’t failing you. It’s trying to get your attention’&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cardiologist highlighted that after over 20+ years in medicine, he has seen the same story repeat itself: “High-performing people, business owners, parents, athletes — running on caffeine, stress, and convenience, until their body finally says no more.” It is because people forget to find the root cause of their problems, Dr Bhojraj stressed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Therefore, the cardiologist stressed that if you’re: &lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Always tired, even after sleep. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experiencing chest pressure, shortness of breath, or anxiety that feels ‘different’.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Foggy, inflamed, or just not feeling like yourself anymore.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using quick fixes to get through the day instead of actually healing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;He highlighted that all of these are not signs that your body is failing you; rather, it’s trying to get your attention.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The truth is, your heart health isn’t just about cholesterol or blood pressure. It’s about inflammation, hormones, gut health, sleep quality, stress response — all interconnected,” he added.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Therefore, he emphasised that it is essential to combine advanced diagnostics, personalised functional medicine, and decades of cardiology expertise to help people regain their vitality from the inside out. “Because health isn’t about doing more. It’s about doing what’s right for you,” the cardiologist said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 03:17:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgJBVV95cUxNZnAzOUd6RWhEMXIxckx3UXVJOFhLRlZBc0R4amh6cXJNeWFEWGxldDJ3bGZwa21MMTVlUUtQYkpoTmRWeFFCYnRBUkRhOHlaaXp5QWJCRldDOElhVjN1dmJ2SUR6M0MyUm9SWTFkSVdYSk1tMGZRODRCbWhuXzBoRW9NLTJhdFdoS3M5Q0ZHdkR6SWVuQWNucDY0UkRNdGdtSG5LcVdUN1NoX09pWmI2YThKNnJJU1VyZjNaN2wwWlJ3VnBTWTg3ZjgtTjFZcU9INHNQcUNteGFmd0R4WmhEdUVqX01mOW5jS2oweExPbFdmdE5SbG02QUxDSGJqMzVLNzhJSWhLSHl6Nmtyc2o5MXZn0gGXAkFVX3lxTE5waWJkeUNud1FaTURGb0ktcXJEMmthSHZKS1JrbHlxeVZlRTFOajdlbDFxcWttMmdKSmUxbFk5VnE3bE1LQm1mZHlVd1ZLd3M4bS1ORXlIZmlVUnhGajVDakRLZ0xSTkdoQnAyVE14cHlLU3IzWlNZekpUZ0M5Zlh3cnpTbDJLb3J1MXBnSTM4bVB6VDhncU1NMkJESFo4eWlZYzBaZWVmckJ4ZUotUWVMcUFmRW9VSlVYVGp3N29vNXlQZUJYTU1DN01rNTNray1Gd3owTWFYcTBNUFFWM004eUxra3VjVHM0eFpQV3hjWm45a1VLX0ZjbEktaHQyMFJnLTZwcC1yNTV2SEpSVE9ZS0QxcW1qTQ</guid></item><item><title>ADHD药物不仅能帮助你集中注意力，研究显示- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/adhd-drugs-do-much-more-than-help-you-focus-study-reveals</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;An  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-adhd" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73112" data-postid="177368" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;ADHD&lt;/a&gt; diagnosis means a person is prone to impulsivity and distractibility, which can manifest in the form of substance misuse, traffic accidents, criminality and even suicidal behavior.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study published in the &lt;em&gt;British Medical Journal&lt;/em&gt; has shown that medications like methylphenidate (brand name Ritalin) can significantly reduce these harmful outcomes in newly diagnosed patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first years after an ADHD diagnosis can be a bumpy ride, bringing a sense of validation and relief, along with new challenges in figuring out how to manage newfound neurodivergence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/common-adhd-drug-could-make-some-people-better-drivers"&gt;Common ADHD Drug Could Make Some People Better Drivers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Globally, about 5 percent of children and 2.5 percent of adults have ADHD. For many, the way their brains work means they struggle with tasks that require focus and planning, which, at the lower end, means daily stress and inconvenience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But sometimes, it's a recipe for disaster. For example, a&lt;span&gt;dults with ADHD are more at risk &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/1741-7015-10-99"&gt;road accidents&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7215254/"&gt;motor vehicle injuries&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2810131"&gt;traffic tickets, and hard braking events&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Studies have found that stimulant medications, such as Ritalin, can &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/adhd-medication-could-literally-add-years-to-some-peoples-lives"&gt;literally add years to some people's lives&lt;/a&gt;. These stimulants &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/how-do-stimulants-actually-work-to-reduce-adhd-symptoms-215801"&gt;increase the amount of key neurotransmitters&lt;/a&gt; in the brain, and improve attention, impulse control and decision-making.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study adds &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/1741-7015-10-99"&gt;further evidence&lt;/a&gt; that these drugs can tackle some of the most serious outcomes people with ADHD face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers from the &lt;span&gt;Karolinska Institute in Stockholm, Sweden led the study, drawing on data from 148,581 patients, ranging from 6 to 64-years-old, who received an ADHD diagnosis between 2007 and 2018. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients who started drug treatment (about 57 percent) within three months of diagnosis saw reduced risk across most of the serious outcomes assessed. In about 88 percent of cases, the drug they took was methylphenidate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medication reduced the risk of first-time substance misuse by 15 percent, and recurrent misuse by 25 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It reduced first-time suicidal behavior by 17 percent, and subsequent suicide attempts by 15 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First instances of criminal behavior were reduced by 13 percent, and repeat instances, by 25 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also found medication reduced the risk of first-time traffic accidents by 12 percent, and recurrent events by 16 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Oftentimes there is no information on what the risks are if you don't treat ADHD," study author and psychiatrist Samuele Cortese, from the University of Southampton, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/crr2j792drro"&gt;told journalist Philippa Roxby at the BBC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"Now we have evidence they [ADHD medications] can reduce these risks."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This research was published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1136/bmj-2024-083658"&gt;British Medical Journal&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If this story has raised concerns or you need to talk to someone, &lt;a href="http://www.suicidestop.com/call_a_hotline.html"&gt;please consult this list to find a 24/7 crisis hotline in your country, and reach out for help.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 21:01:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxQcGY4Z2pBbGtoMWJCczhDZGkyMEF6MGtCZk40QXl2bmZFRmtIcDFtYUhpTmtza3VrRzdwcjhzVzNfU05qemV2bGNLTmwzSWh1T2NSSnpocHoyU2FORnlzcmhPaHlaMk9nU084NWt4S1NtVGE1ZURSa3VVbjNCMmw0WmtLMHkyU1lrWlV1Rm9Tcw</guid></item><item><title>电视节目主持人玛丽·格鲁格（ Mari Grug ）描述了她为癌症治疗而战</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c23105yk4pdo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;I've had to battle for cancer care, says TV presenter &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC Presenter Mari Grug smiling. She is wearing a purple jumper and her short, dyed blonde hair is tied back. She is sitting on a sofa, which has light-coloured purple cushions." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;S4C presenter Mari Grug has been diagnosed with stage 4 metastatic breast cancer&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A TV presenter has described how she has had to fight for treatment and scans as she battles breast cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari Grug, 41, from Mynachlog-ddu in Pembrokeshire, was diagnosed with breast cancer in 2023 and it has spread to her liver and lymph nodes, which means it's &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://breastcancernow.org/about-breast-cancer/secondary-breast-cancer/secondary-breast-cancer-symptoms?utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=paid&amp;amp;utm_campaign=secondarysignsandsymptoms&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=23027343305&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAADn49ossrjQ1poeqndWJkvRjORShb&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAjwx-zHBhBhEiwA7Kjq62BMVrzDv8Y3KSSGiSh6533gy_d_BEDX0kCAza69l2iYar3GMcxOwhoCzQ4QAvD_BwE" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;metastatic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ahead of a documentary on S4C on Sunday, Mari, who appears on shows such as &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.s4c.cymru/en/entertainment/heno/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Heno&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.s4c.cymru/en/entertainment/prynhawn-da/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Prynhawn Da&lt;/a&gt;, called her  journey a "battle".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Hywel Dda University Health Board said it's always open to discussing treatment with patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari has had both of her breasts removed and continues to have chemotherapy treatment every three weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I thought, you hear the word cancer and they're on it, you will be treated," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Yes, I have been treated, but I have had to fight for operations and I'm still fighting now for some scans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I have had to battle and challenge, been on the phone constantly. Not everyone has the energy to ring and to hassle."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She added: "That's the main shock I've had following my diagnosis."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Mari Grug Mari Grug's family visiting her in the hospital" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Mari Grug&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Mari Grug's family have visited her during hospital stays&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari has documented her journey for a programme called 'Mari Grug: Un dydd ar y tro &lt;i id="(mari-grug:-one-day-at-a-time)" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;(Mari Grug: One day at a time)&lt;/i&gt; to raise awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As a mother to three young children she said she wanted to live for "as long as possible".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Thinking about not being here for them breaks my heart. That's what makes it difficult," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"When I was given the diagnosis that the cancer had spread, I was told 'there's not much we can do except for palliative care'. That was a blow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"But in reality, this type of care has developed so much. Perhaps the terminology needs to change, because when someone hears that word at the start, it's very upsetting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Mari Grug Mari (left) is wearing a red and white polka dot halter neck dress with a white fascinator in her blonde coloured hair, which is tied back. Her sister, Lisa, (right), is wearing a long sleeve purple dress and her short blonde hair is curled. They are both smiling in a selfie at a wedding in a barn." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Mari Grug&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Mari (left) and her sister, Lisa (right), have both been diagnosed with breast cancer&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari said her younger sister, Lisa, was diagnosed with breast cancer last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Unfortunately, Lisa was diagnosed last year. My younger sister, both of us have a faulty rad-51 gene," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's been a really difficult time for the family. But, we've been able to help each other."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said it was her "duty" to raise awareness about the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"One in two of us will get cancer. One in seven will get breast cancer," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Tinopolis / S4C Mari smiling during chemotherapy treatment. She is wearing a cold cap on her head, which is a method of scalp cooling used during chemotherapy to reduce hair loss. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Tinopolis / S4C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Mari continues to have chemotherapy treatment every three weeks&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She added: "The documentary is Mari Grug - the mother, the wife, the daughter, the sister - and obviously the presenter which is a very big part of my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"All the emotions are there, throughout the documentary, and hopefully people will appreciate that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari said she will continue to have treatment until it stops working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Hywel Dda health board's Sharon Daniel said: "We are always open to receiving feedback and to discussing a patient's treatment with them, to offer reassurance and consider alternatives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We see every one of our patients as an individual and we do our best to offer them the care they need to support them on the road to recovery."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:52:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE44OGJFbjQ3UVg3Vm13RU81NFVVbHlSOWxmWERXT0tHRnJzZjY2RnZ2MGdsMGpIVUVjV1V4czYtaHlwUncyQVBLbkNhS3o0U3lWZWVwZ045VVdXUdIBX0FVX3lxTE1NTHZpS2c2U3JIUzhpMkM0RjFfbmtCUG5lZ0lRS0pQZWU0c0VUTDJabjItcW9nSW12QW1xUWxlc2NmYTJxeDI2Zmd4RkhtdUhSaXJRalZqbmdLSzgzZzg0</guid></item><item><title>电视节目主持人玛丽·格鲁格（ Mari Grug ）描述了她为癌症治疗而战</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c23105yk4pdo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;I've had to battle for cancer care, says TV presenter &lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/a96a/live/39397c80-b0c5-11f0-a4e2-3dc7e4914bd9.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC Presenter Mari Grug smiling. She is wearing a purple jumper and her short, dyed blonde hair is tied back. She is sitting on a sofa, which has light-coloured purple cushions." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;S4C presenter Mari Grug has been diagnosed with stage 4 metastatic breast cancer&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A TV presenter has described how she has had to fight for treatment and scans as she battles breast cancer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari Grug, 41, from Mynachlog-ddu in Pembrokeshire, was diagnosed with breast cancer in 2023 and it has spread to her liver and lymph nodes, which means it's &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://breastcancernow.org/about-breast-cancer/secondary-breast-cancer/secondary-breast-cancer-symptoms?utm_source=google&amp;amp;utm_medium=paid&amp;amp;utm_campaign=secondarysignsandsymptoms&amp;amp;gad_source=1&amp;amp;gad_campaignid=23027343305&amp;amp;gbraid=0AAAAADn49ossrjQ1poeqndWJkvRjORShb&amp;amp;gclid=CjwKCAjwx-zHBhBhEiwA7Kjq62BMVrzDv8Y3KSSGiSh6533gy_d_BEDX0kCAza69l2iYar3GMcxOwhoCzQ4QAvD_BwE" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;metastatic&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ahead of a documentary on S4C on Sunday, Mari, who appears on shows such as &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.s4c.cymru/en/entertainment/heno/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Heno&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.s4c.cymru/en/entertainment/prynhawn-da/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;Prynhawn Da&lt;/a&gt;, called her  journey a "battle".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Hywel Dda University Health Board said it's always open to discussing treatment with patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari has had both of her breasts removed and continues to have chemotherapy treatment every three weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I thought, you hear the word cancer and they're on it, you will be treated," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Yes, I have been treated, but I have had to fight for operations and I'm still fighting now for some scans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I have had to battle and challenge, been on the phone constantly. Not everyone has the energy to ring and to hassle."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She added: "That's the main shock I've had following my diagnosis."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/dd63/live/6f8cb6d0-b0d9-11f0-b2a1-6f537f66f9aa.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Mari Grug Mari Grug's family visiting her in the hospital" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Mari Grug&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Mari Grug's family have visited her during hospital stays&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari has documented her journey for a programme called Mari Grug: Un dydd ar y tro &lt;i id="(mari-grug:-one-day-at-a-time)" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;(Mari Grug: One day at a time)&lt;/i&gt; to raise awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As a mother to three young children she said she wanted to live for "as long as possible".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Thinking about not being here for them breaks my heart. That's what makes it difficult," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"When I was given the diagnosis that the cancer had spread, I was told 'there's not much we can do except for palliative care'. That was a blow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"But in reality, this type of care has developed so much. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Perhaps the terminology needs to change, because when someone hears that word at the start, it's very upsetting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/c7ef/live/f1d4f010-b0c7-11f0-a624-a701f0c6125b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Mari Grug Mari (left) is wearing a red and white polka dot halter neck dress with a white fascinator in her blonde coloured hair, which is tied back. Her sister, Lisa, (right), is wearing a long sleeve purple dress and her short blonde hair is curled. They are both smiling in a selfie at a wedding in a barn." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Mari Grug&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Mari (left) and her sister, Lisa (right), have both been diagnosed with breast cancer&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari said her younger sister, Lisa, was diagnosed with breast cancer last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Unfortunately, Lisa was diagnosed last year. My younger sister, both of us have a faulty RAD51 gene," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It's been a really difficult time for the family. But, we've been able to help each other."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She said it was her "duty" to raise awareness about the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"One in two of us will get cancer. One in seven will get breast cancer," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251021-134202-667692b2c6-web-2.32.2-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/f4f0/live/2f587640-b0d3-11f0-bf5a-11e181bfe30d.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Tinopolis / S4C Mari smiling during chemotherapy treatment. She is wearing a cold cap on her head, which is a method of scalp cooling used during chemotherapy to reduce hair loss. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Tinopolis / S4C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Mari continues to have chemotherapy treatment every three weeks&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She added: "The documentary is Mari Grug - the mother, the wife, the daughter, the sister - and obviously the presenter which is a very big part of my life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"All the emotions are there, throughout the documentary, and hopefully people will appreciate that."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Mari said she will continue to have treatment until it stops working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Hywel Dda health board's Sharon Daniel said: "We are always open to receiving feedback and to discussing a patient's treatment with them, to offer reassurance and consider alternatives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We see every one of our patients as an individual and we do our best to offer them the care they need to support them on the road to recovery."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 20:52:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE44OGJFbjQ3UVg3Vm13RU81NFVVbHlSOWxmWERXT0tHRnJzZjY2RnZ2MGdsMGpIVUVjV1V4czYtaHlwUncyQVBLbkNhS3o0U3lWZWVwZ045VVdXUQ</guid></item><item><title>新的研究挑战了关于噪音如何影响多动症特征的领先理论- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/new-study-challenges-a-leading-theory-on-how-noise-affects-adhd-traits/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study challenges a leading explanation for why auditory stimulation, such as pink noise, can improve cognitive performance in people with traits of attention deficit hyperactivity disorder. The research found that both random noise and a non-random pure tone had similar effects on a brain activity measure linked to neural noise, which contradicts key assumptions of the prominent moderate brain arousal model. These findings were published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10870547251357074" target="_blank"&gt;Journal of Attention Disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, scientists have observed that listening to random auditory noise, like white or pink noise, can benefit cognitive functioning in individuals with ADHD or elevated traits of the condition. The moderate brain arousal model was proposed to explain this phenomenon. This model is built on two primary assumptions. First, it suggests that ADHD is associated with lower-than-optimal levels of internal neural noise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, it proposes that external random noise boosts this internal neural noise through a mechanism called stochastic resonance, improving the brain’s ability to process signals. However, these foundational ideas had not been sufficiently tested, particularly because most studies lacked a direct measure of neural noise or a proper non-random sound condition to isolate the effects of stochastic resonance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joske Rijmen and her colleagues at Ghent University aimed to directly test these two core assumptions of the moderate brain arousal model. They designed an experiment to measure neural noise directly while participants listened to different types of sound. The researchers wanted to see if ADHD traits were indeed linked to lower neural noise at baseline. They also sought to determine if the effects of sound on brain activity were specific to random noise, as the theory of stochastic resonance would predict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To conduct their investigation, the researchers recruited 69 neurotypical adults. Participants first completed the Adult ADHD Self-Report Scale, a questionnaire used to assess the number and frequency of symptoms associated with the condition. This allowed the scientists to examine ADHD as a spectrum of traits rather than a simple diagnostic category.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each participant then underwent a resting-state electroencephalogram, a non-invasive procedure that records the brain’s electrical activity. While their brain activity was monitored, participants sat with their eyes closed for three distinct two-minute periods: one in silence, one while listening to continuous pink noise (a random signal), and one while listening to a continuous 100 Hz pure tone (a non-random signal).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team analyzed the electroencephalogram data by focusing on a specific feature known as the aperiodic slope of the power spectral density. This measure reflects background brain activity that is not part of rhythmic brain waves and is considered a direct index of neural noise. A steeper slope in this measurement corresponds to less neural noise, while a flatter slope indicates more neural noise. By examining how this slope changed across the different sound conditions and in relation to participants’ ADHD traits, the scientists could test the predictions of the moderate brain arousal model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study’s findings presented a direct challenge to the model’s first assumption. During the silent condition, the researchers found a relationship between ADHD traits and the aperiodic slope. Individuals who reported more traits of ADHD tended to have a flatter slope. This finding suggests that they had more background neural noise, not less. The result is the opposite of what the moderate brain arousal model predicted and aligns with other recent studies that have also found evidence for increased neural noise in older children and adolescents with ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results also contradicted the model’s second assumption regarding the mechanism of stochastic resonance. When participants with elevated ADHD traits listened to pink noise, their aperiodic slope became steeper. This change signifies a reduction in their neural noise. This outcome is contrary to the model’s suggestion that random noise should increase neural noise in this group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most significantly, the researchers found that the non-random pure tone had a virtually identical effect on brain activity as the pink noise. Listening to the 100 Hz tone also led to a steeper aperiodic slope, or a decrease in neural noise, in participants with higher levels of ADHD traits. The fact that a non-random sound produced the same effect as a random sound strongly questions the idea that stochastic resonance, which requires a random signal, is the necessary mechanism behind the benefits of auditory stimulation. If stochastic resonance were the driving force, only the pink noise should have produced this effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors propose that an alternative explanation may be needed. Rather than relying on stochastic resonance, both types of sound might have a more general effect on brain arousal. This idea is more consistent with the state regulation deficit account of ADHD, which suggests that individuals with the condition have difficulty regulating their arousal levels to match situational demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to this view, any form of additional stimulation, not just random noise, could help modulate arousal to a more optimal state. The researchers also noted the puzzling observation that stimulation appeared to decrease brain arousal in individuals with higher ADHD traits. They speculate this might relate to difficulties these individuals have in achieving a truly restful state, and the continuous sound may have helped them to calm or regulate their brain activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study has some limitations that the authors acknowledge. The research was conducted with neurotypical adults who varied in their traits of ADHD, so the findings need to be replicated in a group of individuals with a formal clinical diagnosis. Another point is that the brain activity was measured during a resting state, not while participants were engaged in a cognitive task where the benefits of noise are typically observed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research should explore whether these same brain activity patterns occur during tasks that require attention and focus. Investigating these effects in a clinical sample of people with diagnosed ADHD will be an important next step to confirm these conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/10870547251357074" target="_blank"&gt;Pink Noise and a Pure Tone Both Reduce 1/f Neural Noise in Adults With Elevated ADHD Traits: A Critical Appraisal of the Moderate Brain Arousal Model&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Joske Rijmen, Mehdi Senoussi, and Jan R. Wiersema.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 18:05:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPMmtMeWVYVUxDWVhvR3pzdTVVbFNxeGZtdDZLMVRCQUhnQWtmX1VTclpCYTBQMmh6VEJxNEI4dy1TWDRqU0JkUllMQnpPdmRxLWctaVhHZTRLUzUzbFhXb1A0M1FpWEdBOHBfdGtuY2Y4Y3ZBSHQyTURKV3R5N1hiYnNpX2stWnM5cXZrNmdvSHVDUXF4RnJtZGdSNA</guid></item><item><title>根据心理学， 9种日常习惯比任何补充剂都能更好地保护您的大脑- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/z-t-9-daily-habits-that-protect-your-brain-better-than-any-supplement-according-to-psychology/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;There’s no shortage of supplements claiming to boost focus, sharpen memory, or keep your brain young.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But here’s the truth. No pill can replace what real daily habits do for your mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your brain isn’t a static organ. It’s constantly adapting, responding, and reshaping itself based on what you do, eat, think, and feel. Research in psychology shows that lifestyle choices have far greater effects on brain health than any supplement ever could.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to protect your brain long-term, start with these nine powerful habits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1) Get consistent, quality sleep&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sleep is your brain’s nightly reset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you rest, your brain clears out waste, stores memories, and repairs connections that keep your thinking sharp. Skipping rest doesn’t just make you tired. It slows down attention, weakens focus, and makes emotional regulation harder.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Studies from the &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/sleep-deprivation/health-effects" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/a&gt; show that even one night of poor sleep affects how your brain processes information. Over time, chronic sleep loss can contribute to cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, treat sleep as non-negotiable. Aim for seven to eight hours every night. Keep your room dark, avoid screens before bed, and go to sleep at the same time each evening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good sleep is free medicine for your brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2) Move your body every day&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exercise is one of the best things you can do for mental clarity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you move, your brain receives more oxygen and nutrients. Movement also releases neurochemicals that boost mood, sharpen focus, and help create new brain connections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to train like an athlete. Even &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/things-to-do/k-if-you-commit-to-these-5-weekly-activities-youll-age-better-than-95-of-your-peers/"&gt;moderate activities&lt;/a&gt; like brisk walking, yoga, or cycling help your brain perform better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Personally, I’ve found that going for a run in the morning clears mental fog faster than coffee. The rhythm of movement resets my thoughts and sets the tone for the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exercise isn’t just about muscles or fitness. It’s brain fuel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3) Feed your brain nutrients it actually needs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What you eat has a direct impact on how you think and feel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Research consistently links diet quality with &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s44220-024-00226-0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;brain health&lt;/a&gt;. The Mediterranean diet, for instance, is rich in omega-3s, antioxidants, and plant-based foods that protect brain cells from inflammation and oxidative stress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eat more foods that support long-term brain health:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leafy greens like spinach and kale&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Berries for antioxidants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nuts and seeds for healthy fats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whole grains for steady energy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legumes for protein and fiber&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As someone who eats vegan, I’ve seen how clean energy from whole foods keeps my mind focused throughout the day. Processed foods, sugar, and alcohol, on the other hand, can make your brain sluggish.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t have to overhaul your diet overnight. Just make more choices that feed your mind instead of depleting it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4) Keep learning new things&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The brain loves novelty.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Learning strengthens neural pathways and increases plasticity, which helps your mind stay flexible and creative. It doesn’t have to mean going back to school. Try reading new subjects, learning an instrument, or practicing a language.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When &lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/gen-8-signs-youre-far-more-capable-than-you-give-yourself-credit-for-according-to-psychology/"&gt;you challenge yourself&lt;/a&gt; to learn, your brain forms fresh connections. This process keeps it strong well into older age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve mentioned before that when I started diving into behavioral psychology, it completely changed how I viewed human decision-making. That mental challenge reignited my curiosity and made me realize how important lifelong learning really is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every time you learn something new, your brain literally upgrades itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5) Spend time in nature&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="alignnone size-full wp-image-65565" src="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50.png" alt="" srcset="https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50.png 1600w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-300x158.png 300w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-1024x538.png 1024w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-768x403.png 768w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-1536x806.png 1536w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-1200x630.png 1200w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-857x450.png 857w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-900x473.png 900w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-420x221.png 420w, https://vegoutmag.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/es-50-840x441.png 840w" sizes="(max-width: 1600px) 100vw, 1600px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your brain wasn’t designed to stare at screens all day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nature helps it recharge. The sounds, colors, and movement of natural environments soothe the nervous system and improve focus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers have found that even short &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0272494425002713#:~:text=A%20consistent%20body%20of%20evidence,et%20al.%2C%202015)." target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;exposure to nature&lt;/a&gt; reduces stress hormones and restores attention. Just 20 minutes outdoors can improve cognitive performance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like to grab my camera and head to the nearest park when I need a reset. Observing light, trees, and patterns in nature always brings me back to the present moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need a mountain trail to get the benefits. A walk around your block or sitting under a tree works just fine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6) Practice mindfulness or meditation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A wandering mind is an anxious mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mindfulness trains your brain to stay in the present, reducing stress and increasing clarity. Regular meditation strengthens the prefrontal cortex, which handles focus, decision-making, and self-awareness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need to meditate for hours. Even five to ten minutes of quiet breathing or paying full attention to what you’re doing can make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you find traditional meditation difficult, try mindful walking, cooking, or simply taking a pause before responding to something stressful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Calm attention is one of the most powerful habits for long-term brain health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7) Nurture real social connections&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Human beings are wired for connection.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strong relationships don’t just make you happier; they protect your brain. &lt;a href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2017/04/over-nearly-80-years-harvard-study-has-been-showing-how-to-live-a-healthy-and-happy-life/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Research from Harvard’s&lt;/a&gt; long-term adult development study shows that meaningful social ties are one of the strongest predictors of both happiness and cognitive longevity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Loneliness, on the other hand, has been linked to memory loss and depression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Make time for friends, family, or even small daily interactions with neighbors or coworkers. The conversations you have, the laughter you share, and the empathy you give all stimulate your brain’s social and emotional circuits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I make a point to call a friend or grab coffee with someone at least once a week. It’s not about networking or small talk. It’s about staying human.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your brain thrives when it feels connected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8) Manage your stress&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Stress is unavoidable, but chronic stress is harmful to your brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long-term exposure to cortisol, the body’s stress hormone, can damage neurons in the hippocampus, which is responsible for memory and learning.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/gen-the-art-of-staying-calm-7-habits-of-people-who-never-lose-their-cool/"&gt;Managing stress&lt;/a&gt; doesn’t mean eliminating challenges. It means giving your brain space to recover.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Try breathwork, physical activity, time outdoors, or any routine that helps you slow down. I like to end my evenings by putting my phone away, having tea, and reading a few pages of a good book. It tells my brain it’s time to wind down.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Balance is what keeps your brain resilient.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;9) Get comfortable with boredom&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In a world full of constant stimulation, boredom has become rare. Yet it’s one of the healthiest states for creativity and problem-solving.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When your brain isn’t flooded with information, it activates what neuroscientists call the “&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/topics/neuroscience/default-mode-network" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;default mode network&lt;/a&gt;,” which helps you process experiences and form new insights.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some of your best ideas come when you stop trying to have them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So resist the urge to reach for your phone every time you feel restless. Sit in silence. Let your mind wander.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Boredom gives your brain space to connect dots you didn’t even know were there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You don’t need supplements to protect your brain. You need consistency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These nine habits might sound simple, but they work because they align with how your brain naturally thrives. Sleep, movement, learning, calmness, and connection — these are what keep your mind strong for life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you care for your brain daily, you’ll notice the difference not just in how well you think, but in how fully you live.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take it one day at a time, and your brain will thank you for decades to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-3593601358"&gt;&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What’s Your Plant-Powered Archetype?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ever wonder what your everyday habits say about your deeper purpose—and how they ripple out to impact the planet?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This 90-second quiz reveals the plant-powered role you’re here to play, and the tiny shift that makes it even more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;12 fun questions. Instant results. Surprisingly accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 17:03:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxPT3F4b3E1WjBhMGRkd0EyWlBtZnRpQWRTSXItdWwxcnRRLXJWbzFmLUhIYmdGUDdnMlEyOEczVFZNTDRudlZRM1VBVEtXLUhNMWdfODdkYjhxSDE0aVRWT3lLU1FTQWRUY3JZX2tPdmxvN0xBLW5sQTFLSnFEYzgyRV9KdnJCT2ZqSUJRYk5TTXFrOEFWZnIyOE5XZTJSaXlZeURSWGwtVm1NdVBCcHZyLVBpb2NuX3psWXNyVWg0ZmE5ai15</guid></item><item><title>关于难以发现的快速上升的乳腺癌形式的须知- GhanaWeb</title><link>https://www.ghanaweb.com/GhanaHomePage/NewsArchive/What-to-know-about-a-rapidly-rising-form-of-breast-cancer-that-s-hard-to-detect-2006662</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-left"&gt;
&lt;p class="article-image"&gt;&lt;a href="What-to-know-about-a-rapidly-rising-form-of-breast-cancer-that-s-hard-to-detect-2006662?gallery=1"&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.ghanaweb.com/imagelib/pics/195/19572610.295.jpg" alt="File photo of breast cancer awareness" title="File photo of breast cancer awareness"&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="image_caption"&gt;&lt;span&gt;File photo of breast cancer awareness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="article-content-area"&gt;&lt;p id="article-123"&gt;Rates of one type of breast cancer — invasive lobular carcinoma — have been rising in the United States more than three times faster than those of all other breast cancers combined over the past decade, according to a new study.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
This elusive breast cancer that’s hard to spot in routine mammograms is behind more than 1 in 10 cases nationwide.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
The research, published in Cancer, the journal of the American Cancer Society, analyzed national data from 2012 to 2021 and found that rates of invasive lobular carcinoma increased by about 2.8% each year, while rates of all other breast cancer rose by about 0.8% a year.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
What exactly is invasive lobular carcinoma, and how common is it? How is it diagnosed, and why can it be more difficult to find during screenings? Who is most at risk? What are the treatment options? And what should women know about reducing their risk of developing this and other types of breast cancer?&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
To help us with these questions, I spoke with CNN wellness medical expert Dr. Leana Wen, an emergency physician and adjunct associate professor at the George Washington University. Wen previously served as Baltimore’s health commissioner.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: What is invasive lobular carcinoma, and how common is it?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Dr Leana Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Invasive lobular carcinoma, also known as ILC or lobular breast cancer, is a type of breast cancer that begins in the milk-producing glands of the breast, called lobules, and then spreads into nearby tissue. These malignant tumors are often hormone receptor-positive, meaning the cancer cells grow in response to estrogen or progesterone.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
ILC is the second most common type of breast cancer, after invasive ductal carcinoma, and accounts for 10% to 15% of all new breast cancer diagnoses, according to the National Cancer Institute. About 47,500 ILC cases are diagnosed in the US each year, and more women are diagnosed with it than with brain, kidney, liver, pancreatic or ovarian cancer.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: Why is ILC often more difficult to find with routine mammograms?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: This type of tumor tends to grow in a way that doesn’t change the breast’s structure as much as other cancers. Instead of forming a defined mass, the cancer cells spread through the tissue in thin strands that appear more like normal breast tissue on imaging. Because of this, mammograms may show only subtle changes, or sometimes none at all. Women may also be less likely to feel a distinct lump during a breast self-exam, which can delay detection.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: What other imaging is used to diagnose ILC?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: A breast ultrasound can help spot areas of thickened tissue that don’t show up on a mammogram, and a breast MRI provides a more detailed view that can reveal cancers hidden in dense breast tissue.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
These tests aren’t routinely recommended for everyone. Mammography remains the standard screening tool for most women. But those at higher risk, including women with dense breasts and those with a strong family history of breast cancer or known genetic mutations, may be advised to have an ultrasound or MRI in addition to regular mammograms.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: What does this study show in terms of the rise of cases and who is most at risk?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Researchers found that ILC has been increasing across every racial and ethnic group, but the steepest rise was seen among Asian American and Pacific Islander women, whose incidence grew by about 4.4% each year in the study period. Age is also a risk factor, as women 65 and older are more likely to be diagnosed with ILC than with invasive ductal carcinoma. About 70% of new ILC cases were diagnosed in women 60 and older; the median age of diagnosis is 66.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: How do the study authors explain the rise especially in this type of breast cancer?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Several factors may be driving this greater increase. Because ILC is strongly linked to hormones, changes in hormone exposure over time could be part of the reason. Rising rates of obesity and alcohol use, along with changes in childbearing and menopause patterns, may also contribute to the steady increase.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Improvement in diagnosis and greater awareness of ILC may be leading to more accurate identification. Some lobular cancers may have been misclassified as ductal cancers in the past, so part of the rise may reflect better recognition. In addition, more women are living longer after menopause, which can increase the likelihood of developing ILC compared with other types of breast cancer.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: What are the treatment options for ILC?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Treatment is similar to that for other breast cancers. Surgery to remove the tumor, followed by radiation, is common, as is hormonal therapy, since most tumors grow in response to estrogen or progesterone. Chemotherapy may be used in some cases. For advanced disease, newer targeted drugs combined with hormonal therapy can help slow progression and improve outcomes. However, ILC may have greater resistance to treatment, especially in more advanced disease, and tends to carry a poorer prognosis once it has spread.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;CNN: How can women reduce their risk of developing ILC and other types of breast cancer?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Wen&lt;/b&gt;: Some risk factors can’t be changed, such as age or family history, but many lifestyle choices can make a difference. Quitting smoking, limiting alcohol, maintaining a healthy weight and staying physically active all help lower the risk of breast cancer. Eating a balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables and whole grains supports overall health and may reduce inflammation linked to cancer.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Regular screening and knowing what’s normal for your breasts are key for early detection. Talk with your doctor about your risk factors and decide together when you should begin screening and whether you need tests in addition to a mammogram.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Finally, pay attention to changes in your breasts, such as thickening, swelling, nipple discharge, different colors or new areas of fullness, and seek medical evaluation as soon as something looks or feels different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GhanaWeb</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:37:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxQYldXWlJuZ0J5SlhfSnRIckVvUE5IRU1SbHprQjZoaWJFMXZMeEJ1bmNySlZua3N3V3ZYZW1rN0RIQkVYM3dmbk1zaWNDMXRZMFdLTkpPVTFqdW4zbHR4VWlrRVhLV0VIU29XTWZ2d0dMbWJUUUVpbWktUm51WU5jeUl0dnUtU1c1Ny1GbFFGekRrWWxvaXE3dGVhWEV2b1Z6RDJDUXdRMDh5aTZEQXJsNzdUeThJX3F6dGM2bEFQelFYSHFqOFlPd0RReGNfQjVNR1ZyZg</guid></item><item><title>科学家们刚刚发现了白发与癌症之间令人惊讶的联系-科学日报</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251025084553.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Throughout life, our cells are continually exposed to both internal and external influences that can harm DNA. This DNA damage is a well-known factor in the development of aging and cancer, yet scientists have long struggled to understand the exact link -- especially how DNA-damaged stem cells affect tissue health over time.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Melanocyte stem cells (McSCs) are specialized cells that give rise to melanocytes, the pigment-producing cells responsible for the color of our hair and skin. In mammals, these stem cells are found in a region of the hair follicle known as the bulge-sub-bulge area. Here, they exist as immature melanoblasts, ensuring that hair and skin maintain their color through repeated cycles of regeneration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discovering How DNA Damage Drives Hair Graying&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Published online on October 6, 2025, in &lt;em&gt;Nature Cell Biology&lt;/em&gt;, a study led by Professor Emi Nishimura and Assistant Professor Yasuaki Mohri at The University of Tokyo explored how McSCs react to different types of DNA damage. Using long-term lineage tracing and gene expression profiling in mice, the researchers discovered that when McSCs experience DNA double-strand breaks, they undergo a process known as senescence-coupled differentiation (seno-differentiation). In this state, the stem cells permanently mature and are eventually lost, which leads to hair turning gray. The process is controlled by the activation of the p53-p21 signaling pathway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When McSCs are exposed to certain carcinogens, including 7,12-dimethylbenz(a)anthracene or ultraviolet B radiation, they do not follow the same protective path. Even with DNA damage present, these cells avoid seno-differentiation and continue to renew themselves. They expand clonally instead, aided by KIT ligand signals released from surrounding tissue and the epidermis. These niche-derived signals block the protective differentiation response, pushing the stem cells toward a cancer-prone state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opposing Cellular Fates: Graying or Cancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Nishimura, "These findings reveal that the same stem cell population can follow antagonistic fates -- exhaustion or expansion -- depending on the type of stress and microenvironmental signals." She adds, "It reframes hair graying and melanoma not as unrelated events, but as divergent outcomes of stem cell stress responses."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers emphasize that their findings do not imply that developing gray hair prevents cancer. Instead, seno-differentiation appears to serve as a stress-triggered defense mechanism that removes damaged stem cells before they can become harmful. When this safeguard fails or is bypassed, those damaged cells can survive and potentially lead to melanoma.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Linking Aging, Cancer, and Cellular Self-Destruction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By uncovering the molecular pathways that determine whether stem cells undergo protective exhaustion or dangerous expansion, this study connects the biology of tissue aging with cancer formation. It also highlights the value of naturally removing compromised stem cells through "senolysis," a biological process that helps prevent cancer by sacrificing cells that could otherwise become malignant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;E.K.N. is supported by a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (S) (25H00439), an AMED CREST Project (JP22gm1710003-JP25gm1710003), an AMED Project for Elucidating and Controlling Mechanisms of Ageing and Longevity (JP17gm5010002-JP21gm5010002), an AMED SCARDA Japan Initiative for World-leading Vaccine Research and Development Centers (JP223fa627001), a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (A) (20H00532), and a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research on Innovative Areas 'Stem Cell Aging and Disease' (26115003), International Joint Research Projects Selected for FY 2025 (No: K25-1185).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yasuaki Mohri is supported by a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Young Scientists (18K15114) and a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (C) (25K10315).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Jun Seita is supported by an AMED Project for Elucidating and Controlling Mechanisms of Ageing and Longevity (JP19gm5010003, JP20gm5010003) and a JSPS Grant-in-Aid for Scientific Research (C) (18K08377).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Science Daily</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:29:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBta2lUcHdtOW5CVjR5QjZkamY0a0w3T2VCWnlsWGxJNnYtY09wMkp5MGtOOUMtSlJ3ZGZxMkFnSFJBR0JUc0RYaktqNllNUGE5ZDZVV0ZFeGM0c1RsV3B3ejZSY01JaUhVeFJsQnhvYw</guid></item><item><title>科学家们启动了$ 1420万的项目来绘制人体的“隐藏的第六感” -科学日报</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/10/251025084616.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;How does your brain know when to take a breath, stabilize your blood pressure, or fight off an infection? The answer lies in interoception, a lesser-known process through which the nervous system constantly monitors the body's internal signals to keep essential functions running.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, a collaborative team from Scripps Research and the Allen Institute has received the National Institutes of Health (NIH) Director's Transformative Research Award to develop the first comprehensive atlas of this internal sensory system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A Major Investment in Brain-Body Research&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leading the project is Nobel Prize-winning neuroscientist Ardem Patapoutian, joined by Li Ye, the N. Paul Whittier Chair in Chemistry and Chemical Biology at Scripps Research, and Bosiljka Tasic, Director of Molecular Genetics at the Allen Institute. Xin Jin, Associate Professor at Scripps Research, will serve as co-investigator, directing the genomic and cell-type identification work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The NIH has awarded the team $14.2 million over five years to carry out this ambitious project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"My team is honored that the NIH is supporting the kind of collaborative science needed to study such a complex system," says Patapoutian, the Presidential Endowed Chair in Neurobiology at Scripps Research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Patapoutian, who shared the 2021 Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine for his discovery of cellular sensors that detect touch, will now apply his expertise to understanding interoception.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We hope our results will help other scientists ask new questions about how internal organs and the nervous system stay in sync," adds Ye. Like Patapoutian, he's also a Howard Hughes Medical Institute Investigator.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Established in 2009, the Transformative Research Award funds groundbreaking interdisciplinary projects that push beyond traditional scientific boundaries. It is part of the NIH Common Fund's High-Risk, High-Reward Research Program, designed to support innovative ideas that could reshape our understanding of human health but might otherwise struggle to receive funding through conventional mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Makes Interoception Unique&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike the classic senses -- such as smell, sight, and hearing -- which rely on specialized sensory organs that detect stimuli from the outside world, interoception involves a vast network of neurons that sense what's happening inside the body. These neural circuits track critical processes including circulation, digestion, and immune activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because interoceptive signals originate deep within the body and are often processed unconsciously, scientists often describe this system as our "hidden sixth sense."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite its fundamental role, interoception has received little scientific attention. The signals it produces are complex, overlapping, and difficult to measure. The sensory neurons that carry them are distributed throughout organs such as the heart, lungs, stomach, and kidneys, making them hard to isolate and map precisely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mapping the Brain-Body Connection&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the NIH's support, the Scripps and Allen Institute researchers plan to map how sensory neurons connect with a wide variety of internal organs, including the heart and gastrointestinal tract. Their goal is to create a detailed anatomical and molecular atlas that reveals how these neural pathways are organized.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To achieve this, one part of the project will label sensory neurons and use whole-body imaging to trace their routes from the spinal cord to different organs, producing a high-resolution 3D map. The second part will use genetic profiling to distinguish between different cell types, such as neurons that send signals from the gut, bladder, or fat tissue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, these datasets will form the first standardized reference for understanding the body's internal sensory wiring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Interoception Matters for Health&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By decoding how interoception works, scientists hope to uncover key principles of brain-body communication that could lead to new treatments for disease. Disruptions in these internal sensory pathways have been linked to a range of conditions, including autoimmune disorders, chronic pain, neurodegenerative diseases, and high blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Interoception is fundamental to nearly every aspect of health, but it remains a largely unexplored frontier of neuroscience," says Jin, who's a Howard Hughes Medical Institute Freeman Hrabowski Scholar. "By creating the first atlas of this system, we aim to lay the foundation for better understanding how the brain keeps the body in balance, how that balance can be disrupted in disease and how we might restore it."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Science Daily</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:19:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE5oc3FwbzBQSUJBQXlCLVBncGFsakpuY3VyODhIWXBtUEpZT3p0VDVfVXRVZElRRy1MSDhQNUttYU5CX25GS05iZXpGbnVnUXNiUk9KVTZETTU1QU05SWNPSWVER3A4OVR0QVhhWWNFdw</guid></item><item><title>得益于斯坦福新技术SFGATE ，这些患者恢复了视力</title><link>https://www.sfgate.com/bayarea/article/patients-get-vision-stanford-tech-21116556.php</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="rel"&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:-mx40 lg:-mx56 x100vw sm:cw-80 lg:cw-112 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0 ruduv2y"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prototype glasses have a camera attached. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Science Corporation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://med.stanford.edu/profiles/daniel-palanker" data-link="native" class=""&gt;Daniel Palanker&lt;/a&gt;, a professor of ophthalmology at Stanford University, first envisioned a way to reverse blindness two decades ago — and this week, he finally shared the successful invention with the world. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;With new wireless chips implanted behind their eyes and high-tech glasses, around 30 people with advanced age-related macular degeneration — a &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/conditions-and-diseases/agerelated-macular-degeneration-amd" data-link="native" class=""&gt;common&lt;/a&gt; eye disease — have regained their ability to read again. The device is the first of its kind to bring back functional sight, albeit blurry and only black and white, to patients with this type of incurable vision loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="A300" data-large-id="Inline-1" data-unit="hnp-sfgate.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Palanker and his international colleagues &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2501396" data-link="native" class=""&gt;published the results&lt;/a&gt; from their clinical trial on Oct. 20 in the New England Journal of Medicine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We were surprised that patients could see so well — that was unpredictable,” Palanker told SFGATE. “Until this implant, people tried retinal prosthetics many times, resulting in just light perception but not form vision.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:mx0 x100vw sm:x100 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0 ruduv2y"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A scientist examines the prototype glasses in the lab. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Science Corporation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The advanced form of macular degeneration, called geographic atrophy, causes people to lose sight over time. It’s most commonly found in &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/geographic-atrophy/symptoms-causes/syc-20582973" data-link="native" class=""&gt;people over 60&lt;/a&gt; and can cause irreversible blindness, affecting over &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa2501396" data-link="native" class=""&gt;5 million people&lt;/a&gt; worldwide — and an &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11695844/#:~:text=BACKGROUND%3A,in%20at%20least%201%20eye." data-link="native" class=""&gt;estimated 1 million&lt;/a&gt; in the U.S. The condition destroys photoreceptor cells in the retina, the neural tissue in the back of the eye responsible for transforming light into electrical signals for the brain. Many people keep their peripheral vision, though they often become &lt;a href="https://afb.org/blindness-and-low-vision/eye-conditions/low-vision-and-legal-blindness-terms-and-descriptions" data-link="native" class=""&gt;legally blind&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="md:pt16 md:sy16 md:bb md:bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class="vh y0 mb0 md:vv md:y100 md:mb16"&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="NTV7ARD" data-large-id="Inline-2" data-unit="hnp-sfgate.com/article_dtc" class="lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new device has two parts that talk to each other: an implanted chip and special glasses. The glasses — a prototype which Palanker admits is a “little awkward-looking” —  have an attached camera that captures images and then projects them, via infrared light, to the chip. Meanwhile, the 2-by-2-millimeter chip — implanted into the patients’ damaged retinas — converts those images into electrical stimulation, restoring sight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:mx0 x100vw sm:x100 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0 ruduv2y"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared to a household key, the chip pales in size. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Science Corporation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were 32 participants who completed the clinical trial — all older than 60 and with sight worse than &lt;a href="https://www.nvisioncenters.com/improve-eyesight/20-100-vision-and-up/" data-link="native" class=""&gt;20/320&lt;/a&gt; in at least one eye. Once they had the new technology, some could make out patterns immediately, while it took others months of training before their sight improved. A year after receiving the device, the vast majority — 27 people — had regained the ability to read, though they could only see a few letters at a time. With their artificial retinas, some could read with 20/42. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nineteen trial participants experienced side effects, such as pressure, tears and bleeding — though most of these issues resolved within two months. Two-thirds of the participants reported medium to high user satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="Inline-1" data-large-id="Inline-3" data-unit="hnp-sfgate.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px pb16 aic lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sheila Irvine, who is registered blind at age 70, expressed her joy at being able to read and do crosswords again to &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/c0qpz39jpj7o" data-link="native" class=""&gt;the BBC&lt;/a&gt;: “It’s beautiful, wonderful. It gives me such pleasure.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is certainly an important development,” said Dr. &lt;a href="https://ophthalmology.ucsf.edu/jacque-duncan-md/" data-link="native" class=""&gt;Jacque Duncan&lt;/a&gt;, a distinguished professor of ophthalmology and the department chair at UC San Francisco, who was not involved in this research. &lt;strong&gt;“&lt;/strong&gt;There are existing treatments to try and prevent vision loss — but once vision has been lost, there aren’t really any treatments to bring vision back for people with this disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists hope to make the new technology available outside of the lab. Science Corp., based in Alameda, recently bought the assets of Pixium Vision SA, which originally developed the device before going out of business. Science Corp. has submitted the paperwork necessary to sell the device in Europe. Palanker is also exploring a pathway to bring it to the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="Inline-2" data-large-id="Inline-4" data-unit="hnp-sfgate.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px pb16 aic lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh250px lg:pb16 lg:aic"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:mx0 x100vw sm:x100 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0 ruduv2y"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an up-close view of the implant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Science Corporation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Palanker is not finished inventing, however. He is developing software that could enable patients to see not only black and white but also shades of gray — a key aspect of face recognition. He’s also working on the next generation of chips that would enable higher resolution vision, getting people closer to 20/20, and a pair with sleeker glasses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There was huge excitement and relief, since I didn’t know what to expect until the clinical trial,” Palanker said. “I’m very happy to see that the results were consistent, with almost all patients having a very similar performance. It wasn’t a one-off.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn top"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SFGATE</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 15:09:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxQa1ZKRVFrXzEzVHlKWnQ3Q0UxMGtsLWdLTWFuZVkxbEJjSXUybVNzZVdILVVQOFoycUppSVVyQ2FJZE1SRnl3VVRyLV9pMTRTOTNwOHJQTFlBMEJMUFZvYThLTUVtbFh3MGRBcHo0aG1ScXRweTdpNGd1SXk0b1Z4Z3JWLVlMT2FEUEVScDhn</guid></item><item><title>5种有助于强化肝脏并改善其功能的日常食物-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/5-everyday-foods-that-can-help-strengthen-the-liver-and-improve-its-function/photostory/124803832.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our liver is the largest internal organ of the body, that performs as many as 500 essential functions! Yes, that is right. These include filtering blood, processing nutrients, producing bile, regulating blood clotting, and detoxifying the body, apart from many others. Sometimes, the liver becomes weak and sluggish, resulting in many conditions. These could occur due to poor lifestyle, alcohol, accidents, or others. Hence, it is important to take care of our liver, and here are 5 everyday foods, that do just that, backed by &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7780776/"&gt;science&lt;/a&gt;. Take a look...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi9gFBVV95cUxQVmdYWTBXWmZMazdsV3hQRVBuUGVLLThPYzRRM2JwU2VqNmRNa2NTX1BLbTRxY2lqd2NnMU1KVFotclRUdUl6T2YyakVlcVdRQzQ4NFBFbU5oYzFncUNQc0NhZ1FxazlHRnc5dWYwMTVTc3BtZnRJc2lYc0FuUFRpM2NkX1BWcTA0R2tRa0pPWDRQOHBtWHRvOC1XWGdRQWpJMU42QTN0MnBoZ1R5bWFzOERvVUxuOU1FTlRiSVFGUGFybGxHWUIxbWI4emhLRGNHZ2xSUGhnWnRYaU1mT1FpdFVxOFp0N1lKSlhxcEVhckdSQ3M2N1HSAf4BQVVfeXFMTzFYbUJqRklGZEFWd20zNXg3djZQTE1fZy1jaWtvMHpZX0VOTlJjdTlIekFhUnJGcHpoMWdVYV8zeFpJMkM3ckdsZmYyY0RsUXdmaTRveTV6ZFdsV2UtRVZCYU8xNzVfaG5SR2VrZE15Mi1rUXk0MlZFbkg5QWRkVkxzdlp6TXd0bTVuYVdIejdZWlhncHJyVXRsNnV4blRDU1VwSTc3U2NlRW91cnhManhhNW54cUFQZnNZOE9ncDVISEZRRVNZclVxUzlPZWZsQm5PZEI1Ym5FeTVDd0lFOVRDdjlPR2EwWGwyWU0tSjY2LUNSSFk0WWdieVA1Mnc</guid></item><item><title>每个女性在11月都需要的一种维生素- sofeminine.co.uk</title><link>https://www.sofeminine.co.uk/the-one-vitamin-every-woman-needs-more-of-in-november/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content clear" itemprop="text"&gt;

		
		&lt;p&gt;Grey mornings steal the colour from the sky, coats get heavier, and energy seems to drain faster than the daylight. Colds circle like gossip, nails snap, moods dip, and sleep feels less restorative than it should. There’s a quiet culprit behind so many November slumps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The bus heater fogs the windows as a woman in a wool scarf taps her Oyster card and stares at the faint sun, a pale coin behind the cloud. In the office, she eats porridge by a screen that glows brighter than the day outside, then walks home under street lamps that flicker before five. Small aches, a steady tiredness, a sense that coffee does less than it used to. The clocks didn’t just shift time; they shifted her body’s chemistry, one missing light signal at a time. It’s the sunshine you can’t see.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874125"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The invisible gap November brings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Call it what it is: **vitamin D** is the thing many women are running short on in November. The sun sits low and the angle means UVB barely reaches you at all in the UK. Winter coats cover skin, commutes happen in the dark, and lunch breaks are swallowed by rain. Your bones, muscles, immune cells and even mood circuitry use this nutrient like a language. When it fades, life feels heavier than it should.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take Priya, 34, who works in an NHS scheduling office in Lewisham. By mid-November she was skipping her evening Pilates because her legs felt leaden and her motivation fell off a cliff. Her GP, familiar with that seasonal pattern, suggested a blood test and a simple daily supplement. She felt steadier by January. In the background, the UK’s own data echoes her story: roughly one in five people have low vitamin D levels in winter and spring, with higher risk if you have darker skin or keep most of your skin covered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874126"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a clean logic to it. The north-of-50-degrees latitude means the sun’s UVB is too weak from roughly October to March for most people to make vitamin D in skin. Food helps, but not much: oily fish, egg yolks and fortified milks offer only small amounts, and vegetarian choices are slimmer still. Melanin reduces vitamin D synthesis, city living limits daylight, and desk jobs do the rest. The body tries to coast on summer stores, then—bang—November arrives and the tank runs low.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="The #1 Vitamin Every Woman Needs for Hormonal Balance (Backed by Science!)" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/oQWQRotp2ss?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874128"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How to top up without turning your life upside down&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The simplest play is boring, which is why it works: take **10 micrograms (400 IU)** of vitamin D daily through autumn and winter. That’s the UK guidance for adults, including women who are pregnant or breastfeeding. Put the bottle next to the kettle or toothbrush and swallow it with your main meal, as fat helps absorption. If you prefer plant-based, look for D3 from lichen; it’s vegan and widely available. Tiny habit, big return.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s be honest: nobody really does that every day. The trick is to lower the friction. Buy a three-month supply in one go. Set a phone reminder for the time you naturally pause, like after lunch. If you regularly forget, a weekly dose can be discussed with your GP or pharmacist. Don’t chase mega-doses on your own, and don’t exceed the UK’s safe upper limit of 100 micrograms (4,000 IU) a day. If you have kidney issues, take certain medications, or have a health condition affecting calcium, ask your clinician for personalised advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874129"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food still counts, but think of it as a nudge, not the fix. A tin of sardines on toast, mushrooms exposed to UV light, fortified yoghurt or plant milks slipped into porridge. Your plate can support what the sky won’t. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“November is when vitamin D goes quiet in Britain,” says a London-based dietitian. “A small, consistent supplement bridges that silence for bone, immune and mood support.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pick D3 where you can; vegan D3 exists and works well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Anchor the tablet to a daily cue: kettle, keys, or toothbrush.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eat oily fish once or twice a week if you enjoy it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for “fortified with vitamin D” on milks and cereals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you cover most skin or have darker skin, speak to your GP about year-round needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What this means for your November&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’ve all had that moment when the early dark feels like it’s winning. The good news is you can change the odds with a habit so small it barely dents your day. Think of vitamin D as a winter foundation—quiet, unflashy, stabilising—so your energy, focus, and sense of steadiness don’t rely on rare blue skies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It won’t fix everything. It can shift the background, the slow hum your body runs on as you stack work, family, and the life you’d still like to live when the sun clocks off at four. If you share a house, make it a household ritual, like tapping the lights off at night or topping the fruit bowl. One tiny pill, the same time, each day. In the gloom of November, that kind of predictability feels like a small act of resistance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Point clé&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Détail&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Intérêt pour le lecteur&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Vitamin D drops in November&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;UK sunlight is too weak for skin synthesis&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Explains why energy and resilience feel lower&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Daily 10 µg works&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Matches national guidance for adults&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Clear, low-effort action to take now&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Food supports, doesn’t replace&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Oily fish, fortified milks, UV mushrooms&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Easy tweaks that stack with a supplement&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;FAQ :&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Can I get enough vitamin D from the sun in November in the UK?&lt;/strong&gt;Not realistically. The sun’s UVB angle is too low for most of the UK, even at midday. Short outdoor time is still great for mood and movement, but it won’t cover vitamin D.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should I choose D2 or D3?&lt;/strong&gt;D3 tends to raise and maintain blood levels more effectively. Vegan D3 from lichen is widely available if you avoid animal products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the safest dose to take daily?&lt;/strong&gt;For most adults, **10 micrograms (400 IU)** daily through autumn and winter is advised in the UK. Don’t exceed 100 micrograms (4,000 IU) a day unless your clinician recommends it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How soon might I feel a difference?&lt;/strong&gt;Some people notice steadier energy within a few weeks, while others simply avoid the slow slide they felt in past winters. The body is topping up a low reservoir, which takes time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What if I’m pregnant, breastfeeding, or have a health condition?&lt;/strong&gt;Stick with 10 micrograms daily unless your midwife or doctor advises otherwise. If you have kidney problems, sarcoidosis, high calcium, or take certain medicines, get personalised guidance first.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874130"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

		
		
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>sofeminine.co.uk</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:15:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQNFZ3SHBmakVjYUJlaHkyX0FxVzZGSnBxMUZnZFp4RS1jUGRmOFJfRFdKVTV4ak9tVjRSam5rZVhlOVN4aHFtdGVqZTc2OHhEekl4N3dSRnRxZ2lvNDY3eWlSWWJUdWVRQ18xcG8wend2b3VLYjJFN2g2bXMtU19na2JDYWdxdDFlSHJV</guid></item><item><title>这些真菌生活在您的体内，它们可能会影响您的健康- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/these-fungi-live-inside-you-and-they-may-affect-your-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The "gut microbiome" has become a popular health term in recent years. It's easy to see why, with an abundance of research showing how important the trillions of microbes living in our gut are for health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what many people might not realize is that the microbiome doesn't only contain bacteria. It also contains other types of microbes – including fungi. The fungal component of the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/gut-microbiome-1624"&gt;microbiome&lt;/a&gt; is called the "mycobiome".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the mycobiome has been &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fped.2020.572538"&gt;less well studied&lt;/a&gt; than its bacterial counterpart, recent research shows it's &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-025-56743-8"&gt;sensitive to diet&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2666-5247(22)00203-8"&gt;may affect our health&lt;/a&gt;, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/we-contain-a-variety-of-microbiomes-heres-a-look-at-a-few-of-the-most-important"&gt;We Contain a Variety of Microbiomes. Here's a Look at a Few of The Most Important.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_178405" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-178405" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/CandidaFungiSEM.jpg" alt="single-celled fungus that is commonly found on the skin and the mucous membranes of the mouth, digestive and respiratory tracts, and the vagina, where it is usually harmless" class="size-full wp-image-178405" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/CandidaFungiSEM.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/CandidaFungiSEM-600x351.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-178405" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; is infamous for causing thrush when the bacteria that usually keeps it in check is out of balance. (Science Photo Library/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best studied mycobiome is the one in our &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2024.04.043"&gt;intestines&lt;/a&gt;. It's composed of many fungal species. The &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/19490976.2024.2399360"&gt;most common fungal species&lt;/a&gt; found there, particularly in the Western world, belong to the &lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK560624/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; family&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; are a type of yeast. For most of us, the &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; population in our mycobiome is kept in check by our &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26053625/"&gt;immune system and our gut bacteria&lt;/a&gt;. But changes to either of these can cause &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/21505594.2016.1247140"&gt;populations of &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to expand in the mycobiome. This can be a problem, because &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; may cause &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41577-022-00826-w"&gt;life-threatening infections&lt;/a&gt; in people with damaged immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For example, research found that hospital patients who are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1097/ccm.0000000000000746"&gt;given antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; are more likely to develop &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is partly explained by the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.mib.2011.07.015"&gt;effect of antibiotics&lt;/a&gt;, which kill off certain species of gut bacteria that compete with &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; for space and resources within the intestine. Antibiotics have also been found to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.chom.2022.04.013"&gt;directly alter our immune cells&lt;/a&gt; and how they fight fungal infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another study, which analyzed the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41591-019-0709-7"&gt;mycobiome of cancer patients&lt;/a&gt;, found that those who developed serious &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; infections had an overgrowth of the fungus in their mycobiome just before the infection started. Combined with the damaging effects of chemotherapy on the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00210-023-02781-2"&gt;immune system&lt;/a&gt;, this made it harder for patients to fight off the infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disruption in the mycobiome's &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; balance has also been linked to several other diseases. For instance, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1128/mBio.01361-14"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; levels are high&lt;/a&gt; in patients who are critically ill. This suggests that too much Candida in our guts is a sign of poor health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changes in the fungal mycobiome have also been linked to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/17562848211047130"&gt;several gut diseases&lt;/a&gt;, including inflammatory bowel disease. Research on &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-022-04502-w"&gt;Crohn's disease&lt;/a&gt; has also shown that patients have an overgrowth of &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt;. These fungi also produce toxins that irritate the gut lining, which could potentially explain some of the symptoms Crohn's patients experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High levels of &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; in the gut can activate immune cells as well, making them more inflammatory. This has been seen in patients with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41590-023-01637-4"&gt;severe COVID-19&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Mycobiomes in the body&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mycobiome isn't only found in our gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also have a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/21505594.2016.1249093"&gt;skin mycobiome&lt;/a&gt;. In fact, the skin &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/nature12171"&gt;between our toes&lt;/a&gt; contains a more diverse number of fungal species than any other skin mycobiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/37703811/"&gt;skin mycobiome&lt;/a&gt; is mostly dominated by a fungus called &lt;em&gt;Malassezia&lt;/em&gt;. This yeast has adapted to grow on the skin's surface.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Malassezia&lt;/em&gt; can &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/21505594.2016.1249093"&gt;activate the immune cells&lt;/a&gt; that reside between the skin's layers. This may lead to inflammation linked to &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jaad.2008.07.058"&gt;skin disorders&lt;/a&gt;, such as psoriasis and eczema.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_178397" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-178397" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/IllustrationOfPsoriasisExcessiveSkinCellGrowthFormingPlaques.jpg" alt="illustration of excessive skin cell growth in psoriasis forming plaques" class="wp-image-178397 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/IllustrationOfPsoriasisExcessiveSkinCellGrowthFormingPlaques.jpg 727w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/IllustrationOfPsoriasisExcessiveSkinCellGrowthFormingPlaques-642x424.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/IllustrationOfPsoriasisExcessiveSkinCellGrowthFormingPlaques-600x396.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 727px) 100vw, 727px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-178397" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Psoriasis is a skin condition where excessive growth of skin cells can lead to itchy, scaly, thickened patches (plaques) of skin which may become infected. (Nemes Laszlo/Science Photo Library/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Candida auris&lt;/em&gt; is also a cause for concern. This fungus is &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2666-5247(23)00114-3"&gt;resistant to many antifungal drugs&lt;/a&gt;, which is why it can be a problem if it grows on the skin's surface. In a hospital or emergency room, this could be dangerous – particularly to patients who have immune system problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women also have a mycobiome within the vagina. Its balance with the bacterial communities living there can be a big determinant for vaginal health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/s1473-3099(18)30103-8"&gt;most common fungal infections&lt;/a&gt; globally is vaginal candidiasis (thrush). It can &lt;a href="https://www.nhs.uk/pregnancy/related-conditions/common-symptoms/thrush"&gt;cause symptoms&lt;/a&gt; such as intense itching, pain and swelling. Many adult women will experience at least one thrush infection in their lifetime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The source of thrush is another fungus from the Candida family: &lt;em&gt;Candida albicans&lt;/em&gt;. This is a common member of the vaginal mycobiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.1002611107"&gt;vagina's microbiome&lt;/a&gt; is normally dominated by the bacteria &lt;em&gt;Lactobacillus&lt;/em&gt; which help keep &lt;em&gt;Candida&lt;/em&gt; populations in check. But if the balance between bacteria and fungi gets disrupted (for example, by antibiotics), the fungus can &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s12934-020-01464-4"&gt;overgrow or produce inflammatory molecules&lt;/a&gt; within the vagina. This inflammatory response is responsible for common thrush symptoms such as redness and itching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probiotics may help to restore the balance between fungi and bacteria to prevent vaginal yeast infections – although this has had &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/femsre/fuaf013"&gt;limited success so far&lt;/a&gt;. Some &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1126/scitranslmed.adi3363"&gt;new treatments&lt;/a&gt; that target inflammation-causing fungal molecules have shown promise in animal models and in small numbers of women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's good evidence to suggest we might also have a mycobiome in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/s2213-2600(18)30510-1"&gt;lungs&lt;/a&gt; and in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.fgb.2019.03.008"&gt;breastmilk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Controversially, some have even suggested that we may have small numbers of fungal cells in the brain – and these fungal cells may be linked with neurodegenerative disorders such as &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.7150/ijbs.42257"&gt;Parkinsons&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/srep15015"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fnagi.2018.00159"&gt;Autopsy studies&lt;/a&gt; have found evidence of fungi in the brains of people who died from brain disorders – but this doesn't prove the fungi caused their illness or that it was there during their life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell-reports/pdf/S2211-1247(23)01252-4.pdf"&gt;Experimental studies in mice&lt;/a&gt; have also shown that small numbers of fungal cells can survive in the brain for long periods of time – and the presence of these fungal cells was linked with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41467-018-07991-4"&gt;reduced memory function&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pbio.3003020"&gt;Experiments in flies&lt;/a&gt; have also shown fungi may travel to the brain and affect function. This is the best evidence we currently have showing small numbers of fungi may get into the brain and survive long-term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether this occurs in people, and if this would be considered a true mycobiome, remains to be proven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There's still much we don't know about the mycobiome. But with continued research in this area we may soon better understand the mycobiome's importance in our health and how we can nurture and care for it.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/264545/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/rebecca-a-drummond-1344962"&gt;Rebecca A. Drummond&lt;/a&gt;, Professor, Immunology and Immunotherapy, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-birmingham-1138"&gt;University of Birmingham&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/the-fungi-living-in-the-body-play-an-important-role-in-health-heres-what-you-should-know-about-the-mycobiome-264545"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:02:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxPVERqeHVXanhpWm5xakZybmR3TWxCVWh6UlBlWEk4LVFMajFlWVpfdVJRLXNQOU9Lamt3OUUwYW9mQ1dmMkIyY3ZaV0ZBZjA5TkJMSmFCeUZCcDFFMERPTm9acUlENlV5aGZhczh3ZVQ2bng0bTF1ZE96SHllWlFVclp3S0NEMlZNU2J0a1FndENWZw</guid></item><item><title>全球调查显示，正常BMI中隐藏的肥胖导致代谢紊乱- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-global-survey-reveals-obesity-hidden.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
									    
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/weight-management.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/weight-management.jpg" data-sub-html="Credit: Unsplash/CC0 Public Domain"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/weight-management.jpg" alt="weight management" title="Credit: Unsplash/CC0 Public Domain"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                Credit: Unsplash/CC0 Public Domain
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;A multinational team of researchers has discovered that over 20% of adults with a normal BMI range experience levels of abdominal obesity that puts them at higher risk of hypertension, diabetes, high total cholesterol, and elevated triglycerides.&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                        
                                          
                                         
										

                                                                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;Cardiometabolic disorders rank among the leading causes of death and disability worldwide. Over the past three decades, cardiovascular disease cases rose from 271 million to 523 million, with disability-adjusted life-years nearly doubling.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abdominal obesity, especially &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/visceral+fat/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;visceral fat&lt;/a&gt;, disrupts &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/metabolic+processes/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;metabolic processes&lt;/a&gt; via inflammatory pathways that contribute to &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/insulin+resistance/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;insulin resistance&lt;/a&gt;, dyslipidemia, &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/high+blood+pressure/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;, and impaired glucose regulation. Diabetes affected an estimated 828 million adults in 2022.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BMI often fails to capture actual fat distribution, and studies have reported greater cardiovascular risk and mortality among individuals with normal BMI but higher waist circumference.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the study, "Cardiometabolic Outcomes Among Adults With Abdominal Obesity and Normal Body Mass Index," &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamanetworkopen/fullarticle/2840296" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;i&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/i&gt;, researchers used a cross-sectional design to investigate the global prevalence of normal-weight &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/abdominal+obesity/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;abdominal obesity&lt;/a&gt; and its association with cardiometabolic outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                        
    &lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
          
        
        &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7099578867"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                                                                                                                                &lt;p&gt;Data came from the World Health Organization Stepwise Approach to Surveillance of Noncommunicable Disease Risk Factors (WHO STEPS) surveys in 91 countries between 2000 and 2020, including 471,228 participants aged 15 to 69 years across Africa, the Americas, the Eastern Mediterranean, Europe, Southeast Asia, and the Western Pacific.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abdominal obesity was defined as high waist circumference (≥80 cm in women; ≥94 cm in men). Normal-weight abdominal obesity combines normal BMI (18.5–24.9) with high waist circumference. The main outcomes were hypertension, diabetes, high total cholesterol, and high triglycerides. Measurements were via standardized interviews, physical body measures, and biochemistry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across the global dataset, abdominal obesity was associated with several behavioral and metabolic factors. Individuals with larger waist circumferences were more likely to report low fruit and vegetable intake (odds ratio [OR] 1.22) and physical inactivity (OR 1.60). Clinically, those with abdominal obesity but a normal body mass index showed higher odds of hypertension (OR 1.29), diabetes (OR 1.81), high total cholesterol (OR 1.39), and high triglycerides (OR 1.56).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Intriguingly, higher education trended toward higher odds of the presence of abdominal obesity, with &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/primary+education/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;primary education&lt;/a&gt; (OR 1.53) and secondary or higher education (OR 2.38) raising the risk compared with no formal schooling. Africa was the lone exception with secondary and &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/higher+education/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;higher education&lt;/a&gt; associated with lower odds (OR 0.64).&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                            &lt;p&gt;Across the pooled sample, 21.7% of participants with normal BMI had abdominal obesity, ranging from 15.3% in the Western Pacific region to 32.6% in the Eastern Mediterranean region. Lebanon showed the highest country-level prevalence at 58.4%, and Mozambique the lowest at 6.9%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adults with a normal BMI but enlarged waist circumference faced higher odds of adverse metabolic conditions compared with peers of normal BMI without abdominal obesity. Hypertension, diabetes, high total cholesterol (OR 1.39), and high triglycerides showed globally significant increases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few regional exceptions were discovered as high total cholesterol was not observed in the Americas, high triglycerides were not found in Europe and hypertension did not rise in the Western Pacific.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The authors conclude that relying solely on BMI may be insufficient to identify high-risk individuals with normal-weight abdominal obesity.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                    
                                        											&lt;div class="article-main__support"&gt;
												    &lt;p&gt;
    Written for you by our author &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/editorial-team/#authors" target="_blank"&gt;Justin Jackson&lt;/a&gt;, edited by &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/editorial-team/" target="_blank"&gt;Gaby Clark&lt;/a&gt;, and fact-checked and reviewed by &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/help/editorial-team/" target="_blank"&gt;Robert Egan&lt;/a&gt;—this article is the result of careful human work. We rely on readers like you to keep independent science journalism alive.
    If this reporting matters to you,
    please consider a &lt;a href="https://sciencex.com/donate/?utm_source=story&amp;amp;utm_medium=story&amp;amp;utm_campaign=story"&gt;donation&lt;/a&gt; (especially monthly).
    You'll get an &lt;b&gt;ad-free&lt;/b&gt; account as a thank-you.
    &lt;/p&gt;

											&lt;/div&gt;
										                                        
                                        											&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
												                                                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
                                                    Kedir Y. Ahmed et al, Cardiometabolic Outcomes Among Adults With Abdominal Obesity and Normal Body Mass Index, &lt;i&gt;JAMA Network Open&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2025.37942" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2025.37942&lt;/a&gt;
																								
																								&lt;/p&gt;
																							&lt;/div&gt;
                                        											
										                                                                                    &lt;p class="article-main__note mt-4"&gt;
                                                © 2025 Science X Network
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                
                                        
                                        &lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
                                                 &lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
                                                 Global survey reveals obesity hidden in normal BMI contributing to metabolic disorders (2025, October 25)
                                                 retrieved 26 October 2025
                                                 from https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-global-survey-reveals-obesity-hidden.html
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
                                            This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
                                            part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 14:00:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwFBVV95cUxNdkYxLTVnYmhaNV9KV3h4U2trRkZDQkM3X2cta2x4NHVvenVIVmtQc3Y4Wkl4bW9jcTM0RnVzTUo2cTNkLTlvWEFoYngxMlhCVUY2TnVyZjJBem4zaXFYQWp5aEJlc0dlYUlUd21BZHVzbUNoZ05QTE1rbFJzb1FrNGdnVUNmZUk</guid></item><item><title>霍乱正在迅速蔓延，但它可以被阻止。我们为什么不把它写进历史？ --《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/oct/25/cholera-global-spread-vaccine-production-africa-zambia</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The last outbreak of cholera in Britain was in 1866; in the United States there has not been an outbreak since 1911.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;And yet today people are sick with this ancient disease in &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/publications/m/item/multi-country-outbreak-of-cholera--external-situation-report--30--26-september-2025" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;32 countries&lt;/a&gt;, with more than 6,800 deaths reported so far this year –already exceeding all of last year’s toll of &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/12-09-2025-cholera-kills-more-people-for-second-consecutive-year-while-prevention-and-treatment-available" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;6,000 deaths, which was itself a 50% increase on 2023&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The most severe outbreaks are in Africa, where conflict is accelerating the spread and hampering control efforts in some countries. &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/cholera" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Cholera&lt;/a&gt; is the definitive disease of deprivation. It persists not for lack of science or solutions, but because leaders have failed to act with the urgency and commitment the crisis demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A consortium of more than 50 partners, led by the World Health Organization (WHO), is responding to these outbreaks through the &lt;a href="https://www.gtfcc.org/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Global Task Force on Cholera Control&lt;/a&gt;– a partnership established in 1992 to enable access to essential supplies, as well as work on the detection, prevention and treatment of cholera and set global priorities to sustainably control the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Complementing the work of the taskforce, in August the WHO and the &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/africa" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Africa&lt;/a&gt; Centres for Disease Control and Prevention launched a continental cholera emergency response plan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="8b6c02be-b19e-4970-9fc8-43b3873fb026" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-47fhrn"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":5,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Sudan cholera outbreak kills 40 in a week as health centres overwhelmed","elementId":"8b6c02be-b19e-4970-9fc8-43b3873fb026","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/global-development/2025/aug/14/sudan-cholera-outbreak-water-health-medecins-sans-frontieres-msf-war-refugees"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":8,"display":0,"theme":1}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Cholera is caused by a bacterium ingested in food or water contaminated with faeces from an infected person, and the only way to prevent it is by ensuring access to safe water and sanitation. This is why it is now practically unheard of in countries with those facilities, but thrives in communities afflicted by inequality, poverty, conflict, displacement and climate-related disasters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The disease can be prevented with effective vaccines. An injectable vaccine was first developed in the late 19th century, and was superseded by oral vaccines in the 1980s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;But because the disease afflicts almost exclusively the poorest countries and communities, the vaccine does not attract investment from developers, for whom it offers little market opportunity. There is currently only one manufacturer producing cholera vaccines at the scale needed for mass vaccination campaigns: EUBiologics, based in South Korea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To manage cholera outbreaks, the WHO and other partners established a global &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/groups/icg/cholera/stockpiles" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;cholera vaccine stockpile&lt;/a&gt; for outbreaks in 2013 under the International Coordinating Group on Vaccine Provision (ICG) to ensure rapid, equitable and effective access to vaccines in emergencies, especially in low-resource settings. Since then, the stockpile has distributed almost 255m doses of vaccine to 34 countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Almost 75% of those doses have been distributed since 2021, in response to the global resurgence of cholera. So far this year, the stockpile has disbursed more than 49m vaccine doses – already eclipsing the previous record for a single year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Given the increasing frequency and severity of outbreaks, vaccines from the stockpile can only be used to bring outbreaks under control, rather than to conduct preventive campaigns in areas at risk of cholera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The stockpile is replenished every week but production cannot keep up with demand, and it is regularly below the &lt;a href="https://www.gavi.org/vaccineswork/everything-you-need-know-about-global-emergency-vaccine-stockpiles" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recommended threshold&lt;/a&gt; of having 5m doses ready to respond to outbreaks at any time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To stretch supplies further, the ICG suspended the standard two-dose vaccination regimen in 2022 in favour of a single dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="#EmailSignup-skip-link-14" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;skip past newsletter promotion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;aside aria-label="newsletter promotion" class="dcr-av5vqf"&gt;&lt;div class="dcr-10et71f"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-rsfwa"&gt;Sign up to &lt;span&gt;Global Dispatch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-1xjndtj"&gt;Get a different world view with a roundup of the best news, features and pictures, curated by our global development team&lt;/p&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SecureSignup" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"newsletterId":"global-dispatch","successDescription":"Get a different world view with a roundup of the best news, features and pictures, curated by our global development team"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;span class="dcr-1eusqlu"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Notice: &lt;/strong&gt;Newsletters may contain information about charities, online ads, and content funded by outside parties. If you do not have an account, we will create a guest account for you on &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;theguardian.com&lt;/a&gt; to send you this newsletter. You can complete full registration at any time. For more information about how we use your data see our &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://www.theguardian.com/help/privacy-policy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt;. We use Google reCaptcha to protect our website and the Google &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/privacy" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="https://policies.google.com/terms" rel="noreferrer" class="dcr-1rjy2q9"&gt;Terms of Service&lt;/a&gt; apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p id="EmailSignup-skip-link-14" tabindex="0" aria-label="after newsletter promotion" role="note" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;after newsletter promotion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;This was based on evidence showing that a single dose provides protection, but it wanes faster than it would with a two-dose regimen. Single-dose vaccination is only therefore a temporary solution to scarce supplies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Demand shows no sign of abating, meaning supply must increase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In October 2024, &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/zambia" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Zambia&lt;/a&gt; signed a memorandum of understanding with China’s Jijia Medical Technology Company to establish a cholera vaccine-production facility in Lusaka. The planned production will still require rigorous quality assurance and clinical trials to confirm safety and efficacy before any locally manufactured doses can be approved by the WHO and deployed in mass vaccination campaigns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While expanding vaccine production in Africa is essential for preventing and responding to outbreaks of this historical disease, the only long-term solution is for governments to invest in safe drinking water and sanitation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There are some diseases that cannot be completely prevented, such as Alzheimer’s and most cancers. But cholera is not one of them – it can be stopped. Cholera persists because poverty, inequality, conflict and displacement persist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Stopping it is therefore not a scientific, medical or technical challenge; fundamentally, it’s a political one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:38:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxQNDZVMmVrdS1LWkNudG1oSkZNTTFibjBjcUM1VlYtbVloOTN0RU5iR242QzRyTi04ZHA0aHByYjNWWEhQT1pELTZBOS16QUNiZHRVbENBZ2JlQXRQeHdjb1dZM0Y3RXZBNDRHdkdMSExUSkEwV0FCQ1NSenR5NjUyNVJvZEpNb2oyN0VLeVlvSHhPMFRLZE11clRySnhtN1V4ZWdELVBDWU9nbElVaG5QZnMtRQ</guid></item><item><title>在刷牙之前或之后，您应该用牙线清洁牙齿吗？牙医揭示正确的技术- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/floss-teeth-brush-them-dentists-103200640.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;div class="no-margin"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Should You Floss Your Teeth Before You Brush?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;PeopleImages - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;i&gt;"Hearst Magazines and Yahoo may earn commission or revenue on some items through these links."&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You know you should brush teeth twice and floss once a day at a minimum to keep your teeth clean and breath fresh. But it turns out those two things may make a difference in both the cleanliness of your mouth and the health of your whole body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In addition to protecting your smile, maintaining excellent oral hygiene contributes to better overall health,” says &lt;a href="https://www.aae.org/patients/directory/people/steven-j-katz/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Steven J. Katz, DDS, MS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Steven J. Katz, DDS, MS&lt;/a&gt;, the president of the American Association of Endodontists. &lt;strong&gt;“&lt;a href="https://www.amjmed.com/article/S0002-9343(23)00755-6/fulltext" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research has shown;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Research has shown&lt;/a&gt; that people who take care of their teeth and gums also enjoy a lower risk of cardiovascular disease, improved control of diabetes, and even &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pcd/issues/2025/25_0083.htm" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:better cognitive health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;better cognitive health&lt;/a&gt; as they age.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To ensure you’re taking the best possible care of your teeth so you can reap those potential health benefits, you may want to rethink your dental care routine. We reached out to two dentists to find out if it makes a difference whether you brush your teeth first and floss after, or floss first and brush after. Apparently it does!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why do we need to floss our teeth?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Flossing entails sticking something thin (usually a special string) between your teeth and moving it around to help dislodge any matter that shouldn’t be there, which supports the health of our entire mouth. “Flossing is a simple yet crucial step in maintaining oral health, as it removes debris and plaque from areas your toothbrush can’t reach,” says &lt;a href="https://go.redirectingat.com?id=74968X1596630&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.aspendental.com%2Fproviders%2Fashley-boling%2F1265743710%2F&amp;amp;sref=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.goodhousekeeping.com%2Fhealth%2Fwellness%2Fa69000438%2Fshould-you-floss-your-teeth-before-or-after-you-brush%2F" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Ashley Boling, DDS/DMD;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Ashley Boling, DDS/DMD&lt;/a&gt;, a dentist and the owner of an Aspen Dental practice in Hixon, Tennessee. “This &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7375740/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reduces the risk;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;reduces the risk&lt;/a&gt; of cavities, gum disease and other dental issues.” As noted above, those dental problems can also put you at risk for additional whole-body health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should you floss before or after brushing your teeth?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It might sound counterintuitive to put floss between teeth that you know are still dirty, but &lt;strong&gt;it’s best to floss first and brush second.&lt;/strong&gt; “Flossing first removes food particles and plaque from between the teeth — areas that a toothbrush simply can’t reach,” says Katz. &lt;strong&gt;“Clearing out those spaces not only reduces the risk of cavities and gum disease, but also allows the fluoride in your toothpaste to reach more surfaces of your teeth.&lt;/strong&gt; That means &lt;a href="https://www.ada.org/resources/community-initiatives/fluoride-in-water/fluoridation-faqs" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:stronger enamel;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;stronger enamel&lt;/a&gt;, healthier gums, and better protection against decay.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boling agrees. “You can floss before or after brushing as long as you are doing it thoroughly and are reaching areas that your toothbrush can’t,” she says. &lt;strong&gt;“Flossing beforehand, however, can help dislodge food particles and plaque, making brushing more effective.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When is the best time of day to floss?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best time to floss your teeth is the time that you will stick to every day. “For many people, &lt;strong&gt;the easiest habit is to floss at night before brushing and right before bed,” says Katz. “That way, you go to sleep with a clean, healthy mouth.&lt;/strong&gt; Once flossing becomes part of your nightly routine, you’ll quickly notice that it feels incomplete when you skip it — almost like forgetting to wash your face or lock the door.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the best flossing tool?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I find &lt;strong&gt;traditional string floss to be the most effective for scraping plaque from beneath the gumline, but tools like floss picks and water flossers are great alternatives,&lt;/strong&gt; especially for those with dexterity challenges or braces,” says Boling. “The key is consistency — the best flossing tool is the one you’ll use regularly!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Pro 1000 Rechargeable Electric Toothbrush&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B003UKM9CO?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C10055.a.69000438%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$39.94 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$39.94 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;4100 Power Toothbrush&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B09LD7WRVS?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C10055.a.69000438%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$39.99 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$39.99 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;9900 Prestige Rechargeable Electric Power Toothbrush with SenseIQ&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure align-caption-with-image"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="link rapid-noclick-resp athena-button" href="https://www.amazon.com/dp/B08YCVJKXV?tag=syn-yahoo-20&amp;amp;ascsubtag=%5Bartid%7C10055.a.69000438%5Bsrc%7Cyahoo-us" data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized" rel="sponsored" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:$349.99 at amazon.com;elm:affiliate_link;elmt:premonetized;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;$349.99 at amazon.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bottom line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Consistent brushing and flossing, combined with regular dental visits, are the best way to maintain strong oral health and avoid complex dental procedures,” says Katz. If you want to make the most of your dental routine, &lt;strong&gt;it’s smart to floss your teeth before you clean them with a toothbrush so as much debris is removed as possible.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:13:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE9PM1laZUxZT0hsWGRVMG1CbE5oZldtdWNNTmNoSURnYUdvYVNmbXhHSW02TWd2TnJSdlFVUEItMm1OaVJRUlYxU0JuWXg1SnVpaTlJMGpSODVabzFVSEFtSjNUYlVFSXJ0bFlVWGRTR09OYUNJ</guid></item><item><title>房客专栏|发霉的食物与癌症和神经损伤等严重健康问题有关-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/10/25/mold-toxins-old-food-health-risks/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FGLST642LNAMFIKSK65AKORAVE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When you open your refrigerator and find a wedge of cheese flecked with green mold or a package of chicken that smells faintly sour, it can be tempting to gamble with your stomach rather than waste food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:01:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNQmFRV2hpWFVBWGRtQVBKVWdzV0p5YlFaRW1ndXRPS05vdWx0WjdCSnphdzhHdkE3cUdOcWRsbXczOGZMZ2szVGx2T0lvNXN5Xy13aGJqWktzdzBXdDlMSjBVTzJ0VVFfbk9yZ1AtaFV6M2dxc09YeXEyV3Npb3loSnlVRzdBZThOUVZjWjVB</guid></item><item><title>人民药店：每天服用阿司匹林可以帮助预防结肠癌吗？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://www.oregonlive.com/advice/2025/10/peoples-pharmacy-can-taking-aspirin-daily-help-keep-colon-cancer-at-bay.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BWVOY24CQBDELDXQ6NXPISPPEE"&gt;Q. My father died of colon cancer back in 1999. His brother and sister both died of colon cancer too, so this is a big concern in our family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="SH5V53MGWNHDNLVNYVBGWXHVRY"&gt;After my father died, I read up on things that might possibly reduce this disease. Aspirin was one, so for 15 years, I took coated aspirin every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5E4SU4O3F5GVXDXOG6OUU6R7KE"&gt;This past spring, I was admitted to a hospital because I needed a number of tests. One was a colonoscopy. Naturally, the doctors who heard about my family history of colon cancer expected the worst. We were all surprised by the results. My colon had no cancer or even any polyps. I believe that taking aspirin for years might have protected me from this disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WSSY54KIQ5GMLEZEBKP557AWTM"&gt;A. A study published in the New England Journal of Medicine (Dec. 5, 1991) concluded that “Regular aspirin use at low doses may reduce the risk of fatal colon cancer.” A new study from Sweden confirms that aspirin may help prevent colorectal cancer in people with a genetic susceptibility (New England Journal of Medicine, Sept. 18, 2025). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HFLLKLJTVBARTK56BXRB6ZPRPY"&gt;Anyone who plans to take aspirin on a regular basis needs medical supervision. Even low doses can sometimes cause complications such as stomach irritation, bleeding or drug interactions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AW27S6DSHFCL3LRTWJSJCAN7NU"&gt;Q. Do you have more details about the use of testosterone replacement in men? My understanding is that a relatively recent large-scale study showed that men using testosterone replacement therapy did not have more cardiovascular risks. That has long been the concern of the medical community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PBUUUVZPLJFLRKOHWWZ24X3DEE"&gt;A. Earlier this year, the Food and Drug Administration revised the required labeling for testosterone products prescribed for men with low hormone levels. The agency said drug companies should remove the Boxed Warning about adverse cardiovascular outcomes from their testosterone labels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="FAJ5RTRNFZAORMHODH5BS7M3IA"&gt;This is based on the outcomes of the TRAVERSE study (New England Journal of Medicine, June 16, 2023). It showed no difference between testosterone and placebo when it came to risks of heart attacks, strokes or stents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV6MCHOH2VEWXPLJQLBNMTAT4M"&gt;&lt;i&gt;In their column, Joe and Teresa Graedon answer letters from readers. Write to them in care of King Features, 628 Virginia Drive, Orlando, FL 32803, or email them via their website: www.PeoplesPharmacy.com. Their newest book is “Top Screwups Doctors Make and How to Avoid Them.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxPVGxhTzZEOVhqRTJOZlRoUURXOTJ3Wk53NmRWUlJtUnFNMmlMQWtzTTZJd0s5akRRMThNN2tHZmkyd0JVV3Q4a3F3U212ak82Wm9YQ0JQRXNiY24tR2pMcVo0QXFmQno2X043Uy1OM0JYaEJXOXF5OVZKaHE1dk5TVVJUTEltc1VucUJKUTlPd2t1UzVDcUNFampsNGN6d25hU1Bva18xUmM1b3FmSFBoVUtOOVhRWWg4N2fSAc4BQVVfeXFMUHNVTTZUVWphaTI1UHNkaWN4RngzUDZCdm5Vd1Y5MWJOUWJ6YmwyTDdTM2daY19kdEl4MWRiZjNCR2RjME9sakN4MWNEXzdQWUxEejdoaEpuTW1UMHBYOHZ6RFl5dU9QWEdpVEVKTTlFekRDVFROOTlZempydU5Od3p0TUI3S0Ezb3FFa3psS25zRUF2OVR2d2QzSnY4S1FHcml4N2k3RGFNeXpkUTJqV2J1Ni14cG15ZkRpVUNYdFhjaEpUenVJMkJMSFhQT2c</guid></item><item><title>根据毒理学家- CNN的说法，您对食物中铅的最佳防御</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/25/health/lead-in-food-wellness</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5byblv000x26p5946d2zkw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lead shouldn’t be in your food, right?
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp00083b6nnhjx8ahb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Exposure to the substance has been linked to a wide range of health impacts, including developmental problems, nervous system damage and hearing problems in children; and high blood pressure, joint pain and reproductive problems in adults.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp00093b6n7qi572xg@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            At the same time, reports continue to document high levels of lead in food products such as &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/09/12/health/lead-cinnamon-powder-spices-wellness"&gt;applesauce&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/02/06/health/cinnamon-applesauce-lead-fda"&gt;cinnamon powder&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/09/health/protein-powder-heavy-metals-wellness"&gt;protein powder&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/07/31/health/cacao-dark-chocolate-lead-heavy-metals-wellness"&gt;chocolate&lt;/a&gt;. This year, the US Food and Drug Administration established new guidance on limits of lead content in &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/06/health/lead-baby-food-fda-wellness"&gt;baby food&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000a3b6n6m8z26g8@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It makes sense to ask: Why would there be lead in your diet at all?
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000b3b6nlasen1i4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lead is a naturally occurring metal found in our planet, and it has been used in products such as gasoline, paint, plumbing, cosmetics, ceramics and batteries, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.niehs.nih.gov/health/topics/agents/lead" target="_blank"&gt;National Institute of Environmental Health Science.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000d3b6n6ruw1qpi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Often, lead in food comes from the soil. “The most common reason is because lead, like other metals and heavy metals, is a naturally occurring part of the earth and the Earth’s crust,” said Dr. Joseph Zagorski, a toxicologist and assistant professor at Michigan State University’s Center for Research on Ingredient Safety.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000e3b6nvf1ymt37@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some plants are more prone to absorbing the lead in the soil and storing them in their own tissue, he added. If crops are grown in areas with higher levels of lead in the environment, they may contain more of the metal.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000f3b6nkfv9s0sv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But not all the lead sources in the environment are natural, Zagorski said. Human activities such as smelting frequently lead to lead contamination, and there have been pesticides that contained lead, he added.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000g3b6nzq74qs5a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Use of leaded gasoline can also lead to contamination of plants through the air, said Dr. Tasha Stoiber, a senior scientist for the Environmental Working Group. Lead has been phased out of gasoline for cars, but is &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/08/30/business/lead-gasoline-car-climate-change-intl"&gt;still used&lt;/a&gt; in some fuel types.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000h3b6nnnv7z60p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Contamination also can occur through someone adding lead to food, as appeared to be &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2024/02/06/health/cinnamon-applesauce-lead-fda"&gt;the case in 2023&lt;/a&gt; with some applesauce pouches. But that is not usually the case.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000i3b6n78p346sc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Because the heavy metal is found in the environment, people are unlikely to reach a point of zero lead exposure in our food or anywhere. However, lead –– even in small doses –– can have health impacts, Stoiber said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000j3b6nr1jnv2tk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For children, the concern is particularly great because their smaller bodies and metabolisms put them at a greater vulnerability for harms caused by exposure, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/environmental-contaminants-food/closer-zero-reducing-childhood-exposure-contaminants-foods" target="_blank"&gt;FDA.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000k3b6nv1e5nozb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The federal agency has been working to reduce dietary exposure to contaminants for children to as close to zero as possible. And no safe level of exposure to lead has been identified, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/lead-prevention/php/news-features/updates-blood-lead-reference-value.html" target="_blank"&gt;US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000l3b6n5gngssut@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, the &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35690180/" target="_blank"&gt;FDA does use a benchmark&lt;/a&gt; of 2.2 micrograms per day of dietary lead exposure for children and 8.8 micrograms per day for women of childbearing age. Experts use those numbers to evaluate when an exposure is potentially a concern and a product needs to be alerted.&lt;s&gt;&lt;/s&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000m3b6n3y4xir9h@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The guidelines on dietary lead exposure are hard to translate into practical use at home, and you likely won’t know exactly how much is in the food you are eating, Stoiber said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000n3b6n1dagwvtp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            She recommends looking into brands that regularly test their food products for lead levels. And your best defense against lead –– and any other toxin –– is a diverse, nutritionally dense diet, Zagorski said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000o3b6n11bexvtw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Eating a variety of foods can help in two ways. First, it reduces the likelihood that you are eating too much of one food that may be more likely to contain lead.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000p3b6nme5lm7c1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For example, earlier this year &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/01/09/health/protein-powder-heavy-metals-wellness"&gt;a report found lead&lt;/a&gt; in protein powders. Occasional use of those protein powders isn’t as concerning as a person making protein shakes three times a day.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000q3b6ntflm3vsk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Protein powder is intended to be a supplement and not a diet,” Zagorski said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000r3b6nelkccouc@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Second, a nutrient-dense and varied diet also can help with your body’s natural defenses against unwanted elements, he added. Your body prefers absorbing iron over lead — so if you have enough iron in your diet, your digestive system is more likely to let the lead pass through, he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmh5bzrgp000s3b6nab5v9hbp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The dose makes the poison,” Zagorski said. “Your body is very good at taking care of itself and getting rid of toxins, so (make) sure that we are giving it the tools it needs and not overconsuming one thing.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  
&lt;p data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/editor-note/instances/cmh5ggc7y00043b6n9c6k07n9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="editor-note" class="editor-note-elevate vossi-editor-note_elevate inline-placeholder " data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
    Sign up for &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/newsletters/eat-but-better?source=nl-acq_article"&gt;CNN’s Eat, But Better: Mediterranean Style&lt;/a&gt;. Our eight-part guide shows you a delicious expert-backed eating lifestyle that will boost your health for life.
&lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMia0FVX3lxTFB4ekxncU5ESGZBNWMtaXY2eHlVSXo4S0lSTjliV1lfLXhQVlE2anpXUTV4OFZDYlF1NUtfVXE1Nk5ldVFoTzVROW9YdHJwN0c2YU9yaUNQSkN6NGFyN2tfT3Rtc3NOdlpmaHU0</guid></item><item><title>COVID-19 mRNA疫苗可以触发免疫系统识别和杀死癌症，研究发现- Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/cancer/covid-19-mrna-vaccines-can-trigger-the-immune-system-to-recognize-and-kill-cancer-research-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto paywall-locker"&gt;
&lt;p id="d5d2ee61-1cea-4820-a582-d16bffa5f21f"&gt;The &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/coronavirus" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/coronavirus"&gt;&lt;u&gt;COVID-19&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; mRNA-based vaccines that &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamahealthforum.2025.2223" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamahealthforum.2025.2223" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;saved 2.5 million lives globally&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; during the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/tag/pandemic" data-auto-tag-linker="true" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/tag/pandemic"&gt;pandemic&lt;/a&gt; could help spark the immune system to fight &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/cancer" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/viruses-infections-disease/cancer"&gt;&lt;u&gt;cancer&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This is the surprising takeaway of a new study that &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09655-y" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09655-y" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;we and our colleagues published in the journal Nature&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While developing &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/what-are-mrna-vaccines-and-how-do-they-work" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/medicine-drugs/what-are-mrna-vaccines-and-how-do-they-work"&gt;&lt;u&gt;mRNA vaccines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for patients with brain tumors in 2016, our team, led by &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://directory.ufhealth.org/sayour-elias" target="_blank" data-url="https://directory.ufhealth.org/sayour-elias" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;pediatric oncologist Elias Sayour&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, discovered that mRNA can train immune systems to kill tumors — &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41551-025-01380-1" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41551-025-01380-1" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;even if the mRNA is not related to cancer&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="d5d2ee61-1cea-4820-a582-d16bffa5f21f-2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true"&gt;Based on this finding, we hypothesized that mRNA vaccines designed to target the SARS-CoV-2 virus that causes COVID-19 might also have antitumor effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="110b7ed4-d6e7-4d6b-a874-7a23d84905ac"&gt;So &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=AqVdPM4AAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en" target="_blank" data-url="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=AqVdPM4AAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;we looked at clinical outcomes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for more than 1,000 late-stage melanoma and lung cancer patients treated with a type of immunotherapy called &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2023.03.006" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2023.03.006" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;immune checkpoint inhibitors&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This treatment is a common approach doctors use to train the immune system to kill cancer. It does this by blocking a protein that tumor cells make to turn off immune cells, enabling the immune system to continue killing cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remarkably, patients who received either the Pfizer or Moderna mRNA-based COVID-19 vaccine within 100 days of starting immunotherapy were more than twice as likely to be alive after three years compared with those who didn't receive either vaccine. Surprisingly, patients with tumors that don't typically respond well to immunotherapy also saw very strong benefits, with nearly fivefold improvement in three-year overall survival. This link between improved survival and receiving a COVID-19 mRNA vaccine remained strong even after we controlled for factors like disease severity and co-occurring conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand the underlying mechanism, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=E2q2tK8AAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en" target="_blank" data-url="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=E2q2tK8AAAAJ&amp;amp;hl=en" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;we turned to animal models&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. We found that COVID-19 mRNA vaccines act like an alarm, triggering the body's immune system to recognize and kill tumor cells and overcome the cancer's ability to turn off immune cells. When combined, vaccines and immune checkpoint inhibitors coordinate to unleash the full power of the immune system to kill cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="youtube-video youtube-facade" data-nosnippet="" id="_D_Iz9s9Y6k"&gt;
&lt;div class="video-aspect-box"&gt;
&lt;div class="watch-on-iframe-_D_Iz9s9Y6k" data-yt-video-token="_D_Iz9s9Y6k" title="COVID-19 mRNA vaccine sparks immune response to fight cancer, study finds - YouTube"&gt;
&lt;span class="youtube-video-title"&gt;COVID-19 mRNA vaccine sparks immune response to fight cancer, study finds - YouTube&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/_D_Iz9s9Y6k/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="COVID-19 mRNA vaccine sparks immune response to fight cancer, study finds - YouTube" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="play-button" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 234.67 165.33"&gt;&lt;path fill="red" d="M229.763 25.817c-2.699-10.162-10.65-18.165-20.748-20.881C190.716 0 117.333 0 117.333 0S43.951 0 25.651 4.936C15.553 7.652 7.6 15.655 4.903 25.817 0 44.236 0 82.667 0 82.667s0 38.429 4.903 56.85C7.6 149.68 15.553 157.681 25.65 160.4c18.3 4.934 91.682 4.934 91.682 4.934s73.383 0 91.682-4.934c10.098-2.718 18.049-10.72 20.748-20.882 4.904-18.421 4.904-56.85 4.904-56.85s0-38.431-4.904-56.85"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="m93.333 117.559 61.333-34.89-61.333-34.894z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;a class="watch-on-youtube-_D_Iz9s9Y6k" href="https://youtu.be/_D_Iz9s9Y6k" target="_blank" data-url="https://youtu.be/_D_Iz9s9Y6k" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Watch On &lt;svg class="youtube-logo" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 507.9 113.39"&gt;&lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;path d="M64.792 80.99V32.396l42.082 24.297zm93.803-63.285a20.285 20.285 0 0 0-14.32-14.32C131.642 0 80.99 0 80.99 0S30.337 0 17.705 3.385a20.286 20.286 0 0 0-14.32 14.32C0 30.338 0 56.693 0 56.693S0 83.049 3.385 95.68A20.285 20.285 0 0 0 17.705 110c12.632 3.386 63.285 3.386 63.285 3.386s50.652 0 63.285-3.386a20.284 20.284 0 0 0 14.32-14.32c3.385-12.632 3.385-38.988 3.385-38.988s0-26.355-3.385-38.988m94.473 74.326c.887-2.314 1.332-6.098 1.332-11.35V58.556c0-5.097-.445-8.822-1.332-11.178-.888-2.355-2.452-3.533-4.69-3.533-2.163 0-3.69 1.178-4.577 3.533-.888 2.356-1.332 6.081-1.332 11.178V80.68c0 5.25.424 9.035 1.275 11.35.848 2.318 2.392 3.475 4.633 3.475 2.239 0 3.803-1.157 4.691-3.475zm-17.953 11.122c-3.207-2.16-5.486-5.52-6.835-10.079-1.352-4.554-2.027-10.617-2.027-18.185v-10.31c0-7.644.771-13.784 2.316-18.417 1.544-4.633 3.956-8.011 7.24-10.135 3.282-2.123 7.587-3.186 12.916-3.186 5.251 0 9.459 1.082 12.626 3.243 3.165 2.162 5.482 5.542 6.95 10.136 1.466 4.595 2.2 10.715 2.2 18.36v10.31c0 7.567-.714 13.65-2.142 18.243-1.43 4.595-3.747 7.955-6.951 10.077-3.205 2.124-7.548 3.186-13.03 3.186-5.64 0-10.06-1.082-13.263-3.243m248.053-57.981c-.81 1.005-1.352 2.646-1.621 4.923-.272 2.278-.404 5.734-.404 10.367v5.097h11.697V60.46c0-4.555-.155-8.011-.463-10.367-.309-2.355-.868-4.014-1.678-4.98-.812-.966-2.067-1.449-3.766-1.449-1.7 0-2.954.503-3.765 1.506zm-2.025 29.886v3.591c0 4.557.132 7.974.404 10.251.269 2.279.828 3.94 1.68 4.982.849 1.041 2.16 1.564 3.938 1.564 2.392 0 4.035-.927 4.923-2.781.887-1.853 1.37-4.942 1.447-9.268l13.785.812c.077.62.116 1.469.116 2.548 0 6.565-1.795 11.47-5.387 14.712-3.589 3.242-8.669 4.865-15.232 4.865-7.876 0-13.398-2.47-16.564-7.414-3.168-4.94-4.75-12.586-4.75-22.935V63.589c0-10.657 1.641-18.436 4.924-23.342 3.281-4.903 8.9-7.355 16.854-7.355 5.482 0 9.691 1.004 12.626 3.012 2.933 2.01 5 5.137 6.197 9.383 1.197 4.247 1.796 10.117 1.796 17.607v12.163h-26.757m-284.953-1.33-18.187-65.68h15.869l6.37 29.77c1.623 7.339 2.82 13.594 3.591 18.766h.464c.54-3.706 1.738-9.922 3.591-18.65l6.603-29.886h15.869l-18.417 65.68v31.51h-15.754v-31.51M322.115 34.23v71.007h-12.511l-1.39-8.688h-.347c-3.399 6.564-8.496 9.845-15.291 9.845-4.71 0-8.185-1.543-10.425-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.359-7.915-3.359-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.348 5.426 1.043 6.776.695 1.353 1.853 2.027 3.475 2.027 1.39 0 2.722-.423 3.996-1.275 1.274-.849 2.22-1.928 2.838-3.241V34.229h15.986m81.995.001v71.007h-12.511l-1.391-8.688h-.345c-3.402 6.564-8.498 9.845-15.292 9.845-4.711 0-8.186-1.543-10.426-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.358-7.915-3.358-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.347 5.426 1.041 6.776.696 1.353 1.855 2.027 3.476 2.027 1.391 0 2.723-.423 3.996-1.275 1.275-.849 2.22-1.928 2.839-3.241V34.229h15.985"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M365.552 20.908h-15.87v84.329h-15.637v-84.33h-15.869V8.05h47.376v12.858m76.811 53.636c0 5.174-.215 9.229-.639 12.162-.424 2.937-1.139 5.021-2.143 6.255-1.004 1.236-2.357 1.854-4.053 1.854a7.404 7.404 0 0 1-3.65-.927c-1.12-.618-2.026-1.544-2.722-2.78V50.796c.54-1.93 1.467-3.513 2.78-4.749 1.313-1.234 2.74-1.853 4.285-1.853 1.623 0 2.876.637 3.766 1.91.886 1.275 1.505 3.418 1.853 6.43.348 3.011.523 7.297.523 12.857zm14.652-28.964c-.967-4.478-2.531-7.721-4.692-9.73-2.163-2.007-5.136-3.011-8.919-3.011-2.935 0-5.676.83-8.224 2.49a16.926 16.926 0 0 0-5.908 6.545h-.117l.001-37.416h-15.405v100.777h13.204l1.622-6.717h.347c1.235 2.393 3.088 4.285 5.56 5.675 2.47 1.39 5.213 2.085 8.225 2.085 5.404 0 9.382-2.491 11.931-7.471 2.548-4.982 3.823-12.76 3.823-23.341V64.23c0-7.953-.484-14.17-1.448-18.65"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a id="elk-f81a0f95-4252-41bd-b055-18efdd53e6e2" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="why-it-matters-3"&gt;Why it matters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="9126cac2-27e6-4442-a69c-7c673f20ee40"&gt;Immunotherapy with immune checkpoint inhibitors has &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2023.03.006" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cell.2023.03.006" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;revolutionized cancer treatment&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; over the past decade by producing cures in many patients who were previously considered incurable. However, these therapies are ineffective in patients with &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/cold-tumor" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/cold-tumor" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;"cold" tumors&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that successfully evade immune detection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-UkaQPY7j3SYFwCapiP6V3Q" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-UkaQPY7j3SYFwCapiP6V3Q slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our findings suggest that mRNA vaccines may provide just the spark the immune system needs to turn these "cold" tumors "hot." If validated in our upcoming clinical trial, our hope is that this widely available, low-cost intervention could extend the benefits of immunotherapy to millions of patients who otherwise would not benefit from this therapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-13185a60-4cd5-49ca-89db-46af8135339a" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-other-research-is-being-done-3"&gt;What other research is being done&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="d3879fbc-7791-438b-9a65-91492b549592"&gt;Unlike vaccines for infectious diseases, which are used to prevent an infection, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/modernas-experimental-cancer-vaccine-treats-but-doesnt-prevent-melanoma-a-biochemist-explains-how-it-works-197003" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/modernas-experimental-cancer-vaccine-treats-but-doesnt-prevent-melanoma-a-biochemist-explains-how-it-works-197003" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;therapeutic cancer vaccines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are used to help train the immune systems of cancer patients to better fight tumors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We and many others are &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/modernas-experimental-cancer-vaccine-treats-but-doesnt-prevent-melanoma-a-biochemist-explains-how-it-works-197003" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/modernas-experimental-cancer-vaccine-treats-but-doesnt-prevent-melanoma-a-biochemist-explains-how-it-works-197003" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;currently working hard&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to make &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/customizing-mrna-is-easy-and-thats-what-makes-it-the-next-frontier-for-personalized-medicine-a-molecular-biologist-explains-216127" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/customizing-mrna-is-easy-and-thats-what-makes-it-the-next-frontier-for-personalized-medicine-a-molecular-biologist-explains-216127" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;personalized mRNA vaccines&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/brain-cancer-in-children-is-notoriously-hard-to-treat-a-new-mrna-cancer-vaccine-triggers-an-attack-from-within-228666" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/brain-cancer-in-children-is-notoriously-hard-to-treat-a-new-mrna-cancer-vaccine-triggers-an-attack-from-within-228666" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;patients with cancer&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This involves taking a small sample of a patient's tumor and using machine learning algorithms to predict which proteins in the tumor would be the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-022-01270-x" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-022-01270-x" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;best targets for a vaccine&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. However, this approach can be &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-023-01674-3" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41392-023-01674-3" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;costly and difficult to manufacture&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, COVID-19 mRNA vaccines do not need to be personalized, are already widely available at low or no cost around the globe, and could be administered at any time during a patient's treatment. Our findings that &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09655-y" target="_blank" data-url="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41586-025-09655-y" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;COVID-19 mRNA vaccines have substantial antitumor effects&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; bring hope that they could help extend the anti-cancer benefits of mRNA vaccines to all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-0360b2b0-5aa7-4d73-a110-c8a0c9134676" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-s-next-3"&gt;What's next&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="cabb8cd4-853e-4687-98b2-c182965eefd3"&gt;In pursuit of this goal, we are preparing to test this treatment strategy in patients with a nationwide clinical trial in people with lung cancer. People receiving an immune checkpoint inhibitor will be randomized to either receive a COVID-19 mRNA vaccine during treatment or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="03558f35-9487-44d0-904f-6a34a842406c"&gt;This study will tell us whether COVID-19 mRNA vaccines should be included as part of the standard of care for patients receiving an immune checkpoint inhibitor. Ultimately, we hope that this approach will help many patients who are treated with immune therapy, and especially those who currently lack effective treatment options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This work exemplifies how a tool born from a global pandemic may provide a new weapon against cancer and rapidly extend the benefits of existing treatments to millions of patients. By harnessing a familiar vaccine in a new way, we hope to extend the lifesaving benefits of immunotherapy to cancer patients who were previously left behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This edited article is republished from &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="http://theconversation.com/" target="_blank" data-url="http://theconversation.com/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Conversation&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://theconversation.com/covid-19-mrna-vaccines-could-unlock-the-next-revolution-in-cancer-treatment-new-research-258992" target="_blank" data-url="https://theconversation.com/covid-19-mrna-vaccines-could-unlock-the-next-revolution-in-cancer-treatment-new-research-258992" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;em&gt;original article&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-b04dac75-7394-41a8-89a6-76ad4bd94625" class="paywall" aria-hidden="true" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AFBVV95cUxOZGpyLVBmTVhkLUZSQXV1Zk15R0psNVlXTzBaaHhkWHNmTVZUVmVKTnVXcjUtTWg4YjZISWh0bUc5QXg0WkxVTjZWWmF2bzJRdUhLLUxUc0kwYlctZk15Y3FHckdHQ0tCYW9xbW9OTVNzOTI4bkpkbWdPcHBMZWRVaDRPWU5lbmJyRUVsd2JVRkotc056dC1GbWxnX3g2dkw0YzIzaXpvZjJjWTR5OVBPa0hxNFpHV3dWLS16R1RDcmNqZzlsZzZNbVdHNEJmbDI4SHlGbw</guid></item><item><title>解释：多少蛋白质才是过多的蛋白质？ -印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/explained-how-much-protein-is-too-much-protein/articleshow/124806467.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="1"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;i&gt;TL;DR: &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;keyword id="24300" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="Protein" source="Orion"&gt;Protein&lt;/keyword&gt; is essential for building and repairing the body, but it’s being oversold. Most adults already consume enough, and eating more won’t necessarily boost strength or &lt;keyword id="6358794" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="Weight-Loss" source="Orion"&gt;weight loss&lt;/keyword&gt;. Studies show benefits plateau around 1.3–1.6 g/kg per day when combined with resistance training. Moderate intake is safe, but extreme “high-protein” diets add little benefit and may pose cardiovascular risks. Balance, variety, and exercise matter more than chasing protein numbers.&lt;br&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; For much of modern nutrition’s history, food has been a soap opera of shifting villains. In the 1980s, fat was the moustache-twirling antagonist, blamed for everything from heart disease to moral decay. We banished butter, exiled ghee, and declared war on cholesterol. Then came the 2000s, when carbohydrates took the fall. White bread became public enemy number one, and pasta was treated like a controlled substance. Now, in the latest season of the macronutrient melodrama, protein stands alone as the misunderstood hero turned messiah. Every supermarket aisle looks like a shrine to it: high-protein biscuits, protein water, protein pancakes, protein pasta. We have protein-ified our diets and, in doing so, deified a molecule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; But this cult of protein is not just science, it is spectacle. Somewhere between a gym influencer’s Instagram reel and a corporate marketing meeting, a biological necessity became a billion-dollar aesthetic. Protein stopped being what your body needs to build and repair, and started being what your ego needs to feel productive, disciplined, superior. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has become a moral macronutrient, wrapped in muscle and marketed with monk-like minimalism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The irony is almost poetic. We once feared fat because we wanted to be thin. Now we worship protein because we want to be strong. And yet, beneath the gloss of nutrition labels and influencer endorsements, the question remains the same. Do we really understand what we are consuming, or are we simply consuming what we are told to believe in? The story of protein is not just about diet. It is about desire, capitalism, and the strange human impulse to moralise molecules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Protein is indispensable to life. About 42 percent of the human body’s dry mass is made of protein. It is not just in muscles, but also in skin, hair, nails, and connective tissue. As nutrition columnist Tamar Haspel writes in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/food/2025/10/23/protein-muscle-mass-weight-loss-faqs/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, fat and carbohydrates fuel us, but protein literally builds us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The biological reason lies in nitrogen. As explained in Food Intelligence by Kevin Hall and Julia Belluz, plants derive nitrogen from soil, and we obtain it by eating plants or animals that eat them. Without nitrogen, amino acids—the building blocks of protein—cannot form, and life as we know it cannot persist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br&gt;How Much Protein Do We Actually Need?&lt;br&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; There is no single number that fits everyone, but most scientific bodies agree on a broad range. The Recommended Dietary Allowance (RDA) for adults is 0.8 grams per kilogram of body weight per day, based on nitrogen balance studies. These experiments measure how much nitrogen enters and leaves the body to determine the minimum required for equilibrium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="32"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; According to nutrition scientist Kevin Klatt, this baseline ensures adequacy for most people. However, newer research suggests slightly higher targets may help preserve lean mass as we age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/nutritionreviews/article/79/1/66/5936522" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;meta-analysis in Nutrition Reviews (2021)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that muscle gains increase with protein intake up to about 1.3–1.6 g/kg/day, but level off beyond that. Similarly, a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sportsmedicine-open.springeropen.com/articles/10.1186/s40798-022-00508-w" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2022 review in Sports Medicine – Open&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that resistance-trained adults benefited from extra protein up to around 1.5 g/kg/day, with diminishing returns after.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; For a 70-kilogram adult, that is roughly 90 to 110 grams of protein per day, achievable with a balanced diet rather than supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protein and Muscle: What the Research Shows&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A 2018 &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/52/6/376" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;meta-analysis in the British Journal of Sports Medicine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; reported that increasing protein intake modestly enhances muscle mass and strength when paired with resistance exercise. Additional protein beyond 1.6 g/kg/day provided no further benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Likewise, a 2022 review in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sportsmedicine-open.springeropen.com/articles/10.1186/s40798-022-00508-w" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Sports Medicine – Open&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; confirmed that protein supplementation improves lean mass only when combined with weight training. Simply eating more protein without resistance exercise offers negligible benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Even in weight-loss contexts, protein’s power is limited. A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39002131/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2024 systematic review in Clinical Nutrition ESPEN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that higher protein intake can preserve muscle mass during calorie restriction but does not significantly enhance strength or metabolic outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="62"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Does More Protein Mean Better Weight Loss?&lt;br&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="63"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The short answer: not really.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="65"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; High-protein diets may improve satiety and slightly boost metabolism in the short term, leading to modest weight reduction. However, a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/ajcn/article/101/6/1320S/4564505" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;review in The American Journal of Clinical Nutrition (2015)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that long-term outcomes show little difference between higher-protein and moderate-protein diets once calorie balance is controlled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Haspel’s column summarises it neatly: higher protein may help in the short term, but its advantage “disappears in the long term.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plant vs. Animal Protein&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; ID 124806750 Plant vs Animal Protein etimes.in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="76"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Protein quality—the proportion of essential amino acids and how efficiently the body uses them—varies across sources. Animal proteins (meat, eggs, dairy) are generally more bioavailable than plant proteins (beans, lentils, tofu). But that gap narrows when plant proteins are combined or processed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/ajcn/article/105/2/394/4637850" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;study in the American Journal of Clinical Nutrition (2017)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; found that total protein intake, not its source, primarily determines muscle synthesis when diets are balanced for amino acids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="83"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Haspel even cites a beef-industry-funded trial in which omnivorous and vegan participants consuming equal protein showed no difference in muscle synthesis after nine days of resistance training, a rare case where the meat lobby admitted defeat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Upper Limit: When Protein Becomes Too Much&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; There is little evidence of harm from moderately high protein intakes (up to about 2 g/kg/day) in healthy individuals. But data beyond that are less reassuring. A review in &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/12/8/2481" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Nutrients (2020)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; reported potential increases in cardiovascular risk markers when 40 percent or more of calories came from protein, especially from red or processed meat. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="92"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The consensus: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;moderate increases are safe, extreme ones are unproven and possibly unwise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="96"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Protein Myth: Marketing vs. Metabolism&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="97"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; The global protein supplement market now exceeds 25 billion dollars, fuelled by gym culture and influencer marketing. Yet as Hall and Belluz remind us in Food Intelligence, humans are “astonishingly adaptable omnivores.” We can thrive across a broad range of macronutrient ratios, provided calorie and micronutrient needs are met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="99"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Most Americans already consume above-recommended protein levels, according to the FAO and USDA. For the average person eating a mixed diet, the question is not deficiency but excess. The obsession with “high-protein” foods is driven more by marketing than metabolism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="103"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="104"&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Bottom Line&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="105"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Protein is vital, but it is not magical. It builds, repairs, and preserves, yet beyond a moderate threshold, more is not better. The scientific consensus across dozens of controlled trials and meta-analyses is clear:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="107"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="108"&gt;&lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Aim for 0.8–1.6 g/kg/day, depending on activity and age.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Combine it with resistance training for real benefits.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Diversify protein sources rather than rely solely on supplements.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Focus on overall dietary quality, not a single nutrient.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;We have probably gone as far as we need to with protein. The rest is just branding.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="109"&gt;&lt;b&gt;FAQ&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="110"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="111"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: How much protein do I really need each day?&lt;br&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most adults need about 0.8 g/kg of body weight per day. Active individuals or older adults may benefit from 1.2–1.6 g/kg to preserve muscle mass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="114"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="115"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: Can I eat too much protein?&lt;br&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes. Intakes above 2 g/kg/day offer no added benefits for most people and could increase cardiovascular or kidney strain in those with pre-existing conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="117"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="118"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: Does more protein mean faster weight loss?&lt;br&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not in the long run. High-protein diets may improve satiety and metabolism short-term, but long-term weight loss depends on overall calorie balance, not protein alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="120"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="121"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: Is plant protein as good as animal protein?&lt;br&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When total protein intake and amino acid balance are adequate, plant and animal proteins support muscle growth equally well. Combining legumes, grains, and soy can provide complete proteins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="125"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="126"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: Do I need protein shakes or supplements?&lt;br&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not usually. Most people can meet their needs through whole foods like eggs, lentils, dairy, tofu, paneer, and lean meats. Supplements are useful mainly for athletes with high demands or limited access to meals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="128"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="129"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: What’s the healthiest way to get enough protein?&lt;br&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aim for a varied diet that includes both plant and animal sources, pair protein intake with regular strength training, and focus on overall diet quality rather than a single macronutrient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="131"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="132"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="133"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="134"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 12:59:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi3wFBVV95cUxOOHhDRzlzRHNjMHZRX3NKRXNNNWlEbXNySXBwcTFiWUo4bjhKdU9kMW1wVUp2alBiclAwU0toeWpJajBPWHlFOGZWMklTTFZMYk5iMl9CbGgwak9uWkQ2dzRjVVRjT0ViSm5aaTEzR0czSnI5cF9JT185Y3E3aS1QUUJtQlZfVFdueUFhc0JKOHRvYXQ1WTh5YTJqd3VkUzVTbFRMTm52NXFmVG9SSHFLWXRoUjJJbmw5RHFkNTM5V1Z2TUdDUWx5Rzl5cHJWSFFNcFBLd001WWwyZlFDV2hZ0gHkAUFVX3lxTFBuaWh0Nno0aHNYMlR4c3BEeDJnMFpoSmFvd2VkNDlWdDdNanpCeDFHM0J0UnNLalVUckYzWUhVR0lMWE83c1ROX2tCWmliaEE4cGZFREZVcWFRZmJQR1E3MWFDZ0dzVDA5STM1VVhNT21oR3hiUEFielo5Y25fV1plODVNdkgyX1ZYMVRUQ3EyRFdNMFE0NTJjdVJsSzRVWWxHZ08zS3dENjZ0ZGJrUkZ5VXhUcEZoYkQ2bXMyU2NJbzRSV0tiOWE2c2Z2cjRMU0VfR0VLS3BlYjFJOXlfWUVBcUc3SQ</guid></item></channel></rss>