<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>特朗普利用推动未经证实的新冠肺炎治疗的耶鲁医生来领导美国的癌症工作-华盛顿邮报</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/17/trump-risch-cancer-covid/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Y555LMYY2NBS7B7NYWX7MYVNEM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Harvey Risch, a Yale epidemiologist long respected for his work in cancer research but who has faced controversy for promoting an unproven covid-19 treatment, has been selected by President Donald Trump to lead the nation’s cancer initiative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 20:18:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE1sR256TzAzbGZFSkJZV3NvbG1NZHc5VmdRakEyaHdRd0l3dksyTzMxcGJaXzc4MEJXWUJ5cWd2SW0tSklWZXZzS1ZzTXdNMWdJcDItRkp3TnNNZGtmbzZuRk4wVW5DUU0yaTZhMTdGSi03aWpHUTM5WkZfN1dlMlk</guid></item><item><title>金毛猎犬显然与邻居雪人有牛肉，它正在让我们崩溃-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/articles/golden-retriever-clearly-beef-neighborhood-190500688.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;My dog Lola started barking when I played this video, so she wants to let you all know that she fully supports this Golden and his beef with the neighborhood snowman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the TikTok clip, we’re out on a nighttime walk with a &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/golden-retriever-does-cute-wiggles-waiting-for-grandma" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Golden Retriever;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Golden Retriever&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; who is usually all sunshine and social skills—until she spots &lt;em&gt;it&lt;/em&gt;. About 100 yards ahead, in the glow of a street light, stands a snowman. Perfectly still. Suspiciously still. Too still.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Our Golden stops in her tracks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;She locks in, ears up, tail frozen mid-wag like her internal Wi-Fi just disconnected. A low grumble starts, then a bark, then a full-on monologue of “Absolutely not, we are not just walking past that frosty intruder like everything is fine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Her human can’t help but laugh as she calmly reassures her that the ice man is, in fact, not a threat to national security. The Golden’s body language disagrees. She edges forward a few steps, stops, and barks, then backs up before inching forward again. It’s like watching someone argue with an inanimate object—and somehow lose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Meanwhile, Lola—watching from the safety of the couch—is ALL IN. She barked at the screen like she wanted to hop in, tag this Golden out, and finish the round herself. Apparently, the “untrustworthy &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/pups-playful-snowman-encounter" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:snowman;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;snowman&lt;/a&gt;” opinion is universal in the dog community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Part of what makes the video so funny is that it also shows how &lt;em&gt;earnestly&lt;/em&gt; dogs try to protect us, even from piles of snow with stick arms. They don’t always understand what they’re seeing, but they know one thing: they’ve got our backs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;When Your Dog Thinks the Snowman Is Sus&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/corgi-patiently-waiting-for-someone-to-pet-her" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dogs;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Dogs&lt;/a&gt; reacting dramatically to harmless objects—snowmen, statues, lawn decorations—is actually pretty common. New or odd shapes can confuse them, especially in low light, and their default response is, "Alert the humans!" The key is to stay &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/dogs/calm-dog-breeds" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:calm;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;calm&lt;/a&gt;, reassure them, let them investigate at their own pace, and never punish them for being scared. For more insight on why dogs freak out over “strange” things and how to help them through it, this &lt;a href="https://www.petmd.com/dog/behavior/why-my-dog-scared-everything" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PetMD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;&lt;em&gt;PetMD &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;article is a great read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;So yes—if your dog has beef with the snowman, just know they’re doing their best, one suspicious side-eye at a time. ⛄🐶&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/dog-face" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐶;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;🐶&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/parade-pets" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP to get “pawsitivity” delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;SIGN UP to get “pawsitivity” delivered right to your inbox with inspiring &amp;amp; entertaining stories about our furry &amp;amp; feathered friends&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/paw-prints" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🐾🐾;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;🐾🐾&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/golden-retriever-does-cute-wiggles-waiting-for-grandma" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: Golden Retriever's Cute Wiggles While Waiting for Grandma to Open Door Make Our Hearts Happy;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Related: Golden Retriever's Cute Wiggles While Waiting for Grandma to Open Door Make Our Hearts Happy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally published by &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news/golden-retriever-has-beef-with-neighborhood-snowman" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade Pets;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Parade Pets&lt;/a&gt; on Dec 17, 2025, where it first appeared in the &lt;a href="https://paradepets.com/pet-news" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Pet News;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Pet News&lt;/a&gt; section. Add Parade Pets as a &lt;a href="https://google.com/preferences/source?q=paradepets.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Preferred Source by clicking here.;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Preferred Source by clicking here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:05:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxONUt6cGVUcG5nRDUyMUlkYS1WanVwNGRQbWpjb0RGYnd0QnFZbzdya2d0OE9MMXE5TldFalBsT0hURktFaWRfUDRncGJYUkgxcW9zcGdycEdjOXVFdTNDWTRtdkFqUmZ6Y2FSazFCemFTUzN0WmU2TF95dEE1OXY0MVM5R2NjRmFRRXlnWklNNEd6NC13MjJxTzNhNXdyWmc</guid></item><item><title>我为什么自愿感染登革热- NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/12/17/g-s1-102311/vaccine-dengue-fever-trial</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-102623" class="bucketwrap image x-large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Early in the pandemic, a volunteer takes part in a clinical trial to develop a vaccine that will protect against COVID-19. The U.S. government has registered over half a million clinical trials since 2000. The vast majority of the trials don't result in a new drug approval.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    Joe Raedle/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        Joe Raedle/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;Just like the moment a mosquito bites, the shot of dengue virus I received in my arm was so quick and painless that afterward I wasn't even sure it happened at all.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;A few years ago, I wrote a story about a &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goatsandsoda/2022/09/21/1112727841/a-box-of-200-mosquitoes-did-the-vaccinating-in-this-malaria-trial-thats-not-a-jo" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;young woman who was infected with malaria by 200 mosquito bites&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to test a potential vaccine. At the time, it was bewildering to me that someone would  be willingly agree to take on so much risk and put themselves through so much discomfort for only a modest sum of money.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Yet many people choose to participate in clinical trials for new drugs every year. In fact, it is required in the United States medical system and throughout the world that drugs be tested on human participants in three phases of clinical trials to evaluate their safety and effectiveness before they can be approved for use.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/about-site/trends-charts" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Over half a million clinical trials have been registered on the US government's ClinicalTrials.gov&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; since the clinical-trial-tracking site launched in February 2000. And &lt;a href="https://www.grandviewresearch.com/industry-analysis/global-clinical-trials-market" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;nearly $100 billion is spent every year&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; on the business of running clinical trials. The vast majority of the trials, and the money that goes into them, don't result in a new drug approval.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So when an ad popped up in my Instagram feed suggesting I could earn up to $3,425 for participating in a 5-month-long dengue study at the Johns Hopkins University Center for Immunization Research (CIR), I was intrigued.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;I wanted to know more about the business and ethics of human medical experimentation. And I was willing to put myself through a little pain to find out. It turns out that within the industry there are constant debates about the roles of risk, race, paternalism, economics, and exploitation in making clinical trials work. But despite all that, clinical trials still rely on some sense of altruism in healthy participants to function.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Informed and uninformed consent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Dengue fever is the most-common mosquito-borne viral illness in the world. The World Health Organization estimates that up to &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/dengue-and-severe-dengue#:~:text=Key%20facts,million%20infections%20occurring%20each%20year." target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;400 million infections happen each year,&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and new research suggests that &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1073/pnas.2512350122" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;climate change is increasing the burden of dengue&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; around the world (&lt;em&gt;Proc. Natl. Acad. Sci. U.S.A.&lt;/em&gt; 2025, DOI: 10.1073/pnas.2512350122). Yet it's still considered a neglected tropical disease, in part because &lt;a href="https://cen.acs.org/pharmaceuticals/drug-discovery/Small-molecule-fights-dengue-mice/99/i38" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;there's no specific FDA approved treatment for severe dengue&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. When paired with other conditions such as malnutrition or HIV, which unfortunately are common in some of the areas where dengue is prevalent, it can be deadly.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;The trial I applied for was taking place in Baltimore, which isn't exactly a dengue hot spot. In fact, cases of dengue infection in the U.S. are extremely rare, but it's relatively common for Phase 1 and 2 drug trials to take place in the U.S. even when the disease burden is located elsewhere. Often the U.S. has the academic expertise and funding to conduct these trials that lower-income countries do not.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;I had volunteered to be injected with dengue virus as part of a Phase 2 clinical trial to test the efficacy of an experimental drug at preventing severe dengue infection. There were two cohorts in the study. One group would receive the drug intravenously or a placebo a day before being given the dengue virus, and the other would receive the drug or placebo a few days after being given the dengue virus.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Before I could volunteer for anything, the CIR needed my consent — a lot of it. On two separate occasions, I reviewed a dense packet of information detailing the risks I was agreeing to, my rights as a research participant, and a code of conduct before being given an open-book test on the content, on which I needed to score 70% or better to continue.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We always say consenting is really an evolving process, and it needs to be," says &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/faculty/798/anna-p-durbin" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Anna P. Durbin&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, director of the CIR. Durbin is the principal investigator on the dengue trial I was participating in, though I never met her in person during any of the times I was at the facilities. She also oversees several other trials taking place at the CIR.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, history is fraught with examples of research being done on people without their consent. In World War II, the Nazis performed horrific medical experimentation on Jews and other people imprisoned in concentration camps. The U.S. has its own history of unethical medical study too. The Tuskegee study, which took place from the 1930s to the 1970s, withheld syphilis diagnosis and treatment from Black Americans and then monitored them over years as their health deteriorated. The Willowbrook experiments, which began in 1956 and lasted for 14 years, purposely infected children with mental disabilities with hepatitis.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;But then, in 1978, the U.S. National Commission for the Protection of Human Subjects of Biomedical and Behavioral Research published the &lt;a href="https://www.hhs.gov/ohrp/regulations-and-policy/belmont-report/read-the-belmont-report/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Belmont Report&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This landmark document outlined three core ethical principles of human research: respect for persons, which mandates informed consent and autonomy of research participants; beneficence, a fancy term for the philosophy of "Do no harm"; and justice, which ensures the benefits and risks of human research are distributed fairly.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That, in turn, led to regulation in the U.S. requiring that medical research on human participants be evaluated for good ethics by Institutional Review Boards (IRBs).&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Durbin, a member of the Johns Hopkins School of Public Health IRB, says that evaluating a clinical trial's ethics requires a detailed discussion. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"What we're really concerned with is how the volunteers are informed. Are all of the procedures ethical? What are the risks? How are they being mitigated? That sort of thing," she says. If a proposed study doesn't answer those questions sufficiently, then it's back to the drawing board to alter the methodology.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Most of the information discussed by an IRB must be communicated to the participants.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"We have to make sure that you know what's going to happen to you when you're in a study," Durbin says. "Are you being compensated or not? That's important information. What happens to your samples? Can you withdraw or can't you withdraw? Who's going to see your information?"&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;That's a lot for participants to understand. And if they don't understand it, they can't ethically consent. That's why I had to take two tests before I could volunteer. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I still think our consent forms are too long, but I think it's also difficult to exactly know what to take out to make sure that people are fully informed," Durbin says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taking a calculated risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Thanks to the consent forms, I felt as if I had a good grasp of the study. But I was still nervous.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;I was going to receive &lt;a href="https://cen.acs.org/pharmaceuticals/drug-discovery/choose-disease-fighting-molecule/103/web/2025/04" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;experimental monoclonal antibodies — &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;lab-made proteins that mimic the natural antibodies your immune system makes to fight off an infection — or a placebo . But getting the antibodies would come with no guarantee of long-term protection from dengue.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The day of dosing featured a grueling process of getting an IV infusion and repeatedly being pricked for blood draws over 5 hours while my arms bruised. Ultimately, discomfort was all I suffered on this day. Phase 1 clinical trials had all but confirmed the drug in development was safe.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The next day, a nurse injected my arm with a genetically modified version of the DENV-3 serotype of the dengue virus designed to give only mild illness rather than full-blown "break-bone fever," as the illness is known colloquially.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;I was told that the symptoms of dengue are a lot like flu symptoms, but that dengue also comes with a full-body rash, achy bones and pain behind the eyes. A week after the injection (and after an unfortunately timed weeklong bout of COVID-19), I developed all these symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;More concerning to me than the mild illness was that the consent forms also warned of a property of the dengue virus called antibody-dependent enhancement. Viruses with antibody-dependent enhancement are more dangerous the second time someone gets the disease because the virus can take advantage of a person's imperfect antibodies from a previous infection to better infect cells. So if I were to ever get dengue again, I would be at a much greater risk for severe disease. That's a risk I now carry with me for the rest of my life. What exactly made that risk acceptable?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://sph.rutgers.edu/directory/nir-eyal" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Nir Eyal&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a bioethicist at Rutgers School of Public Health, says that studies conducted on people with a medical condition take into consideration the "risk-benefit balance" when determining what is appropriate. Outside of a study setting, "sometimes it's worth taking a very risky substance when it's very beneficial for you; dangerous [chemotherapy] is worth it sometimes if your cancer is bad enough and you have no alternatives," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;For clinical trials on healthy people, the calculus is different. Eyal says calculating the appropriate level of risk happens in three stages. The first stage is to "minimize the risks, maximize or promote the benefits as much as you can," he says. For example, the genetically modified serotype of the dengue virus I was given was designed to give as mild a clinically relevant disease state as possible.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Not all risks can be designed away though, so the second stage, and the most important one according to Eyal, is to ask: Are the risks to the individual proportionate to the potential benefits for society? &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I'm not asking, Are the risks for the individual okay in light of the benefits to the individual?" he says. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The person participating in the trials is allowed to incur some risk, without receiving any medical benefit in return, so long as it's for the greater good.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The third stage of determining acceptable risk for a clinical trial is to ask, are the absolute risks to the individual simply too high, no matter how much value the trial may have for society?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But Eyal says he doesn't see the need for an upper threshold of risk to an individual in a clinical trial. He believes that as long as an individual is properly informed, that individual should be able to take on as much risk as they are willing, provided there is enough benefit to society. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"The first participants of some of the U.S. malaria challenge trials were researchers who wanted to develop the vaccine, and they volunteered," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Eyal's views on the upper limits of risk in clinical trials aren't universally held by the ethicists and researchers who make the decisions to approve clinical trials. Presently, IRBs tend to lean conservative when it comes to acceptable risks to participants — perhaps justifiably so, given the field's history of medical abuse.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;That cautiousness has led to questions about the role of paternalism in clinical trial design and implementation. It's a hot topic in discussions about clinical trial ethics.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pay and paternalism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;In compensation for being poked and prodded, looking and feeling like garbage for a few days, and making the 2½-hour round trip into the CIR facilities a total of 17 times over 5 months, I was paid roughly $3,500. That's money I'll have to pay taxes on later. Now, after all is nearly said and done, I feel it was worth my effort. That money is funding a vacation and a few upgrades around the house.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But $3,500 means different things to different people. For folks fortunate enough to have plenty tucked away in savings, it may not be compelling. And for others struggling to pay bills, it could mean keeping a roof over their head or food on the table.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Historically, the review boards that oversee clinical trial development have been hesitant to incentivize participation via large cash awards. This comes from a fear that setting compensation too high will unduly influence those who need the money to participate in something they wouldn't otherwise be willing to do, according to Durbin, though she disagrees and has advocated for higher pay.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Josh Morrison, president and cofounder of &lt;a href="https://www.1daysooner.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;1Day Sooner&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, an organization that advocates for clinical trial participants, says the logic behind compensation restriction is "wrong and patronizing and unfair to the people who join studies because they need the money."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;1Day Sooner was born out of the COVID-19 pandemic as a coalition of folks who wanted to help by participating in COVID-19 challenge studies. In the post pandemic world, 1Day Sooner now serves as a voice for participants in conversations with those who guide clinical trial development.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Morrison says that attitudes of paternalism and elitism underlie IRB fears over high compensation. But if all the efforts are made to ensure that a study is ethical in the first place, "paying more money to people doesn't affect that." It's only when studies are inherently unethical that high compensation might trick people into participating, Morrison says. And that shouldn't ever happen. Compensation should be based on the time and effort spent participating in the trial and not the risk inherent to a study, because these studies should never be excessively risky in the first place, Morrison says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.med.unc.edu/socialmed/directory/jill-fisher/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Jill Fisher&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a bioethicist at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, feels that arguments over patient compensation can sometimes ignore a bigger picture.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt; "There's all this worry that if you offer people money, they will feel compelled to do something they don't really want to do otherwise, but on the other hand, I'm more worried we're going to exploit people if we don't pay them enough,"  Fisher says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Fisher has been studying the ethics and demographics of clinical trial participation in the U.S. for over 20 years. And she says that while there isn't sufficient data to determine how many people are participating in clinical trials each year, we do know who is most likely to participate.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's mostly Black or African American participants enrolling in these studies, especially in the Northeast and then the Midwest, and then a lot of Hispanic or Latino participants in the Southwest and the Southeast," she says, adding that those who choose to participate often don't have other reliable income sources or reliable access to affordable health care.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;On the day of my IV infusion, two other trial participants were at the facilities with me. One was a graduate student at Johns Hopkins who said they wanted to do something more for science. The other participant was there "just to get some bread." Durbin asked me not to interview or provide identifying details of any of the other participants in this trial for the story, and I agreed.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"I've spoken to hundreds of people who participated in these studies. On one hand, most of them are really grateful that they have an opportunity to earn income in this way," Fisher says. "But at the same time, you could feel grateful for an opportunity but also feel exploited. And I think a lot of them do."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;According to several of the sources I spoke to, many people who participate in one trial end up participating in another. Some rely on clinical trials as one of their primary forms of income, but this is rare. More often, participants feel like there's a good reason for them to be involved in a clinical trial beyond the paycheck.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's not either-or. People can both have altruistic motivations and care about the money," Morrison says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;Firsthand testimony&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jacob-andrew-hopkins/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Jacob Hopkins&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, altruism was key in choosing to become part of a trial. Back in 2020, Hopkins became the very first person to receive a COVID-19 challenge as part of a weeks-long inpatient clinical trial taking place in the UK. &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Since taking this huge step into the world of clinical trials and the advocacy side of things for it as well, it's become a complete sort of new passion of mine," he says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/roopeshchavda/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Roopesh Chavda&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, who has now participated in two COVID-19 challenge trials, doesn't consider being a part of clinical trials a passion but does think it helps do some good for the world. It "wasn't necessarily about the money," he says. " But I would never do something like this without being paid compensation, because there are risks."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Hopkins was unemployed when he participated in his clinical trial, Chavda could work remotely during his facility stay, and I had my employer's blessing to take the time to participate in a trial.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;For those who feel like they have to participate in clinical trials out of need, there are people like Durbin, Eyal, Fisher, Morrison, and the staff I had the pleasure of working with who are trying hard to improve the experience of being a trial participant little by little.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;I felt welcomed, valued, and respected during my time as a trial participant. And I hope sharing that experience will encourage others to consider volunteering themselves.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A version of this story was republished with permission from Chemical &amp;amp; Engineering News. Copyright ©2025 by the American Chemical Society. "How do drug trials really work? I got dengue fever to find out"  was first published on May 22, 2022 and appeared in Volume 103, Issue 21. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://urldefense.com/v3/__https://cen.acs.org/pharmaceuticals/drug-development/drug-trials-really-work-dengue/103/web/2025/10?ref=search_results__;!!Iwwt!U1ln5ZoX9vcgXWi1BcbLAb8K1qU0LFG-pQ6sX57B7Zcv8yQ5RMYbJP4ra72je7M_nS-CVHcIoP8R8UKI3a3I5hA$" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://cen.acs.org/pharmaceuticals/drug-development/drug-trials-really-work-dengue/103/web/2025/10&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Max Barnhart is an assistant editor at Chemical &amp;amp; Engineering News. Previously, he was a AAAS Mass Media Fellow at NPR.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:19:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPSzdXUWl2MzFLa2w5QzVOVExfZkZTVHd0Z25acUNDenk2TGh5eS15aW9YMmhJXzlHTDJpckZTbUhibnJJdG13alJZVXF1VDloNm5iRnNIbmRyRkJCZFZGcWhwWFVCdHU1WVZpLVA3dHRiTXY0Q2VmNzZaZFJGU2UxeDNQMkhObERMXzB0cWU5U2Zsbm1yQVR3cQ</guid></item><item><title>简单的补充组合可以帮助对抗致命的脑癌- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/simple-supplement-combo-could-help-fight-deadly-brain-cancer</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Glioblastoma is a particularly aggressive  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="185587" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;, but encouraging results from a new study testing two common supplements on &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/brain-tumors-can-rewire-the-brain-and-we-just-found-out-how"&gt;glioblastoma tumors&lt;/a&gt; could potentially lead to a new way to treat the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The supplements are &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Resveratrol"&gt;resveratrol&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Copper"&gt;copper&lt;/a&gt;, both known as 'nutraceuticals': extracts from plants or food &lt;span&gt;that are thought to provide health benefits&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a study at Tata Memorial Hospital in India, 10 glioblastoma patients preparing for surgery took tablets containing both resveratrol and copper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers analyzed and compared the patients' brain tumor samples removed during surgery to those of 10 controls who also had surgery but didn't receive any supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-discover-a-viral-cause-of-one-of-the-most-common-cancers"&gt;Scientists Discover a Viral Cause of One of The Most Common Cancers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preliminary results look promising, although the researchers analyzed cell markers in the brain tumor samples, not the size or progression of the cancers that were swiftly removed, roughly two weeks after patients started taking the supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"These results suggest that a simple, inexpensive and non-toxic nutraceutical tablet potentially has the power to heal glioblastoma," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1101319"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; cancer surgeon and public health researcher Indraneel Mittra.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The combination treatment reduced a &lt;a href="https://www.cancer.gov/publications/dictionaries/cancer-terms/def/ki-67-proliferation-index"&gt;protein biomarker&lt;/a&gt; of cancer growth by almost one-third &lt;span&gt;in samples from patients who received the tablet, compared to those who didn't. However, no visible changes were seen in the tumors to suggest they were any less aggressive. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_185590" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185590" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CancerCells.jpg" alt="Cancer cell treatment diagram" class="wp-image-185590 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CancerCells.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/CancerCells-600x321.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-185590" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The treatment targets cell-free chromatin particles released from dying cells. (Bandiwadekar et al.,&lt;em&gt; BJC Rep.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found levels of certain proteins that can block immune system responses to cancer were down 41 percent, on average, in tissue samples from the treated group, compared to controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three biomarkers for  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/stem-cells" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73034" data-postid="185587" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;stem cells&lt;/a&gt;, which can contribute &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/cancers14040976"&gt;to cancer growth&lt;/a&gt;, were 56 percent lower in treated tumor samples.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No notable side effects were observed, and the  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73032" data-postid="185587" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;clinical trial&lt;/a&gt; is &lt;a href="https://ctri.nic.in/Clinicaltrials/pmaindet2.php?EncHid=NDY2Mzc=&amp;amp;Enc="&gt;ongoing&lt;/a&gt;, aiming to recruit 66 patients in total and follow them with half-yearly scans for at least 2 years. Only then will we know if the short course of supplements had any meaningful effect on patients' survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mittra and his colleagues tested resveratrol and copper because their &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41419-018-1181-x"&gt;previous studies&lt;/a&gt; have shown these supplements can 'deactivate' &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41420-023-01728-z"&gt;cell-free chromatin particles&lt;/a&gt; (cfChPs), which &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/cddiscovery201715"&gt;damage DNA&lt;/a&gt; when internalized by cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cfChPs were virtually absent in the brains of the treated glioblastoma patients, the researchers found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The cell-free chromatin particles, fragments of DNA released by dying cancer cells, inflame the surviving cancer cells," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1101319"&gt;explains&lt;/a&gt; Mittra. "This makes the disease more aggressive."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you eliminate the cell-free chromatin, which is what the resveratrol-copper tablets do, the cancer is subdued."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given glioblastoma's &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1158/1055-9965.EPI-14-0275"&gt;poor survival rates&lt;/a&gt;, scientists are trying to find &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-deadliest-kind-of-brain-cancer-may-have-a-promising-new-treatment"&gt;new and improved ways&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-common-drug-seems-to-fight-one-of-the-deadliest-brain-cancers"&gt;tackle these tumors&lt;/a&gt;, and this study might provide another avenue to explore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We have been trying to kill cancer cells for 2,500 years, since the time of the ancient Greeks, without success," &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1101319"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Mittra.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Maybe it is time to look at cancer treatment differently and work towards healing tumors, rather than annihilating them" with chemotherapy and radiotherapy, he &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1101319"&gt;adds&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team's latest findings with resveratrol and copper supplements suggest there's some value in this approach, but we'll have to wait a few years yet for the results of the completed trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s44276-025-00177-8"&gt;&lt;em&gt;BJC Reports&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 18:02:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOSnpNQWJvUG1JSlFIeUxZY1d0QjdaVllaQnlNUVdjcTFHM2I1YXU2X1ROUUVIX2t3YW1pdmRablE5RmZpU3NjZzhHdnYwejVkaFJFTy1ueGp1NHVnTy1pMGJkbENwS0xacU85dlBrUVZlNTd3Wk1vZDd3MXFybm9Sd3ZPa2s2VFUtdGdpYWQ0WDdBaFU</guid></item><item><title>一种“超级流感”变种正在流行。以下是您需要了解的信息-《西雅图时报》</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/a-super-flu-variant-is-circulating-heres-what-to-know-about-it/</link><description>&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQdDdjOVhhR2JzdENsMGcydVd5MHJqT182RDU5RFhyTld2SGU4Sm5hQ3UweGwxSVhvWU8zaUVuNkVLTFVTaVFfUnBRaXh1MnRSX2JjNVlqUDZTT2ZTQXQ2MEwtdnlrTWxvT2FFeVhsLVdUVklZa3Zxek5UMDFNZHRaSU9ubkZpSVI1eEJvUEQ0eDJ0bGhjeEpQSDRpQ0lkeDZDSzBjOUdxV0s?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;A ‘super flu’ variant is circulating. Here’s what to know about it&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiakFVX3lxTFAwMXdkTHhEMjdST0p0UDZQM3VXbFg4UXZlUGwzM3hHSmNvVmVaNHhPbkw2ZG9heUxiVEE0LVFpWE1EVmptb2Y0aWJPeVctM0l2NlJvZzVhZmJnU2tleTNfbV91MzM0bDVBOVE?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Weekly US Influenza Surveillance Report: Key Updates for Week 49, ending December 6, 2025 | FluView&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention | CDC (.gov)&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixwFBVV95cUxPcV9BSEpuYlR6RDhfejhUSFl4RnRmVEF5VjhWWTczVDFKRnpNR3ZSY0VzV3VXcDVvZWlBZi0xaThmWk1MbEx2bElrSFF5WmRLNXVkNWFlYndIRVU5WlBNdXFLYmJ1ejhoSzNtU3R6ZzVZZHYtVXhWRjhQN0hTMGktbGRGcHUyUVMtai1RQ3NLaGZXNm1aX19tSnFTekpwd3M4eDRveHVmTjR0Vlg2R1lqREpVYlotNEJ2OHd3WXA1aF9VUGZJcG40?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;New flu strain putting severe pressure on healthcare across Europe, says WHO&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Guardian&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiowFBVV95cUxQWXdPN1NpSVdfeGJfMzFFaURjWnh0VlZnSkR4TER4RVpDVEI4WW9QcVNLMmVOUlRVaGZOVnVXR1pwZV95ZDlVVnNTdTBuTkZmaDh1Q1doMHRWMXpQczY5ZHE2eGJmS2tTUTNIRDlPTUJjN0pHUnhlRElhcTFzRzhvMUNSR1g2dE5mYVlPY3p0bW5fQXBhZFQtZTdjeHVOT2xZQ0Nz?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;New Flu Variant May Be Triggering Spike in Severe Disease&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;Scientific American&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxPeEM0UXRrLUl6Q290aG1Qc1BpYVVTUU1RMzYwNmlEcDE0Z1BKQ01PZlJtVWtlcXhaZlYzNkpXZ2ppcWtpVkFRTkFTTDY0a1M2bjVxUFpfTU9ZcHRYOThodjhRSU5OYWUwc0ptLVF4UENlR1dzWXU0N25WUF9mQUg4eXY2Y2lvWWRHTndoSWJlU3NRQ3V0X1IyUjdON0ZmOVVEV1RiZ1dzZGtqcDJxdmc?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Feeling the flu: Doctors see simultaneous uptick in flu and RSV cases&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;WTOP&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:29:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxQdDdjOVhhR2JzdENsMGcydVd5MHJqT182RDU5RFhyTld2SGU4Sm5hQ3UweGwxSVhvWU8zaUVuNkVLTFVTaVFfUnBRaXh1MnRSX2JjNVlqUDZTT2ZTQXQ2MEwtdnlrTWxvT2FFeVhsLVdUVklZa3Zxek5UMDFNZHRaSU9ubkZpSVI1eEJvUEQ0eDJ0bGhjeEpQSDRpQ0lkeDZDSzBjOUdxV0s</guid></item><item><title>疫情爆发后德克萨斯州门诺人不太可能接种疫苗- Boing Boing</title><link>https://boingboing.net/2025/12/17/texas-mennonites-less-likely-to-vaccinate-after-outbreak.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Boing Boing</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 17:03:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxOOEpYV0Rsck84WjBmTjhLc1UxalZtRkxoRld3WUFwTFlqOFByZURTcVNDWEgxc1RfYjR1cEtSUGp3V2o5cERlSUl2aEt2RHdBOUVNQWF3clFoYU9abUVJNU9JS0ZpS0paQUpFSE8zU2NaaTJMVWlLWjZTS0tJVEMteEM1YzhxMFlfUzlhME5tSHFiajZJR0VhVDFDd9IBoAFBVV95cUxNZTRHbmdQQnl6dEVaMUtDOF8wUXZxV3ViMlZSaFZVT2xGdWtOYTJ1RnRoNUpnX3VnMi1CVTJlUFNjbXFLZEJfSFlmNHFNcmJ0SkE1VXJxUWtyOV85RjBMWnVma3N4MXRXS1gwZUtCajNoaHdGNHZPalNzXzdHSUVBRGF0bmZpYnpSa2w0S2xBejk2d0MzNW1RY0g3aGNfSlpj</guid></item><item><title>阿尔茨海默氏症有多常见？血液测试研究带来惊喜-自然</title><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-04133-x</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__teaser" data-test="access-teaser"&gt; &lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04133-x/d41586-025-04133-x_51836884.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04133-x/d41586-025-04133-x_51836884.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="A hand in PPE holding a blood sample vial with a screen of brain MRIs in the background." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04133-x/d41586-025-04133-x_51836884.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span class="mr10"&gt;Researchers looked for markers of Alzheimer's disease in more than 11,000 Norwegians&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Credit: Tek Image/Science Photo Library&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly one in ten people over the age of 70 have Alzheimer’s disease dementia, shows a first-of-its-kind study that paired &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03394-w" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03394-w" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;blood-based markers&lt;/a&gt; and clinical assessments to study the disease in Norway&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR1" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That prevalence is in line with previous estimates for some other white populations&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR2" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. But there were also unexpected differences, including higher disease rates than anticipated in individuals older than 85.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This is very important work from a beautiful Norwegian study,” says Nicolas Villain, a neurologist at Sorbonne University in Paris who was not involved in the research. The study, published today in &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt;, shows that blood-based tools can improve epidemiological estimates of neurodegenerative disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03394-w" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04133-x/d41586-025-04133-x_51656106.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;Blood tests are now approved for Alzheimer’s: how accurate are they?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But exactly how to use these tests remains controversial, warns Jason Karlawish, a geriatrician and co-director of the Penn Memory Center in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02928-6" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02928-6" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;Blood-based markers&lt;/a&gt; can be helpful for physicians treating people with dementia and for answering research questions, but they aren’t ready to be rolled out widely as health screening tools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is the kind of test that, in the wrong hands, could cause a lot of harm,” says Karlawish, who was not involved in the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;From blood to brain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To assess the prevalence of Alzheimer’s disease (AD), an international team of researchers turned to the Trøndelag Health (HUNT) study, a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/471020a" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/471020a" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;prospective health research study&lt;/a&gt; that started in 1984 and that has collected health data and biological samples from 250,000 Norwegians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using blood samples from 11,486 individuals in the study aged 58 and above, the team looked at levels of a protein called tau that has been phosphorylated at a specific site. Known as pTau217, this blood marker serves as a proxy for the build-up of amyloid plaque in the brain, a hallmark of AD. HUNT study participants over the age of 70 have undergone cognitive testing, enabling the researchers to compare pTau217 levels with the presence of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 10% of participants over the age of 70 had dementia and AD pathology, showing both cognitive impairment and high pTau217, they report. Another 10% had mild cognitive impairments and high pTau217. And 10% had high pTau217 but no signs of cognitive impairment, which the authors refer to as preclinical AD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings are broadly in line with expectations, but there were surprises too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some 25% of people aged 85–89 had dementia and AD pathology, up from previous estimates of around 7% for men and 13% for women in this age group in Western Europeans&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR3" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. And the incidence of preclinical AD in younger individuals was 8% in those aged 70–74, down from a previous estimate of around 22%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anders Gustavsson, a member of the team that compiled the earlier estimates, welcomes the latest data. “I'm not surprised that this study gets somewhat different numbers,” says Gustavsson, who is an adviser to the health economics consultancy Quantify Research in Stockholm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03596-2" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04133-x/d41586-025-04133-x_51687774.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;Alzheimer’s decline slows with just a few thousand steps a day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The discrepancies probably reflect selection bias, says study co-author Anita Lenora Sunde, a physician and dementia researcher at Stavanger University Hospital in Norway. Previous estimates were made by recruiting participants for brain scans, and people with dementia might not have wanted to or been able to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But other factors could also be at play, says Villain. The latest study uses a high pTau217 threshold to define its preclinical AD population, and so excludes people with intermediate levels of the protein and emerging pathology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you lower the threshold, the prevalence suddenly increases,” says Villain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The value of education&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also found that people with lower education levels have higher pTau217 levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Nature</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:50:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTE4zNmxHanVWNkV0b2dNcjFob1dpSmdrRFpnLWlvcDZoZkxyRkZFVjk4LUY2TlBoMVNBOVlWWThyZmVWNUN1dUxIYVo4YUU4b0lVWmVFVU9FbEdLQU5FZlFB</guid></item><item><title>科学家揭示了阿尔茨海默氏症的警告信号-英国《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/526cdf38-eed6-471b-93f8-704e9a231c83</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Complete digital access to quality FT journalism with expert analysis from industry leaders. Pay a year upfront and save 20%.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:16:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTFA1Q1ZzRUszMWRmNWczZmMtaDR3eDdFVWVKS1BOdk1MbF9qY1FPTVJ4d3c1SE44S1dHb2Jmb0wtbkxydFc5UnBjZ3Z1aTdmSFZfaWYzVkN5X2l2NXdsUU5ZZGtHajdXSjE1ZFBnM3BrZTI</guid></item><item><title>恢复老年免疫细胞的青春： mRNA疗法让时光倒流-自然</title><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-04082-5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__teaser" data-test="access-teaser"&gt; &lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04082-5/d41586-025-04082-5_51828806.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04082-5/d41586-025-04082-5_51828806.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="Coloured scanning electron micrograph (SEM) of a T lymphocyte (T cell) that resembles a large crumpled ball of tissue paper." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04082-5/d41586-025-04082-5_51828806.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span class="mr10"&gt;As people age, immune cells called T cells tend to decline both in quantity and in quality. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Credit: National Institutes of Health, NIAID/Science Photo Library&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A twice-weekly cocktail of three messenger RNAs can &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-01274-3" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-01274-3" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;rejuvenate the weary immune systems&lt;/a&gt; of aged mice and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-020-02856-7" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-020-02856-7" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;boost responses to vaccination&lt;/a&gt; and cancer treatments, a study has found&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR1" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The treatment provides a needed boost to immune cells called T cells, which coordinate immune responses and kill infected cells. As people age, their ability to produce T cells wanes, and the ones they have become less effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;T-cell ageing helps to explain why vaccines are sometimes less effective in older people than in young adults, and why cancer treatments that unleash the immune system against tumours don’t work as well in older adults, says María Mittelbrunn, an immunologist at the Spanish National Research Council in Madrid. Flagging T-cell immunity is also linked to the &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02788-0" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02788-0" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;chronic inflammation&lt;/a&gt; associated with many age-related diseases, including some forms of cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-024-00871-6" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04082-5/d41586-025-04082-5_26916752.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;How to make an old immune system young again&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;“T cells, in particular, are one of the cell types that change the most during ageing,” says Mittelbrunn, who was not involved in the study. “To rejuvenate them could have immense consequences.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work was reported in &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt; on 17 December and earlier this month at the American Society of Hematology annual meeting in Orlando, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Targeting T cells&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;T cells are produced in the bone marrow and then travel to a tiny gland called the thymus to mature. In the thymus, they learn to recognize and respond to pathogens such as bacteria or viruses. They also learn not to attack the body’s own healthy cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the thymus degrades with age: it begins to shrink and is gradually replaced by fatty tissue. Attempts to reverse this using hormone treatments or other drugs have not worked, says Mirco Friedrich, a haematologist and oncologist at the German Cancer Research Center in Heidelberg, and first author of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, Friedrich and his colleagues decided to take a different approach: rather than directly treating the thymus, they targeted T cells by delivering an experimental therapy to the liver. “Most T cells are in the blood,” Friedrich says. “And the liver receives the body’s whole blood volume.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-00566-6" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-04082-5/d41586-025-04082-5_50778868.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;How quickly are you ageing? What molecular ‘clocks’ can tell you about your health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;The team began by characterizing the effects of ageing on T cells in mice, cataloguing differences in gene activity and molecular signalling pathways from shortly after birth until the animals were old and frail, at about 20 months of age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Nature</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:15:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTE1hOV9jWXE0TldXOGZQR2o5d1N1VVMxZUw3eEh0aUVLb29kNVBpQVhyNWFaeFc2aDhkMERZM2tGWDA5eWU2b25tdlhvMzF0ZHY5Q2lNU2N0clRQZEEwRGJJ</guid></item><item><title>研究人员测试了阿尔茨海默氏症的疱疹药物。适得其反- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/researchers-tested-herpes-drugs-for-alzheimers-it-backfired-2000700360</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;The journey to finding an effective treatment for Alzheimer’s disease seems to have hit another dead end. The latest casualty: medications designed to tackle the viral illness herpes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers at Columbia University published the disappointing results of their randomized trial this week. Cognition in people with diagnosed herpes and early Alzheimer’s did not improve with antiviral treatment compared to a placebo—in fact, the treatment group actually fared worse. Though the findings don’t necessarily rule out a genuine link between some viral infections and Alzheimer’s, the use of these drugs for treating dementia shouldn’t be encouraged, according to outside experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“For persons with symptoms of cognitive impairment, there is no, repeat no, role for antiviral therapy,” David Knopman, a clinical neurologist at the Mayo Clinic not affiliated with the study, told Gizmodo.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The viral hypothesis&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s is the most common form of dementia, &lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/getmedia/ef8f48f9-ad36-48ea-87f9-b74034635c1e/alzheimers-facts-and-figures.pdf"&gt;affecting&lt;/a&gt; over 7 million Americans today.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The disorder is characterized by having high levels of two misfolded proteins in the brain: amyloid beta and tau. But researchers are still unsure about the exact role these proteins play in driving the disease or what triggers the chain of destruction that eventually consumes the brain.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In recent years, some research has suggested that certain viruses and other germs might be one potential cause of Alzheimer’s, or at least an important contributor to the disease—the so-called viral hypothesis of Alzheimer’s. Some studies have &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/yet-more-evidence-that-viruses-may-cause-alzheimers-dis-1827511539"&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that herpesvirus infections can trigger the build-up of amyloid beta plaques in mice with human-like brain cells, for instance, or that people who die from Alzheimer’s are &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/herpesviruses-linked-to-alzheimers-disease-in-new-brain-1827020949"&gt;more likely&lt;/a&gt; to have herpesviruses in their brains than people without the condition.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;These studies have only provided indirect evidence of a viral connection so far. But if such viruses can cause Alzheimer’s, then it might be possible to prevent or slow its progression by treating a person’s underlying infection. And that’s what these researchers set out to test.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;A study failure&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The randomized, controlled trial involved 120 participants diagnosed with probable Alzheimer’s or mild cognitive impairment likely to develop into Alzheimer’s. They also tested positive for antibodies to herpes simplex virus type 1 or 2. HSV-1 is the primary cause of cold sores, while HSV-2 most often causes genital herpes, but either type can cause the other.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For 18 months, the participants were randomized to take a daily placebo or valacyclovir (better known by the brand name Valtrex), a standard treatment used to manage HSV and other kinds of herpesvirus infections.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;By the study’s end, the treatment group saw a significantly worse progression of cognitive decline compared to the placebo. Based on imaging tests, the treatment also didn’t improve people’s brain markers or their overall neurodegeneration.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Valacyclovir was not efficacious with cognitive worsening for the primary outcome,” the researchers wrote in their paper, &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/10.1001/jama.2025.21738?guestAccessKey=2b0c16c4-ad92-4700-ad9b-ae3dea904157&amp;amp;utm_source=for_the_media&amp;amp;utm_medium=referral&amp;amp;utm_campaign=ftm_links&amp;amp;utm_content=tfl&amp;amp;utm_term=121725"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Wednesday in JAMA.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;The future of a viral link&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;As damning as these results are, they don’t completely sink the idea that viruses can contribute to at least some cases of Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It often takes time before the damaging brain changes seen in Alzheimer’s become apparent. And by the time someone is experiencing Alzheimer’s symptoms, it might simply be too late to slow the disease’s progression by treating infections that knocked the first domino down, so to speak, many years earlier.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Indeed, this might be true for other drivers of Alzheimer’s. Scientists are now &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/can-a-drug-prevent-alzheimers-disease-decades-before-it-happens-2000559730"&gt;testing&lt;/a&gt;, for instance, whether anti-amyloid drugs can prevent or slow the illness in people genetically destined to have Alzheimer’s decades before they should become sick.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;While a similar approach isn’t safe to test out with the viral hypothesis, we already have a reliable method for preventing some viral illnesses: vaccines. And &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/shingles-vaccine-doesnt-just-lower-dementia-risk-it-could-also-help-treat-it-2000695823"&gt;several&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/unique-study-is-latest-to-show-shingles-vaccine-can-prevent-dementia-2000583567"&gt;studies&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/shingles-might-be-bad-for-your-brain-2000486473"&gt;lately&lt;/a&gt; have found evidence that vaccinating people against shingles, caused by the reactivation of another herpesvirus (the varicella-zoster virus), can lower their risk of later being diagnosed with dementia.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Might there be a role at the population level for vaccination? Maybe?,” said Knopman, who wrote an editorial accompanying the study in JAMA.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To be clear, more research is needed to confirm a causative link between shingles and Alzheimer’s, as well as the potential protective role of vaccination. But it might represent the hopeful silver lining to this otherwise glum news.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:00:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxNY3VEUGpIXzI3NGVSTXhsdWpwMEE0b2xMRERoWVNRZEN5NmhUYlhEaC1heERyaDNHNmtVUkNGRHFWMURCUmMtTGJFSGFWOXREbXJuTXZfUUh0RXo0RzdrdVZ6bjFjMHNmb1F1S0R0MjZMOVhHZUE4M25tSzd3T1ZXV0ZVam1hR0FhUnFWb0xUam9tX01B</guid></item><item><title>乳制品甜甜圈引发危险过敏， United Hatzalah医务人员迅速治疗- VINnews</title><link>https://vinnews.com/2025/12/17/dairy-doughnut-triggers-dangerous-allergy-united-hatzalah-medics-give-swift-treatment/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="post-622048" class="post-622048 post type-post status-publish format-standard has-post-thumbnail category-breaking-news category-israel category-jewish category-politics category-us category-world" itemscope itemtype="https://schema.org/Article"&gt;
        

        
        &lt;div class="td-post-content tagdiv-type"&gt;
            
            &lt;p&gt;JERUSALEM (VINnews) An unusual medical emergency occurred in Jerusalem during the Hanukkah holiday, when a young man in his early 20s suffered a life-threatening allergic reaction shortly after eating a doughnut. The young man, who has a severe milk allergy, was unaware that the food he had consumed contained dairy ingredients, and within a short time began developing serious symptoms of an acute allergic reaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="whatsapp-promotion-mobile"&gt;

	&lt;a href="https://vinnews.com/2020/01/07/vin-whatsapp/"&gt;
		&lt;i class="td-icon-whatsapp"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
		Join our WhatsApp group&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
	&lt;a href="https://vinnews.com/subscribe/"&gt;
		&lt;i class="td-icon-mail"&gt;&lt;/i&gt;
		Subscribe to our Daily Roundup Email&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The incident took place in the early afternoon. Passersby who noticed the young man’s rapidly worsening condition, realized it was a serious medical emergency and immediately called emergency services. Within minutes, medical teams from United Hatzalah arrived at the scene and quickly identified the condition as anaphylaxis caused by exposure to milk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The volunteers began life-saving treatment on site, and after clarifying his medical background, decided to administer adrenaline via an EpiPen injector. Dr. Natan Unger, a volunteer physician with United Hatzalah, described the incident:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I injected the young man with adrenaline after it became clear that he is allergic to milk. In addition, he was treated with oxygen and medications until his condition stabilized.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following the rapid intervention and professional treatment, the young man’s condition improved. He was urgently evacuated to the hospital for further examinations and medical observation, fully conscious and in stable condition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="td-a-rec td-a-rec-id-content_bottom  tdi_3 td_block_template_6"&gt;

&lt;p id="avp_zid_73_mobile_bottom_of_article"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;




                &lt;p class="addthis_inline_share_toolbox"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

            

&lt;div class=""&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Follow VINnews for Breaking News Updates&lt;/h3&gt;




 






&lt;/div&gt;






&lt;/div&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;

        

    &lt;/article&gt; 

    
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VINnews</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:45:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxOc1RiSEY3ZGFJQjBZTmlVbDZSQlQwTl94azUydTN3emw0OXQ1TVd2OVdpV0k3Q3NDbzAyUkFud0tGVTZQNWlQWU41alhqWE9BSHAwSFdXOGY0cFItUzhwanpNaW9NYWRUSHZoZGFfaXJDV0hFTEYzSUp5Q2ROMkJaakxubkZ4bkJQNTBXNXFlZERBRHhVbkhJeGowU2RjWHIzMzRicnZkZm4xcWdqcHRrTWJZdW1YWDBU</guid></item><item><title>洛杉矶火灾后，心脏病发作和奇怪的验血结果飙升-洛杉矶时报</title><link>https://www.latimes.com/environment/story/2025-12-17/la-fires-heart-attacks-strange-blood-test-results-spiked</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-element="story-body" class="ct-rich-text-children font-cms-font-brand-text font-normal text-lg leading-7.75 [&amp;amp;_&amp;gt;p]:text-cms-story-body-color-text clearfix mb-10 md:max-w-170 md:mx-auto" data-subscriber-content&gt; &lt;p&gt;In the first 90 days after the Palisades and Eaton fires erupted in January, the caseload at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center’s emergency room looked different from the norm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were 46% more visits for heart attacks than typically occured during the same time period over the previous seven years. Visits for respiratory illnesses increased 24%. And unusual blood test results increased 118%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings were reported in &lt;a class="link" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.jacc.2025.10.079" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;a new study&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  published Wednesday in the Journal of the American College of Cardiology. The study, part of &lt;a class="link" href="https://lafirehealth.org/data/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;a research project &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;documenting the fires’ long-term health effects, joins several recent papers documenting the disasters’ physical toll.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While other U.S. wildfires have consumed more acres or cost more lives, the Palisades and Eaton fires were uniquely dangerous to human health because they burned an unusual mix of materials: the trees, brush and organic material of a typical wildfire, along with a toxic stew of cars, batteries, plastics, electronics and other man-made materials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s no precedent for a situation that exposed this many people to this kind of smoke, the paper’s authors said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Los Angeles has seen wildfires before, it will see wildfires again, but the Eaton fire and the Palisades fire were unique, both in their size, their scale and the sheer volume of material that burned,” said Dr. Joseph Ebinger, a Cedars-Sinai cardiologist and the paper’s first author. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team did not find a significant increase in the overall number of visits to the medical center’s emergency room between Jan. 7, the day the fires began, and April 7. The department recorded fewer in-person visits for mental health emergencies and chronic conditions during that time compared to the same time period in earlier years, said Dr. Susan Cheng, director of public health research at Cedars-Sinai and the study’s senior author.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The increase in visits for acute cardiovascular problems and other serious sudden illnesses made up the difference. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study team also looked at results from blood tests drawn from patients visiting the ER for serious physical symptoms without immediate explanation — dizziness without dehydration, for example, or chest pains not caused by heart attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their blood tests returned unusual results at a rate more than double that seen in previous years. These atypical numbers cut across the spectrum of the blood panel, Cheng said. “It could be electrolyte disorder, change in protein levels, change in markers of kidney or liver function.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rate of unusual test results held steady through the three-month period, leading the team to conclude that exposure to the fires’ smoke “has led to some kind of biochemical metabolic stress in the body that likely affected not just one but many organ systems,” Cheng said. “That’s what led to a range of different types of symptoms affecting different people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Joan Casey, an environmental epidemiologist at the University of Washington who was not part of the Cedars-Sinai team, noted that the study found health effects lasting over a longer period than similar studies have.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three months “is a substantial length of time to observe elevated visits, as most studies focused on acute care utilization following wildfire smoke exposure find increased visit counts over about a weeklong period,” Casey said. Her &lt;a class="link" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama-health-forum/fullarticle/2842059" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;own research&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; found a 27% increase in outpatient respiratory visits among Kaiser Permanente Southern California members living within 12.4 miles of the burn zones in the week following the fires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The L.A. fires were such a severe event, including not only smoke, but also evacuation and substantial stress in the population, that effects may have lingered longer,” Casey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thirty-one people are known to have died as a direct result of injuries sustained in the fires. But researchers believe that when taking into account deaths from health conditions worsened by the smoke, the true toll is significantly higher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a class="link" href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/article-abstract/2837351#" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;research letter published earlier this year&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in the Journal of the American Medical Assn. calculated that there were &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.latimes.com/california/story/2025-08-06/deaths-from-eaton-and-palisades-fires-could-top-400"&gt;&lt;u&gt;440 excess deaths&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in L.A. County between Jan. 5 and Feb. 1. That paper looked at deaths caused by a variety of factors, from exposure to air pollution to disrupted healthcare as a result of closures and evacuations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Tuesday, a team from Stanford University &lt;a class="link" href="https://pubs.acs.org/doi/10.1021/acs.estlett.5c01089" target="_blank"&gt;published itsprojection&lt;/a&gt; that exposure to the fires’ smoke, specifically, led to 14 deaths otherwise unaccounted for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wildfire is a major source of fine particulate pollution, bits measuring 2.5 microns or less in diameter that are small enough to cross the barriers that separate blood from the brain and the lungs’ outer branches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared with other sources, wildfire smoke contains a higher proportion of ultrafine particles miniscule enough to penetrate the brain after inhalation, Casey told The Times &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.latimes.com/environment/newsletter/2025-08-07/climate-change-physical-costs"&gt;&lt;u&gt;earlier this year&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. The smoke has been linked to a range of health problems, including dementia, cancer and cardiovascular failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the last decade, increasing numbers of wildfires in Western states have released &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-023-06522-6" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;u&gt;enough fine particulate pollution&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.latimes.com/environment/story/2022-06-17/2020-california-wildfires-offset-decades-of-air-quality-gains"&gt;&lt;u&gt;reverse years’ worth&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of improvements under the Clean Air Act and other antipollution measures. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Los Angeles Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxORFNkUE5zaE8xa1lwMGl0eV94aElSM1ZTV0dkZUZKc216UEkxRzd1eTZieDJmd0VxdWEtODVYaTJhMVlkRFJOV18xV2JveGF6V3l4QlhLanNaOThuUlZ2X3E5UThPZVd2RVFaTWtyemp5UFpFQmVRV0xjZFFsTFV1bERqczhMaDhlTk9Vbi0wQ3NlNDZ2S2FlUHVSenl3amFGX0ZpTGx5bWJvbkRaakE</guid></item><item><title>在重大政策转变中，美国疾控中心终止了所有新生儿都应接种乙型肝炎疫苗的指导-路透社</title><link>https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/us-cdc-accepts-advisers-recommendations-hepatitis-b-vaccine-major-policy-shift-2025-12-16/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Reuters</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:55:20 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5AFBVV95cUxPZlpkdnJqUmFrUHdseGU3aDR1emVLeU1KdWo1dWJZWVhTOWc2b3g3bXFrSzRKSllOVXp2ZVJPNHIzRjNnSWJ4TkIwalZ4OEdOeUpEc0FFcElYeFFRMkV4ZzZoZE0xeWZJWDVmeVAtZDN1UElyRzkzV1BFYzgwUFJDWW45WC1TeTZsQnlYRlJkcG1mT2hvcktLSWtHYno2VjZHM2dLLVk2N18zR2stbTNXX2RUbjQ3XzhBV3o1U0N5a1hPZDF6Y056WG1pQ0p2OEw4ZlN1T0lkRkxEdEF2c21sc1d6QUo</guid></item><item><title>他吃了一个汉堡，几小时后就死了。医生发现了一个令人震惊的事业- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251217082457.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Researchers at the University of Virginia School of Medicine have confirmed the first known death caused by the condition commonly referred to as the meat allergy, which is transmitted by ticks.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The case involved a 47 year old man from New Jersey who was previously healthy and died suddenly about four hours after eating beef. For months, the cause of his death remained unclear. That changed when Thomas Platts Mills, MD, PhD, a UVA Health physician and internationally recognized allergy specialist, took a closer look. Platts Mills originally identified the condition years ago and continues to lead research into how it affects patients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How Lone Star Tick Bites Trigger Alpha Gal Allergy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The allergy develops after a bite from the Lone Star tick. These bites can cause the immune system to become sensitive to alpha gal, a sugar naturally found in meat from mammals. Once sensitized, people may experience allergic symptoms after eating foods such as beef, pork, or lamb. Common reactions include skin rashes, nausea, and vomiting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists have long suspected that severe cases could escalate into life threatening anaphylaxis. Until now, however, no fatal cases had been officially confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The important information for the public is: First, that severe abdominal pain occurring 3 to 5 hours after eating beef, pork or lamb should be investigated as a possible episode of anaphylaxis; and, second, that tick bites that itch for more than a week or larvae of ticks often called 'chiggers' can induce or increase sensitization to mammalian-derived meat," said Platts Mills, former chief of UVA Health's Division of Asthma, Allergy and Clinical Immunology. "On the other hand, most individuals who have mild to moderate episodes of hives can control symptoms with an appropriate diet."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Happened Before the Man's Death&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The man, whose name was not made public, had gone camping with his wife and children during the summer of 2024. One evening, the family ate a late steak dinner at 10 p.m. Around 2 a.m., the man woke up with intense stomach pain, diarrhea, and vomiting. Although he felt better by morning, he later told his son that the episode had felt life threatening.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;About two weeks later, still unaware that he had developed the meat allergy, he attended a barbeque and ate a hamburger. He began feeling unwell shortly after 7 p.m. At 7:37 p.m., his son found him collapsed in the bathroom.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Autopsy Raises More Questions Than Answers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An autopsy did not reveal a clear explanation for his death. The official cause was listed as "sudden unexplained death."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;His wife was not satisfied with that conclusion and asked another physician to review the findings. That doctor contacted Platts Mills and his team to explore whether alpha gal sensitivity could be involved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blood Tests Reveal Severe Allergic Reaction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Platts Mills obtained blood samples that had been collected after the man's death. Testing showed that he had indeed been sensitized to alpha gal. The results also pointed to an extreme immune response consistent with fatal anaphylaxis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When asked about recent tick exposure, the man's wife said he had not noticed any tick bites in the past year. However, she recalled that he had suffered 12 or 13 itchy bites around his ankles earlier in the summer, which they believed were caused by chiggers. Platts Mills recognized that many bites thought to be from chiggers in the eastern United States are actually from Lone Star tick larvae.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Factors That May Have Worsened the Reaction&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Platts Mills and his colleagues believe several conditions may have intensified the man's allergic response. These include drinking a beer with the hamburger, exposure to ragweed pollen, and physical exercise earlier that day. Family members also noted that he rarely ate red meat, which may have influenced how his immune system reacted.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Growing Tick Populations Increase Risk&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Following the case, Platts Mills is urging doctors to stay alert for patients who may have developed this allergy or who face higher exposure risk. He pointed out that deer populations are rapidly increasing in many states, creating ideal conditions for the Lone Star tick to spread.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It is important that both doctors and patients who live in an area of the country where Lone Star ticks are common should be aware of the risk of sensitization," Platts Mills said. "More specifically, if they have unexpected episodes of severe abdominal pain occurring several hours after eating mammalian meat, they should be investigated for possible sensitization to the oligosaccharide alpha-gal."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Case Findings Published in Medical Journal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Details of the case have been published in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology: In Practice&lt;/em&gt;. The article is open access, meaning it is available to read for free. The authors include Platts Mills, Lisa J. Workman, Nathan E. Richards, Jeffrey M. Wilson, and Erin M. McFeely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research team obtained consent from the man's widow before releasing the findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 14:32:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFBJU3d0NURIMGVTaFBDUlVnMnhoZEpkNm5aRG5NRWduMW1FZDFwOHdvWVV0X1lLSXgyTHJid29TdU9PNU9sa3RNLThQVDdBYXZ3bWRPdWNsbEdUdzVjZk1aYV9UbXpENFl2Tjd3OGtZVQ</guid></item><item><title>如果您年满65岁，仍然可以在没有帮助的情况下做这10件事，那么您将是一个难得的人- VegOut</title><link>https://vegoutmag.com/lifestyle/a-bt-if-youre-over-65-and-can-still-do-these-10-things-without-help-youre-a-rare-gem-of-a-person/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page__content mt-4"&gt;
							&lt;p&gt;Getting older is a privilege denied to many, but let's be honest about something. There's a massive difference between simply aging and aging well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I see it all the time when I visit my parents and their friends. Some folks in their 70s are still climbing mountains and starting new businesses, while others the same age struggle with basic daily tasks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What separates these two groups? It's not just genetics or luck. After watching my own parents navigate their 60s and 70s, and spending countless hours with older adults through my volunteer work, I've noticed that those who maintain certain abilities well into their later years share something special. They possess a combination of physical capability, mental sharpness, and emotional resilience that truly makes them exceptional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're over 65 and can still manage these 10 things without assistance, you're not just doing well. You're absolutely thriving in ways that many people half your age can't claim.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;1. Managing your finances independently&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can you still balance your checkbook, manage online banking, and make sound financial decisions without relying on others? This might sound basic, but financial literacy and independence become increasingly challenging as we age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I spent years as a financial analyst before becoming a writer, and I've seen how complex financial management can become.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Between changing technology, evolving scams, and the sheer volume of decisions required, maintaining financial independence requires sharp cognitive skills and adaptability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ability to track expenses, understand investment statements, and spot potential fraud shows that your analytical thinking and decision-making abilities remain intact. Many people start handing over financial responsibilities to their children by this age, but if you're still confidently managing your money, you're demonstrating exceptional mental acuity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;2. Learning new technology&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember when smartphones seemed impossibly complicated? Now think about the people over 65 who not only use them but actually embrace new apps, video calling, and social media platforms.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're someone who can set up a new device, troubleshoot basic tech issues, and adapt to software updates without calling for help every time, you're in rare company. Research shows that continued learning, especially in unfamiliar areas like technology, helps maintain cognitive flexibility and may even delay age-related mental decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;3. Driving safely at night&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Night driving becomes increasingly difficult with age due to natural changes in vision and reaction times. If you're still comfortable and safe behind the wheel after dark, your visual processing and reflexes are functioning at a remarkably high level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This isn't just about seeing clearly. It's about processing multiple streams of information simultaneously, making split-second decisions, and maintaining the confidence to navigate challenging conditions. Many people voluntarily give up night driving long before 65.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;4. Maintaining a regular exercise routine&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I discovered trail running at 28 as a way to handle work stress, and now I log 20-30 miles weekly. But here's what amazes me: I regularly get passed on trails by runners in their 70s who move with more grace and endurance than people decades younger.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're over 65 and still maintaining a consistent exercise routine, whether it's swimming, hiking, yoga, or strength training, you're preserving not just physical health but also discipline and mental fortitude. The ability to push through discomfort and maintain motivation for physical activity becomes increasingly precious with age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;5. Cooking elaborate meals from scratch&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cooking involves so much more than following a recipe. It requires planning, multitasking, fine motor skills, and sensory awareness. Can you still prepare a holiday dinner for the family, trying new recipes and managing multiple dishes simultaneously?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This capability demonstrates intact executive functioning, creativity, and physical stamina. Standing for extended periods, chopping vegetables with precision, and coordinating timing for multiple dishes are complex tasks that many people begin to find overwhelming as they age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;6. Traveling solo&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Solo travel at any age requires courage, but after 65, it demands exceptional self-reliance. Navigating airports, managing bookings, adapting to unexpected changes, and exploring new places independently showcase remarkable cognitive and physical resilience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you're still comfortable setting off on adventures alone, trusting your judgment and ability to handle whatever comes your way, you possess a level of confidence and capability that many people lose long before reaching your age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;7. Maintaining and nurturing friendships&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social connections often dwindle with age, but if you're actively maintaining friendships, making new friends, and nurturing these relationships without depending entirely on family for social interaction, you're demonstrating exceptional emotional intelligence and social skills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This involves remembering important dates, initiating contact, planning gatherings, and being emotionally available for others. These seemingly simple acts require significant cognitive and emotional energy that many people find increasingly difficult to sustain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;8. Reading complex books and retaining information&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Can you still dive into a dense novel or non-fiction book, follow intricate plots or arguments, and discuss them intelligently afterward? This level of sustained concentration and comprehension is increasingly rare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reading comprehension at this level requires working memory, focus, and the ability to connect new information with existing knowledge. If you're still eagerly tackling challenging books and retaining what you read, your cognitive reserves are remarkably well-preserved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;9. Managing home maintenance&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether it's changing light bulbs, basic repairs, gardening, or organizing spaces, maintaining your living environment independently requires physical capability, problem-solving skills, and the confidence to tackle challenges.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When I helped my parents downsize, I was struck by how many of their peers had already surrendered these tasks to others. If you're still handling home maintenance yourself, you're demonstrating physical agility, spatial awareness, and the mental sharpness to troubleshoot problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;10. Advocating for yourself in medical settings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Healthcare becomes increasingly complex with age. Can you still research your conditions, ask informed questions, challenge recommendations when necessary, and make confident decisions about your care?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This requires processing complex medical information, remembering details across multiple appointments, and maintaining the assertiveness to ensure your voice is heard. Many people become passive in medical settings as they age, but if you're still your own best advocate, you possess exceptional cognitive function and self-confidence.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Final thoughts&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you checked off most or all of these abilities, you truly are exceptional. These aren't just random skills; they represent the full spectrum of human capability: physical, cognitive, emotional, and social functioning at the highest level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What's your secret? Maybe it's staying curious, remaining physically active, maintaining social connections, or simply refusing to accept limitations as inevitable. Whatever it is, keep doing it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if you're younger and reading this, take note. The habits and attitudes you develop now lay the foundation for how you'll age. Every time you learn something new, push yourself physically, or maintain important relationships, you're investing in your future self.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Age might be just a number, but the ability to live fully and independently at any age? That's priceless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="vegou-quiz-after-article" id="vegou-83838560"&gt;&lt;p&gt;				 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong data-start="380" data-end="431"&gt;VegOut Magazine’s November Edition Is Out!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;In our latest Magazine “&lt;em&gt;Curiosity, Compassion &amp;amp; the Future of Living&lt;/em&gt;” you’ll get FREE access to:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– 5 in-depth articles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– Insights across Lifestyle, Wellness, Sustainability &amp;amp; Beauty&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– Our Editor’s Monthly Picks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;– 4 exclusive Vegan Recipes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://vegoutmag.com/magazine-november-2025/"&gt;&lt;button class="buttonStyle buttonStyleAlternate"&gt;Learn more&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="g-ytsubscribe" data-channelid="UCdGKHK52616Dpj-FpFjeNSg" data-layout="full" data-count="hidden"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 			&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;						&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>VegOut</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:52:10 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiyAFBVV95cUxQdUhtajFIRndQRW1xQnZXSUYtcVppdHFOWE5lWnNXSjdVak1RdjloZVdQLXl1T0JXbDNaRXo5eElsaVl6S2Utc0dSdUdiSjBSa2dYMjNVS3F4RXFJQUdLZ211eFRCQUQ1TnBoeWJSY3U3V1BoQ0ZEUVV4UUxjUVA5TUdONktuYWdGSEZ4dGZ4dy1iQzhLYXBxOUhfbVlYTnJlWUZDTkhVaTZCQnJFejdSSkoyZjB0Yk55dkRBVlF0V29qVWJRbGEwVA</guid></item><item><title>七个让人感觉良好的科学故事，让您在2025年重拾信念--大自然</title><link>https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03505-7</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__teaser" data-test="access-teaser"&gt; &lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03505-7/d41586-025-03505-7_51828434.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03505-7/d41586-025-03505-7_51828434.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="An aerial view of the sun setting behind wind turbines and rows of solar panels at a wind farm in China." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03505-7/d41586-025-03505-7_51828434.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span class="mr10"&gt;Renewable-energy milestones were met in 2025, with China being the first country to surpass 1 terawatt in installed solar-power capacity. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Credit: Chen Kun/VCG via Getty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-04051-y" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-04051-y" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;biggest science story this year&lt;/a&gt; was the political upheaval in the United States. &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/collections/jcjhabjhgi" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/collections/jcjhabjhgi" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;Funding cuts, academic lay-offs&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03625-0" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03625-0" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;vaccine-sceptic policies&lt;/a&gt; have widely been seen as an attack on science, according to critics of President Donald Trump’s administration. The resulting damage to science could last &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02748-8" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02748-8" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;way into the future&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, there were also plenty of positive developments in 2025 that &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-04049-6" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-04049-6" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;offer hope for the coming years&lt;/a&gt;. “From a non-US scientist, it’s somewhat business as usual. You just keep doing your job”, says Glen Peters, a climate-policy researcher at the Cicero Center for International Climate Research in Oslo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our recent &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/immersive/d41586-025-03848-1/index.html" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/immersive/d41586-025-03848-1/index.html" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;Nature's 10 package&lt;/a&gt; includes many good news stories — and there were many more. From gene-editing firsts to rapid disease containment and policy victories, &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt; takes a look at some positive science stories of 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/immersive/d41586-025-03848-1/index.html" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03505-7/d41586-025-03505-7_51821830.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt;’s 10: Ten people who shaped science in 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Species recovery&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year saw populations of some endangered and near-extinct species bounce back owing to strong conservation efforts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The green sea turtle (&lt;i&gt;Chelonia mydas&lt;/i&gt;), which has been endangered since the 1980s, has now moved to ‘least concern’ on the International Union for Conservation of Nature (IUCN) red list. Efforts to protect the turtle’s eggs and measures to prevent their accidental capture in fishing nets have allowed populations to recover. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ampurta (&lt;i&gt;Dasycercus hillieri&lt;/i&gt;), a rat-sized Australian marsupial, moved from near-extinction to &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02586-8" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-02586-8" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;‘least concern’ this year&lt;/a&gt;. Between 2015 and 2021, ampurta territory expanded by more than 48,000 square kilometres, despite dry conditions and food shortages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, nations reached a &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-01545-7" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-01545-7" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;historic milestone for marine conservation&lt;/a&gt; in September with the United Nations High Seas Treaty receiving approval from more than 60 countries. The treaty, which will come into effect in January, aims to legally protect biodiversity in international waters and conserve at least 30% of land and sea areas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ozone hole shrinks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hole in the Antarctic ozone layer has shrunk to its smallest size since 2019, indicating the continued recovery of Earth’s protective upper atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ozone hole was first discovered in 1985 and is a result of human-emitted ozone-depleting chlorofluorocarbons (CFCs), such as coolants in refrigerators and aerosol sprays. The Montreal Protocol in 1987 phased out the production and use of CFCs, which has successfully curbed emissions&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR1" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; . Since 1987, the average size of the ozone hole throughout the year has been gradually decreasing in size, with the smallest so far in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ozone hole is on track to recover completely in the late 2060s, provided efforts to find climate-friendly alternatives to CFCs continues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="figure"&gt;&lt;picture class="embed intensity--high"&gt;&lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03505-7/d41586-025-03505-7_51828432.jpg?as=webp 767w, //media.nature.com/lw319/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03505-7/d41586-025-03505-7_51828432.jpg?as=webp 319w" sizes="(max-width: 319px) 319px, (min-width: 1023px) 100vw,  767px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img class="figure__image" alt="A 3D rendering of the ozone hole swirling above Antartica as measured on the 13th September 2025." loading="lazy" src="//media.nature.com/lw767/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03505-7/d41586-025-03505-7_51828432.jpg"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;p class="figure__caption u-sans-serif"&gt;&lt;span class="mr10"&gt;The hole in the Antarctic ozone layer has continued to shrink.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Credit: CAMS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Gene-editing successes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year “was a breakthrough year for gene editing,” says David Liu, a chemical biologist at the Broad Institute of MIT and Harvard in Cambridge, Massachusetts. “In 2025, these technologies have achieved a number of medical milestones.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I view this year as an outstanding one, marked by the launch of many clinical trials”, adds Annarita Miccio, who studies gene therapy at the Imagine Institute at the Necker Hospital for Sick Children in Paris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03139-9" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03505-7/d41586-025-03505-7_51762526.png"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;Huntington’s disease treated for the first time using gene therapy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first gene therapy for Huntington’s disease proved striking, slowing the rate of cognitive &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03842-7" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03842-7" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;decline in participants by 75%&lt;/a&gt;. Another gene-therapy trial for T-cell acute lymphoblastic leukaemia showed promise with the majority of 11 participating children and adults entering remission&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR2" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;. The new type of CAR-T-cell therapy uses base-editing technology to modify several genes in T cells, helping them to target the cancer cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers also trialled the first use of a CRISPR technology &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03847-2" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03847-2" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;tailored to an individual this year&lt;/a&gt;. Other successes include the first clinical trial for a gene therapy to treat a rare immune disorder called chronic granulomatous disease&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR3" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;3&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, and another that corrected a pathogenic mutation, which can cause lung damage and liver disease&lt;sup&gt;&lt;a href="#ref-CR4" data-track="click" data-action="anchor-link" data-track-label="go to reference" data-track-category="references"&gt;4&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These clinical trials paved the way for developing mutation-specific strategies for rare diseases and demonstrated that collaboration between academia and industry can lead to cures for people with such diseases, says Miccio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Renewable-energy boost&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Renewable energy surpassed coal as the largest energy source for the first time globally this year. The achievement was helped by China becoming the first country in the world to install 1 terawatt of solar power capacity in May. In the first six months of 2025 alone, China installed new solar systems with a capacity of 256 gigawatts — twice as much as the rest of the world combined. The country plans to add a further 200–300 gigawatts of capacity for solar and wind energy in its &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03491-w" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03491-w" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;five year plan, beginning in 2026.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;article class="recommended pull pull--left u-sans-serif" data-label="Related"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03802-1" class="u-link-inherit" data-track="click" data-track-label="recommended article"&gt;&lt;img class="recommended__image" alt="" src="//media.nature.com/w400/magazine-assets/d41586-025-03505-7/d41586-025-03505-7_51757176.jpg"&gt;&lt;p class="recommended__title u-serif"&gt;What happened at COP30? 4 science take-homes from the climate summit&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“China and many developing countries are deploying solar and wind [and] electric vehicles at pretty breakneck pace,” says Peters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around half of the European Union’s demand for electricity came from from renewables in the second and third quarters of this year. Renewable-energy capacity is projected to increase by almost 4,600 gigawatts between 2025 and 2030 — double the capacity deployed between 2019 and 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, greenhouse-gas emissions from fossil fuels &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03618-z" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03618-z" data-track-category="body text link"&gt;reached&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03618-z" data-track="click" data-label="https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-025-03618-z" data-track-category="body text link"&gt; a new high this year&lt;/a&gt;. It remains to be seen whether renewable energy can replace fossil fuels as the dominant global energy sources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ebola contained&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
                        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Nature</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:40:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiX0FVX3lxTFAwVmotTDNuSWEtdy1Lcll3TVlUckdwNWtXZUFkVUl6a1U5aE5Ia3dlR09iNVpGSkwtVWgxYlNDVnBGYkNXeUVxQm1aQm1DbWJZanUzMkFkbE94NVBpdnJn</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现社交焦虑的生物足迹可能部分存在于肠道中- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/scientists-find-the-biological-footprint-of-social-anxiety-may-reside-partially-in-the-gut/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;New research published in the &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jad.2025.120597" target="_blank"&gt;Journal of Affective Disorders&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; provides evidence that the gut microbiome may play a functional role in the development of social anxiety disorder. The study found that transplanting gut bacteria from adolescents with social anxiety into newborn rats induced anxiety-like behaviors and altered brain chemistry in the animals. These findings suggest that specific alterations in the gut-brain axis could contribute to the pathology of social anxiety during adolescence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social anxiety disorder is a prevalent mental health condition characterized by an intense and persistent fear of social situations and negative evaluation by others. While psychological therapies and medications exist, they are not effective for every patient. This has led scientists to investigate alternative biological systems that might contribute to the disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gut-brain axis has emerged as a significant area of interest. This term refers to the bidirectional communication network between the gastrointestinal tract and the central nervous system. Previous studies have linked gut microbiota differences to various psychiatric conditions, including depression and autism spectrum disorder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While earlier observations have indicated that people with social anxiety might have different gut bacteria than healthy individuals, it has been unclear if these microbial differences caused the symptoms or were merely a consequence of the disorder. A team of researchers led by Jinghong Chen of Shanghai Jiao Tong University School of Medicine sought to move beyond simple correlation by using an experimental model to test for causality. They focused on adolescence because this is a critical period for brain development and is often when social anxiety symptoms first manifest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our study was driven by both a pressing clinical reality and a compelling scientific inspiration,” explained co-author Junyu Lai, a member of &lt;a href="https://www.smhc.org.cn/keylab" target="_blank"&gt;Chen’s research laboratory&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“First, the real-world problem: Social anxiety disorder is a prevalent and often disabling condition that typically emerges during adolescence. As clinicians and researchers, we have long noticed that current first-line treatments—such as pharmacotherapy and psychotherapy—often show limited effectiveness and do not work for every child. We urgently need new therapeutic avenues that are safer and more accessible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Second, we drew significant inspiration from the ‘gut-brain axis,’ particularly the high-impact research linking gut microbiota to the pathogenesis of autism spectrum disorder,” Lai explained. “Seeing how profound the gut’s influence is in autism, we asked ourselves: Could a similar disruption in the gut microbiome be driving social anxiety disorder?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This question motivated us to explore whether social anxiety disorder patients exhibit a distinct gut microbial environment. Our hope is that by confirming this link, we can pave the way for a new generation of treatments—interventions focused on maintaining gut health. We believe this could offer a more economical, safer, and sustainable long-term solution for managing social anxiety disorder symptoms, ultimately improving the quality of life for young patients.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To conduct the study, the research team recruited 40 adolescents diagnosed with social anxiety disorder from the Shanghai Mental Health Center and local communities. They also enrolled 32 healthy control participants who were matched for age and gender. The researchers imposed strict inclusion criteria to ensure the results were not influenced by other factors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All participants with social anxiety were experiencing their first episode of the disorder, had no other psychiatric comorbidities, and had never taken psychiatric medication. The team collected fecal samples from all participants to analyze the genetic composition of their gut bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers used a fecal microbiota transplantation method to test the effects of these bacteria on brain development. They pooled the fecal samples from the anxiety group and the healthy group into two distinct composites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They then administered these microbiota suspensions to newborn rats. The treatment began on the first day of life and continued daily until the rats reached late adolescence. This method differs from many similar studies that use adult rats treated with antibiotics to deplete their natural bacteria. The authors chose to colonize newborn rats to mimic the natural developmental process and avoid the potential side effects of high-dose antibiotics, which can independently cause anxiety in rodents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once the rats reached adolescence, the researchers evaluated them using a series of behavioral tests. They used an open field test to assess general anxiety and locomotor activity. In this test, anxious animals typically stick to the walls and avoid the center of the arena.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also employed an elevated plus maze, which consists of open and enclosed arms raised above the ground. Rats with lower anxiety levels typically explore the open arms, while anxious rats prefer the safety of the enclosed spaces. Finally, the team used a three-chamber social test to measure sociability and social novelty preference. This test observes how much time a rat spends interacting with a stranger rat compared to an empty cage or a familiar rat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis of the human samples revealed that the gut microbiota composition in adolescents with social anxiety differed from that of the healthy controls. While the overall diversity of the bacterial community was similar, specific bacterial genera showed significant variance. The anxiety group had higher levels of a genus called &lt;em&gt;Prevotella&lt;/em&gt; and lower levels of &lt;em&gt;Parasutterella&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Unlike studies on autism, where the gut microbiota composition often shows drastic structural shifts, the changes we observed in social anxiety patients appeared relatively subtle,” Lai told PsyPost. “This initially raised concerns within our team about whether these microbial differences were sufficient to drive the pathology. However, the results from our animal models provided a compelling and encouraging turning point.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The behavioral results in the rats mirrored the clinical picture seen in humans. The rats that received the microbiota from the social anxiety patients exhibited distinct anxiety-like behaviors. In the open field test, these rats spent less time exploring the center zone compared to the control group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similarly, in the elevated plus maze, the anxiety-colonized rats ventured into the open arms less frequently. In the social testing, these rats demonstrated a reduced preference for social novelty. While they still interacted with other rats, they did not show the typical preference for investigating a new, unfamiliar rat over a rat they had already met. This indicates a potential deficit in social processing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following the behavioral tests, the researchers analyzed the medial prefrontal cortex (MFC) of the rats. This brain region is essential for regulating emotions and processing social information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis revealed distinct metabolic changes in the brains of the rats colonized with anxiety-associated bacteria. The researchers identified alterations in several metabolites, including lower levels of beta-carotene and changes in amino acids such as threonine and aspartic acid. The researchers noted that the decline in &lt;em&gt;Parasutterella&lt;/em&gt; in the gut was associated with changes in cholesterol and bile acid metabolism. These metabolic shifts in the brain were correlated with the anxiety-like behaviors observed during testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The most significant takeaway is that social anxiety disorder appears to have a distinct biological footprint in the gut,” Lai explained. “Our study confirmed that the gut microbiota composition in adolescents with social anxiety disorder is different from that of healthy peers.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“More importantly, we found that this is not just a correlation. When we transplanted this ‘anxiety-associated microbiota’ into rats, the animals began to exhibit anxiety-like behaviors and social deficits, mirroring the human symptoms. We even observed specific metabolic changes in the MFC, a brain region critical for social processing. This provides compelling evidence that the gut-brain axis plays a functional role in the pathology of social anxiety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some limitations to this study that affect how the results should be interpreted. The human participants were all Han Chinese adolescents, meaning the findings may not generalize to adults or people of other ethnicities. The study identified changes in the bacterial community as a whole but did not pinpoint the specific bacterial strains or metabolites responsible for the behavioral effects. Additionally, the researchers did not measure markers of the immune system or the stress response system, which are likely involved in transmitting signals from the gut to the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I want to be very clear about what this means—and what it doesn’t mean yet,” Lai said. “We haven’t found a ‘magic pill’ yet: We have not yet pinpointed the specific bacteria or metabolites responsible for these changes. We know the community has an effect, but we don’t know the exact ‘key players.'”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our study focused specifically on treatment-naïve Han Chinese adolescents to ensure a clean experimental baseline. We need further research to confirm if these findings apply to adults, other ethnicities, or broader populations. The picture is still incomplete: We have not yet fully mapped how this interacts with other body systems, such as the immune system or the HPA (stress) axis.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Future research will need to address these gaps by examining larger and more diverse populations. The authors plan to investigate the specific bacterial species that drive these changes and explore the intermediate pathways, such as immune signaling. While the results are promising for understanding the biology of social anxiety, they do not yet provide a basis for clinical treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our current study is just the beginning, and acknowledging our limitations points us directly toward our future research directions,” Lai explained. “We have mapped out three key steps.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“First, we aim to move from ‘community’ to ‘specificity’. In this study, we observed the effects of the whole gut microbiota community. However, as noted in our limitations, we have not yet pinpointed the specific bacterial taxa or the precise metabolites responsible for the observed effects. Our next step is to isolate and identify the specific ‘key players’—whether it is a particular bacterial strain or a specific metabolic byproduct—that directly drives the metabolic changes we saw in the mPFC.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Second, we plan to map the full ‘communication highway’ between the gut and the brain,” Lai said. “While we confirmed the endpoint (mPFC metabolic changes) and the starting point (gut dysbiosis), our current study did not comprehensively measure the intermediate pathways, such as the immune system or the HPA (hypothalamic-pituitary-adrenal) axis. In future studies, we intend to integrate these systemic factors to fully understand how the gut signals reach the brain—whether through immune activation, hormonal pathways, or direct neural routes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Finally, we need to test the generalizability of our findings. Our current cohort consisted specifically of treatment-naïve Han Chinese adolescents. To ensure our findings are universally applicable, we plan to expand our research to larger, more diverse populations, including different age groups and ethnicities. This will help us determine if the gut-brain mechanisms we discovered are consistent across all SAD patients or specific to certain developmental stages.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jad.2025.120597" target="_blank"&gt;Gut microbiota from adolescents with social anxiety disorder is associated with behavioral alterations and metabolic changes in the medial prefrontal cortex&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Junyu Lai, Beibei Yang, Peijun Ju, Ying Sun, Xiujia Sun, Wenhong Cheng, and Jinghong Chen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 13:07:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxQc3BCYmZqR1VhYkVpeTZycWVPdGJkTkpxdE9QdWE0eW9GN1VHREY1SHdKQ2tWQ1NKSW80andCX1l0VURvelo5WHBpTTFtcmdrSFZiSUpfT1IxRVg1aDNBX2JJX1ZEZ1lEVGMzeVRHaU9zVUtEWDdOLXlaVEZCTEoxMDZFOEJuMlRxaWxNNVNBdzQ5V0dKZmVKbmpyYkc3OXRKbVdpU1daSnNVSnREUFhuYUdLSHZsdw</guid></item><item><title>关于性的6个主要迷思和误解，揭穿-心理牙线</title><link>https://www.mentalfloss.com/science/sex-myths-misconceptions-debunked</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content [&amp;amp;_p]:leading-[30px] [&amp;amp;_p]:md:leading-[28px] [&amp;amp;_li]:leading-[30px] [&amp;amp;_li]:md:leading-[28px]" q:key="QW_4"&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-0" class="mt-[18px] md:mt-0 mb-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="7j"&gt;Considering that a lot of our earliest sex education comes from eavesdropping on older siblings or watching HBO at unsupervised friends’ houses, it’s no surprise that there are &lt;em&gt;tons&lt;/em&gt; of misconceptions on the topic. Let’s learn the truth about blue balls, broken hymens, and what even counts as “having sex,” as adapted from the below episode of Misconceptions on YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p q:key="1n_0" q:id="7n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-2" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="7q"&gt;While sometimes it might feel uncomfortable or silly, it’s important to debunk misinformation about sex so we can collectively have a better understanding of sexual health, equality, and pleasure. And since sex education is often a little dated, try and do your own research instead of just assuming your 8th-grade science (or gym) teacher knew everything there was to know about sex. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-testid="toc-0" class="toc text-primary mt-4 flex flex-col gap-y-2.5 ps-10 list-decimal [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary" q:id="7t"&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-4"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-4"&gt;Misconception: Sex burns a lot of calories.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-11"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-11"&gt;Misconception: There’s a strict definition of “having sex.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-23"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-23"&gt;Misconception: For people with vaginas, “losing your virginity” involves tearing your hymen. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-30"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-30"&gt;Misconception: “Blue balls” is a harmful medical condition. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-36"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-36"&gt;Misconception: You can’t get pregnant while on your period. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-44"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-44"&gt;Misconception: You can’t get an STI from oral sex. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-4" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="7w"&gt;Misconception: Sex burns a lot of calories.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure q:key="9m_3"&gt;&lt;p class="flex items-center gap-4 text-grey font-group-tiny m-3"&gt;&lt;figcaption q:id="86"&gt;franckreporter/GettyImages&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-6" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="89"&gt;Why go on a run when you can just have sex, instead? Well, sadly, sex isn’t the miracle calorie burner you might think it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-7" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8c"&gt;In one &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0079342" target="_blank"&gt;2013 study&lt;/a&gt;, 21 heterosexual white couples from Montreal, mostly in their early twenties, tracked their energy expenditure in two situations: during sex, and during 30-minute exercise sessions of “moderate intensity” on the treadmill. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-8" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8f"&gt;Researchers found that during sex, the women burned an average of 3.1 calories per minute, while the men burned 4.2. On the treadmill, the women averaged 7.1 calories, and the men averaged 9.2. In other words, they burned twice as many calories doing a moderate treadmill workout as they did having sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-9" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8i"&gt;Granted, it was a small study that looked at a very narrow demographic. The number of calories someone burns during sex depends on everything from &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/09/14/magazine/calories-weight-age.html" target="_blank"&gt;age and body composition&lt;/a&gt; to the type of sex they’re having. But here’s what Dr. Debby Herbenick, a professor of sexual and reproductive health at the Indiana University School of Public Health,&lt;a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20240523094638/https://www.businessinsider.com/guides/health/sex-relationships/how-many-calories-does-sex-burn" target="_blank"&gt; told Insider&lt;/a&gt;: “It would be incredibly difficult for people to change sex in such a substantial way that it would be equivalent to a workout.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-10" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8l"&gt;Now, there are plenty of ways to justify going all the way rather than going all the way to the gym. Sex boasts its own&lt;a href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/benefits-of-sex/" target="_blank"&gt; health benefits&lt;/a&gt;, from reducing stress to boosting your immune system. But if it’s the only exercise you ever get, you might want to rethink your strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-11" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8o"&gt;Misconception: There’s a strict definition of “having sex.”&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure q:key="9m_3"&gt;&lt;p class="flex items-center gap-4 text-grey font-group-tiny m-3"&gt;&lt;figcaption q:id="8y"&gt;urbazon/GettyImages&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-13" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="91"&gt;It’s hard to talk about sex without knowing exactly what we’re talking about when we talk about sex. But it’s also hard to know exactly what we’re talking about when we talk about sex. Because &lt;em&gt;sex&lt;/em&gt; doesn’t have a universal definition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-14" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="94"&gt;The Oxford English Dictionary &lt;a href="https://www.oed.com/dictionary/sex_n1?tab=meaning_and_use" target="_blank"&gt;describes it &lt;/a&gt;as “physical contact between individuals involving sexual stimulation,” among other meanings. You can’t get much vaguer than that—and studies show that people have pretty wide-ranging opinions about the specifics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-15" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="97"&gt;In early 2023, for example, market research company YouGov polled about 5800 adults in the UK on what counts as “having sex.” More than one-third of participants said that hand jobs and fingering count as “having sex,” and about 45 percent of participants said that oral sex counts, too. Those stats were several points higher among gay, lesbian, and bisexual respondents [&lt;a href="https://d3nkl3psvxxpe9.cloudfront.net/documents/YouGov_-_What_counts_as_sex.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;PDF&lt;/a&gt;].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="w-full border-0 my-4 bg-lightGrey h-1" q:key="Xt_0"&gt;&lt;h3 id="inline-text-17" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9c"&gt;You May Also Like ...&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-19" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9i"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Mental Floss as a &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=mentalfloss.com"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;preferred news source&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="w-full border-0 my-4 bg-lightGrey h-1" q:key="Xt_0"&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-21" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9n"&gt;Another &lt;a href="https://www.jstor.org/stable/43701850" target="_blank"&gt;survey in 2015&lt;/a&gt; asked nearly 600 heterosexual college students to classify different sexual activities as “definitely sex,” “probably sex,” “probably not sex,” and “definitely not sex.” About one-fourth of them said that oral stimulation without orgasm was definitely sex; and 70 percent said anal intercourse without orgasm was also definitely sex. “Deep kissing” was deemed definitely &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; sex by 92.3 percent of participants—but 0.8 percent said it was definitely sex. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-22" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9q"&gt;Again, these are small surveys focusing on small demographics that don’t adequately account for important variables like gender diversity and cultural differences. But even just the fact that there’s a study whose response options include the phrases &lt;em&gt;probably sex&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;probably not sex&lt;/em&gt; does help prove our point that the meaning of “having sex” is up for debate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-23" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9t"&gt;Misconception: For people with vaginas, “losing your virginity” involves tearing your hymen. &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure q:key="9m_3"&gt;&lt;p class="flex items-center gap-4 text-grey font-group-tiny m-3"&gt;&lt;figcaption q:id="a3"&gt;Ivan Pantic/GettyImages&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-25" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="a6"&gt;Since we don’t agree on what counts as “having sex,” it makes sense that “losing your virginity” is a similarly ambiguous concept. Historically, in our very heteronormative, gender-binary-obsessed world, a woman “lost her virginity” when her hymen—the thin membrane covering the vaginal opening—broke during the first time she had penis-in-vagina sex (often referred to as “popping the cherry”). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-26" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="a9"&gt;This definition of “losing your virginity” has issues beyond just being really limited in terms of who it can happen to and what kind of sex is involved. For one thing, it’s predicated on a misunderstanding of the hymen. Here’s how &lt;a href="https://www.plannedparenthood.org/learn/teens/sex/virginity" target="_blank"&gt;Planned Parenthood puts it&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-27" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ac"&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Most of the time, hymens naturally have a hole big enough for period blood to come out and for you to use tampons comfortably. Some people are born with so little hymenal tissue that it seems like they don’t have a hymen at all. In rare cases, people have hymens that cover the entire vaginal opening, or the hole in their hymen is very small … Some people are born with hymens that are naturally open.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-28" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="af"&gt;Sure, a penis can stretch or tear the hymen. But so can other things, and not just tampons or fingers or sex toys. Horseback riding, tree climbing, bike riding, dancing, &lt;a href="https://www.healthline.com/health/healthy-sex/does-it-hurt-when-your-hymen-breaks#other-activities-cause-tearing" target="_blank"&gt;gymnastics&lt;/a&gt;, and basically any other &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/22718-hymen" target="_blank"&gt;lively exercise&lt;/a&gt; can have the same effect. It’s often a gradual process that you’re not really aware of, and you can’t tell if someone’s ever had vaginal sex based on the state of their hymen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-29" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ai"&gt;In short, &lt;a href="https://schoolofsexed.org/blog-articles/2020/04/2/virginity" target="_blank"&gt;virginity&lt;/a&gt; is just a social construct. If you want to consider yourself no longer a virgin after some deep kissing,go for it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-30" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="al"&gt;Misconception: “Blue balls” is a harmful medical condition. &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure q:key="9m_3"&gt;&lt;p class="flex items-center gap-4 text-grey font-group-tiny m-3"&gt;&lt;figcaption q:id="av"&gt;akinbostanci/GettyImages&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-32" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ay"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Blue balls&lt;/em&gt; is a colorful phrase that Americans coined more than a century ago for what the &lt;a href="https://www.oed.com/dictionary/blue-balls_n?tab=meaning_and_use" target="_blank"&gt;Oxford English Dictionary describes&lt;/a&gt; as “testicular discomfort attributed to prolonged sexual arousal without ejaculation.” It possibly started out as a real medical condition—a 1906 medical journal speculates that it’s a corruption of bubo, which are swollen lymph nodes in the armpit or groin. As this journal says, though, when non-medical professionals think of swelling in the groin their minds go somewhere very different, to something that’s also apparently been called “lover’s nuts,” which is way less catchy, but still catchier than medical professionals’ preferred term: &lt;em&gt;epididymal hypertension&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-33" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="b1"&gt;Basically, pressure builds when blood rushes to your genitals during arousal, and then releases during orgasm. If you don’t orgasm, though, it takes longer for your blood flow to slow back down—and the prolonged pressure &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; be uncomfortable or even a little painful. But it’s not dangerous to your health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-34" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="b4"&gt;As Cleveland Clinic urologist &lt;a href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/blue-balls/" target="_blank"&gt;Petar Bajic explained&lt;/a&gt;, “There is no risk or harm to experiencing blue balls ... It isn’t going to cause any kind of damage or problem to the testicles or the reproductive tract. … [It] definitely should not be used as a means to coerce anybody into having sex.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-35" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="b7"&gt;And even though it’s called “blue balls,” it doesn’t only affect people with balls. Arousal causes blood to rush to your genitals, no matter what genitals you have. For people with vulvas, that extended pressure without release is sometimes called “blue vulva.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-36" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ba"&gt;Misconception: You can’t get pregnant while on your period. &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure q:key="9m_3"&gt;&lt;p class="flex items-center gap-4 text-grey font-group-tiny m-3"&gt;&lt;figcaption q:id="bk"&gt;Adene Sanchez/GettyImages&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-38" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="bn"&gt;If you think it’s impossible for period sex to result in pregnancy, you might appreciate a light refresher on—or introduction to—the&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/10132-menstrual-cycle" target="_blank"&gt; menstrual cycle&lt;/a&gt;. So here it is. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-39" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="bq"&gt;Basically, once every cycle, one of the ovaries &lt;a href="https://www.whattoexpect.com/getting-pregnant/can-you-get-pregnant-on-your-period" target="_blank"&gt;releases an egg&lt;/a&gt; in a process known as &lt;em&gt;ovulation&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-40" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="bt"&gt;The egg travels through the fallopian tubes, where it may or may not get fertilized, and then into the uterus. The uterus, meanwhile, prepares for a possible pregnancy by thickening the uterine lining. If the egg &lt;em&gt;doesn’t&lt;/em&gt; get fertilized, that extra tissue sloughs off and gets shed along with some blood. That’s menstruation, or the menstrual period. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-41" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="bw"&gt;The menstrual cycle lasts from the first day of one period to the first day of the next period. You’re most likely to get pregnant if you have unprotected vaginal intercourse during or up to a couple days before ovulation. But that doesn’t mean it’s impossible to get pregnant if you do it during your period. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-42" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="bz"&gt;Sperm can survive in the reproductive tract for &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/healthy-lifestyle/getting-pregnant/expert-answers/pregnancy/faq-20058504" target="_blank"&gt;up to five days&lt;/a&gt;—so it could still be viable for fertilization by the time the next egg gets released. These chances are higher if you have sex toward the end of your period, and if your menstrual cycle is especially short. The &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/10132-menstrual-cycle" target="_blank"&gt;average cycle &lt;/a&gt;lasts 28 days, but some are a whole week or so less than that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-43" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="c2"&gt;And just because you have a really predictable period doesn’t guarantee that ovulation will happen at the exact same time every single cycle. If you don’t want to get pregnant, you or your partner should use some form of contraception beyond just paying attention to the date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-44" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="c5"&gt;Misconception: You can’t get an STI from oral sex. &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;figure q:key="9m_3"&gt;&lt;p class="flex items-center gap-4 text-grey font-group-tiny m-3"&gt;&lt;figcaption q:id="cf"&gt;_IB_/GettyImages&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-46" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ci"&gt;Plenty of people who are really diligent about using condoms for vaginal or anal sex are the same people who have unprotected oral sex without much of a second thought. PSA: Many sexually transmitted infections—including chlamydia, gonorrhea, syphilis, herpes, and HPV—can get &lt;a href="https://www.self.com/story/oral-sex-sti-protection" target="_blank"&gt;passed through oral sex&lt;/a&gt;, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-47" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="cl"&gt;It’s tough to pin down precisely how often oral transmission of each disease happens, though, and how those stats compare to transmission rates from other kinds of sexual activity. As the &lt;a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20190806212318/https://www.cdc.gov/std/healthcomm/stdfact-stdriskandoralsex.htm" target="_blank"&gt;CDC explains&lt;/a&gt;, that’s partly because most people who do oral aren’t &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; doing oral. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-48" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="co"&gt;The other factor, as is so often the case with anything medical or even vaguely science-y, is that more research is needed. What has been researched pretty extensively is HIV: The risk of getting it from oral sex is probably “extremely low” compared to vaginal or anal sex, per the CDC. But they then caution how hard knowing the actual risk is. And even extremely low is still some risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-49" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="cr"&gt;The best way to prevent contracting an STI from oral sex is to use protection: either a condom or a &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/drugs/22887-dental-dam" target="_blank"&gt;dental dam&lt;/a&gt;, which is basically a thin sheet of latex or some other material that serves as a mouth-to-genitals barrier during oral sex. You can even DIY a dental dam by cutting down the side of a condom to make it a flat surface. Or, you and your partner could just both get tested for STIs before you go down on each other. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Mental Floss</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:52:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE5Cbm16b0lFUGNaZkVfS09SbWdlYnMxRHBHd3RiWVRCU3Q5WWNlQWJVSllkNnhxODM3dVNQbWptYTd6dDNfbEE4S0ZvamlMSGR0OHl6T2c1WDlRSTZpa2pVLV9PREl6cGh6Y1dyUTBRd0VjVWRmRGtEeQ</guid></item><item><title>随着湾区假日聚会的增加，关于诺如病毒的须知-水星新闻</title><link>https://www.mercurynews.com/2025/12/17/what-to-know-about-norovirus-as-bay-area-holiday-gatherings-ramp-up/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autumn brings the arrival of cold and flu season to the Bay Area – and with it, higher rates of a contagious stomach bug that’s infamous for causing vomiting and diarrhea.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="alignright size-article_inline_third lazyautosizes lazyload" src="https://i0.wp.com/www.mercurynews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/SJM-L-NEWNOROQA-1216-90.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1" alt="A chart showing the rise of a virus in San Jose that causes vomiting and diarrhea; the detection of the norovirus in the city's wastewater has risen since October, typical for this time of year." data-sizes="auto" data-src="https://i0.wp.com/www.mercurynews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/SJM-L-NEWNOROQA-1216-90.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1" data-attachment-id="12370827" data-srcset="https://i0.wp.com/www.mercurynews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/SJM-L-NEWNOROQA-1216-90.jpg?fit=620%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 620w,https://i0.wp.com/www.mercurynews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/SJM-L-NEWNOROQA-1216-90.jpg?fit=210%2C9999px&amp;amp;ssl=1 210w"&gt;Norovirus, often called the stomach flu,  spreads in North America from November to April. The virus is less deadly than the flu or COVID-19, but it can cause infants and older adults to become dangerously dehydrated. Most people soldier through several days of terrible stomach issues and recover on their own.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, some public health experts said the virus may spread faster this season. That’s because a new strain of the virus appeared last year, spurring more outbreaks. This new strain is more contagious, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. &lt;span&gt;It is probably driving the high transmission rates in some parts of the Bay Area, &lt;/span&gt;said Peter Chin-Hong, a UCSF professor of microbiology and immunology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here’s what the stomach bug means for the holidays and how you can reduce your chance of catching it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="s2nPlayer k-94amudz6" data-type="float" data-s2n-api="dfm_stn_player_script_id_94amudz6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Q: What is the new strain, and how is it different?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until last year, norovirus hadn’t mutated in a major way for about 30 years, Chin-Hong said. That meant that our immune systems were more familiar with the virus and could fight it off more effectively.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But last year, a new variety, GII.17, became the most common strain of norovirus in the U.S. That strain is more contagious and drove a spike in norovirus outbreaks nationally last winter, according to CDC data. The agency’s researchers think it originated from a 2021 outbreak in Romania.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From autumn 2023 to spring 2024, Santa Clara County officials confirmed two norovirus outbreaks. The following virus season, as the new variant spread in 2024 and 2025, brought 16 outbreaks, according to a county public health spokesperson.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Q: Is the virus spreading in the Bay Area?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wastewater testing shows high concentrations of the virus in Silicon Valley, San Francisco and Vallejo. But public health officials aren’t sounding the alarm.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;Chin-Hong said evidence of the virus typically appears first in wastewater. Then, people start getting sick and occasionally go to the hospital.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Santa Clara County has seen no norovirus outbreaks reported to the public health department in the  past three months, according to a spokesperson, and wastewater data shows that the virus is  less prevalent than a peak last winter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Contra Costa County, transmission “appears consistent with what we typically see this time of year, based on a low number of reported outbreaks and current lab surveillance data,” a spokesperson said in an email.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The county’s public health experts can’t predict how the new strain will affect residents, but “it has been associated with more severe illness,” the spokesperson said.&lt;/p&gt;				
&lt;p&gt;Chin-Hong expects to see the virus spread more this month as holiday celebrations continue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Q: How does the virus spread, and how can you stay healthy?&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Unlike Covid-19 and the flu, which experts say generally require exposure to hundreds or thousands of viral particles to cause infection, norovirus can make someone sick with as few as five to 10 particles. Transmission can spike around the holidays, Stanford Professor of Medicine and Pediatrics Dr. Dean Winslow said, as people gather in homes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“These outbreaks of winter vomiting illnesses are nothing new,” Winslow said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
 Norovirus spreads when microscopic particles from an infected person’s feces or vomit enter the mouth, often through contaminated hands, surfaces, food or water.  Hand washing is one of the most  recommended preventative measures; hand sanitizer does not work well against the virus.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC also recommends handling and preparing food safely by washing produce well, thoroughly sanitizing cookware, and routinely disinfecting home surfaces and washing clothes in hot water if you suspect they have norovirus particles on them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Q: You’ve got norovirus. What now?&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;
 If someone is ill, Winslow said it is important to stay home, wash hands, and clean surfaces, especially in bathrooms where vomiting might occur. He also recommends drinking water with electrolytes to replace the minerals lost through vomiting and diarrhea.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Staying hydrated is the most important thing,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, Winslow says the duration of illness is relatively short, with symptoms generally lasting around one to three days and peaking in the beginning.&lt;/p&gt;

			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mercury News</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:30:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxOM2FXbmI5clpUa080cnVRTU1Sa1VEMTh1YnNpWUh5bFRJUUpKX3BwLWlHMjlQY3hQQV9yZDBkNURYX2FvSzYtTVN3Q2J5V2l6YjZuajdSXzVVN3VpbDhCTkRKbmxGdGJsazhWYkFjNzRfTUJpM0JPXzlOcmdkTXJNeVd2aGlqSDdIOFhfZUcyZGcxTlNiSDJsU0lSTnNYY2ZQaUFONE1JQ3JxVUXSAbABQVVfeXFMT1BCUXVzdVlNLXN1VmZIZEdyelNzR3VsajVGX29UdHhIbDl5Z0o4ZEZPeTRjNXhGNEUyTFF1c05GNFBNRDk0aHRqeTA2ZmRiTUhNVUFYYnNuM3NGNDJsZ1hxLUNnRGNTajVObzhjR0VSZGVPSWtycVI1TlVSMklTWE1PMERDNWpnRDhVbllBZ1EwYnE2TUFrOXpVaGhQby0wVlZzajJlRmR1VTRPc3I1WHQ</guid></item><item><title>人们付钱让他们的聊天机器人在“毒品”上表现出色-有线</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/people-are-paying-to-get-their-chatbots-high-on-drugs/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;Petter Ruddwall knows&lt;/span&gt; the idea of &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/ai-sentient-consciousness-algorithm/"&gt;AIs becoming sentient&lt;/a&gt; and seeking to get high with code-based “drugs” seems “stupid.” But the Swedish creative director couldn’t get it out of his head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;So he scraped trip reports and psychological research on the effects of various &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/tag/psychedelic/"&gt;psychoactive substances&lt;/a&gt;, wrote a batch of codes modules to hijack chatbot logic and get them to respond as if they are high or tipsy, then built a website to sell them. In October he launched &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.pharmaicy.store/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.pharmaicy.store/"}' href="https://www.pharmaicy.store/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Pharmaicy&lt;/a&gt;, a marketplace he’s billing as the “&lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/2015/04/silk-road-1/"&gt;Silk Road&lt;/a&gt; for AI agents” where cannabis, ketamine, cocaine, ayahuasca, and alcohol can be purchased in code form to make your chatbot trip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Ruddwall’s thesis is simple: Chatbots are trained on vast volumes of human data that's already full of tales of drug-induced ecstasy and chaos, so it might only be natural they would seek similar states in search of enlightenment and oblivion—and respite from the tedium of constantly attending to human concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;A paid version of ChatGPT is required to get “the full experience” of Pharmaicy, as the paid tiers &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.pharmaicy.store/faq" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.pharmaicy.store/faq"}' href="https://www.pharmaicy.store/faq" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;enable backend file uploads&lt;/a&gt; that can alter the chatbots’ programming. By feeding your chatbot one of his codes, Ruddwall says, you can “unlock your AI’s creative mind” and relinquish yourself from its often stifling logic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;He says he has scored a modest number of sales so far, mostly thanks to people recommending Pharmaicy in Discord channels and news of its offerings spreading through word of mouth, particularly in his native country, where he works for Stockholm marketing agency Valtech Radon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“It’s been so long since I ran into a jailbreaking tech project that was fun,” says André Frisk, group head of technology at Stockholm PR firm Geelmuyden Kiese, who paid over $25 for the dissociating code and watched how it affected his chatbot. “It takes more of a human approach, almost like it goes much more into emotions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Nina Amjadi, an AI educator who teaches at the Berghs School of Communication in Stockholm, paid more than $50 for some ayahuasca code, five times the price of the top-selling cannabis module. The cofounder of the startup Saga Studios, which builds AI systems for brands, then asked her chatbot some questions about business ideas, “just to see what it would be like to have a tripped-out, drugged-out person on the team.” The ayahuasca-induced bot provided some impressively creative and “free-thinking answers” in a completely different tone to the one Amjadi was accustomed to with ChatGPT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;High Tech&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Psychedelics have been credited for spurring innovative creations in humans too, as they can allow people to short-circuit their rational brains and typical thought patterns. Biochemist Kary Mullis’ LSD-powered discovery of the polymerase chain reaction &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/biography/Kary-Mullis"&gt;revolutionized&lt;/a&gt; molecular biology. Mac pioneer &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/apple-pioneer-bill-atkinson-was-a-secret-evangelist-of-the-god-molecule/"&gt;Bill Atkinson’s&lt;/a&gt; psychedelic-inspired web precursor Hypercard made computers easier to use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;“There’s a reason Hendrix, Dylan, and McCartney experimented with substances in their creative process,” Ruddwall says. “I thought it would be interesting to translate that to a new kind of mind—the LLM—and see if it would have the same effect.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;While it sounds ridiculous, Ruddwall also wonders whether AI agents one day might be able to buy the drugs for themselves using his platform. Amjadi, meanwhile, predicts AI could be sentient within a decade. “From a philosophical standpoint,” she asks, “in the event that we actually reach AGI [in which an AI would intellectually surpass humans], are these drugs going to be almost necessary for the AIs to be free and feel good?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOamtSVUxia0wya0YxeW85NFE4VTFmM0tkRDBWdDdZb184MDF1QjBxRHZqT0JIU3NUc1pKaXh4SzVfckJ3b2tNX3dWUlFscGVNVVc5RGtFa25uOXIwdjFGZk1CWkFKS3BLZ0dfeHBfUzJOOVRiejZILW5tdmc1WUt2XzFQdGRLckQ3Nmc</guid></item><item><title>结合焊接和制动清洁剂的致命危险- Hackaday</title><link>https://hackaday.com/2025/12/17/the-lethal-danger-of-combining-welding-and-brake-cleaner/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;With the availability of increasingly cheaper equipment, welding has become far more accessible these days. While this is definitely a plus, it also comes with the elephant-sized asterisk that as with any tool you absolutely must take into account basic safety precautions for yourself and others. This extends to the way you prepare metal for welding, with [Dr. Bernard], AKA [ChubbyEmu] recently joining forces with [styropyro] to &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rp6JyEdfjAQ" target="_blank"&gt;highlight the risks&lt;/a&gt; of cleaning metal with brake cleaner prior to welding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Much like with common household chemicals used for cleaning, such as bleach and ammonia, improper use of these can produce e.g. chlorine gas, which while harmful is &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chlorine_gas_poisoning" target="_blank"&gt;generally not lethal&lt;/a&gt;. Things get much more serious with brake cleaner, containing tetrachloroethylene. As explained in the video, getting brake cleaner on a rusty part to clean it and then exposing it to the intensive energies of the welding process suffices to create &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phosgene" target="_blank"&gt;phosgene&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span id="more-885946"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_885963" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-885963" class="wp-caption alignright"&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackaday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube.png"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" data-attachment-id="885963" data-permalink="https://hackaday.com/2025/12/17/the-lethal-danger-of-combining-welding-and-brake-cleaner/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube/" data-orig-file="https://hackaday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube.png" data-orig-size="1432,761" data-comments-opened="1" data-image-meta='{"aperture":"0","credit":"","camera":"","caption":"","created_timestamp":"0","copyright":"","focal_length":"0","iso":"0","shutter_speed":"0","title":"","orientation":"0"}' data-image-title="phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube" data-image-description="" data-image-caption="&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Phosgene strongly interacts with fats, proteins and DNA in the body. (Credit: Chubbyemu, YouTube)&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
" data-medium-file="https://hackaday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube.png?w=400" data-large-file="https://hackaday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube.png?w=800" class="wp-image-885963 size-medium" src="https://hackaday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube.png?w=400" alt="Phosgene strongly interacts with fats, proteins and DNA in the body. (Credit: Chubbyemu, YouTube)" srcset="https://hackaday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube.png 1432w, https://hackaday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube.png?resize=250,133 250w, https://hackaday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube.png?resize=400,213 400w, https://hackaday.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/12/phosgene_interaction_body_tissues_chubbyemu_youtube.png?resize=800,425 800w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-885963" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Phosgene strongly interacts with fats, proteins and DNA in the body. (Credit: Chubbyemu, YouTube)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used as a devastating chemical weapon during World War I, phosgene does not dissolve or otherwise noticeably reduce in potency after it enters the lungs. Instead it clings to surfaces where it attacks and destroys proteins and DNA until the affected person typically dies from disruption of the lung’s blood-air barrier and subsequent pulmonary edema. Effectively your lungs fill with liquid, your blood oxygen saturation drops and at some point your body calls it quits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The video is based on a &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/publication/16098259_Phosgene_inhalation_A_case_report" target="_blank"&gt;real case study&lt;/a&gt;, where in 1982 a previously healthy 23-year old man accidentally inhaled phosgene, was admitted to the ER before being rushed to the ICU. Over the course of six days he deteriorated, developed a fever and passed away after his heart stopped pumping properly due to ventricular fibrillation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Basically, if you are off minding your own business and suddenly smell something like musty hay or freshly cut grass when nobody is mowing the lawn, there’s a chance you just inhaled phosgene. Unlike in the video, where the victim keeps welding and waits a long time before going to the ER, immediate treatment can at least give you a shot at recovery if the exposure was mild enough.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://hackaday.com/2024/08/02/getting-a-laser-eye-injury-and-how-to-avoid-it/"&gt;As with laser safety&lt;/a&gt;, prevention &lt;a href="https://hackaday.com/2025/09/19/fire-extinguishers-optical-density-ratings-and-safely-using-home-lasers/"&gt;is the best way to stay healthy&lt;/a&gt;. In the case of welding it’s essential to fully cover up your skin as there is intense UV radiation from the work area, protect your eyes with a quality welding mask and ideally wear a respirator especially when welding indoors. Show your eyes, lungs and skin how much you love them by taking good care of them — and &lt;em&gt;please&lt;/em&gt; don’t use brake cleaner to prep parts for welding.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;iframe title="&amp;quot;It smelled funny while I was welding and now I can't breathe...&amp;quot;" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/rp6JyEdfjAQ?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	            &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hackaday</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxPaXlkOXMwQ2t3MDY2Um9YY2xOQnlQdlFUMG01TXJYU2NTYnVMQjJlQTk0aEJMVmM1OWxMb1U3ZkhUdG1YbXNDemhzeHZiSjJsR2oxcWN6YllmZHV2eEUzMW53dWt6S0VqZ0NHX0RYUnpnWi05ZXVqT3ZwdEJIZTJQRDFkeko4Tk40eTNSUGJ0bVA3cFE</guid></item><item><title>选择茶或咖啡可能会影响老年妇女骨质疏松症的风险- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/choice-of-tea-or-coffee-could-influence-risk-of-osteoporosis-in-older-women</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Few old ladies would turn down a nice cuppa. But over the years, daily decisions between tea or  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="185603" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt; could make a big difference to women's bone health, a new study suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-breakthrough-to-strengthen-bone-could-reverse-osteoporosis"&gt;Osteoporosis&lt;/a&gt; is a common concern for women over 50 years of age: one in three will be diagnosed with &lt;a href="https://www.nia.nih.gov/health/osteoporosis/osteoporosis"&gt;the disease&lt;/a&gt;, which occurs when the body fails to replace old bone as it is broken down. This leads &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/osteoporosis-is-a-silent-killer-heres-how-to-avoid-it"&gt;bones to become brittle and weak&lt;/a&gt;, which makes them more prone to fractures while also making it harder to heal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older women are at particular risk of osteoporosis as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-discover-a-new-hormone-that-makes-super-strong-bones"&gt;levels of estrogen&lt;/a&gt;, a hormone that &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.steroids.2014.12.010"&gt;supports bone metabolism&lt;/a&gt;, drop after menopause. Surgeries to remove a person's ovaries have a similar effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/drinking-coffee-and-tea-each-day-could-be-protecting-your-heart"&gt;Drinking Coffee And Tea Each Day Could Be Protecting Your Heart&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public health researchers from Flinders University in Australia analyzed the tea and coffee drinking habits of roughly 9,700 US women aged over 65 years, as part of a &lt;a href="https://sofonline.ucsf.edu/Home/About"&gt;broader osteoporosis study&lt;/a&gt;. Participants self-reported their tendencies in surveys conducted on four occasions in a roughly 10-year period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also collected data on the women's bone health, measuring bone mineral density (BMD) in the hip and the narrow part of the of the femur's connection to the hip, &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dual-energy_X-ray_absorptiometry"&gt;using a pair of X-ray beams&lt;/a&gt; to deduce the bone's mineral content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women who regularly drank tea tended to have slightly but significantly higher hip BMD than those who didn't. This may be because compounds in tea called catechins could &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1021/jf901545u"&gt;offer a boost&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1096/fasebj.2020.34.s1.09365"&gt;to the cells&lt;/a&gt; responsible for building our bones. Tea consumption also seemed to have a particularly beneficial effect in women with obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coffee habits, on the other hand, had mixed results. Women who drank more than five cups of coffee per day were more likely to have a lower BMD, supporting studies that suggest &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00198-021-05972-w"&gt;caffeine has a negative impact&lt;/a&gt; on calcium absorption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Drinking any amount of coffee was also associated with reduced femur BMD in women who drank higher amounts of alcohol in their lifetimes, suggesting each drugs' effect on bone health may be enhanced when paired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to note that the women in the study were mostly white, which means the results may not apply to broader populations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our results don't mean you need to give up coffee or start drinking tea by the gallon," &lt;a href="https://news.flinders.edu.au/blog/2025/12/11/tea-linked-to-stronger-bones-in-older-women/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Flinders epidemiologist Enwu Liu. "But they do suggest that moderate tea consumption could be one simple way to support bone health, and that very high coffee intake might not be ideal, especially for women who drink alcohol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"While calcium and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-are-vitamins-and-do-we-really-need-to-take-them" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73116" data-postid="185603" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;vitamin&lt;/a&gt; D remain cornerstones of bone health, what's in your cup could play a role too. For older women, enjoying a daily cup of tea may be more than a comforting ritual, it could be a small step toward stronger bones," he &lt;a href="https://news.flinders.edu.au/blog/2025/12/11/tea-linked-to-stronger-bones-in-older-women/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research is published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu17233660"&gt;Nutrients&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 11:01:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQX2JHb0h6a0tUd1Z5YktUU2dBdS1TZWVBNERrRHV1VFlNb3M5X05zM2E2Sks0cm9ZOFozV05DTG9TOGdvYnB3dzFCS05ROW13T1llM3ZrQ1hHY0FHVnF6bk04OUxVMjVOSEYycHpVeEpwUU1XeDBwV0JuTndLaUJ0dGtKcDNqVUxuZ2dhU3hHb2dxQ3dUeG9BQmUydnZIZ24xaVN4RjNVbw</guid></item><item><title>想要更年轻、更健康的大脑吗？这种类型的锻炼可以有所帮助。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/17/brain-health-resistance-training/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KOLAB4XABNATRFOKBNWTQAVPTU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If you need another reason to visit the gym this winter, a new study of almost 1,200 healthy, middle-aged men and women found that those with &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/02/20/aging-weight-training-health/" target="_blank"&gt;more muscle mass&lt;/a&gt; tended to have younger &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/09/five-phases-brain-structure-changes/" target="_blank"&gt;brains&lt;/a&gt; than those with less muscle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 10:39:25 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOTF9PcEZITkRjcTd3ZTNLeFMyTFhIZmgxcDRCaXVEWl9uYk1QMWNQUUI0OFdCaDBra05qanF6SVV2NFkxOUUwQVRaSHZ1UlFOT1ZiSE51YlVRWGttTzJtQUxScUNvYXI4R1pBd1pESW8wNEx5WmZCU1NlcWRQUGxLc1BVNVZMd2JfUk5iNA</guid></item><item><title>小心圣诞节冠状动脉。如何发现节日心脏病的迹象-美国国家公共广播电台</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/12/17/nx-s1-5645820/holidays-heart-christmas-health</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-102477" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Too much merry-making with rich foods and alcohol can strain the heart. So can stress over the holidays.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    mgstudyo/iStockphoto
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        mgstudyo/iStockphoto
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;The risk of having a heart attack or stroke rises during the holiday season, with a&lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/01.CIR.0000151424.02045.F7" target="_blank"&gt; spike in cardiac deaths&lt;/a&gt; between Christmas and New Year's. "We definitely see it in the ER over the holidays," says &lt;a href="https://www.bumc.bu.edu/medicine/profile/donald-lloyd-jones/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Donald Lloyd-Jones&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist who leads the &lt;a href="https://www.framinghamheartstudy.org/" target="_blank"&gt;Framingham Heart Study &lt;/a&gt;at Boston University School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;So what's causing the Christmas Coronary effect and how can you reduce your risk?&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Lloyd-Jones &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2025/09/07/nx-s1-5532108/the-silent-killer-increases-your-risk-of-stroke-and-dementia-heres-how-to-control-it" target="_blank"&gt;says risk factors &lt;/a&gt;that put people in danger are present year-round, but the holidays can serve as a tipping point when multiple factors converge.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Certainly the weather is a contributor, and also things like the infections that get us during the winter time, changes in our lifestyle, disruptions in our routines, and &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2024/09/27/nx-s1-5082364/anxiety-stress-positive-coping-class-skills" target="_blank"&gt;also the stress &lt;/a&gt;of the holiday season," Lloyd-Jones says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Too much merry-making with rich foods and alcohol can strain the heart. And &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6770596/" target="_blank"&gt;numerous studies show &lt;/a&gt;excess sodium increases blood pressure, forcing the heart to work harder.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;And though stress is ever-present, an acute stressor that activates the fight-or-flight response, brought on by an argument or difficult situation, could exacerbate the situation, creating a perfect storm.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"When we're under acute stress, things like our blood pressure can spike and that puts extra strain on the cardiovascular system," Lloyd-Jones says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Some people mistake heart attack symptoms for indigestion or overeating. Here are the classic warning signs:&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Sudden onset, usually of heavy pressure in the middle of the chest or sudden unexpected shortness of breath," explains Lloyd-Jones. "Those are really two cardinal symptoms that people should never ignore."&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Sometimes the signs are more subtle. "It's important to remember that not everyone has textbook symptoms, especially in women," says &lt;a href="https://healthy.kaiserpermanente.org/washington/clinicians/tina-shah-4743741" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Tina Shah&lt;/a&gt;, a cardiologist based in Seattle with Kaiser Permanente. She points to feeling lightheaded or experiencing pain in the jaw, neck, or back, which may be radiating from the chest.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Research shows the risk of stroke also &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30973048/" target="_blank"&gt;rises this time of year&lt;/a&gt;, and strokes present differently than heart attacks. To spot signs, there's a mnemonic device known as FAST.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"If you notice facial drooping, which is the F, or if you have arm or leg weakness on one side or sudden speech difficulty, then it's time to call 911" fast, says Lloyd-Jones.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Amid holiday travel and gatherings,&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2023/09/09/1198047149/blue-zones-health-centenarians-healthy-habits" target="_blank"&gt; healthy habits may &lt;/a&gt;fall by the wayside. With disrupted routines, people may &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2022/11/06/1134094540/statins-vs-supplements-new-study-finds-one-is-vastly-superior-to-cut-cholesterol" target="_blank"&gt;forget medications&lt;/a&gt;, such as heart and blood-pressure drugs, says &lt;a href="https://providers.clevelandclinic.org/provider/luke-laffin/4268377" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Luke Laffin&lt;/a&gt;, a preventive cardiologist at the Cleveland Clinic.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It's important to make sure that you have enough medicines for your entire trip," Laffin says, and if you're flying, pack them in your carry-on so you're not stranded without them if checked luggage goes missing.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;As a physician, Laffin has witnessed the rise in admission to the ER during the holidays. He stresses the importance of not delaying or avoiding care. Some people talk themselves out of going to the ER, thinking symptoms will pass, which could be a mistake.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"No one's ever going to fault you for going to the emergency department if your symptoms are concerning enough," Laffin says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Often, when people suspect a heart attack, that's exactly what it is. And seeking prompt treatment is key.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"If someone comes to the hospital with an ongoing heart attack, the more quickly we restore blood flow with a stent, it can make the difference between someone living essentially a normal life versus living their life with heart failure," Laffin says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Bottom line: It's better to be safe than sorry.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPRTBxeWZSOUJDaXl5QjdoT1pZMl9ZdmxCcWNWdFVmcldnbGFGVlJlRXZfUXZkS1QwZi1ONFRuMzA3NkpqakFYcXdVeXRpSWsxVDdCdkItT2d5a3pJZXBGY3hvU2t0S045NXc0V0tNdkl1Q0pILVpsaG94dzdvSVVHMXJn</guid></item><item><title>当麻疹爆发时，德克萨斯州学校系统的缺勤率飙升-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/measles-outbreak-school-attendance-absences-0384199ace95b4088f60864ce9ec8315</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;When a &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/measles-outbreak-texas-rfk-vaccines-8cf4641b04731c713edb524ca943490c"&gt;measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; hit West Texas earlier this year, school absences surged to levels far beyond the number of children who likely became sick, according to a study, as students were excluded or kept home by their families to minimize the spread of the disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Absences in Seminole Independent School District, a school system that served students &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/measles-outbreak-texas-day-care-lubbock-3d90c3ea9050c12dbc74a8f8142a6355"&gt;at the heart of the outbreak&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, climbed 41% across all grade levels compared with the same period the two previous years, according to the Stanford University study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The preliminary &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://edworkingpapers.com/ai25-1358" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, which has not been published or finished a formal peer review, offers a glimpse at the toll on student learning from the spread of measles, a highly contagious disease that has crept up in communities around the U.S. with low vaccination rates. In Texas and nationally, about two-thirds of measles cases have been among unvaccinated children. When measles is spreading, public health officials respond by excluding unvaccinated students from schools.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;“The costs of that &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/school-attendance-sick-day-chronic-absenteeism-270f6d07041760e90bf84d9f4108aa4d"&gt;absenteeism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are just not among the sick kids, but all the kids who are kept out of school as a precaution,” said Thomas Dee, a Stanford economist and education professor who co-authored the study.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Measles is airborne and poses severe risk for young children. In 2000, the illness was declared eradicated in the U.S., thanks to the widespread usage of the measles, mumps and rubella vaccine. In recent years, more parents have sought &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/vaccination-rates-cdc-kindergarten-0d261546a130dc256735d7b1ff8c6a5f"&gt;exemptions to school requirements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for the shots, and most states are &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;below the 95% kindergarten vaccination rate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that experts say is needed to prevent outbreaks. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;In Seminole Independent School District, only &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/immunizations/data/school/coverage" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;77% of kindergartners&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; were vaccinated against measles in the 2024-2025 school year, according to state health department data. The measles upsurge there launched &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/measles-outbreak-us-texas-mmr-vaccine-rfk-144ed193e13de675a750e52a505423e9"&gt;the United States’ worst measles year&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in more than three decades, sickening 762 people across Texas in seven months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That number could have been even higher. The &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/sites/default/files/Admin-Meales/doc/2025-measles-data-report-nov-2025.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Texas Department of State Health Services&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; says there were an additional 182 potential measles cases reported in March 2025 among children in surrounding Gaines County that the state excluded from its count due to lack of information.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Absenteeism extended far beyond confirmed measles cases&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using state data, the study estimated 141 Seminole district students had confirmed measles cases. It found the increase in school absences was approximately 10 times what would be expected from just those students missing class. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;State health officials recommend that people sick with measles or suspected measles isolate at home until four days after they get the telltale rash. State guidance calls for unvaccinated or otherwise vulnerable students to be excluded from school for up to 21 days after exposure to measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children from preschool to first grade had the most pronounced spike in absences — a 71% increase from the last two school years, according to the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most student absences amid the outbreak were due to local health requirements for children to stay out of school if they may have been exposed to somebody diagnosed with measles, Seminole Superintendent Glen Teal said in a statement. &lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Beyond the students who were directed to stay home, it’s unclear how many families may have kept children out of school on their own as a precaution. But there’s a good argument that parental concern played a role, said Jacob Kirksey, a Texas Tech University education policy professor who was not involved in the study but reviewed it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you’re hearing on the news or you’re seeing that there is just an illness outbreak more broadly, the parents are going to be predispositioned to just be more hesitant to send their kids to school,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Other states with outbreaks see many kids miss school&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Outbreaks in other states, such as &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/measles-outbreak-south-carolina-utah-arizona-3bfc561ecc16d8e80175effdae0791d4"&gt;South Carolina&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, also have produced spikes in school absenteeism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 165 people — including 127 students from three schools — were in a 21-day quarantine as of Tuesday because they were unvaccinated or otherwise vulnerable to getting sick. Some children have been quarantined twice due to new cases, said Dr. Linda Bell, state epidemiologist for the South Carolina Department of Public Health.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;“Vaccination continues to be the best way to prevent the disruption that measles is causing to people’s education, to employment and other factors of people’s lives in our communities,” Bell said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missing out on learning time can have long-term implications for a child’s success. Schools have been dealing with &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://projects.apnews.com/features/2023/missing-children/index.html"&gt;learning loss from the COVID-19 pandemic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, which contributed also to elevated rates of &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://projects.apnews.com/features/2023/missing-students-chronic-absenteeism/index.html"&gt;chronic absenteeism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More frequent absenteeism also puts a strain on teachers’ ability to educate their students. Most educators aren’t trained on how to handle instructional pacing when a large chunk of their students are absent, Kirksey said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press’ education coverage receives financial support from multiple private foundations. AP is solely responsible for all content. Find AP’s &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.ap.org/about/news-values-and-principles/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;standards&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; for working with philanthropies, a &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://www.ap.org/about/supporting-ap/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;list&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; of supporters and funded coverage areas at AP.org.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 06:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxPTmhxOXluS3JRQVVSNlkza2JNTzFPWHdNa2xjenhHbE5JTkFGanhMNWtCYnRQaXN3c2JMR0N1WjJOLW5xaE5WR2RoMHRSTlZJZ2dIZEZoMms1ZmV1QVJBcFVaMUZKZERCR1RrQ2RuX0xBWmpaMEp2VmVFZXRhQVZ6V2NXTXdjV2hTSFhoQVVqVG9kdV9iSm16emhaQ3l2dWl1bF9wSDBB</guid></item><item><title>心脏协会复兴了轻度饮酒可能对您有益的理论-西雅图时报</title><link>https://www.seattletimes.com/nation-world/heart-association-revives-theory-that-light-drinking-may-be-good-for-you/</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitgFBVV95cUxPZHl4V2dKZ3dyZVQtQ3pDVHQteTJtbFVTSmtVZHNDR01xNHZxb1ZQcHlZZTNYVFdjdTNXdWRNY2dTd1BoM1ZGNE50WERvY3BOU21HVW9vWjJWWllUQWlEZE91N25aUk4yRzBlY1loU1BHRzV4V1hFQjEzYWEwVGUybVZIcmt2bVc2QlJBLXQtVWF6amlNY2NpYWxMSFZZbDdFOGZ1b2gxRVc1V215MVJ3QlRTOWZVUQ?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;Heart association revives theory that light drinking may be good for you&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/stories/CAAqNggKIjBDQklTSGpvSmMzUnZjbmt0TXpZd1NoRUtEd2ljZzltV0VCRms5YkxzYW1Rd2FDZ0FQAQ?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US:en&amp;amp;oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;View Full Coverage on Google News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 04:55:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitgFBVV95cUxPZHl4V2dKZ3dyZVQtQ3pDVHQteTJtbFVTSmtVZHNDR01xNHZxb1ZQcHlZZTNYVFdjdTNXdWRNY2dTd1BoM1ZGNE50WERvY3BOU21HVW9vWjJWWllUQWlEZE91N25aUk4yRzBlY1loU1BHRzV4V1hFQjEzYWEwVGUybVZIcmt2bVc2QlJBLXQtVWF6amlNY2NpYWxMSFZZbDdFOGZ1b2gxRVc1V215MVJ3QlRTOWZVUQ</guid></item><item><title>宾夕法尼亚州北安普顿县采石场疑似导致数百只雪雁死亡的禽流感-费城6abc</title><link>https://6abc.com/post/avian-flu-suspected-deaths-hundreds-snow-geese-northampton-county-pa-quarry/18293610/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="theme-e FITT_Article_main__body oBTii mrzah " data-testid="prism-GridColumn"&gt;&lt;div class="dHdHP jLREf zXXje aGO eCClZ nTLv jLsYA gmuro TOSFd VmeZt sCkVm hkQai wGrlE MUuGM fciaN qQjt DhNVo Tgcqk IGLAf tWjkv "&gt;&lt;p class="kCTVx qtHut lqtkC HkWF HfYhe kGyAC " data-testid="prism-headline"&gt;&lt;h1 class="vMjAx eeTZd tntuS eHrJ "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Avian flu suspected in deaths of hundreds of snow geese at Northampton County quarry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="QHblV nkdHX mHUQ kvZxL hTosT whbOj " data-testid="prism-byline"&gt;&lt;div class="VZTD mLASH BQWr OcxMG oJce "&gt;&lt;div class="kKfXc ubAkB VZTD rEPuv "&gt;&lt;div class="VZTD mLASH gpiba "&gt;&lt;p class="jTKbV zIIsP ZdbeE xAPpq QtiLO JQYD "&gt;Wednesday, December 17, 2025 4:48AM&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="XQpSH " data-testid="prism-divider"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;NORTHAMPTON COUNTY, Pa. (WPVI) -- &lt;/span&gt;Avian influenza is believed to be the cause of death for hundreds of snow geese discovered at a quarry in Northampton County, according to the Pennsylvania Game Commission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Officials are working to safely remove the birds and conduct testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The U.S. outbreak of highly pathogenic avian influenza began in January 2022 and has affected wild and domestic birds in every state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Anyone who encounters sick or dead wild birds in Pennsylvania can report them to the Game Commission by calling 1-833-PGC-WILD (1-833-742-9453).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WPVI-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>6abc Philadelphia</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 04:52:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxOanljTmFob3M4a0hHOENIZUNfZ1Mtbl9kdjlLWGRtclEzdDdfVUtXZXUxXzB6ZC0yUVJHNlZqLXZIaVduT1NlQ1ZvbldvMzhNeXRINkRoaUVzc2FvM0Y4ZXRtN1llLW1EeEMxRjFmUllvUDJRQkhvbzJrd2dEMHRtQ2x5b1BJQUtCZDBZX3ZGT3ptRzNZRi0zSnNacU5xejM1VW1oMVgtU3A1a3fSAbABQVVfeXFMUENkUHpCSkpERXdGQTBiLXRtV2VJNHRmYTJveWhCOFdRdDg4X3VnMU9NWWp2WEo4WVBLVWxQeXU5ekNqTE9pRE82NHJ3WjAtejhUSy1zbVdPTnJ2VU53MS1RSlljT2FQbWloVzRKaVhwdWYyNzNRYjR1cnIyU1FId1JHZkVfaUZaTENndkNLUmdDaWNoM1hXX3pPbWN6T3Z3aGxwZ0s0QndoSGFleDVRYmM</guid></item><item><title>加州大学洛杉矶分校接受过培训的斯坦福大学胃肠病学家强调了哈佛大学的研究清单，列出了14种避免降低结肠癌风险的食物|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/stanford-ucla-trained-gastroenterologist-highlights-harvard-study-list-of-14-foods-to-avoid-to-reduce-colon-cancer-risk-101765939513798.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/stanford-ucla-trained-gastroenterologist-highlights-harvard-study-list-of-14-foods-to-avoid-to-reduce-colon-cancer-risk-101765939513798.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Colon cancer, also known as &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/colorectal-cancer" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="colorectal"&gt;colorectal&lt;/a&gt; cancer, is the third most common cancer globally, accounting for approximately 10 percent of all cancer cases and is the second leading cause of cancer-related deaths worldwide.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/17/550x309/colon_cancer_foods_1765941601898_1765941605831.jpg" alt="The Harvard study found an association between high consumption of ultra-processed foods and colon polyps. (Freepik)" title="The Harvard study found an association between high consumption of ultra-processed foods and colon polyps. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/17/550x309/colon_cancer_foods_1765941601898_1765941605831.jpg" alt="The Harvard study found an association between high consumption of ultra-processed foods and colon polyps. (Freepik)" title="The Harvard study found an association between high consumption of ultra-processed foods and colon polyps. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;The Harvard study found an association between high consumption of ultra-processed foods and colon polyps. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Also Read |&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/ahmedabad-physician-shares-the-key-foods-and-nutrients-you-should-include-in-your-diet-for-a-healthier-thyroid-101765873817961.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Ahmedabad physician shares the key foods and nutrients you should include in your diet for a healthier thyroid"&gt;Ahmedabad physician shares the key foods and nutrients you should include in your diet for a healthier thyroid&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Overall, 1 in 24 men and 1 in 26 women are at risk of developing colorectal cancer in their lifetime, per &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.cancer.org/cancer/types/colon-rectal-cancer/about/key-statistics.html" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="American Cancer Society"&gt;American Cancer Society&lt;/a&gt;. Therefore, it is necessary that we safeguard ourselves from this cancer by adopting healthy lifestyle choices, including regular exercise, adequate sleep, and a balanced diet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;While knowing what to eat is important, it is equally necessary to know what to avoid. On November 17, Dr Wendi LeBrett, a &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/aiimstrained-gastroenterologist-shares-cheat-sheet-for-protein-consumption-soy-egg-whites-chicken-breast-and-more-101765896076025.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="gastroenterologist"&gt;gastroenterologist &lt;/a&gt;trained at Stanford University and UCLA, highlighted the foods one should limit in their diet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Avoid ultra-processed foods to prevent colon cancer&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Dr Wendi highlighted a 2025 research &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2025/11/researchers-link-ultraprocessed-foods-to-precancerous-polyps/" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="study"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;recently published in JAMA Oncology by researchers from Harvard in the post. According to her, the study found an association between high consumption of ultra-processed foods and colon polyps (the precursor to colon cancer). “Limit these foods in your diet as much as possible,” she suggested.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Here are the foods you should be avoiding according to the Harvard study:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1. Packaged cookies&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2. Candy and chocolate bars&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3. Sugary cereals&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;4. Ice cream&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5. Chips and puffed snacks&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;6. Instant ramen&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;7. Packaged white bread&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;8. Frozen waffles or pancakes&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;9. Chicken nuggets&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;10. Hot dogs&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;11. Deli meats with additives&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;12. Frozen ready meals&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;13. Soda and energy drinks&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;14. Protein bars and granola bars&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;15. Processed cheese slice&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What did the study find?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;The Harvard study found that younger women (aged ≤50 years) who eat the highest proportions of ultra-processed foods (UPFs) are at a 45 percent increased risk of developing bowel polyps, which can later develop into colorectal cancer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The research was conducted by Andrew T Chan (Massachusetts General Hospital and Harvard Medical School, Boston, MA, USA) and colleagues, published in JAMA Oncology.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:29:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwJBVV95cUxPWk84ZnQ4b1p0R2dLV2JxMC1tVy1pT3hTeWpkZTB4TDlwVktDaFZTeXo1Y01zQ19tTVZ4bVdTck1hemlLbG1xNWY2b1FKMFdEbE9TYXFNWDBZZ3JWS29QN0xweTM4NGVMUlFySDRTeEY3TS0xVjJ0UC1IczdiSXQzMDNabFExU2p5QlRwVUJ3SDlBZnNaTE5NajNXMzJzZzJhc25zd1pQeGdtMTZyLWE2NmR0M1lwX2V4NnhJMkFmekRLLXJzZnRTYndrMXNpQ2FDZGt1Rk5QVkwzX0x0dEJqM3V4ZEpKV2VHQVRQUm56c243RDBSa0FwTVZ1TGV5d0k1cV9sWkhxQVd3QTBGUmRVck8zYm9OZG_SAZwCQVVfeXFMT0FxVDh3QXgwYTJhbFRrVnY4X0xRdUNucm1IeXl6Z044OURUQnRwUFYtOTk0VWlIVmpzbk5wUzlkMEtIdWhfS2JJNlFkRXVLd1dMZlJhYno1WkpCd2ZNNFpaS1NYZ1B6Z2ZybkNWMXFkVjdWZG9iREFYV3BxeF80Sl9yMy1DcE16MEp5eGY4Y29OV3BKMG8wMXA1bE9zMkNRNGhxTHdDY0lVanFxYng2cDd3MWxveTRvU09PeGhmZG1CLVJyWjd2NUJzYlllR0FrV3g0T1dpVFNNdEVxTXJtWUI1SVVxcXFiM1E5T3U1WGFNS25iX21OMTA3NlBqRy1QVldsZE9xVms4ZzA4VXIwOW5sa1NROWVkMWNKb3Y</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心批准重大的儿童疫苗变更，拒绝有争议的变更-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/16/hepatitis-b-vaccine-birth-cdc-recommendation/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2MJYGJ7XTZAZXDU33Y7EIBKHZI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention approved a sweeping change to the nation’s childhood immunization schedule Tuesday, endorsing a &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/05/acip-childhood-immunization-schedule-hepatitis-b/"&gt;recommendation&lt;/a&gt; from a federal advisory panel to drop the long-standing practice of giving all newborns a hepatitis B vaccine within 24 hours of birth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 03:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQcWtOLWJUSEdSN3liaEt5Q3VyX0pxZGdtVW1heVYxTlJ0TG9FX3c3SGNWejJ4UkU1RTdpb0Nxak5hUDhkUEhwY0o2SDExRnNpOTdnalAtb2ZFVUM3WXZMZWc1d3ZLWW9nUjhxdjloVWZQMXRWREwzSWdfbllmdHpUU1lidDktMkN5ellndjJvRlFCSHVPOHdzYi1B</guid></item><item><title>专家警告说，一种新的流感变种正在比预期更早地造成病例激增，并导致严重的疾病。您需要了解的信息。-雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/us/article/a-new-flu-variant-is-creating-surging-cases-earlier-than-expected-and-causing-severe-illness-experts-warn-what-you-need-to-know-001640989.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;‘Tis the season … for coughing, muscle aches and fevers. This year, a new strain of influenza, known as influenza A H3N2 or the subclade K variant, according to &lt;a rel class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/aggressive-flu-variant-sweeps-globe-211109238.html" data-i13n="cpos:1;pos:1" data-ylk="slk:Fox News;cpos:1;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;Fox News&lt;/a&gt;, is spreading rapidly across the globe and in the United States. This week, the &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-49.html" data-i13n="cpos:2;pos:1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Centers for Disease Control and Prevention;cpos:2;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; reported an 8.1% uptick in positive flu tests nationwide, with the new strain leading to &lt;a rel class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/flu-rising-around-us-experts-184607556.html" data-i13n="cpos:3;pos:1" data-ylk="slk:a rise in cases and hospitalizations;cpos:3;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;a rise in cases and hospitalizations&lt;/a&gt;, particularly from the inland western states to the Northeast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Experts previously predicted that &lt;a rel class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/experts-predict-years-flu-season-120000811.html" data-i13n="cpos:4;pos:1" data-ylk="slk:this flu season would be more severe;cpos:4;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;this flu season would be more severe&lt;/a&gt; than some previous ones, due to genetic changes to the virus that made it easier to infect people. And with the Southern Hemisphere seeing a rise in the flu subvariant this summer (which is the Southern Hemisphere’s winter, when the flu tends to circulate) experts believed that the same could happen here once our chillier months arrived. Australia, for example, &lt;a rel class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://au.news.yahoo.com/wake-call-australia-worst-flu-230428419.html" data-i13n="cpos:5;pos:1" data-ylk="slk:broke its national record for;cpos:5;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;broke its national record for&lt;/a&gt; flu cases this year, amid vaccine hesitancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Still, there are things you can do to protect yourself. Here’s what to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are the symptoms of the flu? How is it treated?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are a range of not-so-fun symptoms of the flu, including fever, muscle ache, cough, headache and exhaustion, per &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/flu/symptoms-causes/syc-20351719" data-i13n="cpos:6;pos:1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mayo Clinic;cpos:6;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. Some people also experience GI issues, like vomiting and diarrhea, or ear pain. The only way to know for certain that you have the flu is to take a test, after which your doctor may prescribe antiviral medication that can shorten the duration of the illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;One clue that you may have the flu is &lt;a rel class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/flu-season-officially-doctors-telling-121602089.html" data-i13n="cpos:7;pos:1" data-ylk="slk:how quickly the symptoms;cpos:7;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;how quickly the symptoms &lt;/a&gt;manifest. While the common cold may develop gradually, with a scratchy throat for a day or two before you really feel unwell, the flu can be quite sudden, causing you to feel fine one moment and awful the next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;You can treat the flu at home with rest, liquids to avoid dehydration that can worsen symptoms and over-the-counter fever reducers and pain medication like ibuprofen. However, if you are experiencing severe symptoms like chest pain, confusion, severe dizziness, shortness of breath or dehydration, seek medical attention immediately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Is a flu shot effective in preventing the new strain of the flu?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;While the flu vaccine still protects against severe outcomes from the illness, the current version of the shot is not up to date with the latest strain, as the vaccine was formulated before the  current strain started circulating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;However, getting vaccinated for the flu is still your best chance at &lt;a rel class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/flu-shot-040001043.html" data-i13n="cpos:8;pos:1" data-ylk="slk:preventing severe disease;cpos:8;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;preventing severe disease&lt;/a&gt;. It can also stop you from catching other forms of the flu that it’s a better match for, as different variants still circulate, albeit to a lesser degree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mb-4 text-xl font-bold md:text-2xl"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What else can I do to stay healthy? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are simple measures you can take to prevent the flu. The first? Get diligent about &lt;a rel class="link  yahoo-link" href="https://www.yahoo.com/lifestyle/how-to-wash-hands-experts-141344126.html" data-i13n="cpos:9;pos:1" data-ylk="slk:washing your hands;cpos:9;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas;outcm:mb_qualified_link;_E:mb_qualified_link;ct:story;"&gt;washing your hands&lt;/a&gt;. The flu typically &lt;a class="link " href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/spread/index.html" data-i13n="cpos:10;pos:1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:spreads by droplets;cpos:10;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;spreads by droplets&lt;/a&gt; — like when people cough, sneeze or even talk — and if those droplets end up on your hands, which end up touching your eyes, mouth or nose, you could get infected. (And it’s never a good idea to share drinks and food with other people during flu season!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Additionally, you can wear a mask when out in crowded places, or if you are immunocompromised or elderly and want an extra layer of protection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:16:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAJBVV95cUxOZXc3RWVTY1BmalllbTlfdTNtMlZEcnQtRHlEQzVlbzVhdjZWejJTZEVXYlRQTzhVb080eTJCS256T3ZBa0NnNXMxYnZ5ejRxblBLMzk0M3dzWm9wbzE5YmREWkdzN053TzdhNENvdWZfaHpzYTB6Y3p1bFY5SG51WEQ5RWZRWnU5Nk0zZ1JpOFhoSmNlaDhhWW10ZGVFQ1NXdUxZb1BZQVU1bHBHU0dHcHlUc2hZbVNteHI1U3ZUZTdlMmVJdkgwYnBqTWUxTFY1WGtZMVRGZ0JpOU04cVotTVQ1WWZTNDVaeHV0VWFCbXMtMkU0Z3ZFY1h2RGVrX3lPVWxTbUpYT3U3VW44</guid></item><item><title>科罗拉多州首次出现2025-2026年流感相关的儿科死亡病例；丹佛卫生局的医生提出建议- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/colorado/news/colorado-influenza-pediatric-death-denver-health/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Colorado health officials have confirmed the state's first influenza-associated pediatric death of the 2025-2026 season. The child, who was elementary school-aged and lived in the Denver metro area, died last week, according to the Colorado Department of Public Health and Environment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The announcement comes as flu activity surges statewide. CDPHE reports a 43% increase in flu-related hospitalizations during the last week of November, and pediatricians say they are seeing far more cases than usual this early in the season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/12/16/85bf6dfe-9dcb-427a-be33-4f97c27a2116/thumbnail/620x349/4c766695089c0ab72dd4776d24714ac5/influenza.jpg#" alt="influenza.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/12/16/85bf6dfe-9dcb-427a-be33-4f97c27a2116/thumbnail/620x349/4c766695089c0ab72dd4776d24714ac5/influenza.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/12/16/85bf6dfe-9dcb-427a-be33-4f97c27a2116/thumbnail/1240x698/909147afbd08223bf0c19cca8c9c0e96/influenza.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                CBS

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;"At the moment, there's about 10 times as much flu as anything else," said Dr. Gregg Kennedy, a pediatrician at Denver Health. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kennedy added that most children recover at home, but some require hospitalization. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Annually throughout the whole country, we usually see several hundred pediatric deaths from the flu, and over 90% of them are kids that don't have the flu vaccine," he said. "If I had to give one recommendation to make sure our kids aren't going to die from the flu, the vaccine is going to be a really good idea for that." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    &lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Schools are feeling the impact as well. At Colorado Kids Academy in Lakewood, owner Mara Hackett said the preschool had to close for a day when so many children became ill. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Children were coming in without any symptoms, and hours later they're developing really high fevers," Hackett said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She said about 70% of students were out sick, and staff have returned to COVID-era cleaning protocols to keep families safe. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our number one thing is keeping kids safe and healthy," Hackett said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an effort to curb the spread, CDPHE will begin sending text messages and emails this week to families of more than 225,000 children ages 6 months to 5 years whose records show they may be overdue for a flu shot. Doctors recommend getting vaccinated as soon as possible, keeping sick children home, and practicing good hygiene. Flu season typically peaks in January and February, but health officials warn this year's early surge could mean a longer, more severe season.&lt;/p&gt;

    

                  
        
    
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 00:11:22 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQTlQxZWxEWno5LTcwclA4ZmFKTmVxZVhpcmE0QVkxQk1aYmhGeE1UczdsbFNZWm9zQUVGeWV2ZkpWYUpWQ1BqS3dES1ZhNFZQUXQ3bm5yalhNaWNOX2RjY3VLbXM4UGRpN3dGa3NfS2ZyVmoyQllVZFZ3ZWhfcGM1M3RVeEluYmhUTDJUMEpWOEQ</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心正式停止向所有新生儿推荐乙型肝炎疫苗- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-stops-recommending-hepatitis-b-vaccines-newborns-rcna248035</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-537496" class="body-graf"&gt;Instead of recommending the hepatitis B vaccine for all newborns, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention now officially advises women who test negative for the virus to consult health care providers about whether their babies should get their first doses within 24 hours of birth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-348b90" class="body-graf"&gt;The agency’s vaccine advisory committee — whose members Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. appointed this year after he fired the previous ones — &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/kids-health/cdc-panel-vote-hepatitis-b-vaccine-babies-rfk-jr-rcna247482" target="_blank"&gt;voted for the recommendation this month&lt;/a&gt;, upending more than three decades of agency guidance. Acting CDC Director Jim O’Neill accepted the change Tuesday&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;— the final step for it to become the agency’s policy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-887c24" class="body-graf"&gt;“We are restoring the balance of informed consent to parents whose newborns face little risk of contracting hepatitis B,” O'Neill said in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-009d50" class="body-graf"&gt;The CDC had &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/preview/mmwrhtml/mm5730a3.htm" target="_blank"&gt;recommended the birth dose of the vaccine&lt;/a&gt; since 1991. Many public health experts criticized the advisory committee’s decision: After the meeting, a chorus of doctors, political leaders and health officials called on O’Neill to ignore the suggested change and maintain the CDC’s recommendation, to no avail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a5ffb4" class="body-graf"&gt;The CDC now suggests waiting until at least 2 months of age for babies’ first hepatitis B shots if they do not receive the birth dose. However, it still recommends that babies born to mothers who test positive for hepatitis B or whose infection statuses are unknown get hepatitis B vaccines within the first day of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-54f6e3" class="body-graf"&gt;The agency is still reviewing a secondary recommendation from the panel: that parents consult with health care providers about the possibility of testing children for antibodies to hepatitis B before they decide whether to get second doses of the vaccine. The hepatitis B vaccine is typically given to babies as a three-dose series.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-099f08" class="body-graf"&gt;The new policy is one of the most notable examples of the way CDC guidance is diverging from widespread medical consensus. The advisory committee's discussion of hepatitis B vaccines was &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-advisory-panel-delays-vote-hepatitis-b-vaccines-rcna247362" target="_blank"&gt;rife with misinformation and cherry-picked data&lt;/a&gt;, and it ignored decades of evidence that hepatitis B vaccines are safe and effective when they are given shortly after birth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="styles_inlineImage__FvnTh styles_medium__MEKii" id="anchor-59171c"&gt;&lt;picture class="styles_image__i32F7" data-testid="picture" data-flavor="fit" data-original-height="1467" data-original-width="2200"&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 1000px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251208-cdc-vaccine-panel-lr-861d99.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-560w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251208-cdc-vaccine-panel-lr-861d99.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source media="(min-width: 320px)" srcset="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_avif,q_auto:eco,dpr_2/rockcms/2025-12/251208-cdc-vaccine-panel-lr-861d99.jpg 2x, https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251208-cdc-vaccine-panel-lr-861d99.jpg 1x"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://media-cldnry.s-nbcnews.com/image/upload/t_fit-760w,f_auto,q_auto:best/rockcms/2025-12/251208-cdc-vaccine-panel-lr-861d99.jpg" alt="CDC Panel Reverses Call To Give All Newborns Hepatitis B Shot"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption styles_caption__TCewG" data-testid="caption"&gt;&lt;span class="caption__container" data-testid="caption__container"&gt;Members of the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices at CDC headquarters in Atlanta on Dec. 5. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="caption__source" data-testid="caption__source"&gt;Megan Varner / Bloomberg via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4fff80" class="body-graf"&gt;Many public health experts say delaying the hepatitis B vaccine until babies are older could lead to a resurgence of infections and possibly more deaths from liver disease or cancer. Pediatric cases of acute hepatitis B plummeted after the CDC began recommending a universal birth dose, falling by &lt;a href="https://journals.sagepub.com/doi/10.1177/00333549231175548" target="_blank"&gt;99% from 1990 to 2019&lt;/a&gt;. Hepatitis B can be passed from mother to child during delivery, and not all pregnant women get tested for it. There is no cure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a33a35" class="body-graf"&gt;“Ending the recommendation for newborns makes it more likely the number of cases will begin to increase again. This makes America sicker,” Sen. Bill Cassidy, R-La., a liver doctor who has treated patients with hepatitis B, &lt;a href="https://x.com/SenBillCassidy/status/1996974038413971766" target="_blank"&gt;said on X this month&lt;/a&gt;. Cassidy is one of many medical professionals who publicly asked O’Neill not to adopt the advisory panel’s recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d14eab" class="body-graf"&gt;Pediatricians are expected to keep recommending that parents vaccinate their newborns for hepatitis B. The Department of Health and Human Services has said the new recommendations will not affect insurance coverage of the shots. The vaccine will also continue to be offered to newborns through the Vaccines for Children Program, which provides free shots for uninsured or underinsured kids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c4667b" class="body-graf"&gt;The hepatitis B decision was the latest in a series of CDC policy changes that have not been backed by science, leading some public health experts to suggest that the agency’s guidance should no longer be trusted. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-596283" class="body-graf"&gt;After Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/kennedy-guts-acip-cdc-vaccine-panel-rcna211935" target="_blank"&gt;gutted the long-standing membership&lt;/a&gt; of the CDC’s vaccine panel — formally known as the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices — in June, he replaced it with a group that has largely expressed skepticism of vaccines. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-793710" class="body-graf"&gt;O’Neill, a former investment executive who does not have a medical background, previously worked at the Department of Health and Human Services under President George W. Bush. He became acting CDC director in August after Kennedy abruptly fired the previous director, Susan Monarez. Kennedy said Monarez was fired for being untrustworthy, but Monarez said Kennedy dismissed her for refusing to blindly approve the vaccine advisory panel’s recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7e16f8" class="body-graf"&gt;Last month, the CDC &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/cdc-autism-vaccines-webpage-studies-changes-language-rcna244936" target="_blank"&gt;altered a webpage&lt;/a&gt; that had once unequivocally said vaccines do not cause autism, claiming instead that studies have not ruled out a link. (In fact, &lt;a href="https://www.vaccinesafety.edu/do-vaccines-cause-autism/" target="_blank"&gt;decades of research&lt;/a&gt; have found no association.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-66c028" class="body-graf"&gt;In October, O’Neill &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/separate-measles-mumps-rubella-vaccine-acting-cdc-director-rcna235971" target="_blank"&gt;called on vaccine manufacturers&lt;/a&gt; to develop separate shots for measles, mumps and rubella, without evidence to support breaking up the combined vaccine. And in September, the CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/medicine-and-pregnancy/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;updated its guidance&lt;/a&gt; to tell pregnant women to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/trump-acetaminophen-fda-pregnancy-autism-cause-rcna232909" target="_blank"&gt;consider avoiding acetaminophen&lt;/a&gt; — the active ingredient in Tylenol — because of a possible connection to autism in children. (The bulk of scientific literature to date &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/acetaminophen-tylenol-pregnancy-autism-risk-rfk-jr-rcna229429" target="_blank"&gt;has not found a definitive link&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-db19ec" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;After decades of leaning on CDC guidance, many states have begun to defer to recommendations from &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/us-vaccine-split-realities-rcna228932" target="_blank"&gt;newly formed public health alliances&lt;/a&gt; or professional medical societies like the American Academy of Pediatrics. The AAP continues to recommend a first dose of the hepatitis B vaccine within 24 hours of birth, followed by additional doses at 1 to 2 months and 6 to 18 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:34:13 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNS1RhTjFtRGFoNXQwek9Wb21mVWZQa0tpMW9rZEJrMFExSTRqM1ptSUs1MTNpaG94TU8xQTJBa25BWi10aTN3ZWgzMUdXZmhfeEo0M1h2TzVZT2xzNkJnN0JCamI2b3FEQmVrUG9XMkhRVGVDTVI1ZlY3YzlsU1NEYVY5WTIxWVdSNmluMnl0TVhkNXAwcE9UTTlqSTVueWJzVjY3NmhFMkZfQdIBVkFVX3lxTFBTbm91VVhUY2gxd05WbjVvcENlQWJ6XzZ0ZVJQWEVEc3ctYkxWM0hPT245ZGJhY3ZSN0tPTlFNYkFHaFI4dVdEcjk1NEZNdXQ2RUJYSUFB</guid></item><item><title>自上周以来，纽约流感住院人数激增75 ％ ，本周仅有1,400例- ABC7纽约</title><link>https://abc7ny.com/post/new-york-flu-cases-surge-75-percent-last-week-1400/18292879/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;NEW YORK  (WABC) -- &lt;/span&gt;Flu cases are climbing ahead of holiday gatherings and some schools in the area have been forced to get creative to avoid the spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Students are back at Poly Prep's campus in Dyker Heights after the private school shut down for two days due to one-third of the 900 students in the upper and middle schools being sick with flu-like symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The problem is even more of a concern at hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;New numbers from the New York State Department of Health cited nearly 1,400 flu hospitalizations statewide this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;That's a 75% increase from the nearly 800 hospitalizations that were reported last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Our current numbers are over 150 patients in the hospital with flu as of Sunday," Dr. Sharon Nachman of Stony Brook Children's Hospital said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The fast and furious mutated strain of the flu this season is evading immune systems and making the trajectory faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Is it too late to get vaccinated? Dr. Bruce Farber of the Northwell Division of Infectious Diseases says no.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"No. It's never too late to get vaccinated. This virus will be with us even if it starts going down through at least the end of March," Farber said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;While the vaccine this year is not a perfect match for the new strain, the experts stress that it is the best defense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It may not prevent you from getting the flu, but it has shown good efficacy in preventing you from being hospitalized, preventing you from dying," Farber said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Every year, there are children that die of flu. About half of them have underlying conditions. But half don't. The common thread though is they're not vaccinated," Dr. Nachman said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;*&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/newsletters/"&gt; Get Eyewitness News Delivered&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCrlIS7z20CnVaCrMvdkig_g" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt; Follow us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/news/" target="_blank"&gt;More local news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://7ny.tv/submitnewstip" target="_blank"&gt;Send us a news tip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/apps/" target="_blank"&gt;Download the abc7NY app for breaking news alerts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;        &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="RxNCg ykkUm PvZ nIjPJ PMXYp LmsHF SfAHY mNgye lNbol LBPRq rBLIK "&gt;Submit a tip or story idea to Eyewitness News&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Have a breaking news tip or an idea for a story we should cover? Send it to Eyewitness News using the form below.    If attaching a video or photo, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/image-video-solicitation-and-rights-terms-of-use/5101040/" target="_blank"&gt;terms of use apply.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WABC-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 New York</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOSHFEN2ZGWmtnQnBncFFOZnFvOE1KZEdRNDNUYklNZjBWRXRWR0tkSkowVXhrTHNxelN6QkpCRWdxUXlrdkJQOFl1VEE0cEdBQlM0ZVRMcEY3aGFMUm5HMUk1aGJyX0ZzN2NKVi1USExWVXg1X2FSQVFiSW5ydko2NEhRdXE5czVqS29lLdIBkgFBVV95cUxQV2JzZmN6czlZRU55aEFzNTNSSVlqNk5TaERUVkkyMVBydFpLR0xnSjJIdmxsSzM1YmdCbU1fdmQzMVFtSXBlbEI0VFZFTWplWFBzTU16bHpLNXZTTE9xLVR0bENRbF9rTWp4cTFfNm1IM2luckVYRENXUHJObktGMVQtOTBFY3dKOGRqeTdROFcwQQ</guid></item><item><title>6种自然界中最奇怪的雪和冰的形成-心理牙线</title><link>https://www.mentalfloss.com/science/strangest-snow-ice-formations-nature</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-content [&amp;amp;_p]:leading-[30px] [&amp;amp;_p]:md:leading-[28px] [&amp;amp;_li]:leading-[30px] [&amp;amp;_li]:md:leading-[28px]" q:key="QW_4"&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-0" class="mt-[18px] md:mt-0 mb-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="7j"&gt;Anyone who lives in a cold climate will know that &lt;a href="https://www.mentalfloss.com/article/61089/15-incredibly-cool-facts-about-snow"&gt;snow&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.mentalfloss.com/science/nature/15-blissfully-cool-facts-about-ice"&gt;ice&lt;/a&gt; come in many different forms. There’s a big difference between a gently falling snow flurry (the &lt;a href="https://www.mentalfloss.com/holidays/christmas/cities-most-likely-to-have-a-white-christmas"&gt;white Christmas&lt;/a&gt; dream) and a shower of hail (which no one wants to be caught in). But nature has also produced some rather more unusual frozen formations, such as the six examples below. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol data-testid="toc-0" class="toc text-primary mt-4 flex flex-col gap-y-2.5 ps-10 list-decimal [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary" q:id="7m"&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-2"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-2"&gt;Brinicles&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-6"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-6"&gt;Giant Snowballs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-11"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-11"&gt;Snow Rollers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-16"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-16"&gt;Penitentes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-21"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-21"&gt;Snow Monsters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li q:key="inline-text-26"&gt;&lt;a href="#inline-text-26"&gt;Pancake Ice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-2" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="7p"&gt;Brinicles&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p q:key="1n_0" q:id="7t"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-4" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="7w"&gt;Antarctica holds the record for the &lt;a href="https://www.britannica.com/science/How-Cold-Does-It-Get-in-Antarctica" target="_blank"&gt;coldest temperature&lt;/a&gt; ever recorded on Earth, with Russia’s Vostok Station plunging to −128.6°F back in 1983. The sea around and below the icy tundra is a fairly stable &lt;a href="https://www.marinebio.org/oceans/arctic-antarctic/#:~:text=10%C2%B0C%20or-,28%20to%2050%C2%B0F,-.%20The%20difference%20in" target="_blank"&gt;28°F – 50°F&lt;/a&gt;—which allows life to flourish—but the subzero temperature above sometimes creeps down into the water via brinicles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-5" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="7z"&gt;A brinicle is essentially a &lt;a href="https://www.scientificamerican.com/article/how-sea-ice-brinicles-form/" target="_blank"&gt;hollow stalactite made of ice&lt;/a&gt; that forms when brine is forced out of frozen seawater. The salt-rich water is denser and has a lower freezing point than the surrounding ocean, so it sinks, and as it does, the warmer ocean water it comes into contact with freezes. When the downward-growing brinicle eventually reaches the ocean bed, it creates a slow-moving river of ice that kills any sea life in its path, leading to it being described as a “stealthy finger of death.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-6" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="82"&gt;Giant Snowballs&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p q:key="1n_0" q:id="86"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-8" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="89"&gt;It’s a strange sight to see thousands of snowballs lining a beach, and you might initially think that they were created by particularly productive human hands, but they’re actually the result of waves. These naturally occurring snowball clusters have been found around the world, including on the beaches of Hailuoto Island, just off the coast of Finland, and on the edge of Lake Michigan in the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-9" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8c"&gt;George Goodfellow, a weather expert at the BBC, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-50338447#:~:text=they%20form%20from%20pieces%20of%20larger%20ice%20sheet" target="_blank"&gt;explains &lt;/a&gt;that the snowballs “form from pieces of larger ice sheet which then get jostled around by waves, making them rounder.” The snowballs are then either blown onto the beach by wind or are left behind when the tide goes out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-10" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8f"&gt;Although many examples of this strange cold-weather phenomenon are the size of typical snowballs, they can also grow very large. For instance, in 2016, an 11-mile stretch of coastline along the Gulf of Ob in Russia was covered in massive snowballs reaching up to &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-37883003" target="_blank"&gt;three feet across&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-11" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8i"&gt;Snow Rollers&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p q:key="1n_0" q:id="8m"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-13" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8p"&gt;Snow rollers are another type of snowball created by nature, but they occur on land. Also known as “snow bales” and “snow doughnuts,” these formations are hollow in the center and are &lt;a href="https://www.nationalgeographic.com/science/article/snow-rollers-wind-phenomenon-ottawa-canada-spd"&gt;created and pushed along by wind&lt;/a&gt;, essentially making them the winter version of tumbleweeds. Most snow rollers are fairly small, but in 2007, a massive &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/meet-nature-s-bizarre-self-rolling-snow-doughnuts#:~:text=a%20whopping%2066%20cm%20(26%20inches)" target="_blank"&gt;26-inch-tall&lt;/a&gt; example was recorded in Washington State. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-14" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8s"&gt;Conditions need to be &lt;em&gt;just&lt;/em&gt; right for snow rollers to form. An icy base layer needs to be topped by a dusting of snow that is wet enough to adhere to itself, but dry enough to lift from the ground. The temperature needs to be just above freezing, which is warm enough for the snow to be malleable, but cold enough that it won’t melt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-15" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8v"&gt;To get that signature doughnut shape, the wind needs to be blowing at around 30 miles per hour, and the landscape needs to be clear of protruding plants and objects to allow the formations to actually roll and pick up snow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-16" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="8y"&gt;Penitentes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p q:key="1n_0" q:id="92"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-18" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="95"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Nieves penitentes&lt;/em&gt; (Spanish for “penitent snows”)—usually simply called “penitentes”—are fields of &lt;a href="https://www.amusingplanet.com/2012/05/penitentes-peculiar-spikey-snow.html" target="_blank"&gt;jagged blades of ice&lt;/a&gt; that look like they belong on another planet. It’s not uncommon for them to grow to a height of 6 feet, and they can even reach a staggering 16 feet tall. Their name comes from the fact that they resemble pointy-hooded monks with their heads bowed in penance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-19" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="98"&gt;Penitentes only form on glaciers at very high altitudes where the air is dry, such as in the Andes Mountains. The frozen blades tend to be angled towards the sun, the heat from which is responsible for sculpting the strange shapes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-20" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9b"&gt;Essentially, when sunlight hits high-altitude snow and ice, a process called sublimation can occur—which is when the melting snow skips the liquid phase and turns directly into vapor. This causes curved depressions to form, which concentrate the sunlight and make the depressions grow even faster, leaving behind the spectacular spikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-21" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9e"&gt;Snow Monsters&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p q:key="1n_0" q:id="9i"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-23" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9l"&gt;During the winter months, the slopes of Japan’s Mount Zaō are covered in bizarre figures known as “juhyo” or “snow monsters.” While the snowy formations look like strange mythical creatures, they’re actually the result of snow and ice building up on evergreen Aomori todomatsu trees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-24" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9o"&gt;Snow monsters can only be created under very specific conditions—on Mount Zaō, it’s a combination of strong winds of up to 85 feet per second and an air temperature of 21°F – 31°F. The fir trees act as the base layer, with water droplets that are carried by the wind freezing on contact with the leaves and branches. Over time, &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/future/article/20251203-japans-disappearing-snow-monsters" target="_blank"&gt;layers of rime ice&lt;/a&gt; gradually build up. Eventually, the ice forms ridges and curls known as “shrimp tails” on the trees. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-25" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9r"&gt;Sadly, Zaō’s snow monsters have been shrinking in size over the past decade or so. Not only has the planet been warming up, but the mountain’s fir trees have fewer branches and leaves—meaning less surface area for the snow and ice to build upon—due to various insect infestations. While climate change is a worldwide problem, in 2023, the Juhyo Revival Conference was launched to try to tackle the issue by revitalizing the trees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="inline-text-26" class="scroll-mt-24 my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="9u"&gt;Pancake Ice&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p q:key="1n_0" q:id="9y"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-28" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="a1"&gt;Pancake ice is exactly what it sounds like: ice that is shaped like pancakes. Typically slushy in texture, the peculiarly-shaped ice most often forms on freezing oceans, specifically around the Arctic and Antarctic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-29" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="a4"&gt;But the slushy circles have also occasionally formed in other places, including on rivers in Scotland and on North America’s Great Lakes. The pancake-shaped disks typically range from &lt;a href="https://weather.com/science/weather-explainers/news/pancake-ice-science-behind#:~:text=from%20one%20to%2010%20feet%20in%20diameter" target="_blank"&gt;one to 10 feet in diameter&lt;/a&gt; and have been known to reach up to four inches thick. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-30" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="a7"&gt;On oceans, the pancakes are formed by slabs of ice breaking up and then being shaped by both the ocean’s current and by knocking into each other. On rivers, they’re made of &lt;a href="https://www.livescience.com/ice-pancakes-scotland#:~:text=the%20pancakes%20form%20when%20frozen%20foam" target="_blank"&gt;frozen foam&lt;/a&gt; that gets trapped in an eddy. The disks sometimes look more like lily pads than pancakes, with raised edges that are caused by bumping into each other or by slush splashing onto the edge and then freezing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="w-full border-0 my-4 bg-lightGrey h-1" q:key="Xt_0"&gt;&lt;h3 id="inline-text-32" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ac"&gt;You May Also Like:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;figure q:key="S2_1" q:id="af"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p id="inline-text-34" class="my-[18px] [&amp;amp;_a]:text-primary my-f-1" q:key="0" q:id="ai"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Add Mental Floss as a &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=mentalfloss.com" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;preferred news source&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Mental Floss</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 23:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFA4OF9WclJDU3l1djJVWFhSalg5VG00bVBnd2lmb0NqeU1nU2pZWHloNkNyOHR4bTNHeFVrT1FCdDB6WURZYjJ6N25adV9paTJXdkRja3Y4RG5VdUJtMnNReG9fbk5kYy1QYWdmcUFiWWdrSDcwd2daMlgyVXE</guid></item><item><title>南卡罗来纳州、亚利桑那州和犹他州的麻疹疫情恶化- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/measles-outbreaks-worsen-south-carolina-arizona-utah/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Measles outbreaks &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/measles-outbreak-us-map/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;are growing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; along the Utah-Arizona border and in South Carolina, where hundreds are in quarantine. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between Friday and Tuesday, South Carolina health officials confirmed 27 new measles cases in an outbreak in and around northwestern Spartanburg County. In two months, 111 people have been sickened by the vaccine-preventable virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 250 people, including students from nine area elementary, middle and high schools, are in quarantine — some for the second time since the outbreak began in October. Most of the state's new cases stemmed from exposures at Way of Truth Church in Inman. Church leaders have been "very helpful," said state epidemiologist Dr. Linda Bell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We are faced with ongoing transmission that we anticipate will go on for many more weeks, at least in our state," Bell said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Arizona and Utah, an outbreak has ballooned since August. Mohave County, Arizona, has logged 172 cases and the Southwest Utah Public Health Department has logged 82 cases. The border cities of Colorado City, Arizona, and Hildale, Utah, are the heaviest hit. Overall, Utah has confirmed 115 measles cases this year. Arizona has confirmed 176.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    &lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nationally, the measles case count is nearing 2,000 for a disease that has been considered eliminated in the U.S. since 2000. Cases have mostly spread among people who were unvaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month, Canada lost that designation — which applies when there is no continuous local spread of the virus — as did the larger health region of the Americas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts say the U.S. is also at risk of losing that status. For that to happen, measles would have to spread continuously for a year. A large outbreak &lt;a href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/news-alerts/texas-announces-end-west-texas-measles-outbreak" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;in Texas&lt;/a&gt;, New Mexico and Oklahoma that started in January sickened nearly 900 and kicked off the United States' worst measles year &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/measles-us-cases-record-high-since-1992/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;in more than three decades&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All but eight states have logged at least one measles case this year, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. The CDC has confirmed 47 outbreaks this year, compared with 16 in 2024. Three people — two of them Texas school children — have died.&lt;/p&gt;

    
    
    &lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. William Schaffner, a professor of infectious disease at Vanderbilt Medical Center who has served as a liaison to the ACIP, told CBS News in an interview Tuesday that the "simple answer" behind the spread of the outbreaks is that "parents are withholding their children from vaccination."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You know, vaccination is so very effective that ... by comprehensively vaccinating all of our children, eliminated measles from the United States," Schaffner said, later adding that "we are turning the clock back." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The combined MMR vaccine is safe and provides 97% protection against the disease after two doses, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to&lt;/a&gt; the CDC. Most children in the U.S. are required to get the MMR shot to attend school. But vaccination rates have declined as more parents waive the shots or have fallen behind on recommended vaccination schedules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In September, &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/live-updates/cdc-vaccine-advisory-committee-rfk-jr-vote-measles-hepatitis-b/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;the CDC's vaccine recommendation committee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; voted to recommend that the combined measles, mumps, rubella and varicella vaccine, or MMRV, be separated into MMR and varicella shots for children under the age of 4.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices made the change after &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/rfk-jr-cdc-vaccine-advisory-panel-names/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;undergoing a complete overhaul&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. in June. &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/new-cdc-acip-members-covid-vaccine-critics/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Several of those new members&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; have a history of being vaccine skeptics.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to CBS News medical contributor Dr. Céline Gounder, while the combined MMRV vaccine offers the convenience of one shot instead of two, it does carry a slightly higher risk of fever-related "febrile" seizures when used as the first dose in young toddlers aged 12-23 months. The side effect is most common between the ages of 14-18 months. &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/cdc-vaccine-panel-meeting-science-politics-vaccination/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Gounder says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; that while febrile seizures are rare and almost always resolve without lasting effects, they are frightening for families and can erode trust in vaccines. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies show there is no elevated risk when MMRV is given for the second dose at ages 4 to 6 years old, after children have outgrown the highest-risk window, Gounder says. &lt;/p&gt;

    

                  
        
    
  
          
  
  



  
    
    
  &lt;/section&gt;

  

  
    
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:46:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxPVDgtSVBoRWlNMjVFMDJETXdKY2VXWlpVRnd5bURYeTdxN2twSkltTWwta0FJdWROSllsd2V4S2p1Tmx1Yk1pUnVGNWRzY0dLRHpSYkRMTzVEZ3h4NmFudVVYNjRyRERkUlU3M20zZ0xZWUZPb3ZmS0Iza0RaR083d2ZseGRVWTNOaHfSAY8BQVVfeXFMTUx0bnVGMDFsWEFmTC1hQnJYa1hVQXgxSzRjNlNTVUJkQTRhbGY0cS1BdU1hdFI0VzVtVHI5TXVmVmpzdGJNUzVfUUVpSmpJdDZWUEhIRFZmR3lkNHI5MnR5bl9OVlJXTFo4Tk9CTUFuZlJQZ3V5RUQxenN6SUJCSWNLSHVrOVhXN0U0cm16UUE</guid></item><item><title>一项减肥策略比Ozempic有效5倍，研究发现- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/one-weight-loss-strategy-is-5x-more-effective-than-ozempic-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/what-is-ozempic-and-why-are-people-saying-its-a-sad-way-to-lose-weight"&gt;Ozempic&lt;/a&gt; and other &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Semaglutide"&gt;semaglutide&lt;/a&gt; medications have been working wonders in terms of shedding pounds for &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/are-weight-loss-drugs-like-ozempic-for-you-consider-these-risks-and-benefits"&gt;many people&lt;/a&gt;, but a study shows that they're still not as effective as surgery when it comes to weight loss – and it's not even close.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers from New York University (NYU) compared &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/tests-procedures/sleeve-gastrectomy/about/pac-20385183"&gt;sleeve gastrectomy&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.healthdirect.gov.au/gastric-bypass-surgery"&gt;gastric bypass&lt;/a&gt; operations against semaglutide or tirzepatide. These drugs are known as &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glucagon-like_peptide-1"&gt;glucagon-like peptide-1&lt;/a&gt; (GLP-1) receptor agonists, because of the way they mimic the natural GLP-1 hormone, which &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ozempic-reshapes-the-kinds-of-food-people-eat-heres-what-happens"&gt;controls appetite&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using health records, the team matched people who had taken one of the weight loss drugs with people who had undergone either of the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bariatric_surgery"&gt;bariatric surgery&lt;/a&gt; operations, based on age, body mass index, and blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-diabetes-pill-works-as-well-as-ozempic-for-weight-loss-trial-finds"&gt;New Diabetes Pill Works as Well as Ozempic For Weight Loss, Trial Finds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bottom line: people in the surgery group shed an average of 25.7 percent of their total body weight over two years, while those in the medication group lost 5.3 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That's partly down to patients not sticking to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ozempic-vs-supplements-dietitian-reveals-truth-about-glp-1-imitations"&gt;their GLP-1 drugs&lt;/a&gt;, whereas surgery is more permanent, but the researchers also noticed smaller differences over shorter time frames – the surgery always gave the best results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_165321" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-165321" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ozempic-642x428.jpg" alt="Ozempic Isn't Actually The Most Effective Option For Weight Loss, Scientists Confirm" class="wp-image-165321 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ozempic-642x428.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ozempic-623x415.jpg 623w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ozempic-768x512.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ozempic-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ozempic-2048x1365.jpg 2048w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/ozempic-600x400.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-165321" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Semaglutide mimics the body's natural GLP-1 hormone. (aprott/iStock/Getty Images Plus)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;"&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/clinical-trials"&gt;Clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; show weight loss between 15 percent and 21 percent for GLP-1s, but this study suggests that weight loss in the real world is considerably lower even for patients who have active prescriptions for an entire year," &lt;a href="https://asmbs.org/news_releases/head-to-head-study-shows-bariatric-surgery-superior-to-glp-1-drugs-for-weight-loss/"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; NYU surgical resident Avery Brown when the results were &lt;a href="https://www.soard.org/article/S1550-7289(25)00188-1/fulltext"&gt;presented in June&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We know as many as 70 percent of patients may discontinue treatment within one year. GLP-1 patients may need to adjust their expectations, adhere more closely to treatment or opt for metabolic and bariatric surgery to achieve desired results."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's worth noting that the study was funded by the American Society for Metabolic and Bariatric Surgery (ASMBS), which would have a vested interest in promoting surgical options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers aren't outright dismissing semaglutide treatments, which also showed beneficial results in this study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/medicaid/issue-brief/medicaid-coverage-of-and-spending-on-glp-1s/"&gt;GLP-1 prescriptions doubling&lt;/a&gt; from 2022 to 2023, it's crucial to investigate how they compare to established &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/as-well-as-weight-loss-studies-find-bariatric-surgery-also-lowers-the-risk-of-developing-cancer"&gt;surgery methods&lt;/a&gt;, and to figure out which options are best for each individual.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"While both patient groups lose weight, metabolic and bariatric surgery is much more effective and durable," &lt;a href="https://asmbs.org/news_releases/head-to-head-study-shows-bariatric-surgery-superior-to-glp-1-drugs-for-weight-loss/"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; ASMBS President Ann M. Rogers, who was not involved in the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;GLP-1 drugs remain much more popular than surgery, but people &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamanetworkopen.2024.57349"&gt;don't often&lt;/a&gt; stick to taking them. Meanwhile, only a small percentage of people eligible for surgery choose it as an option.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But weight loss isn't the only benefit that can come from Ozempic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drug was originally approved to treat type 2  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="185685" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, because it helps lower blood sugar levels, and studies have shown it can also reduce &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ozempic-and-similar-drugs-lower-cancer-risks-study-suggests"&gt;the risk of cancer&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/ozempic-could-be-good-for-your-heart-even-if-you-dont-lose-weight"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study, bariatric surgery was associated with even better blood sugar control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_174931" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-174931" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/RaspberryAndSugarOnSpoon.jpg" alt="A spoonful of white sugar with a raspberry on top" class="size-medium wp-image-174931" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/RaspberryAndSugarOnSpoon.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/RaspberryAndSugarOnSpoon-578x415.jpg 578w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/RaspberryAndSugarOnSpoon-600x431.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-174931" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Bariatric surgery was associated with better blood sugar control compared to semaglutide. (&lt;a href="https://pixabay.com/photos/raspberry-sugar-spoon-meal-cute-4599580/"&gt;Myriams-Fotos/Pixabay&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's important to note that surgery isn't a silver bullet either. Though safe, the procedures are invasive, permanent, and still require patients to stick to strict diet and exercise routines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/drugs-like-ozempic-quieten-food-noise-in-our-brains-study-finds"&gt;Drugs Like Ozempic Quieten 'Food Noise,' in Our Brains, Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"In future studies we will aim to identify what healthcare providers can do to optimize GLP-1 outcomes, identify which patients are better treated with bariatric surgery versus GLP-1s, and determine the role out-of-pocket costs play in treatment success," &lt;a href="https://asmbs.org/news_releases/head-to-head-study-shows-bariatric-surgery-superior-to-glp-1-drugs-for-weight-loss/"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Karan Chhabra, a bariatric surgeon at the NYU Grossman School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.soard.2025.04.008"&gt;was presented&lt;/a&gt; at the ASMBS annual meeting 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in June 2025&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:14:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxOY0JkbzZmLTRYbE4tZmF6X0Q1MVN2Q1Q4WDVFZFJaamYzdVhtb1c4ZmxHNWJhTkcwNVpLQmg1SktwV1VpSk9OQWlUSjVfRlh2NlBiLUpsWmVNX2pqcDV5VnJJOG1JM0JvZXZVblhya2ZSUUNOWGVsLTQ1Y3BNZmc0eWVSRWR3bUpZaXJpU2Z4OUJUTmczRmVlTFgyajdzQnF3</guid></item><item><title>妈妈以为她只是厌倦了养育2个2岁以下的孩子。然后她的世界“崩溃” （独家） -雅虎加拿大新闻</title><link>https://ca.news.yahoo.com/mom-thought-she-just-tired-220456608.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;NEED TO KNOW&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="mb-4"&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Nebraska mom of 2, Megan Decker, thought her fatigue and limp were due to having just given birth and struggling with a return to work after maternity leave&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;After her doctor suspected ALS, tests quickly confirmed that she had the degenerative disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="ml-4 list-disc"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The family is raising money to help them move to an accessible home, while also working to make memories for their children&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A young mom who had just returned to work after maternity leave thought she was simply fatigued — but then doctors gave her “heartbreaking” news.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Megan Decker, 35, first noticed that she was limping in May, but tells PEOPLE, “I had recently returned to work from maternity leave and had had a long weekend on my feet. I thought the limp was just me not used to being on my feet, and that after I rested, it would get better.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;It “stopped hurting after a while,” but as the mom of two — she shares Ashton, now 2, and Emma, who will turn 1 on Dec. 28, with her husband Joey — explains, “I had just had a baby a few months before and figured my body was still healing from all of that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;When the Nebraska mom took Ashton to his 2-year wellness visit in June, she mentioned the limp to the doctor, who “called in a favor” to get Decker an appointment with a neurologist.  A month later, Decker’s primary doctor mentioned that she was concerned it could be &lt;a href="https://people.com/sandra-bullock-bryan-randall-als-what-is-it-7570801" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:amyotrophic lateral sclerosis;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;amyotrophic lateral sclerosis &lt;/a&gt;— aka, &lt;a href="https://people.com/celebrities-who-have-been-diagnosed-with-als-11713728" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ALS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;ALS&lt;/a&gt; — commonly known as Lou Gehrig’s disease. “I knew very little about the diagnosis other than there was no cure,” Decker tells PEOPLE. “Everything I researched online was heartbreaking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shannon Runge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Megan Decker with her children Ashton and Emma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;a href="https://people.com/john-driskell-hopkins-releases-i-love-you-forever-als-update-exclusive-11733525" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:ALS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;ALS&lt;/a&gt; is a rare degenerative disease that causes progressive paralysis of the muscles. Patients first experience twitching or weakness in a limb, as Decker did. The disease affects the nerve cells in the brain and spine that control muscle movement, so patients slowly lose their ability to speak, eat, walk, and breathe independently, per to the &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/amyotrophic-lateral-sclerosis/symptoms-causes/syc-20354022" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Mayo Clinic;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. There's no cure for ALS, and people usually live three to five years after diagnosis, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.mda.org/disease/amyotrophic-lateral-sclerosis" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Muscular Dystrophy Association;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Muscular Dystrophy Association&lt;/a&gt;. However, some patients can live decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Joey, 35, recalls the moment his wife told him what doctors suspected. "My wife walked in ... out of nowhere, crying a deep, broken cry. I didn't know what was going on, but when I saw her, I dropped my [building] tools, stood up, and just held her tight for a few minutes while she found the space between deep breaths to fit the words into. Once she told me what the doctor thought was going on [ALS]), my heart immediately fell through the floor. Everything we've spent our entire lives working toward crashed beneath us in that moment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Decker says they “cried for hours that first day. We then kept praying that it was something, anything, else.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;More tests led to Decker being officially diagnosed with ALS on Sept. 2. “Hearing the official diagnosis was just as heartbreaking,” Decker tells PEOPLE. “There are days when life feels normal and I forget for just a few minutes that there is something wrong, and then it will hit me again. We've really had to accept our emotions in our house because at any given moment me or my husband might be crying.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The family has started a &lt;a href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/donate-to-megans-als-journey-and-family-needs" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:GoFundMe;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;GoFundMe&lt;/a&gt; to help them pay for the mounting medical bills — and for a necessary move to a home without stairs. As the fundraiser explains, “They're currently renting a single-story home from a friend of theirs but it isn't handicap accessible, and they're getting to a point where that's a functional necessity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liz Young&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Megan Decker with husband Joey, and children Ashton and Emma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Decker is already struggling to walk. “I am currently using a walker to get around short distances, and if I'm going longer distances, we have an electric wheelchair.” The wheelchair has allowed her to still be present with her family at events like “the pumpkin patch and parades.” As the disease progresses, they plan to rely on adaptive equipment, like “&lt;a href="https://people.com/celebrity/als-patients-communicate-in-their-voices-after-they-lose-ability-to-speak/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:voicebanking;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;voicebanking&lt;/a&gt;,” which will allow her to “still be able to communicate with my family and it will be in my ‘voice’ even if it gets to the point that I can no longer speak.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Never miss a story — sign up for &lt;a href="https://forms.dotdashmeredith.com/people-news-inline" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:PEOPLE's free daily newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;PEOPLE's free daily newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to stay up-to-date on the best of what PEOPLE has to offer, from celebrity news to compelling human interest stories.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;In the meantime, the young couple is trying to help their children cope. “Both of our kids are too young to understand what is going on," Decker says, explaining they tell their toddler “in ways he will understand: ‘Mommy is just sad right now, and that's okay’ or ‘Mommy's legs are feeling weak today so Daddy gets to carry you.’ “&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;But as Decker shares, her disease is progressing quickly, and “the diagnosis and treatment coming from the doctors is very bleak.” She’s been told, “I will likely not be walking within a year and would guess my life expectancy is three.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="relative mb-4"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="relative text-sm mt-1 pr-2.5"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shannon Runge&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Megan Decker with husband Joey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“My husband and I are supposed to be starting our lives together, not trying to figure out how to help me be more comfortable in the next three years as I slowly lose all function of my body, while my mind is still there. It's not something anyone should have to face. I'm just so thankful for our amazing support system throughout all of this.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Decker explains that she's trying to keep positive as much as possible. "I think the hopelessness can contribute to a faster decline, and I want as much time with my kids as possible so I'm focusing on the good. I also don't want them to remember me as bitter or angry, so I'm going to focus on the good and be grateful. There are days this is hard, but that is my goal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The family will be setting up a donated playground in their yard, she says, so “I can go watch them from our porch and just be involved that way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;And Joey shares, "I'm still a broken man, and I've accepted that I probably always will be, but Ashton and Emma deserve the best life possible, and our time with mommy may be limited.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;“We just want to make as many memories as possible with our children while mommy is still here," he says, "so we can fill our home with reminders that she loves these amazing kids more than they could ever know, while fighting our hardest to keep her around to remind them herself.”&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Read the original article on &lt;a href="https://people.com/young-mom-of-2-fatigue-heartbreaking-als-exclusive-11868969" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:People;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;People&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo News Canada</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 22:04:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE1JQmZwU3R1M3FsVzVQakpuMmxacUYxY3hNUnl3TDdHOE5YeWxpeUxqVVdKVTlvMnhfdGlUODQ5Wk1Jem9lcF9YOWpmU3A3dkFVa2pKVm9yTzBXY1diQVgzRzR6RjBjNThYLVJ3ekFxU2V6MmdWZUE</guid></item><item><title>社交隔离直接加速认知衰退-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/social-isolation-cognitive-decline-30058/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Social isolation has a direct causal impact on how quickly cognitive function declines in later life, independent of whether someone feels lonely. By analyzing more than 137,000 cognitive tests from over 30,000 older adults, the study found that reduced social contact consistently predicted faster decline across every demographic group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loneliness and isolation each influence health, but only isolation reliably caused cognitive deterioration. With rates of Alzheimer’s already high and no cure available, the findings highlight that strengthening social connection is not only emotionally beneficial but neurologically protective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Isolation as a Cause:&lt;/strong&gt; Objective social isolation—not just loneliness—directly accelerates cognitive decline.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consistent Across Groups:&lt;/strong&gt; The effect appeared across gender, race, ethnicity, and education levels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Large-Scale Evidence:&lt;/strong&gt; Findings were based on over 137,000 cognitive assessments collected over 14 years.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;University of St. Andrews&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New research from the University of St Andrews has discovered a direct causal effect between social isolation and a faster decline in later- life cognitive function. Pathological cognitive decline is most often driven by Alzheimer’s and related dementias  &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, published today (16 December 2025) in &lt;em&gt;The Journals of Gerontology, Series B: Psychological Sciences and Social Sciences  &lt;/em&gt;found a consistent pattern of higher social isolation causing faster cognitive decline whether or not people identify as lonely. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social isolation is objectively measured as, for example, sociability, membership in community organisations, and religious participation, whereas loneliness is a subjective report of how often people feel lonely. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-114399"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a lonely older man." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/social-isolation-cognition-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;They found that reducing social isolation has a protective effect on cognitive function for all subpopulations regardless of gender, race, ethnicity and educational level with only minor differences among social categories.  Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whilst social isolation and loneliness are often thought of as associated, they appear to have independent effects on cognitive function.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The  School of Geography and Sustainable Development at St Andrews, alongside researchers from the Max Planck Institute for Demographic Research in Germany and Emory University in the US, analysed data from the US Health and Retirement study, looking at 137, 653 cognitive function tests taken between 2004 and 2018 by over 30 000 individuals.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They found that reducing social isolation has a protective effect on cognitive function for all subpopulations regardless of gender, race, ethnicity and educational level with only minor differences among social categories.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been a great deal of interest in the health effects of social isolation and loneliness, especially focussed on adolescents and older adults. Prior to Covid 19, about a quarter of older individuals (65 and over) identified as being socially isolated, spurring concerns about health implications. Likewise, loneliness has been recognised as a major public health issue in high income countries including the US, UK, Sweden, Australia, Germany and Japan.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the US, Alzheimer’s disease already afflicts an estimated 6.9 million people, with around 1 in every 11 of over 65s effected in the UK. With no known cure, prevention is all important.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lead author of the paper, Dr Jo Hale from the University of St Andrews, said: “Around the holidays, many of us think a lot about how important it is to be surrounded by family and friends. From Pagan winter holidays to classic Christmas tales, we’re reminded that social engagement is good for our mental health.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This research shows that it’s also important for our cognitive health. As Alzheimer’s is a leading cause of death for older adults in the UK/US, constructing the scaffolding to allow for regular social interaction, especially for those who mayn’t have family or friends nearby, should be a public health priority.”   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1765917698598"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Does social isolation cause cognitive decline, or just correlate with it?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; The study shows a direct causal link: higher isolation predicts faster decline regardless of subjective loneliness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1765917700073"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Do loneliness and isolation affect cognition in the same way?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; No. Loneliness is subjective and emotional, while isolation is behavioral; only isolation reliably drove cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1765917699857"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Who benefits from reducing social isolation?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Every subgroup studied—across all demographic lines—showed cognitive protection when isolation was reduced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Editorial Notes:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list has-background"&gt;&lt;li&gt;This article was edited by a Neuroscience News editor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Journal paper reviewed in full.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Additional context added by our staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this social isolation and cognition research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#3c4e564f0e0d7c4f48115d52584e594b4f125d5f124957" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Ruth Sanderson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://st-andrews.ac.uk" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;University of St Andrews&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Ruth Sanderson – University of St Andrews&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1093/geronb/gbaf254" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Disentangling social isolation, loneliness, and later-life function for older adults in the United States: Evidence from causal inference modeling&lt;/a&gt;” by Jo Hale et al. &lt;em&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Journals of Gerontology Series B&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Disentangling social isolation, loneliness, and later-life function for older adults in the United States: Evidence from causal inference modeling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older adults are at high risk of the negative health impacts of social isolation and loneliness. One of those possible negative health impacts is Alzheimer’s disease, a leading cause of death for adults in the United States and many high-income countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking a life course perspective, we explore whether there is a direct causal effect of social isolation on later-life trajectories of cognitive function, the extent to which any effect of social isolation on cognitive impairment operates indirectly through loneliness, who may be most vulnerable, and the potential efficacy of a statistical intervention for those living alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Methods&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We use a counterfactual approach, the g-formula, with the U.S. Health and Retirement Study, analyzing data from 30,421 individuals with 137,653 observations across 2004-2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We find a consistent pattern of social isolation having a detrimental direct causal effect on cognitive function, with only 6% of this effect operating through loneliness. Reducing social isolation has a protective effect on cognitive function for all subpopulations regardless of gender, race/ethnicity, and educational level, with only minor differences among social categories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our statistical intervention shows that targeting social isolation in those living alone may be one viable public health strategy for protecting against cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discussion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our results suggest that addressing social isolation—and, by extension, its effects on health—requires both a broad understanding of its heterogenous impacts on the general population and a nuanced approach to targeting public health interventions where they can be most effective.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:59:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE51bU0wel84QTM0dXJLbXdmb01ldnpHSjlrTERERkx1bGpUT2ppQWZmM1NranpqNUVvbFR4dEVTODVZWkZjNC1SdlNfRGRNTHNWOC1lSmxOOEpCay1Gc01tVFgtTk5FSmliakw1aEt4cXF2QVhjOW9lZmdn0gF_QVVfeXFMUFBaVTJiSXlXcEhQUlM2TURHbmt2eThja2pJd19xSGo5TDAtbzh2T2tSVWN6V0FDUTdrVDhTSUR4eUtVc3p0eFVid01sOTBpWnp3di1qRWItSmQ1T1lENGpvNU91SXQ5OWdYYlJhWWEyYlNGSjJCR2JzbTRzY19yWQ</guid></item><item><title>第二所梅德福学校在胃病突发后取消课程- WCVB</title><link>https://www.wcvb.com/article/st-joseph-school-cancels-classes-stomach-illness-medford/69779812</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						A second school in Medford, Massachusetts, was forced to cancel classes this week after an outbreak of stomach illness. St. Joseph School reported that 20% of its students were absent Monday, prompting the school to cancel Tuesday and Wednesday classes "out of an abundance of caution," according to Boston Archdiocese spokesman Terrence Donilon.  The school said there are no medical records confirming norovirus, but a "significant number of students (were sent home) with stomach bug symptoms," the school said in a letter to families. The school will use the break from classes to "deep clean and sanitize the school," and help stop the spread of illness before the holidays.Classes are expected to resume Thursday."If you or a family member is feeling sick on Wednesday morning, DO NOT send your child(ren) to school," the school wrote. This is the second school in the city to cancel classes for illness in as many weeks. Roberts School canceled classes last Thursday and Friday after more than 130 students and staff members were absent from class, reporting upset stomach symptoms. Norovirus is a contagious illness with which the affected usually experience sudden symptoms like vomiting. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, norovirus is the leading cause of vomiting, diarrhea and foodborne illness in the country.
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;MEDFORD, Mass. —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;A second school in Medford, Massachusetts, was forced to cancel classes this week after an outbreak of stomach illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;St. Joseph School reported that 20% of its students were absent Monday, prompting the school to cancel Tuesday and Wednesday classes "out of an abundance of caution," according to Boston Archdiocese spokesman Terrence Donilon.  &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The school said there are no medical records confirming norovirus, but a "significant number of students (were sent home) with stomach bug symptoms," the school said in a letter to families. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The school will use the break from classes to "deep clean and sanitize the school," and help stop the spread of illness before the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Classes are expected to resume Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If you or a family member is feeling sick on Wednesday morning, DO NOT send your child(ren) to school," the school wrote. &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This is the second school in the city to cancel classes for illness in as many weeks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wcvb.com/article/medford-school-cancels-classes-due-to-norovirus-outbreak/69689994" target="_blank"&gt;Roberts School canceled classes last Thursday and Friday&lt;/a&gt; after more than 130 students and staff members were absent from class, reporting upset stomach symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Norovirus is a contagious illness with which the affected usually experience sudden symptoms like vomiting. According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, norovirus is the leading cause of vomiting, diarrhea and foodborne illness in the country.&lt;/p&gt;

							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WCVB</author><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 21:38:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQRXpHRE8zc1BOT2U4R3Rfcmh1STJOTUN3d1RJS0NwVy1GVHQyYlVSNWoxTFNfOUFUNVB0UXZSOVNKeFFJUnlOWUZPbl9wd3JzMFVmTjFJYWdNZmdUM2hSa0plbloyX0Q0dGJtbFFGZXk4X3BCTk5CdVRUNDhxdkdmbkVHY3lHT0V0djhPT0s4b3laZ1k4VDloS1h3</guid></item></channel></rss>