<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>2025年五大最可怕和最引人入胜的医疗案例- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/health/2025/12/the-top-5-most-horrifying-and-fascinating-medical-cases-of-2025/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;Humans accidentally get infected by eating raw vegetables containing or contaminated by infected slugs or snails, or by eating undercooked creatures that eat slugs or snails, such as land crabs, freshwater prawns, or frogs. In the woman’s case, doctors suspected she got infected from eating raw seafood and salads on a recent trip to Hawaii, where the parasite is a known threat. Luckily, the woman was treated for the infection and made a full recovery.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;It’s not every day a person gets drunk and wakes up with a medical case so enigmatic that a master clinician with an expertise in medical reasoning is called in to help crack it. But a 36-year-old did just that in a case published this year in the New England Journal of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The man showed up at the hospital with abdominal pain, a crackling in his lungs, bacteria in his blood, liver abnormalities, an injury in his small intestine, and a blood clot in his right kidney—and no clear idea of how any of those things happened or how they were connected.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the case report, doctors lay out how they identified all of the aspects of his condition and then how master clinician Gurpreet Dhaliwal of the University of California, San Francisco, unraveled how they fit together.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Providing a fascinating look into diagnostic sleuthing, Dhaliwal reasoned out that it all came down to beers and a toothpick. The man—who had a history of binge drinking—got drunk, ate something, and accidentally swallowed a toothpick, Dhaliwal surmised. While still drunk, the man aspirated some of the food, causing his lung infection. The toothpick, meanwhile, pierced his small intestine near his right kidney, causing the injury and the blood clot. The injury then became infected, causing sepsis and his liver abnormalities.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 14:00:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxNSnc1QXhTbDB0ZC1yUjlUdGVkdlhsc1pYZUJWUjRScXdZamhVTWl3dk9ybGF4UmJMRHkzT0VsYmt1Z0piS1oxV3RZTnZlUmRUWVRZS2pjZm43SU1jNGx2dy1tUmFSU29FNjlFNlp6bmx0RzhXOWlEWWk2cHpDamJLYk10WVh1TG91NnpjUDc0X1ZRdFhZakp3RUlBT01ZemlsUFUxcmNB</guid></item><item><title>异常长寿的人的血液揭示了至关重要的差异- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/blood-of-exceptionally-long-lived-people-reveals-crucial-differences</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;The blood of '&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spanish-study-reveals-secrets-to-superagers-long-lives-and-sharp-minds"&gt;superagers&lt;/a&gt;' is a potential fountain of youth that scientists are keen to tap into.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emerging evidence suggests that centenarians, who live to 100, and supercentenarians, who live to 110, have unique blood profiles that differ from those who don't live as long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If scientists can figure out what sets the oldest among us apart and why, it may help the rest of us live longer and healthier lives, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dna-study-of-117-year-old-woman-reveals-clues-to-a-long-life"&gt;&lt;b&gt;DNA Study of 117-Year-Old Woman Reveals Clues to a Long Life&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Research suggests that centenarians begin showing favorable biomarkers in their blood &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s11357-023-00936-w"&gt;at just 65 years of age&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it's not yet clear how these blood signatures impact ongoing health, or how they are connected to genes or lifestyle, they may play a  'protective' role against age or disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that's true, then they could be targets for future longevity research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Watch the clip below for a summary of this article:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year, researchers in Spain ran one of the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dna-study-of-117-year-old-woman-reveals-clues-to-a-long-life"&gt;most thorough&lt;/a&gt; physiological and genetic analyses published to date on a supercentenarian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maria Branyas, who reached the age of 117, was one of the world's oldest people, and her blood samples show several healthy immune system markers as well as extremely low levels of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-drug-lowers-bad-cholesterol-by-58-in-clinical-trial"&gt;'bad' cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dna-study-of-117-year-old-woman-reveals-clues-to-a-long-life"&gt;say&lt;/a&gt; Branyas' cells behaved as though they were much younger than her true age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_175277" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-175277" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/maria_117_642.jpg" alt="Maria Branyas" class="size-full wp-image-175277" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/maria_117_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/maria_117_642-444x415.jpg 444w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/09/maria_117_642-600x561.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-175277" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Maria Branyas on her 117th birthday. (&lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Maria_Branyas#/media/File:Maria_Branyas_Morera_(117%C3%A8_aniversari).jpg"&gt;Family archive of Maria Branyas Morera/Wikimedia Commons/PD&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, scientists noticed a "huge erosion" in Branyas' &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/do-you-live-in-a-blue-zone-heres-why-you-might-live-longer-for-it"&gt;telomeres&lt;/a&gt; – the caps at the ends of her chromosomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Telomeres protect our genetic material, and shorter ones are linked to a higher risk of death. &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.arr.2018.09.002"&gt;Recent studies&lt;/a&gt;, however, suggest that among the oldest of the old, telomeres are not actually a useful biomarker of aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, having very &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depressive-symptoms-and-memory-loss-in-older-adults-linked-to-telomere-shortening"&gt;short telomeres&lt;/a&gt; may have provided Branyas with an advantage. Hypothetically speaking, the short lifespan of her body's cells may have stopped &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="175263" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; from ever proliferating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The picture that emerges from our study, although derived only from this one exceptional individual, shows that extremely advanced age and poor health are not intrinsically linked," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.xcrm.2025.10236"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers, led by epigeneticists Eloy Santos-Pujol and Aleix Noguera-Castells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-critical-factor-predicts-longevity-better-than-diet-or-exercise-study-says"&gt;One Critical Factor Predicts Longevity Better Than Diet or Exercise, Study Says&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a href="https://www.weforum.org/stories/2021/02/living-to-one-hundred-life-expectancy/"&gt;more people&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/gains-in-human-life-expectancy-may-have-already-passed-their-peak"&gt;live beyond 100&lt;/a&gt;, centenarians have garnered increasing scientific attention, and &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1101/2025.09.10.675341"&gt;analyzing their blood&lt;/a&gt; is a leading avenue of research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study from China, published in July, analyzed the blood profiles among 65 centenarians in one region.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared to older and middle-aged participants, those who lived to 100 had &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.maturitas.2025.108379"&gt;lower levels of fatty acids&lt;/a&gt;, fatty alcohols, and other key metabolites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These could be potential clues, the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.maturitas.2025.108379"&gt;say&lt;/a&gt;, for predicting human lifespan. One day, they could even be used for &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s43587-025-00883-5"&gt;blood tests&lt;/a&gt; that serve as 'longevity clocks', indicating how long someone has to live.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The plasma metabolic profiles of centenarians and nonagenarians differed significantly from those of the two younger populations," &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.maturitas.2025.108379"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings will aid in understanding the metabolic regulation of longevity and may promote the clinical practice of gerontology in the future."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bloodstream seems to be an &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/aging-can-spread-through-your-body-via-a-single-protein-study-finds"&gt;important channel&lt;/a&gt; through which markers of health and longevity flow. What's in your blood can impact your body and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/blood-protein-might-explain-why-exercise-keeps-our-brains-young"&gt;brain&lt;/a&gt;, and your risk of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-blood-type-affects-your-risk-of-an-early-stroke-study-reveals"&gt;disease and death&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent studies have even investigated how young blood reverses aging in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-identify-how-young-blood-reverses-aging-in-human-skin-cells"&gt;human skin cells&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As enlightening as research into &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/elps.201700086"&gt;blood metabolomics&lt;/a&gt; has been, however, the vastness of the field is intimidating. Blood is inherently complex and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-a-medical-mystery-revealed-the-worlds-rarest-blood-type"&gt;extremely diverse&lt;/a&gt;. While finding biomarkers for healthy aging is useful, interpreting those results is another matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this stage, there is no single blood test that can reliably predict how long a person might live based on what's &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-of-more-than-1-million-people-finds-intriguing-link-between-iron-levels-and-lifespan"&gt;flowing through their veins&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_177313" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-177313" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/OldWomanHoldsHerYoungPhotoUp-642x260.jpg" alt="Old Woman Young Photo" class="size-medium wp-image-177313" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/OldWomanHoldsHerYoungPhotoUp-642x260.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/OldWomanHoldsHerYoungPhotoUp-768x311.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/OldWomanHoldsHerYoungPhotoUp-600x243.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/OldWomanHoldsHerYoungPhotoUp.jpg 1024w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-177313" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;(Dimitri Otis/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lifestyle, genetics, and sheer randomness can change the future course of a person's life in unpredictable ways. But maybe the blood of superagers can help us identify &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/looking-deep-into-your-eyes-could-reveal-whether-you-re-a-fast-ager"&gt;'fast' agers&lt;/a&gt;, who are at risk of early mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In November 2024, a study analyzing &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.celrep.2024.114913"&gt;hundreds of metabolites&lt;/a&gt; in blood samples from around 5,000 individuals, aged between 18 and 110, found a unique signature associated with extreme longevity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings, the authors &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.celrep.2024.114913"&gt;argue&lt;/a&gt;, reveal a "critical role of essential fatty acids to connect lipids with other metabolic processes."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-common-diabetes-drug-is-linked-to-exceptional-longevity-in-women"&gt;A Common Diabetes Drug Is Linked to 'Exceptional Longevity' in Women&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the metabolites involved in aging were &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/you-can-add-10-years-to-your-life-simply-by-changing-your-diet-massive-study-finds"&gt;linked to nutrition&lt;/a&gt;, which suggests that diet could be a source of intervention for growing older in a healthier way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Branyas herself ate a &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/12-year-study-reveals-how-the-mediterranean-diet-might-affect-your-brain"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt; high in yogurt, which researchers &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dna-study-of-117-year-old-woman-reveals-clues-to-a-long-life"&gt;suspect&lt;/a&gt; may have played a role in her lengthy life: Her &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/gut-bacteria-might-actually-reveal-how-old-you-are"&gt;gut microbiome&lt;/a&gt; was remarkably youthful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A person's &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/do-your-genes-determine-how-long-you-ll-live"&gt;genome&lt;/a&gt; seems to play a strong role in how long they live, but genes are not fate, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-grandparents-diet-could-still-be-affecting-you-and-your-kids-health"&gt;environment and lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; can also impact the length of a person's life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists remain hopeful that research on centenarians and supercentenarians will one day translate into drug or lifestyle interventions that benefit us all.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:02:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxNd0JFajJGejBUelZrQzRCM1Q2RGN5YWYyc1VHamVXMGg5bUc5bmtZdnBaeTFMXzc0WUJRTW1sUExOeUhlM3pWVU54VHg4NmNKdmludDJQcDluYlBDZHpmU1c4Qzlrc0VWS0ZkNlctZTM1SG0xOHJYb1NaYVpTbW02MDY1UGFDUjZNVFdhaTIxaXlGZWQzRUctYmNMUnpNZw</guid></item><item><title>美国今年已有近28,000例百日咳病例。以下是您需要了解的信息- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/30/health/pertussis-vaccine-symptoms-whooping-cough</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrh81ji00003b6sszm8d3gh@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For the second year in a row, the US has surpassed 25,000 whooping cough cases — another sign of the risks of falling vaccination levels.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrhkx10000f3b6snqjym64e@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Often called the “100-day cough,” whooping cough or pertussis begins with cold-like symptoms such as runny nose, fever or cough that can progress to coughing fits that last weeks or months, according to &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/about/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/a&gt; A “whoop” sound when coughing may appear in the second phase of illness.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrjs424000u3b6scm85j5ri@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The infection can lead to severe illness or death, especially in young children: About 1 in 3 babies younger than 1 who have whooping cough requires &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/signs-symptoms/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;care in a hospital&lt;/a&gt;. Still, experts believe that much of the disease goes unrecognized and unreported, the CDC says.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfqm6e00033b6nwbgwl0xp@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The CDC reported nearly 28,000 cases this year, an elevated level after a peak last year, when the agency reported 35,493 cases. One year earlier, in 2023, there were only 7,063 cases reported.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrhss78000i3b6svqy7jcc9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/php/surveillance/pertussis-cases-by-year.html" target="_blank"&gt;The last time&lt;/a&gt; numbers were similarly high was 2014, when there were 32,971 cases.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrhbeng00043b6svyc8j44o@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Thirteen deaths from pertussis have been reported in the US this year, according to the Pan American Health Organization, most of them children under 1 year old.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmiyzhjid00023b6qvst3qogq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The rise in whooping cough is not unique to the US, according to the Pan American Health Organization, which serves as the World Health Organization’s office for the Americas region. Last year, 977,000 cases of pertussis were reported to WHO, a five-fold increase over 2023.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfqm6e00043b6nljyrmeom@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Scott Roberts, associate medical director for infection prevention at the Yale School of Medicine, believes the US rise is driven by falling vaccination rates along with a loss of population-wide immunity during the Covid-19 pandemic, among other factors.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfqm6e00053b6ntrk78x4r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I worry vaccine hesitancy is playing a role. This is a vaccine-preventable illness, and any decline in vaccine rates will lead to increases in pertussis,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitl3alp00033b6qltcks1gu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/diphtheria/hcp/vaccine-recommendations/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;The CDC recommends&lt;/a&gt; routine diphtheria, tetanus and pertussis (DTaP) vaccination for all infants and children under 7 through a five-dose series beginning at 2 months of age. Children who get all five doses of the DTaP vaccine on schedule are 98% protected from illness within the year after the last dose. About 70% of children are fully protected five years after getting the last dose, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/vaccines/types.html" target="_blank"&gt;according to the CDC&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfqm6e00063b6ni0fundth@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Adults and adolescents are urged to get a booster Td or Tdap vaccination every 10 years, starting at the age of 11 or 12, to maintain protection. Roberts recommends choosing the version that protects against pertussis — Tdap — when possible.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfqm6e00073b6n2zcuefse@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Last year, we had a lot of college outbreaks. What happens is, a lot of people get their childhood vaccine series, and then they don’t get the booster series,” Roberts said. He noted that many of those outbreaks were driven by students who had lost their immunity and were living in group settings where the disease spreads easily.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfqm6e00083b6npxcr43oq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A return to shared indoor spaces after the pandemic may have also contributed to the increase, he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitl5hq000053b6qyui3mm2f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There had been limited exposure to routine pathogens because of Covid-19 mitigation measures, he said, but now “a greater proportion of people are getting exposed to the pathogen, all at the same time. I wonder if there is some degree of loss of population immunity that we’re still recovering from, and maybe things will [stabilize] over the next few years.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmiyue6o900023b6n9i0424rt@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Additionally, the PAHO &lt;a href="https://www.paho.org/sites/default/files/2025-12/8-dec-2025pheepiupdate-pertussisenfinal0.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;epidemiological update&lt;/a&gt; highlights that vaccination coverage in the Americas region for the first and third doses of Tdap dropped to its lowest level in two decades during the Covid-19 pandemic. In 2021, coverage rates were at 87% for the first dose and 81% for the third dose of the vaccine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrhvwh8000p3b6s6xyc9rev@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Roberts emphasizes the importance of pertussis vaccines for children and pregnant women.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrk124v00153b6sz82gw2pl@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/vaccines/tdap-vaccination-during-pregnancy.html" target="_blank"&gt;The CDC&lt;/a&gt; recommends a Tdap booster between weeks 27 and 36 of pregnancy, regardless of prior vaccination timing.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrk0vby00123b6sun44pkay@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When a pregnant woman gets the vaccine, “the mom is going to develop antibodies [against pertussis],” Roberts said. These antibodies “spread through the placenta and get to the baby. When the baby’s born, they’ll have some immunity from that placenta.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrk18hb00183b6sqbui1r1r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            However, maternal antibodies “wane over a couple of months,” Roberts said, underscoring the need for children to complete the DTaP &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/pertussis/hcp/vaccine-recommendations/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;series&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subheader inline-placeholder subheader-elevate vossi-subheader_elevate vossi-subheader_elevate--size-h2" data-editable="text" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/subheader/instances/cmitfqp3r000b3b6nvv5wl2ui@published" data-component-name="subheader" id="whooping-cough-symptoms-and-treatment" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
        Whooping cough symptoms and treatment
&lt;/h2&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfpad500003b6n4u5qwt5a@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Whooping cough differs from flu, Covid-19 and the common cold in that it is caused by a bacterium rather than a virus, although early symptoms can look nearly identical, said Dr. Shira Doron, chief infection control officer for Tufts Medicine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfra4k000h3b6nyqo8dkg0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Even though it can look like a viral respiratory infection, it’s actually a bacterial infection caused by the bacteria Bordetella pertussis, and it’s got some very characteristic features,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfra4k000k3b6n1llnma0v@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A week or two into the illness, some people may have a characteristic &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DB70izafC1Y" target="_blank"&gt;whoop&lt;/a&gt; when trying to catch their breath between heavy fits of coughing.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfra4k000l3b6ngbpxi35q@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            If coughing becomes severe, Doron said, patients may have what’s called post-tussive emesis: “vomiting when you cough or after you cough, and then the whooping sounds that also follow a coughing spell.” She advises people to see a doctor if they have severe worsening cough with symptoms such as vomiting or the whooping sound.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitl91ho00093b6q5lfvi5yo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            These severe symptoms result from airway damage caused by the bacterial toxin.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfra4k000n3b6nxxqea09y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Antibiotics are the main treatment for whooping cough. When started early in the illness, Doron explained, medications can “break the chain of transmission” and lessen contagiousness, but they “do not change the course of the illness.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfra4k000o3b6nnocjk4lk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Because pertussis rapid tests&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;can be hard to find in clinics, Roberts said, health care providers often prescribe antibiotics based on symptoms.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitlxbo9000t3b6qvr1eowu2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s pretty simple to do a five-day course of azithromycin – it’s called a Z-pak – that, in almost all cases, is just going to kill the pertussis right away,” he said. Given the cost and logistics of testing, “Most of the time, [doctors] will say, ‘let’s do the Z-pak and see how it goes.’ ”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmixdkyai00003b6qme2dlz0r@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Children and infants are especially at risk of severe illness, and certain symptoms should signal when whooping cough becomes an emergency.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitl8h9600073b6q37szspj1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Signs of shortness of breath, such as a child struggling to catch their breath or a baby’s skin turning blue, require immediate medical care. Infants are at higher risk of severe illness because their respiratory and immune systems are still developing, but severe cases are rare when children have been vaccinated, Roberts said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrk1g7s001b3b6skd0txjsd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            On Monday, health officials in South Carolina urged residents to ensure that they’re up-to-date on vaccinations amid a “concerning uptick” in cases of measles, whooping cough and chickenpox.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrka27g001m3b6szm3kd2sf@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The unfortunate increase in these diseases is linked to declining vaccination coverage in that region and, frankly, across the state,” Dr. Linda Bell, South Carolina’s state epidemiologist and Health Programs Branch director, said of the Upstate region’s large ongoing &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/12/10/health/measles-surge-us-south-carolina"&gt;measles outbreak&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmjrka27g001n3b6si8ym6ln6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This trend is both preventable and reversible,” Bell said in a news release. “Vaccines are one of the most effective tools we have for protecting our communities. When people choose not to vaccinate, outbreaks become more likely. Choosing not to vaccinate can not only put yourself at risk but also your neighbors, loved ones, and others in and beyond your community.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfroqz000z3b6nssb6d14w@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Local health departments across the country have noticed declining vaccination rates. Dr. Raynard Washington, director of Mecklenburg County Public Health in North Carolina, said the county usually saw one or two whooping cough cases annually before numbers spiked to 68 in 2024. By October 2025, the county had recorded 48 cases this year.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfroqz00103b6ncfa6vvto@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We’ve certainly seen an uptick here, particularly in younger children,” Washington said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitli3tj000i3b6qbml6cwd4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Many cases are among those not up to date on the five-dose childhood series, and there are often clusters in communities where families delay or decline vaccines. “It does put more people in those neighborhoods at risk,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfroqz00113b6n8m1gs4mn@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Older adults are also a concern, he added, given their more vulnerable immune systems. He recommends that grandparents and other older adults “talk to their providers about anything they can do to protect themselves.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfroqz00123b6nweyoxv5x@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Phil Huang, director and health authority of Dallas County Health and Human Services in Texas, said the county had 40 cases in 2023, 160 in 2024 and at least 195 this year.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfroqz00133b6nvllvej0n@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            According to data from the &lt;a href="https://www.dshs.texas.gov/" target="_blank"&gt;Texas Department of State Health Services&lt;/a&gt;, kindergarten vaccination rates against pertussis were estimated to have dropped from almost 94% in the 2023–24 school year to less than 90% in 2024–25 in Dallas.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfroqz00153b6nw15ucfj3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Huang said the best thing parents can do is to ensure that their children are fully vaccinated. “That’s the best protection that we can do,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitlkzbe000m3b6q0cabxjlq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Roberts added that families should monitor local public health department websites for nearby cases, which may affect how doctors approach cold- or flu-like symptoms.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph_elevate" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmitfroqz00173b6nwulzgyuo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “If parents are concerned or the symptoms just aren’t going away after a couple weeks, you know that’s a time to come in and go see your doctor,” he said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxNY2M4MTFsY3RhUnB6SGFaVVdtRHF2ODhNQ3piN3FqMndHbFFuRVcxSnNlM1BGZldoS0MtOEN4WnV4c3QzZDRaTVZ5aWwxazJIQnQ1TUV5YUprVVdrQTNvcVBDYXRGVTRxM0x4VDExTVg2MnVpU3I1ZlB6dmZyMU5uc2NwMEhCQQ</guid></item><item><title>小RFK在特朗普执政第一年重塑公共健康的内幕--《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/30/rfk-jr-hhs-secretary-vaccines/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="20G4MNY8TH20Z6YGMVMNE8YXPC" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;On his way to being confirmed as the nation’s top health official, Robert F. Kennedy Jr. &lt;a href="https://www.finance.senate.gov/imo/media/doc/responses_to_questions_for_the_record_to_robert_f_kennedy_jrpart2.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;promised lawmakers&lt;/a&gt; he would do nothing that “makes it difficult or discourages people from taking vaccines.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="F7RPAQRQ6H2B51MK6H178V9K8G" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Almost 100 days into the job, amid rising measles outbreaks and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/05/14/rfk-jr-congress-testimony/" target="_blank"&gt;congressional scrutin&lt;/a&gt;y of his messaging on vaccines, Kennedy made clear behind the scenes that he&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;wanted to reshape&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;the nation’s immunization system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:31:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxOMjAyeG50VmJUSWJwUnYxdHZITEd2ZHBpOTdGSDAzT1hDT0lYMVMzLVRZUFdHdlZEYXdqb3VVZkZNUExTTGtsOWdqUDJzajlmSzJfalVhM0lYRWtkeENqbjRkS0U4dHBpekQ3T0l2NVlWMm1meHVDeWMzLWFxXzFiSHNfQzFPdw</guid></item><item><title>专栏|我经营了一年的聊天机器人搏击俱乐部。以下是赢得的奖励。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/technology/2025/12/30/best-ai-chatbot/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OPFVRHMJXBDQTJ5GX2SUDSC7YM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Your early-adopter friend swears by ChatGPT for meal planning. Your boss thinks Microsoft Copilot will “10x productivity.” Your social media feed thinks Meta AI is a slop machine. They’re mostly going off vibes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QYNQBBU4KVAPNGX2E2M7IDAHVE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I can tell you which AI tools are worth using — and which to avoid — because I’ve been running a chatbot fight club.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:31:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMieEFVX3lxTE92dlNkVHJMbG4xTUpDcW1RNG12bGdCN1lFaUdJVG56OGYzN3VodU52TUttbWJwR3VZajJNWHNzQ2E0M1RMbFdFNUd3dlJsRnpHVlhvRjR3bjRfdzJ0Q0c1QWg5b1g1ZlhvTWF0Y3A0aVROb294WGFTUQ</guid></item><item><title>开创性的机器人手术，阿尔茨海默氏症血液测试： 2025年7项最大的医学突破- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/groundbreaking-robotic-surgery-alzheimers-blood-test-7-biggest/story?id=128654798</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;From robotic surgery performed 7,000 miles away to the first blood test to help diagnose Alzheimer's disease, 2025 has been a year full of medical breakthroughs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Scientists discovered a brain implant to give some patients back their independence, prevented others from needing to take opioids and made a discovery that could help solve the organ shortage crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Here are seven of the biggest innovations in the health and science space this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;ALS patient is 1st to control iPad by thought with implantable brain sensor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A patient with amyotrophic lateral sclerosis (ALS) became the first person in the world to control an iPad entirely by thought, neurotech company Synchron &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/Health/als-patient-1st-control-ipad-thought-implantable-brain/story?id=124442283" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;announced earlier this year&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The patient, Mark Jackson, from western Pennsylvania, controls the tablet without using his hands or voice command but rather with an implantable brain-computer interface (BCI) that translates his thoughts into actions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;At the time, Jackson told ABC News he doesn't have use of his arms so the BCI helps him watch TV shows, listen to audiobooks, browse social media and send text messages to his children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Mark Jackson, 65, from Pennsylvania has become the first person to control an iPad via thought, using a brain computer interface (BCI).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Synchron&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;BCIs are sensors implanted in the brain and translate brain signals into actions outside of the body. The BCI that Jackson is using was &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20250804537175/en/Synchron-Debuts-First-Thought-Controlled-iPad-Experience-Using-Apples-New-BCI-Human-Interface-Device-Protocol" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;developed by the company Synchron&lt;/a&gt;, which involves a device implanted into one of the veins within the brain in a minimally invasive procedure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"This is really an exciting field, because I think the opportunities are boundless," Dr. Leah Croll, a neurologist at Maimonides Medical Center in New York City, told ABC News. "I think that we're going to see, moving forward, not only using BCIs to control other electronic devices, but also using them to give patients back movement, to give patients back language, really bodily functions that they weren't able to do after whatever neurologic insult happened to them."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Croll said it's important, going forward, to consider legal and ethical considerations such as privacy and data storage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;She also encouraged more research and clinical trials to generate data on how patients can be protected in both research and real-world settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"There's so much we haven't figured out legally and ethically when it comes to storing personal, private data from your brain, and how is that used, and how do we manage that responsibly," she said. "There's a lot of bio-ethical minds at work as to how we deal with this issue and how do we make it so that a patient isn't sort of signing away the rights to their entire brain and inner world and manage something responsibly for them that's helpful and not harmful."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;First pill for obstructive sleep apnea may be around the corner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The first oral pill for obstructive sleep apnea (OSA) could soon be available after a late-clinical showed positive results, according to pharmaceutical company Apnimed Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The drug, AD109, showed "clinically meaningful and statistically significant reductions" in airway obstruction after 26 weeks, the company said in a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://aasm.org/apnimed-second-clinical-trial-sleep-apnea-medication/" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;press release in July&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;OSA is a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://medlineplus.gov/ency/article/000811.htm" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;sleep disorder in which&lt;/a&gt; the airways become narrowed or blocked while sleeping, causing breathing to pause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The investigational once-daily pill is a neuromuscular modulator that stabilizes upper airway muscles and prevents them collapsing, improving oxygenation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;OSA patients treated with the medication saw a nearly 50% reduction in the severity from baseline at week 26, compared to 6.8% of those in the placebo group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The reduction was "significant" at the end of the study period, which concluded at 51 weeks. At the end of the trial, nearly 23% of participants saw "complete disease control."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://nam04.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fapnimed.com%2Farticle%2Fapnimed-to-present-additional-phase-3-data-for-ad109-an-investigational-oral-pill-for-obstructive-sleep-apnea-at-chest-2025-annual-meeting&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CMary.Kekatos%40abc.com%7C618f6d12f70f461724fd08de422661ea%7C56b731a8a2ac4c32bf6b616810e913c6%7C1%7C0%7C639020929776048048%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=Gjjc9R9FfjXVmkCjLL7Lt1vSLMzeYNXXrp22ocTSB7I%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;More recent trial data&lt;/a&gt; published in October found that a meaningful number of patients achieved complete disease control and experienced significant improvements in oxygenation measures.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;First non-opioid medication in more than 20 years approved by FDA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Earlier this year, the FDA &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.fda.gov/news-events/press-announcements/fda-approves-novel-non-opioid-treatment-moderate-severe-acute-pain" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;approved a new type of non-opioid pain medication&lt;/a&gt; to treat moderate to severe acute pain, the first of its kind on more than 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Suzetrigine, also known by the brand name, Journavx, is manufactured by biotech company Vertex Pharmaceuticals and doesn't have addictive properties, unlike opioids often used for this type of pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It's significant in light of all the concerns about the opioid epidemic and addiction substance use disorder," Dr. Jianguo Cheng, a professor of anesthesiology and medical director of the Cleveland Clinic Consortium for Pain at Cleveland Clinic, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;This photo provided by Vertex Pharmaceuticals in January 2025 shows a tablet and bottle of the JOURNAVX (suzetrigine) medication.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Vertex Pharmaceuticals via AP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In two clinical trials, tested on adults between ages 18 and 80, Journavx was found to reduce moderate to severe acute pain for adults from baseline by about 50% in 48 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The average time to meaningful pain relief ranged from two to four hours, compared to eight hours in the placebo group, according to the trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Cheng, who was not involved in the clinical trials, said the studies demonstrated efficacy of the drug not compared to not only placebo, but also to weak opioids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Its efficacy is as good as a weak opioid. So why that is important?" Cheng said. "Because not all patients need opioids, and not all patients need a strong opioid. ... If most of them do need a weak opioid, and if this can replace the weak opioid, that can be a big deal."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;Scientists discover immune reaction behind pig kidney rejection in transplant patients&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Although gene-edited pig kidneys have been seen as a way to help ease the shortage of organs available for those on transplant waiting lists, many of the organs have been rejected not long after transplant surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Until 2021, we had never put one of these gene-edited pig organs into a human ... so it was a bit of a mystery when we started doing the pig-to-human transplants, about what we were going to encounter," Dr. Robert Montgomery, director of the NYU Langone Transplant Institute, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Last month, a team at NYU Langone Health published a study in which they discovered immune reactions that may explain why these organs get rejected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The team collected two months of data from a patient who was brain dead and had a genetically engineered pig kidney transplanted into them. The family had donated the patient's body to science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The team learned that pig organs were being rejected due to an immune system reaction from specific antibodies -- which recognize and attach themselves to foreign substances so they can be removed from the body -- and from T cells, which are white blood cells that help the body fight off germs and other unfamiliar invaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;'So you have this very coordinated immune response that involves antibodies and white cells, and it seems to happen somewhere between two and four weeks after the transplant," said Montgomery, lead author of the study. "Now the good news on that front is that we can detect when it's coming before rejection happens, and we can begin to respond, and we have very good therapeutics that can block the rejection and prevent it from causing damage."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;After rejection, the team used an FDA-approved drug combination to successfully reverse it, with no signs of permanent damage or reduced kidney function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In a second study, Montgomery and his team looked at the body's immune response to the pig organ in greater detail. By measuring levels of biomarkers in the blood, they were able to spot an attack up to five days before it would be visible in bodily tissue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Montgomery said the findings could lead to a future where gene-edited pig organs are a realistic alternative to human organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The pig organ can really replace a human organ and do all the things that a human organ can do, and it's really just a matter of overcoming the immunosuppression and preventing rejection," he said. "I think it's going to happen ... and people will be receiving xenotransplants on a regular basis. It's going to be normalized, and it's going to be something that will benefit thousands, first, and then millions of people around the world."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;FDA clears 1st blood test to help diagnose Alzheimer's disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In May, the FDA cleared the first blood test to help diagnose Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The test, manufactured by Fujirebio Diagnostics, is for those aged 55 and older who are already exhibiting signs and symptoms of the disease, according to the federal health agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The new blood test works by measuring the ratio of two proteins -- pTau217 and β-amyloid 1-42 -- which are found in human plasma, a component of blood. That ratio is then linked to the presence or absence of amyloid plaques in the brain to determine whether a patient is showing signs of Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Lumipulse® G β-Amyloid 1-42 Plasma&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Fujirebio&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In a clinical study, more than 91% of nearly 500 cognitively impaired patients who tested positive on the blood test had their results confirmed by other diagnostic tools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Essentially, it does provide a first quantitative measure of an Alzheimer's disease diagnosis," Dr. Jeffrey Savas, an associate professor in the department of neurology at Northwestern University Feinberg School of Medicine, told ABC News. "This is very important to identify patients which could be good candidates for some of the emerging therapeutics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Savas said the test is rapid, highly accurate and less expensive or invasive compared to previous diagnostic tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Because many Alzheimer's patients need to wait months to see a specialist, the test can allow primary care providers to start the diagnostic process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Many neurological research centers have huge backlogs of patients, and there's not enough physicians or nurses to really see the patients in a timely manner," Savas said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Having this quick diagnostic test, which could be taken in other medical settings, should pave the way for quicker, more effective opportunities and chances for being treated in a timely manner."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://nam04.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.alz.org%2Fnews%2F2025%2Ffda-clearance-blood-test-primary-care-rule-out-alzheimers-related-amyloid-pathology&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CMary.Kekatos%40abc.com%7C618f6d12f70f461724fd08de422661ea%7C56b731a8a2ac4c32bf6b616810e913c6%7C1%7C0%7C639020929776272653%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=4y4dELPVboq15zgI9EemRv36ASD66THEmflq3iizUIU%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;In October&lt;/a&gt;, the FDA cleared a second blood-based test called Elecsys pTau181, made by Roche.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;Groundbreaking remote robotic surgery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A patient living in Angola with prostate cancer underwent surgery this year to cut the cancer out, but the doctor performing the surgery was 7,000 miles away in Orlando, Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The patient was the first in a groundbreaking human clinical trial approved by the FDA to test transcontinental robotic telesurgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Dr. Vipul Patel, medical director of the Global Robotic Institute at Advent Health in Orlando, Florida, who performed the robotic telesurgery.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;ABC News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A team at OrlandoHealth operated on the patient via a multimillion-dollar robot with enhanced visuals and nimble controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Using a robot allows for the procedure to be less invasive, more precise and typically comes with a faster recovery time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The team has said underserved areas in the U.S. and around the world could benefit from the technology by having a surgeon perform an operation even if they are not nearby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;1st-ever gene fix for rare deadly disease saves baby's life&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A baby with a rare and life-threatening metabolic disorder underwent a personalized treatment involving a first-of-its-kind type of gene-editing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;KJ Muldoon was diagnosed as a newborn with carbamoyl-phosphate synthetase 1 deficiency as a newborn. The disorder affects a bodily cycle that causes deadly levels of ammonia to build up in the blood, which can lead to severe and permanent brain damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Dr. Musunuru and Dr. Ahrens-Nicklas hold KJ post infusion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Children's Hospital of Philadelphia&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;If left untreated, it will typically result in the death of the patient, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://rarediseases.org/rare-diseases/carbamoyl-phosphate-synthetase-i-deficiency/" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;National Organization for Rare Disorders&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The treatment for KJ involved the powerful gene-editing tool CRISPR, which allows scientists to precisely slice and repair faulty genes. Using CRISPR, the team was able to create a treatment tailored to the baby's specific genetic mutation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;In June, KJ &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://video.goodmorningamerica.com/wellness/story/baby-saved-gene-editing-therapy-graduates-hospital-home-122487817" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;went home&lt;/a&gt; after spending the majority of his life at Children's Hospital of Philadelphia. Earlier this month, he reached a big milestone: &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abcnews.go.com/GMA/Wellness/baby-saved-gene-editing-therapy-takes-1-st/story?id=128515109" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;taking his first steps&lt;/a&gt; ahead of Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ABC News' Youri Benadjaoud, Liz Neporent and Dr. Keerthana Pakanati&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em class=" "&gt;contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:10:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOR1lSN0YtYjJzRnFiRE80SDJjZi1rVzJhQ0RVTE1VVDlHV0x0R0QxNHVaTThaaktZRmo2cVdqNjZTZTdJeTV2SVRzYXBXNG5STnhISmZrSktnTjNOa0VvMG9yY2JSRXVQa0J0YVZJZnQ3MEIwV00xYzVwbDZrM1VTeEtCMWpDRVNReldiakNhMmtTNVZ3WjQyLU4taGRPYTk0ZjMxOXpMZUY1TXo3ZnlWYtIBtgFBVV95cUxPWkVrZEtqd0E3MFRkMWF5VnczSEthbk1neWhxUS1EcnpvM1FCMEZzX2wzSWF1N2hXNFdMaVd3dmMzdlc5QV9ETlEtY3JHeW1BRFIwb09xaHJXZ0M0VmpPNkUxQ0c4amQzMmpFYzJSSEJjMnhaVENjZHZpbkZfd0VoUjNsUVJhUE9KNlBJWmxLazBmMlg2RkNHbGV5MWo1MHlHSThZTGdWVXd2V0FmOGpTWWVOUC13QQ</guid></item><item><title>总部位于德克萨斯州的血管外科医生警告夜间腿部痉挛，分享了2个可能起触发作用的潜在原因|健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/texas-based-vascular-surgeon-warns-against-leg-cramps-at-night-shares-2-underlying-causes-that-can-act-as-triggers-101767086545544.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/texas-based-vascular-surgeon-warns-against-leg-cramps-at-night-shares-2-underlying-causes-that-can-act-as-triggers-101767086545544.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;Leg cramps are a fairly common experience among us all. Also known as a “charley horse,” it is a sudden, involuntary, intense muscle spasm that is usually felt in the calf, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/diabetic-foot-care-expert-shares-5-signs-that-could-indicate-nerve-damage-in-feet-due-to-diabetes-101766077526713.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="foot"&gt;foot&lt;/a&gt; or thigh.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/30/550x309/pexels-photo-6598240_1767086958496_1767086984779.jpeg" alt="Leg cramps at night are not always caused by dehydration or low potassium, shares Dr Malik.(Pexel)" title="Leg cramps at night are not always caused by dehydration or low potassium, shares Dr Malik.(Pexel)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/12/30/550x309/pexels-photo-6598240_1767086958496_1767086984779.jpeg" alt="Leg cramps at night are not always caused by dehydration or low potassium, shares Dr Malik.(Pexel)" title="Leg cramps at night are not always caused by dehydration or low potassium, shares Dr Malik.(Pexel)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Leg cramps at night are not always caused by dehydration or low potassium, shares Dr Malik.(Pexel)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The tendency to experience &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/harvard-gastroenterologist-explains-how-to-get-rid-of-leg-cramps-quickly-sip-pickle-juice-for-relief-within-seconds-101753762883012.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="leg cramps"&gt;leg cramps&lt;/a&gt; increases with age. According to the Cleveland Clinic, up to 60% of adults get leg cramps at night, compared to 40% children and teenagers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also Read | &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/ahmedabadbased-dermatologist-shares-cheat-sheet-of-9-things-to-avoid-indoors-for-healthy-skin-and-hair-101767080077044.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Ahmedabad-based dermatologist shares 9 things to avoid indoors for healthy skin and hair"&gt;Ahmedabad-based dermatologist shares 9 things to avoid indoors for healthy skin and hair&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The commonness of the phenomenon has brought the tendency to “walk it off” into the collective consciousness. However, Texas-based vascular surgeon Dr Rema Malik believes that the persistent nighttime cramps are not just signs of dehydration or low &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/warning-signs-and-symptoms-of-dangerously-low-potassium-levels-101679753190357.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="potassium"&gt;potassium&lt;/a&gt;, but rather classic distress signals from the vascular system.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Taking to Instagram on November 4, Dr Malik shared the two main vascular causes that she looks out for when it comes to leg cramps at night.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;1. Venous Insufficiency (The "Pressure" Problem)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Malik, this is the predominant vascular cause for leg cramps at night.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“After a long day of sitting or standing, blood pools in your lower legs. &lt;span class="highlight"&gt;At night, that stagnant, waste-filled blood and fluid can irritate your nerves and muscles, triggering intense cramps and that awful ‘restless legs’ feeling,” she explained.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;2. Peripheral Artery Disease (The "Flow" Problem)&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="highlight"&gt;Also known as “rest pain,” the peripheral artery disease (PAD) is an advanced case of clogged arteries, where the leg muscles are deprived of oxygen even while the body is at rest.&lt;/span&gt; The condition can threaten the limb itself.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Such leg cramps cannot be clubbed with the normal effects of ageing, cautioned Dr Malik. The risk significantly increases after the age of 40 for venous insufficiency, and after the age of 50 for PAD, she added.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:06:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxOTEhZQTQ1b09Bb3hSc3VfWXVfLXo1VWFYRFhZMTZMdTZVUGgzUEFnTnRPemt3SDVZMW9VazlRZDRPdV9DWlRSNERfeDFrZTNUNzhBYWJKcUZ0LTZXTmFSUUFoM1h4eVB6MWZybkl3ZW56OW8xTGVzcmNWWXRDSVJvREpVNjVMTlI2N3BDZGJvblprNXFYMUhpS05jbmxqUTlDN2RtdXVuamlyUWFGTldJaDFVazNyY1Q3QlpBTUktRnprbmxxNUgxbnY2eG1RUFVIVFo2TFd4VjNkRzBEVXpGOFFhVnQ5Rk1yY21EYzA5SDBCcDlHMmExM1NDb09vc0ZIMV9CZkFPV3QyVXdldGpRbNIBlgJBVV95cUxQQndxb1ExM2x1X3JyUVowTGRyR3VhZVRiQmhyZ0h3VUY2TTlTb3J6ZVZmODdjWGljMm40SklSeUJzNldlT2lQSHcxYzRkVWpfaUZ5YUY4ZjRBeWlPeDE3ZFlISlNxYXFmSFR0RWJWdlp4OEZIT2xfXzJkRU1weVpDZTZxUWhieG5adWZFME92T0VpTFRNTkRoTGk0YmJqb1NuemFNYmpVWXRlMi1pQ2NXUmxNVDNGRlV6YjFkZER2dTJBUUtkUGVDZHV5WGloV183Y0dvbnM5Z1NqRkc3Q2VDNVg1Mndrd2dfdUdXek1zSjRIRkFWNTdWUHFEMjg5NldFRlI0VUJkMFJ6OV9iMEtCcWxHeHdsQQ</guid></item><item><title>社交吸烟对您有害吗？ -《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/30/well/social-smoking.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:01:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMia0FVX3lxTE5HVTN2NDFJQkNtRkxMdkpDN3hJd0lBQkNFSXRVYXRwbm9TTDd3c1h6a1YyMGs5ejEtdDREZlNiWXVnZVFTaUNabHdnTVQwVHFBTGwxZzhIREpCTm9RSXU2TWVnTFFkc3pOSlUw</guid></item><item><title>2026年的10个营养建议-《纽约时报》</title><link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/12/30/well/eat/healthy-eating-tips-2026.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 10:00:15 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE9ZTVpjOW0xRmhYeDlrWUJtMThOZmtWRUpDX0wzN3RoOG5rM09Ia1Y1UEVJR05YcnBlRjlfdGd0cGxOVlc3ZnZXSkxXNm5IbFdBV3ZQZXpCMGxqX0JONW41WkZ2SzRhX2dkWnVlZlJuZnhfdURZdWVlU3hoTU9nQQ</guid></item><item><title>什么原因导致早发性结肠癌？新研究提供线索- Business Insider</title><link>https://www.businessinsider.com/why-so-many-young-people-getting-colon-cancer-answer-infancy-2025-12</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content full-width-post" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
          
              &lt;p class="drop-cap"&gt;Five years ago, Tim Cannon, a cancer doctor in Virginia, saw that his &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/true-cost-young-colon-cancer-crisis-2025-10" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;colon cancer&lt;/a&gt; patients were getting younger and their cancer was more aggressive. He had just diagnosed three people in their 30s with late-stage colon cancer. More perplexing, all three were athletes who competed in long-distance, endurance sports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Within a six-month period, I saw three extreme athletes in their 30s with metastatic, very advanced, incurable colon cancer," Cannon told Business Insider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All three patients died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannon had a hunch that this pattern wasn't an anomaly. He examined 100 more long-distance runners between 35 and 50 years old and found that 39 had developed precancerous tumors in their colons. Fifteen of those cases were advanced — far more than the expected 1.2%. Nearly one-sixth of all the runners were at risk of developing colon cancer. It was startling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannon's research, which is still in its early stages, points to broader questions that have confounded the medical community:&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Why are so many &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/scientists-uncover-processed-foods-fuel-colon-cancer-how-offset-damage-2024-12" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;young, fit adults getting sick&lt;/a&gt; and dying from colon and rectal cancer? And why are these patients — people who are younger than 45, the age at which screening is first recommended — getting the most aggressive forms of the disease?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The steepest rise is in people in their 20s and 30s," said Dr. Kimmie Ng, director of Dana-Farber's Young-Onset Colorectal Cancer Center. "They're younger, they're healthier, they don't have comorbidities, they get more treatment — and yet they're not living longer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In January, Business Insider reported on the leading scientific theories for &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/colon-cancer-environmental-causes-microplastics-antibiotics-sleep-2025-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;why people with clean diets get colon cancer&lt;/a&gt;. Possible answers ranged from microplastics to antibiotics. Leading theories generally pinpointed the modern diet, including too much sugar, and other facts of modern life, like staring into the blue light of our phones late at night, which can disrupt our natural rhythms.&lt;/p&gt;
            
          
            
          &lt;p&gt;These factors are likely part of the picture, oncologists say. But there's more to explore. Clusters of early-onset cancers like the one that Cannon says he identified are helping us gain a better understanding of the disease — and some answers for what ordinary people can do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer researchers are discovering how different environmental factors interact with our systems in complex ways and at different points of our development.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;aside class="callout-box headline-regular ignore-typography"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Business Insider spent a year investigating the impact the rise in young cancers is having on Americans — financially, emotionally, professionally — and how patients, and the healthcare system, are coping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;See more in our series, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/young-people-cancer-crisis-risk-tips-2025-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"callout_box","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The True Cost of Young Cancer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;p&gt;And they're increasingly zeroing in on the first year of life — from birth itself to our first months out of the womb — for answers about &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/young-people-cancer-crisis-risk-tips-2025-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;young cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p class="drop-cap"&gt;Some early research is scratching at the idea that a vulnerability to colorectal cancer could start in infancy — suggesting the first months and years of life could be a key window for intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;es-blockquote data-styles="pullquote-right" data-quote="&amp;quot;Something that happened at age six months, you don't even consider when you're 35. That disconnect is extremely problematic.&amp;quot;" data-source=""&gt;&lt;blockquote class="pullquote-wrapper pullquote-right"&gt;&lt;q class="pullquote-quotation heading-md"&gt;"Something that happened at age six months, you don't even consider when you're 35. That disconnect is extremely problematic."&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/es-blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;At UC San Diego, molecular biologist Ludmil Alexandrov recently identified a mutational signature in more than half of colorectal tumors found in patients under 40 that appears to be caused by colibactin, a toxin produced by a specific strain of E. coli.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What startled researchers was the timing of the damage. Cancer researchers typically find DNA damage building up in the adult body. Smoking, grilling meats, work like mining or asbestos-spraying — these well-trodden cancer triggers are typically ignited when our DNA is already becoming more decrepit and unstable, with time and age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here — according to the paper Alexandrov published in Nature in April — the infection had occurred before babies reached their ninth month of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexandrov's research, while preliminary, suggests infants can be hit with DNA mutations just months into their lives that might leave them predisposed to developing cancer within a few decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"You get your first hit at age 1 instead of age 30," Alexandrov said. "So you are about 20 to 30 years ahead of schedule for cancer."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Something that happened at age 6 months," Alexandrov added, "you don't even consider when you're 35."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That disconnect is extremely problematic."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Alexandrov's finding is confirmed in bigger studies, it could reframe the mystery of early-onset colorectal cancer. The rise could be rooted in early life, with early adulthood simply being the point at which the long incubation period finally comes to a head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If colibactin infections are a major early trigger, the most effective strategy may be preventing that mutational DNA damage in the first place. The next generation of cancer prevention may involve targeted microbial restoration and dietary strategies designed for an infant's developing immune system. Alexandrov envisions targeted probiotics for infants that neutralize colibactin-producing bacteria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If we can monitor the mutations and see that the ones exposed to the probiotic don't appear," he said, it could mean "we're eliminating the cause."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ng says Alexandrov's findings "cement a role of the microbiome in this disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shifts in how babies eat, including more ultra-processed food and fewer fiber-rich ingredients, could drive up colibactin infection rates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While researchers suspect that colibactin infections in infants have been on the rise in recent decades, there isn't enough data yet to say for sure. More study is also needed to confirm the link of any such rise to colon cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's not just diet that could be playing a role in the rise. Researchers are also looking at shifting trends in &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; babies are born.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p class="drop-cap"&gt;Our first moments of life are a pivotal training ground for the gut — a baby's welcome party to our diverse world of bacteria, fungi, and viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Babies born vaginally pass through the birth canal and pick up critical microbial communities from their mothers — microbes that help train the immune system. C-section babies start life with different microbes, and the evidence is mounting that these early differences may have an impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"There is strong evidence that early-life microbial disruption can influence long-term health risk," said Dr. Maria Gloria Domínguez-Bello, a professor at Rutgers University who has pioneered infant microbiome research and looked at the links between an infant's microbiome and their risk for adult diseases, including IBS, ulcerative colitis, and colon cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She noted that modern changes to birth and feeding practices may lead to subtle yet consequential disruptions to the microbiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2016, Domínguez-Bello launched a landmark study on "vaginal seeding" — taking babies born via C-section and coating them with bacteria from the mother's vaginal canal. It will be years before we know the effectiveness of this approach, but the hope is that this small intervention may have bolstered their microbiome from day one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, there's feeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breastfeeding is one of the ways infants acquire early protective microbes. Breastmilk is packed with complex sugars — human milk oligosaccharides — that babies' gut bacteria can feed on, shaping the early immune system. It can also contain traces of what the mother ingests or has been exposed to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple large-scale studies have found that the gut bacteria of formula-fed babies tend to differ from those of breastfed babies. While questions remain, this research is reshaping the infant formula market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Companies like Biomilq and Helaina are developing "microbiome-friendly" formulas that contain synthetic versions of the complex sugars found in breastmilk. Early clinical trials show these products can nudge a baby's gut bacteria to look more breastfed, though whether that matters decades later remains unknown. Still, these formulas have become one of the fastest-growing segments of the infant nutrition industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p class="drop-cap"&gt;Consuming too much sugar is emerging as a key culprit that may be shaping what happens to our microbiome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ng's group has found that sugary diets — especially sugary drinks including soda, juice, and sports drinks — are associated with a higher risk of early-onset colon cancer.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Food that spikes insulin or glucose "is linked with a higher risk of colorectal cancer," too, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Andrea Cercek at Memorial Sloan Kettering noticed something else: Among her youngest patients with stage 4 cancer, sugar consumption stood out. "There were slight differences in risk factors — and sugars in particular," Cercek said. The idea aligns with prior studies showing that fructose can accelerate polyp growth in animal models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;es-blockquote data-styles="pullquote-breakout" data-quote='"A high fiber diet produces metabolites that suppress colon cancer risk. A high saturated meat diet produces metabolites that are inflammatory and carcinogenic."' data-source=""&gt;&lt;blockquote class="pullquote-wrapper pullquote-breakout"&gt;&lt;q class="pullquote-quotation heading-md"&gt;"A high fiber diet produces metabolites that suppress colon cancer risk. A high saturated meat diet produces metabolites that are inflammatory and carcinogenic."&lt;/q&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/es-blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;It doesn't mean sugar "causes" cancer. But modern, ultra-high levels of sugar intake may be accelerating disease in people whose risk was primed early. And they're crowding out what people once used&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;to balance out sugar's effect on the body, improving blood sugar and aiding digestion at the same time: fiber.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugar can be great for a quick burst of energy, but in the long run, we need fiber to slow it down and promote good gut health. This is especially true of resistant starch (beans, lentils, oats), the type that ferments in the gut and produces short-chain fatty acids that suppress inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Stephen O'Keefe, who studies Alaska Native communities with historically high colorectal cancer rates, recently found that adding a resistant starch supplement to people's diets for just four weeks had measurable effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The supplementation did suppress cancer biomarkers," he said, discussing the findings he presented to colleagues at Digestive Disease Week 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A high fiber diet produces metabolites that suppress colon cancer risk," he said. "A high saturated meat diet produces metabolites that are inflammatory and carcinogenic."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He's seen this kind of thing before, noting important, negative microbial changes occurred quite rapidly when he fed rural, bean-eating South Africans typical American foods like hamburgers and hash browns for two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;O'Keefe believes increasing fiber intake could meaningfully offset other dietary risks, and perhaps reshape the microbiome in protective ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p class="drop-cap"&gt;Once researchers began looking beyond diet, they started interrogating other environmental changes as possible multipliers of an individual's risk of colorectal cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial light at night — particularly from phones — disrupts circadian rhythms that regulate DNA repair. Long periods of sitting can slow gut motility and increase inflammation. Air pollution inflames the gut lining and introduces carcinogenic particles directly to the colon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These aren't "causes" in isolation. But, together with nutrition and metabolism, they can disrupt how genes operate. Over time, these changes can trigger more disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the focus of Dr. Heinz-Josef Lenz's research at the University of Southern California Cancer Center. As a gastroenterologist, he has been troubled by a rise in young Latino men developing colon cancer in high school and college — many of them are athletic and healthy with no known risk factors. Lenz says their higher-than-average occurrence of young colon cancer is not due to any particular genetics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What can it be when it's not genetic? It could be epigenetic," he said. "Meaning, what you do, what you eat, what you drink, and related to your parents — how they acted and behaved."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Already, he's seeing clues that young Latino athletes with colon cancer might be suffering from nutritional changes that span multiple generations, based on changes that are inherited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For one 15-year-old in Los Angeles, it's possible that a daily Gatorade is enough to promote tumor growth in the colon, while for someone else with a different background, it's not such a big deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though Lenz has seen some interesting data on fructose pathways that appear dysregulated in young colon cancer patients, he is cautious to point out that nothing has emerged that is definitively an "it" cancer-causer just yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The data should be becoming available in the next one or two years," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hope is that, with time and some more research, Lenz will be able to better tailor treatments to a patient's genetics and background, making each one more effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One promising target is the circadian rhythm, or a person's body clock. Lenz recently teamed up with top body clock researcher Dr. Steve Kay to examine the effects of manipulating the body clock on cancer treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"What we found is that some circadian clock proteins our lab has been researching for many years are the 'gas pedal' to cancer," Kay said in a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://today.usc.edu/usc-researchers-pioneer-lifesaving-cancer-breakthroughs" data-track-click='{"click_type":"other","element_name":"body_link","event":"outbound_click"}' rel=""&gt;press release&lt;/a&gt;. "Out of that came a whole set of experiments that started to really blow all of us away. Drugs that my lab developed to target the circadian clock showed they could kill colorectal cancer cells."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p class="drop-cap"&gt;For oncologists, the rise in young cases is not just a scientific challenge. Young patients often arrive confused and ashamed because they believe cancer is strongly associated with their own lifestyle choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannon says&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;this misconception adds to the pain. "The public understands cancer as more related to personal behavior than oncologists do," he said. "You don't have total control over this, as far as I can tell."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of the researchers we spoke to for this story cautioned that people shouldn't misinterpret this emerging science as a lifestyle playbook just yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They did encourage some lifestyle modifications. This includes&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;more fiber, less sugar, more movement, and better sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to the extreme athletes Cannon is studying, his own leading hypothesis is that the stress of extreme endurance training might starve intestinal tissue of oxygen and create more opportunities for cancerous mutations. His research is far from conclusive. "The theories are all over the place," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't want to overstate how much you can control this with any behavior," he said. "In the end, it's still a chance event."&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
              &lt;section class="post-promo post-text-promo"&gt;
                &lt;p class="post-promo-content headline-regular"&gt;
                  Business Insider's Discourse stories provide perspectives on the day's most pressing issues, informed by analysis, reporting, and expertise.
                  &lt;/p&gt;
              &lt;/section&gt;&lt;/section&gt;
          
          
          
          
          
          
    
    
    
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 09:07:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNX0JrTmtBbnVSbEE5YVdmU2hKZUJqWUNRVVg5TG14d0dSU1RtRnJ6SEFYTTdLeWo2RXJNYVRGV1ZxQW1STFJMUkdNOUZRZjVEZHkzODhuLU9jM1RWdVQ2VnhRczdxSXhUeThVWkMtV3pCVWx1MmVzWVdhUWxuUU5qVjNpVnB6c2J2YWxVZzlRdVhOWVJqVHpaRm53VnZScDduT3c</guid></item><item><title>这张栖息地沙发床白天和晚上都很好看| - Livingetc</title><link>https://www.livingetc.com/shopping/habitat-julien-sofa-bed</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;

&lt;p id="8f43e770-973b-4324-8e2d-32d534af2a90"&gt;This Christmas, I spent a total of five nights in three different sofa beds. Throw in a few cross-country train trips, and my back was in all sorts of twists and bends. So, as much as I appreciated my family and friends for putting me up — my gosh, was I happy to get into my own (proper) bed at the end of all of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The whole experience has made me clear on one thing: I want to make sure my &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livingetc.com/buying-guides/best-sleeper-sofas-and-sofa-beds" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livingetc.com/buying-guides/best-sleeper-sofas-and-sofa-beds"&gt;sofa bed&lt;/a&gt; is as comfortable as possible for my future guests. But, considering it's not something you often ever use in your own home, it's hard to actually know what it's like to sleep in (unless you're willing to forgo your own bed for a few nights on the sofa). And it's even harder to test in a store.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="8f43e770-973b-4324-8e2d-32d534af2a90-2"&gt;So, instead, I'm reverse-engineering my research. Rather than telling you what I've bought, I'm sharing what you — our trusted &lt;em&gt;Livingetc &lt;/em&gt;readers — have bought. And when it comes to sofa beds, this year &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=livingetc-us-5067389325583867811&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/7661796" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener" data-url="https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/7661796" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/7661796" data-merchant-name="Habitat UK" data-merchant-id="209252" data-merchant-network="CJ" data-merchant-url="habitat.co.uk" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Habitat's Julien Fabric 4-Seater Sofa Bed&lt;/a&gt; was a clear winner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-collectionwidget-384c81c116b66dd0958df4c0f7eb66b8" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div class="product-container standard-product-container"&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_standard" data-id="43bb50a8-1835-4837-bdee-5365559386a8" id="43bb50a8-1835-4837-bdee-5365559386a8"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=livingetc-us-1004273957272884835&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/7661796" data-model-name="Julien Fabric 4 Seater Sofa Bed in Natural" data-model-brand="Habitat" data-url="https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/7661796" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/7661796" data-merchant-name="Habitat UK" data-merchant-id="209252" data-merchant-network="CJ" data-merchant-url="habitat.co.uk"&gt;&lt;div class="product-image-widthsetter"&gt;&lt;p class="vanilla-image-block" data-bordeaux-image-check=""&gt;&lt;img src="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/cTEYRABs8zUdaoXS3XD6UR.gif" alt="Habitat, Julien Fabric 4-Seater Sofa Bed in Natural" loading="lazy" data-new-v2-image="true" data-original-mos="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/cTEYRABs8zUdaoXS3XD6UR.gif" data-pin-media="https://cdn.mos.cms.futurecdn.net/cTEYRABs8zUdaoXS3XD6UR.gif" class="featured_image"&gt;&lt;span class="featured__label standard__label"&gt;20% OFF&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_details_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_title_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;p class="featured__brand"&gt;Habitat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="featured__title"&gt;Julien Fabric 4 Seater Sofa Bed in Natural&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class="subtitle__description"&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a simple fold-out mechanism, Habitat's Julien four-seater sofa bed easily slides between day and night. Probably not best used as your every-day sofa, but instead something styled in the spare room (its fixed cushions make it a bit harder to clean), it comes backed with a manufacturer's 10 year guarantee, can be delivered to your door from just £6.95, and is currently 20% off. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="7f0a23cc-968c-4547-9988-604e2e8b6871"&gt;And look, it's not hard to see why. It seems someone has finally designed a sofa bed that looks just as good by day as it does at night. Comfortably seating four, it looks soft and squishy but still structured, and I particularly like the fitted cushions for a fuss-free look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But its biggest selling point is that it's well... big. At least for a sofa bed. With the sleeping space measuring 137cm wide and 191cm long, it's equivalent to a UK double bed, while most sofa beds are much less (especially if you go down the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livingetc.com/shopping/ikea-armchair-bed" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livingetc.com/shopping/ikea-armchair-bed"&gt;armchair-bed&lt;/a&gt; route). In fact, it's a wide enough &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livingetc.com/advice/how-to-convert-a-sofa-into-a-bed" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livingetc.com/advice/how-to-convert-a-sofa-into-a-bed"&gt;sofa that you could probably convert it into a bed&lt;/a&gt; without even folding it out (if you're only sleeping one).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But don't just take it from me (as, truthfully, I haven't slept on it) — take it from the countless reviews that real customers have left:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="847c6c3a-6e83-4d1d-ac28-c33a28d588fa"&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Great quality for the cost, and the delivery men were lovely."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"A number of guests have now used this sofa bed since our purchase last month — all comment on how comfortable it is."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Does not look like a sofa bed, is the easiest to &lt;a href="https://www.livingetc.com/advice/how-to-style-a-sofa-bed" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livingetc.com/advice/how-to-style-a-sofa-bed"&gt;convert into a sofa bed&lt;/a&gt; I've ever used, and is super comfortable."&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;"Really comfy &lt;a href="https://www.livingetc.com/advice/sofa-depth" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livingetc.com/advice/sofa-depth"&gt;deep sofa&lt;/a&gt; with a good quality fabric. The arms are low, and it's good for lounging. The bed makes up very easily; it's big, firm, and comfortable. You can store bedding underneath when the sofa is up."&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="7c0e6e05-ba4b-4aa2-9050-26d14efdb643"&gt;But if a natural &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livingetc.com/advice/best-sofa-colors" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livingetc.com/advice/best-sofa-colors"&gt;sofa color&lt;/a&gt; feels too dangerous for your household, it also comes in a dark green corduroy-style fabric, although it's not on sale and only available through Argos (it's sold out on Habitat, though it's still the same sofa).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like the look, but don't actually need a sofa bed? The same &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=livingetc-us-6408093100279163437&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/search/julien/?clickOrigin=searchbar:productdetails:term:julien" target="_blank" rel="sponsored noopener" data-url="https://www.habitat.co.uk/search/julien/?clickOrigin=searchbar:productdetails:term:julien" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/search/julien/?clickOrigin=searchbar:productdetails:term:julien" data-merchant-name="Habitat UK" data-merchant-id="209252" data-merchant-network="CJ" data-merchant-url="habitat.co.uk" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link"&gt;Julien style is available as a sofa, too, in a range of colors, fabrics, and size&lt;/a&gt;s (many of which are also on sale right now).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-collectionwidget-7fa51c79882bb2891244438cd1beca1f" data-url="" href="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;div class="product-container hero-product-container product-block-no-wrap"&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="c7f14ec4-4fc3-40b9-a6dd-e4291d30757f" id="c7f14ec4-4fc3-40b9-a6dd-e4291d30757f"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-15618761?sid=livingetc-us-7148190975568225234&amp;amp;url=https://www.argos.co.uk/product/3341711" data-model-name="Julien Fabric 4 Seater Sofa Bed in Green" data-model-brand="Habitat" data-url="https://www.argos.co.uk/product/3341711" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-15618761?sid=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;url=https://www.argos.co.uk/product/3341711" data-merchant-name="Argos" data-merchant-id="535" data-merchant-network="CJ" data-merchant-url="argos.co.uk"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_details_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_title_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;p class="featured__brand"&gt;Habitat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="featured__title"&gt;Julien Fabric 4 Seater Sofa Bed in Green&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="f3ce7682-622e-4a7e-a906-a583b50a1bb4" id="f3ce7682-622e-4a7e-a906-a583b50a1bb4"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=livingetc-us-5692481698326712613&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/3630123" data-model-name="Julien Fabric Footstool in Dark Green" data-model-brand="Habitat" data-url="https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/3630123" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/3630123" data-merchant-name="Habitat UK" data-merchant-id="209252" data-merchant-network="CJ" data-merchant-url="habitat.co.uk"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_details_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_title_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;p class="featured__brand"&gt;Habitat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="featured__title"&gt;Julien Fabric Footstool in Dark Green&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="product-block-row"&gt;&lt;div class="featured_product_block featured_block_hero" data-id="2289c16f-cd5d-4876-8b3d-9de15aedd3e7" id="2289c16f-cd5d-4876-8b3d-9de15aedd3e7"&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=livingetc-us-7952939824595798235&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/7047994" data-model-name="Julien Velvet 2 Seater Sofa in Orange" data-model-brand="Habitat" data-url="https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/7047994" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" rel="sponsored noopener" data-hl-processed="hawklinks" data-google-interstitial="false" data-placeholder-url="https://www.anrdoezrs.net/click-100624753-17220093?sid=hawk-custom-tracking&amp;amp;url=https://www.habitat.co.uk/product/7047994" data-merchant-name="Habitat UK" data-merchant-id="209252" data-merchant-network="CJ" data-merchant-url="habitat.co.uk"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_details_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;div class="featured_product_title_wrapper"&gt;
&lt;p class="featured__brand"&gt;Habitat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="featured__title"&gt;Julien Velvet 2 Seater Sofa in Orange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="5f0b130d-2af0-4092-b06c-9d9ce424c592"&gt;We've mentioned Habitat's Julien Sofa Bed before in other articles, and can see just how many readers went on to buy it, and Habitat's website is telling me that while I've been writing this story, three people have added it to their cart... so, you might want to move fast and make the most of this &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livingetc.com/shopping/sofa-sales-christmas-25" data-mrf-recirculation="inline-link" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livingetc.com/shopping/sofa-sales-christmas-25"&gt;post-Christmas sofa sale&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Livingetc</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 06:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTFA4bHN3SzNpUkhUZHdmX2Q2UnpHMk9KUlFtTmlXbHZWYTAySnJtaTNwQjZVLS1oaXBUcGN6T3JYUE9NSGtPcXY5OFo0OGp0cGlFUDlYaVlCNzZOSEhSNzZ4OWhWczJvSFBmSGc</guid></item><item><title>癌症诊断后，奥罗拉福克斯谷购物中心灵魂景点（ The Soul Spot ）的老板丽莎·保龄球（ Lisa Bowling ）周围的社区集会- ABC7芝加哥</title><link>https://abc7chicago.com/post/community-rallies-around-lisa-bowling-owner-soul-spot-fox-valley-mall-aurora-cancer-diagnosis/18331702/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;AURORA, Ill. (WLS) -- &lt;/span&gt;A community is rallying together to help a west suburban restaurant owner diagnosed with cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Many are even volunteering to keep the restaurant afloat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="shortcode-centertext EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Lisa Bowling says just a week after fulfilling her dream of opening The Soul Spot at Fox Valley Mall in Aurora, she found out she had stage four cancer. Now, while she fights for her life, the community is fighting for her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"It's been like a dream come true since I put all my heart and soul into the restaurant to get it open," Bowling said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Bowling opened Aurora's only soul food restaurant in August, and then her health took a drastic turn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"I had to have open heart surgery and then put on the ECMO machine to breathe for me, and all of that stuff. So now, I'm getting ready to do chemo," Bowling said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"Any day above ground is a good day," family friend Vera Giles-Norris said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Her illness has kept her away from the restaurant for nearly two months, as the community steps in to keep her dream alive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;SEE ALSO:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7chicago.com/post/shock-claus-event-leaves-waitstaff-bolingbrook-golf-clubs-nest-bar-grill-5k-tip-ahead-christmas-2025/18301561/"&gt;Diners leave waitstaff at suburban bar and grill nearly $5K tip ahead of holiday season&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Whether it's volunteering to play music, or clean tables, they're there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We see one of our soldiers fall, to do what we can do to help pick them up. And that's what I'm seeing play out. Business has not stopped since day one," Giles-Norris said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Even the restaurant's one and only chef, Katrina Reed, has been working morning to night every day of the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We bring the soul food; we bring the soul food. We bring the greens, the yams, the macaroni," Reed said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The flavor comes from Bowling's heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"When she was able to give back, she did so much sowing. And so, now in her time of need, it's her time to reap," Giles-Norris said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Bowling said she is out of the hospital, at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Her friends and family are hoping to &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.gofundme.com/f/Supportlisamandys" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;raise &lt;/a&gt;close to $50,000 to help pay for her medical expenses, but also keep her business afloat while she recovers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Visit &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.thesoulspots.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.thesoulspots.com&lt;/a&gt; for more information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WLS-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 Chicago</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:54:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMizAFBVV95cUxPMXMyeGIwckVod0Q1dElOSXFBbnYzNFlyRnNvZDJEbFNHTWF2c21oODRJS0lCV1hDR2c3RmZsVk52TlpTMTR2YlRaMjdwYU9xQm1PRC1rZFlfNTNWcVEyODlJUWRFUmprWVE1dGhmYVg5WmhpblA3czhmNUZjUko1WV82NFhLZUxRS2h3MUZpdmdyTVBBQ2l3Y2staEZGNUpkMU0ycGdKaVRrVnN4b2loVlNERlNTbTZNNjhWeV96U2x2WVkxSnpQXzdLUUjSAdIBQVVfeXFMTThUTy1naGhwZDZuTXBjUjRsanljNFlUcXdwMWxTejE5QndlbXo1b0VCSGVhY1lJYVd5RWVjd0piRmc0bk11NVdiVDBubXd6cEFVVF9vWWItR1lxUU9VMmNkNm51YW1nUGlVMjFIZkhkYXY4c0VEYVZkb3oyTThTUXJhVTRuSGxHU3FFWWdUc3dTQzRTQVNCak12UzJpb0c1VWRGbVc2cDd0SDFlZnAtbkVDcWZ2RVIxZk5XUXBiV0EzelBmT01nUExIOUpEaVBRZHdR</guid></item><item><title>新泽西州卫生局表示，纽瓦克机场的乘客可能已经让其他人接触过麻疹- ABC7纽约</title><link>https://abc7ny.com/post/newark-airport-passenger-may-have-exposed-others-measles-new-jersey-health-department-says/18325181/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;&lt;span class="oyrPY qlwaB AGxeB  "&gt;NEWARK, New Jersey (WABC) -- &lt;/span&gt;A passenger at Newark Airport may have exposed people to measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;New Jersey's Health Department says someone with the disease passed through the airport on Friday, December 12.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The person was in terminals B and C between 7 a.m. and 7 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The Health Department hopes to track down people who were likely exposed. It also suggests anyone who is not vaccinated to get the MMR shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Measles symptoms include a high fever, cough, runny nose, watery red eyes, and a rash that usually appears between three and five days after symptoms begin. The rash usually begins as flat red spots that appear on the face at the hairline and spread downward to the neck, torso, arms, legs, and feet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;----------&lt;br class=" "&gt;*&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/newsletters/" target="_blank"&gt; Get Eyewitness News Delivered&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br class=" "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/new-jersey/" target="_blank"&gt;More New Jersey news&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br class=" "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://7ny.tv/submitnewstip" target="_blank"&gt;Send us a news tip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br class=" "&gt;* &lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/apps/" target="_blank"&gt;Download the abc7NY app for breaking news alerts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br class=" "&gt;*&lt;strong class="vtkaO "&gt;&lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCrlIS7z20CnVaCrMvdkig_g" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt; Follow us on YouTube&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br class=" "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="RxNCg ykkUm PvZ nIjPJ PMXYp LmsHF SfAHY mNgye lNbol LBPRq rBLIK "&gt;Submit a tip or story idea to Eyewitness News&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Have a breaking news tip or an idea for a story we should cover? Send it to Eyewitness News using the form below.    If attaching a video or photo, &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://abc7ny.com/image-video-solicitation-and-rights-terms-of-use/5101040/" target="_blank"&gt;terms of use apply.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="uvrxY zOGtW "&gt;Copyright © 2025 WABC-TV. All Rights Reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC7 New York</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 01:23:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxQdnJfNkpIR0xhU1ZuVjJXc1lld1ZNYVJXZ1NiV3VibklpVzg2dzd6NWh5MTBCS3g3RWM1cURSRzZaejI0Yk9FZE04aEJIVjFKVmwwMWE2YUdMYm1kUnlpVEtPTG5uTHlfWWh6T0tGcEZadFBtdmlTRXFxN09lMFhFZkJNVWxqeUpWQjlHdWlOZWhyNF9QUGtyMWFtUm1zTXJMTkgxc08wSDlUTnZucmVNcTN5TE43RWNiRGFRWmtLTi04QQ</guid></item><item><title>科学家发现有助于清除阿尔茨海默氏症斑块的大脑“开关” - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/scientists-discover-brain-switches-that-help-clear-alzheimers-plaques/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:41:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxQbi1VWUZPankwd2t5Vi1NakF4NXZpMXZXbWIwWVNBUEY2ODNUUk9rRUN5WmJoVEprRmpIbWUyUkVnM2VFbXVaT0Z0Y0Z1eEdCLS1CWW9tdTF5YzM5d2ZNc2JFbmpVTWZXbkxlQlMxOXYya1N1TXg0TmlMcjV5RzJ4aVpXRWFGN3pIQmliR1lnT085Y1VhdGUtaVNndw</guid></item><item><title>东湾报告的麻疹病例：这是感染者在圣诞节前购物的地方-旧金山纪事报</title><link>https://www.sfchronicle.com/health/article/measles-walnut-creek-21266900.php</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;
    
        
&lt;/body&gt;
</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:13:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQem1JUzJza3pfYnNmcmlEdjRtOUZuYUhKWUM0VzQtNEJUVXVjRDFwOXZCdzBPTDRoakdIVzhrcnpSMHBRMnZzR2dheXhrZFhiQXZVYk54YkV2RVJHUHBkdTVPdUtDLTBrNWpNc1VrQTJtUzdzamNPTnA4di05R2tJNzR3</guid></item><item><title>大脑有一种隐藏的语言，科学家刚刚发现了它- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/12/251225235950.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Scientists have developed a protein that can record the chemical messages brain cells receive, rather than focusing only on the signals they send out. These incoming signals are created when neurons release glutamate, a neurotransmitter that plays a vital role in brain communication. Although glutamate is essential for processes like learning and memory, its activity has been extremely difficult to measure because the signals are faint and happen very quickly.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This new tool makes it possible to detect those subtle chemical messages as they arrive, giving researchers access to a part of brain communication that has long been hidden.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why this discovery matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Being able to observe incoming signals allows scientists to study how neurons process information. Each brain cell receives thousands of inputs, and how it combines those signals determines whether it produces an output. This process is thought to underlie decisions, thoughts, and memories, and studying it directly could help explain how the brain performs complex computations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The advance also opens new paths for disease research. Problems with glutamate signaling have been linked to conditions such as Alzheimer's disease, schizophrenia, autism, epilepsy, and others. By measuring these signals more precisely, researchers may be able to identify the biological roots of these disorders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drug development could also benefit. Pharmaceutical companies can use these sensors to see how experimental treatments affect real synaptic activity, which may help speed up the search for more effective therapies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introducing a powerful glutamate sensor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The protein was engineered by researchers at the Allen Institute and HHMI's Janelia Research Campus. Known as iGluSnFR4 (pronounced 'glue sniffer'), it acts as a molecular "glutamate indicator." Its sensitivity allows it to detect even the weakest incoming signals exchanged between neurons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By revealing when and where glutamate is released, iGluSnFR4 provides a new way to interpret the complex patterns of brain activity that support learning, memory, and emotion. It gives scientists the ability to watch neurons communicate inside the brain in real time. The findings were recently published in Nature Methods and could significantly change how neural activity is measured and analyzed in neuroscience research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How brain cells communicate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To understand the impact of this advance, it helps to look at how neurons interact. The brain contains billions of neurons that communicate by sending electrical signals along branch-like structures called axons. When an electrical signal reaches the end of an axon, it cannot cross the small gap to the next neuron, which is known as a synapse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instead, the signal triggers the release of neurotransmitters into the synapse. Glutamate is the most common of these chemical messengers and plays a key role in memory, learning, and emotion. When glutamate reaches the next neuron, it can cause that cell to fire, continuing the chain of communication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From fragments to the full conversation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This process can be compared to falling dominos, but it is far more complex. Each neuron receives input from thousands of others, and only certain combinations and patterns of activity will trigger the receiving neuron to fire. With this new protein sensor, scientists can now identify which patterns of incoming activity lead to that response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until now, observing these incoming signals in living brain tissue was nearly impossible. Previous technologies were too slow or lacked the sensitivity needed to measure activity at individual synapses. As a result, researchers could only see pieces of the communication process rather than the full exchange. This new approach allows them to capture the entire conversation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Making sense of neural connections&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's like reading a book with all the words scrambled and not understanding the order of the words or how they're arranged," said Kaspar Podgorski, Ph.D., a lead author of the study and senior scientist at the Allen Institute. "I feel like what we're doing here is adding the connections between those neurons and by doing that, we now understand the order of the words on the pages, and what they mean."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before protein sensors like iGluSnFR4 were available, researchers could only measure outgoing signals from neurons. This left a major gap in understanding, since the incoming signals were too fast and too faint to detect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Neuroscientists have pretty good ways of measuring structural connections between neurons, and in separate experiments, we can measure what some of the neurons in the brain are saying, but we haven't been good at combining these two kinds of information. It's hard to measure what neurons are saying to which other neurons," Podgorski said. "What we have invented here is a way of measuring information that comes into neurons from different sources, and that's been a critical part missing from neuroscience research."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaboration behind the breakthrough&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The success of iGluSnFR4 stems from our close collaboration started at HHMI's Janelia Research Campus between the GENIE Project team and Kaspar's lab. That research has extended to the phenomenal in vivo characterization work done by the Allen Institute's Neural Dynamics group," said Jeremy Hasseman, Ph.D., a scientist with HHMI's Janelia Research Campus. "This was a great example of collaboration across labs and institutes to enable new discoveries in neuroscience."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new window into brain function&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This discovery overcomes a major limitation in modern neuroscience by making it possible to directly observe how neurons receive information. With iGluSnFR4 now available to researchers through Addgene, scientists have a powerful new tool to explore brain function in greater detail. As this technology spreads, it may help reveal answers to some of the brain's most enduring questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 22:07:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE8tTVpGSmZSNGFjeEpXNm03Qnp6UFdKTUNsWUZlTy0xMlp6SnFqOVNWSk5CczFXT1FwLXhDTGUxWGR5bkpnWm1wT1lqR2YxNDJ2djdXV3VNUmdmTmdPdDI3UDlEeEx2VmxfM2dZQVgtOA</guid></item><item><title>酒精是节日心脏综合征的重要因素，医生警告- KOMO</title><link>https://komonews.com/news/nation-world/doctors-warn-of-holiday-heart-syndrome-irregular-heartbeats-amid-celebrations</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="dateline"&gt;(TNND) — &lt;/span&gt;Doctors are warning people about holiday heart syndrome, a common but preventable disturbance of the heart rhythm that can be triggered by heavy drinking, overeating, stress, travel, lack of sleep and more this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your heart likes routine, which can be disrupted amid the hustle and bustle of the holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“And a person may experience palpitations or the sensation of their heart beating rapidly,” said Dr. B. Keith Ellis, the medical director of cardiology at Houston Methodist Sugar Land Hospital in Texas. “Or typically, people describe a butterfly in the chest.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="YouTubeEmbed_youTubeEmbed__ygKv1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fluttering might be harmless. But it might not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellis said the concern comes if a person experiences atrial fibrillation, which, if left untreated, can increase a person’s risk of stroke, heart failure and cardiomyopathy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellis said doctors see an increase in patients with A-fib around the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anybody, regardless of their health status, can experience holiday heart syndrome. But there are health factors that increase the risk of experiencing holiday heart syndrome. Those include age, high blood pressure, diabetes and sleep apnea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alcohol consumption plays a big factor in holiday heart syndrome, Ellis said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Repeated heavy drinking can shift what starts as a temporary disturbance into chronic A-fib, according to Houston Methodist. Five drinks a day increases A-fib risk by almost 50%, the hospital said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.houstonmethodist.org/blog/articles/2025/dec/holiday-heart-syndrome-why-your-heart-might-be-working-overtime-this-season/" target="_blank"&gt;Holiday heart syndrome symptoms&lt;/a&gt; typically show up 12 to 36 hours after drinking and can include rapid or irregular heartbeat, palpitations, lightheadedness or dizziness, shortness of breath, chest discomfort, or sudden fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to limiting alcohol, Ellis said people can reduce their risk of experiencing holiday heart syndrome by staying hydrated, going easy on the salt, getting enough sleep, and staying physically active.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellis said anyone who experiences persistent palpitations, which he described as over 30 seconds, should reach out to their doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I typically advise patients that if you experience any type of fluttering or palpitation to definitely reach out to your physician in consultation,” he said. “And there are a number of devices that are available that allow us to monitor a person's heart rhythm in the outpatient setting.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KOMO</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 22:07:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitwFBVV95cUxQdWZEczlNOTd6SkNzbE4yN3Jad3pacVhpZ2dSdXJObk5HSzRiZURaUGpWOU5GT190T21zQnFzaF9LMFNzOERDODIzM2VmRVBmbkFUQUVEMmRCRmo2N0xXdVh0NDNyblNvYkJNM0VoOGxZb09NYndWcUhQOFdaSGJvbzhnVkVKV2xzNFpnbHRHcjlvMVVqTFpjUXB4b045aEI2aUpaVkNQbUQ3UnptRkRudEJ3WVdyWnc</guid></item><item><title>流感病例在假期旅行、聚会、疾病预防控制中心最新数据显示中呈上升趋势- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/flu-cases-rise-amid-holiday-travel-gatherings-latest/story?id=128761006</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;Flu activity is increasing across the U.S. amid holiday travel and gatherings, according to the latest data the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-49.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The CDC estimates there have been at least 4.6 million illnesses, 49,000 hospitalizations and 1,900 deaths from flu this season so far, according to data updated as of Dec. 19, and experts expect these numbers will continue to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Public health experts previously told ABC News that many of this season's cases are linked to a new flu strain called subclade K -- a variant of the H3N2 virus, which is itself a subtype of influenza A -- that has been circulating since the summer in other countries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Of the 163 samples of H3N2 viruses collected since Sept. 28 and genetically characterized, 89% were subclade K, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Additionally, three pediatric flu deaths have been reported so far this season, according to an ABC News tally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Last season, the U.S. saw 288 children die from flu, which is the same number of children who died during the 2009 H1N1 pandemic. About 90% of kids who died from flu last year were not vaccinated, a &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://nam04.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.cdc.gov%2Fmmwr%2Fvolumes%2F74%2Fwr%2Fmm7436a2.htm&amp;amp;data=05%7C02%7CMary.Kekatos%40abc.com%7C922d49ba4e854b2c9ce708de470d29b7%7C56b731a8a2ac4c32bf6b616810e913c6%7C1%7C0%7C639026319021537637%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJFbXB0eU1hcGkiOnRydWUsIlYiOiIwLjAuMDAwMCIsIlAiOiJXaW4zMiIsIkFOIjoiTWFpbCIsIldUIjoyfQ%3D%3D%7C0%7C%7C%7C&amp;amp;sdata=BcaCAvedrcYzgw%2Fug8fsrCiHp4PSXukZK7EVo7LxtWM%3D&amp;amp;reserved=0" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC study&lt;/a&gt; published earlier this year found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Stock photo of a sick child.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Natalia Lebedinskaia/STOCK PHOTO/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Meanwhile, New York state is reporting the highest number of flu cases it has ever recorded in a single week. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The emergency room has been busy, and we've been following these numbers," Dr. Darien Sutton, a board-certified emergency medical physician and ABC News medical correspondent, told "Good Morning America" on Monday. "Just a note, national numbers typically lag during the holiday, but state health department numbers are giving us insight to just how severe this flu season is."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A total of 71,123 flu cases were reported for the week ending Dec. 20, according to the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.health.ny.gov/diseases/communicable/respiratory_viruses/activity/2025-2026/docs/current_respiratory_report.pdf" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;New York State Department of Health&lt;/a&gt; (NYSDOH). This marks the highest number of flu cases in a single week since it became mandatory for states to report in 2004. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;This is also 38% higher compared to the previous week which saw 51,365 infections reported, bringing the total flu cases reported in the state to 189,312.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Hospitalizations climbed by 63% in the most recent week, increasing from 2,251 to 3,666 weekly admissions, according to data from NYSDOH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Sutton said it's important to understand that flu is present and to take steps to reduce risk, including masking, washing hands with soap and water and getting the flu vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Currently, the &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.cdc.gov/flu/vaccines/index.html" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;CDC recommends&lt;/a&gt; that everyone aged 6 months and older, with rare exceptions, get a flu vaccine.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The federal health agency states on its website that getting an annual flu shot prevents millions of illnesses and flu-related doctors' visits every year and is especially important for those at higher risk of serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"The flu is so much more than a simple cold. I am treating it in the emergency room," Sutton said. "Understand that people are coming in feeling like they are so sick that it has to be something else than the flu."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;Sutton noted that he is seeing more people in the emergency room and more people being hospitalized but that the disease itself is not more severe, adding "it's not like a super flu."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 21:31:56 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPdTVta0VWM01NaFJCNklUMldhSGZpbGJiOGhIU1ctUXluejFVQVlWTTRGVkswS1pLdFV4NWd5WFh2VmRFMWg0ZDBzYWlxLVI3d0xoTmFMU3RYdzJDNEg2UWw4ak9RZTdCV2tqMktBWWV2N2EtQ2pQQzVTU3hWWTRTUUdPYmhCR3FnUzFZZV9QSGFhNEFOalNVSm9uUTlsOGgxLU5j0gGoAUFVX3lxTE5QLVBHYmlySHNnaV9TU2RwNTV3bEExTTRjWmpzUWV2Zkh2ZTIzeFktX0dINUlXQ0ZHZDNxN1kwbml2VUZ3NFE0bXJ5OEI3R1VkVHl0eDRoREFZUzRGbFlXSjEyV2h4OVFJRVVBSjN5RF9qM3FXbjJRMHRlbENCVVk1U1JfNkNmSS10bVpheHhIX2hzSW5GX1dhdEpMbHlvLUlPa2RtcWJIVg</guid></item><item><title>缺失的大脑受体可能是自闭症的关键-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://neurosciencenews.com/mglu5-autism-neuroscience-30078/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Autistic adults show reduced availability of a key glutamate receptor, mGlu5, across widespread brain regions. This difference supports the theory that an imbalance between excitatory and inhibitory signaling may contribute to autism-related traits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EEG data also showed that electrical activity linked to lower receptor availability can be detected noninvasively, suggesting a more accessible way to study excitatory function in autism. These findings offer rare molecular insight into autism and open potential avenues for improved diagnostics and targeted therapeutics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reduced Receptors:&lt;/strong&gt; Autistic adults showed lower availability of the mGlu5 glutamate receptor across the brain.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excitation–Inhibition Link:&lt;/strong&gt; Findings support the idea that altered excitatory–inhibitory signaling contributes to autistic traits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EEG Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; EEG markers correlated with receptor differences, pointing toward a more accessible diagnostic tool.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Yale&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yale School of Medicine (YSM) scientists have discovered a molecular difference in the brains of autistic people compared to their neurotypical counterparts.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autism is a neurodevelopmental condition associated with behavioral differences including difficulties with social interaction, restrictive or intense interests, and repetitive movements or speech. But it’s not clear what makes autistic brains different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-114476"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows a child's head and a brain." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/12/asd-receptor-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;Researchers propose the involvement of this central mechanism might explain the wide range of differences observed among autistic individuals. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, a new study in &lt;em&gt;The American Journal of Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt; has found that brains of autistic people have fewer of a specific kind of receptor for glutamate, the most common excitatory neurotransmitter in the brain. The reduced availability of these receptors may be associated with various characteristics linked to autism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We have found this really important, never-before-understood difference in autism that is meaningful, has implications for intervention, and can help us understand autism in a more concrete way than we ever have before,” says James McPartland, PhD, Harris Professor of Child Psychiatry and Psychology in the Child Study Center at YSM and the study’s co-principal investigator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Signaling imbalance in autism&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neurons in the brain communicate with one another using electrical signals and chemical messengers called neurotransmitters. When an electrical current propagates through a neuron, it prompts the release of neurotransmitters that relay a signal to other neurons. This signaling in the brain can be either excitatory or inhibitory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excitatory signaling primarily triggers the release of the neurotransmitter glutamate, and it acts as a green light telling other neurons to fire. Inhibitory signaling, on the other hand, acts as a brake that suppresses activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brain needs a precise balance of these two types of signaling in order to function properly. One of the leading hypotheses on the underlying causes of autism is an imbalance of excitatory and inhibitory signaling in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers propose the involvement of this central mechanism might explain the wide range of differences observed among autistic individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Based on this hypothesis, the researchers used magnetic resonance imaging (MRI) and positron emission tomography (PET) to look for differences in the brains of 16 autistic adults and 16 people considered neurotypical. MRI scans enabled the researchers to examine the anatomy of each of the participants’ brains, while PET scans revealed how the brains were functioning at the molecular level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“PET scans can help us pinpoint a molecular map of what’s going on in this glutamate system,” says David Matuskey, MD, associate professor of radiology and biomedical imaging at YSM, and co-principal investigator of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Autistic brains have reduced availability of a crucial receptor&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;These analyses revealed less brain-wide availability of a specific kind of glutamate receptor, known as metabotropic glutamate receptor 5 (mGlu5) in autistic participants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings support the idea that an imbalance of excitatory and inhibitory signals in the brain could be contributing to traits associated with autism, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fifteen of the autistic participants also underwent an electroencephalogram (EEG), a measure of electrical activity of the brain. Based on the EEG, the researchers identified that these electrical measurements were associated with lower mGlu5 receptors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This finding could have significant clinical implications, the researchers say. While PET scans are a powerful tool for studying the brain, they are also costly and involve exposure to radiation. EEG could be a cheaper and more accessible way to further investigate excitatory function in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“EEG isn’t going to completely replace PET scans, but it might help us understand how these glutamate receptors might be contributing to the ongoing brain activity in a person,” says Adam Naples, PhD, assistant professor in the Child Study Center at YSM and the study’s first author.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study gives the researchers novel mechanistic insight into how the brains of autistic individuals are different from those of neurotypical people. Because the molecular underpinnings of autism are still so poorly understood, clinicians today rely on behavioral observation to diagnose it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elucidating the “molecular backbone” of autism, researchers say, could potentially lead to better diagnostic tools and ways to support autistic people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today, I go into a room and play with a child to diagnose autism,” says McPartland, “Now, we’ve found something that is meaningful, measurable, and different in the autistic brain.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are currently no medications that treat the difficulties experienced by many with autism. The findings could also help researchers come up with therapeutics for autism that target the mGlu5 receptor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While many neurodivergent people aren’t hindered by autism and may not need or want medication, novel treatments could help those on the spectrum that experience symptoms that affect their quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Future research directions&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current study only included autistic adults. It is still unclear whether the lower receptor availability is a driver of autism or a result of living with it for decades. Previously, research involving PET scans has been limited to adults due to the risks associated with radiation exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Matuskey, co-investigator Richard Carson, PhD, and their colleagues have developed more sophisticated techniques that open a pathway for much lower exposure to radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In future studies, the team plans to conduct research with these new technologies in children and adolescents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We want to start creating a developmental story and start understanding whether the things that we’re seeing are the root of autism or a neurological consequence of having had autism your whole life,” says McPartland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All autistic participants in the study had average or above average cognitive abilities. McPartland and collaborators are also working together on developing other approaches to PET scans that will enable them to include individuals with intellectual disabilities in future studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Key Questions Answered:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq wp-block-yoast-faq-block"&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1767040196614"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: What molecular difference did researchers find in autistic brains?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; They discovered reduced availability of the mGlu5 glutamate receptor, which plays a central role in excitatory signaling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1767040198085"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Why does this receptor difference matter?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; It supports the long-standing hypothesis that autism involves an imbalance between excitatory and inhibitory brain signaling, which may explain a range of traits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="schema-faq-section" id="faq-question-1767040197872"&gt;&lt;strong class="schema-faq-question"&gt;Q: Could this lead to new diagnostic or treatment approaches?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p class="schema-faq-answer"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A:&lt;/strong&gt; Yes. EEG patterns associated with receptor differences suggest a more accessible diagnostic pathway, and mGlu5-related therapeutics may become future treatment targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Editorial Notes:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list has-background"&gt;&lt;li&gt;This article was edited by a Neuroscience News editor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Journal paper reviewed in full.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Additional context added by our staff.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this autism and neuroscience research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://medicine.yale.edu/profile/isabella-backman/#links-details-section" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Isabella Backman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://medicine.yale.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Yale&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Isabella Backman – Yale&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Closed access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1176/appi.ajp.20241084" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Imaging Metabotropic Glutamate Receptor 5 and Excitatory Neural Activity in Autism&lt;/a&gt;” by James McPartland et al. &lt;em&gt;American Journal of Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Imaging Metabotropic Glutamate Receptor 5 and Excitatory Neural Activity in Autism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Objective:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autism spectrum disorder is a prevalent and heterogeneous condition with features ranging from social and communication differences to sensory sensitivities. Differences in excitatory neurotransmission have been identified in autism, but the molecular underpinnings are poorly understood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To investigate the mechanism underlying these observed differences, the authors assessed glutamatergic receptor density in autistic adults using positron emission tomography (PET) and related it to a functional EEG measure of excitatory activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Methods:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Metabotropic glutamate receptor 5 (mGlu5) availability was compared in autistic (N=16) and neurotypical (N=16) adults between 18 and 36 years of age, using the PET tracer 3-[&lt;sup&gt;18&lt;/sup&gt;F]fluoro-5-(2-pyridinylethynyl) benzonitrile ([&lt;sup&gt;18&lt;/sup&gt;F]FPEB). The PET outcome measure was volume of distribution (V&lt;sub&gt;T&lt;/sub&gt;) computed with equilibrium analysis using a venous input function and partial volume correction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Group differences were quantified using mixed-model analyses. Heterogeneity was further parsed within the autistic group by quantifying the relationship between receptor availability and the slope of the EEG power spectrum, an index of excitatory-inhibitory balance. Correlations between EEG and V&lt;sub&gt;T&lt;/sub&gt; were calculated using Spearman’s rho.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Results:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across all brain regions, mGlu5 availability was significantly lower (by ~15%) in autistic relative to neurotypical control participants. Group differences were generally greatest in the cerebral cortex. Within the autistic group, mGlu5 availability in all regions was significantly correlated with the slope of the EEG (e.g., cerebral cortex, r=0.67), such that shallower slope was associated with lower mGlu5 availability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;Conclusions:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This brain-wide investigation of mGlu5 availability with PET revealed pervasive lower mGlu5 availability across multiple brain areas in autism. Additionally, multimethod analyses revealed associations with a noninvasive electrophysiological index of excitatory neurotransmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These results indicate that lower brain-wide mGlu5 availability may represent a molecular mechanism underlying altered excitatory neurotransmission that has the potential to stratify the heterogeneous autism phenotype.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:35:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMibkFVX3lxTFAwWHY1WWFMWmFFbktpc0JHLWc1cDYyYXFEUGU5S2cySzhFUms5b0RMM19XNjI5OWZONUY2T0puVWI4U3VITHVfZkExbTByakdCUmxDTklaaW9VcGVkVFpRMVQ0TzRKN1h2eUhKR0hR</guid></item><item><title>康特拉科斯塔县确诊麻疹病例-康特拉科斯塔健康</title><link>https://www.cchealth.org/Home/Components/News/News/979/415</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contra Costa Health (CCH) is notifying the public of a confirmed case of measles in the county, identified on Dec. 24, 2025. The individual was contagious in public between Dec. 17 and Dec. 24, and people may have been exposed at the locations listed below.  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Locations of potential measles exposure:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Dec. 17 or Dec. 19: Anthropologie, 1149 South Main St., Walnut Creek&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Dec. 18: Macy’s, 1320 Broadway Plaza, Walnut Creek; ALO, 1292 Broadway Plaza, Suite 1106, Walnut Creek; Apple Store, 1200 South Main St., Walnut Creek&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Dec. 21: STAT Med, 3799 Mount Diablo Blvd. #100, Lafayette &lt;br&gt;
    Dec. 23-24: Kaiser Permanente Walnut Creek Emergency Department, 1425 South Main St., Walnut Creek&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;People who were at these locations during the dates listed above may be at risk of developing measles, especially if unvaccinated, pregnant or immunocompromised. Measles can develop seven to 21 days after exposure. If you were at these locations during these times, you should confirm with your healthcare provider that you have been fully vaccinated against measles or have had measles infection in the past.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If symptoms develop, stay home and call your healthcare provider immediately before seeking care so they are prepared to take care of you. Those who have been symptom free for more than 21 days after being exposed are no longer at risk for developing measles.   &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
A large majority of Contra Costa County residents are fully vaccinated against measles and have lifetime protection against infection. CCH encourages all eligible unvaccinated residents to get immunized against measles with two doses of the measles-mumps-rubella (MMR) vaccine to ensure their protection. &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Measles is a highly contagious respiratory virus that can linger in the air or on surfaces for over an hour after the contagious individual leaves an area. This makes it even easier to spread to those who do not have protection. Also, a person can spread the virus to others even before they develop symptoms.   Symptoms of measles include fever, cough, runny nose, red eyes and a rash that spreads over the body.  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
Although the risk of contracting measles is low for those who are fully vaccinated, members of the public should be aware of the situation and watch for symptoms.  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
CCH is conducting contact tracing and notifying local healthcare providers to be vigilant for possible measles cases. CCH continues to monitor the situation and will provide updates if more information becomes available.  &lt;br&gt;
&lt;br&gt;
More information about measles can be found on &lt;a href="/health-and-safety-information/communicable-disease-program/measles"&gt;our website&lt;/a&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Contra Costa Health</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:09:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiakFVX3lxTE0wOGZTaVJMTXhUclI1X1NPNXlZeDZ4eWZGSXo2ZWlhcHFKaEZnRXM0SXdreGg0TFBFRGc0LTc1d2hsdW5MUy1TNWtRRktVLWZNRHhOYzZCQ3llLTZKMzlBRHpjMjVoZ1JGeVE</guid></item><item><title>美国麻疹爆发超过2000例已知感染- CIDRAP</title><link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/measles/us-measles-outbreak-tops-2000-known-infections</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Measles cases nationwide have reached 2,012, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) reported &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;last week&lt;/a&gt;, as outbreaks in Arizona and South Carolina continue to grow and three other states alert the public about airport exposures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US total reflects 54 new cases, as the country teeters on the brink of losing its measles elimination status—which it earned in 2000—next month. This year’s total is the nation’s highest since 1992, when officials &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/preview/mmwrhtml/00020688.htm"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; 2,200 cases. Coordinated vaccination efforts led to a precipitous drop in cases in the ensuing decades, but vaccine skepticism in recent years has spawned the disease’s resurgence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Vaccine coverage dropping&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccine is very safe and effective,” the CDC said. “When more than 95% of people in a community are vaccinated (coverage &amp;gt;95%), most people are protected through community immunity (herd immunity). However, vaccination coverage among U.S. kindergartners has decreased from 95.2% during the 2019–2020 school year to 92.7% in the 2023–2024 school year, leaving approximately 280,000 kindergartners at risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the confirmed patients this year, 26% have been younger than 5 years, 42% have been from 5 to 19 years, and 32% are older. Fully 93% have been unvaccinated or have an unknown vaccination status. Eleven percent of patients have required hospitalization, 20% of them preschoolers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) vaccine is very safe and effective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;CDC officials have confirmed 50 outbreaks, compared with 16 last year (and 285 cases).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three deaths have been confirmed to have been from measles in 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Outbreaks grow in Arizona, South Carolina&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both Arizona and South Carolina updated their measles numbers last week. Arizona’s &lt;a href="https://www.azdhs.gov/preparedness/epidemiology-disease-control/measles/index.php"&gt;total&lt;/a&gt; grew by five, to 195 infections. All the new cases are in Mohave County, which now has recorded 191 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mohave County and the neighboring southwest region of Utah now have 292 cases, the second-largest US outbreak this year, after one in West Texas this past spring and summer. In August state officials &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/measles/state-officials-declare-west-texas-measles-outbreak-over"&gt;declared&lt;/a&gt; the West Texas outbreak over after 762 cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://dph.sc.gov/diseases-conditions/infectious-diseases/measles-rubeola/2025-measles-outbreak"&gt;South Carolina&lt;/a&gt; has three new measles cases, bringing its 2025 total to 159, all of them since July 9. Of the total, 156 infections have been part of an Upstate outbreak centered around Spartanburg County that has involved many cases related to school exposures. All of the new cases are part of the Upstate outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a December 23 &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9ganSJVF1No"&gt;news briefing&lt;/a&gt;, State Epidemiologist Linda Bell, MD, said about 95% of measles patients in the state have been unvaccinated. She also said some exposures have been in healthcare settings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, health officials in &lt;a href="https://www.fox5ny.com/news/nj-health-officials-warn-possible-measles-exposure-newark-airport"&gt;New Jersey&lt;/a&gt; (Newark Liberty International Airport), &lt;a href="https://www.wcvb.com/article/measles-boston-westborough-massachusetts-texas-visitor/69857705"&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt; (Logan), and &lt;a href="https://www.cpr.org/2025/12/23/dia-potential-measles-exposure/"&gt;Colorado&lt;/a&gt; (Denver International) are alerting the public about potential measles exposures at airports that are linked to infected travelers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:07:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxPU3ZMYms2NjRUUU1xV0NpTWxoQ1h0VzdTQkhNeGNrQnR3WkNTVFkyUUpCUklqM0dYT21pZUhkZTFZY3NmQUduTHg5aXJaLU1MOUtRUEZYTDRwZlZXWmVjenk5OUU3ZklKRzVuVUxmWHRFSEJJSDlLY0ZkUDd4V2ZiVmNVNEloS1ps</guid></item><item><title>为什么增加VO2最大值对改善寿命和日常生活有好处- GQ</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/why-increasing-your-vo2-max-is-great-for-improving-longevity-and-your-daily-life-1</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;And in the meantime, a better V02 max can just make life, well, &lt;em&gt;easier&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Imagine you're wildly unfit, you've never exercised, and you encounter a set of stairs,” says Danny King, director of performance and recovery at athletic club &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.lifetime.life/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.lifetime.life/"}' href="https://www.lifetime.life/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Life Time&lt;/a&gt;. “Going up that set of stairs is likely pushing you to 85 percent of your VO2 max. You'll be working relatively hard.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now imagine you have a higher V02 max. “Going up that set of stairs, you’re at 15–20 percent. It's easy for you,” King says. “[In the first scenario], everything you do in life is done at a higher percentage. But the higher you push your V02 max, the easier basically everything else you do in life is going to be. When you mow your lawn, when you play with your kids, when you go do all these things, if you have a larger tank and a larger capacity, everything is done at a lower percentage, thus making it that much easier for you.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Increasing your V02 max frees up the mental capacity to focus on what matters most to you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While typically pigeon-holed as a physical fitness metric, V02 max could also play an important and holistic role in overall mental health, says &lt;a data-offer-url="https://im8health.com/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://im8health.com/"}' href="https://im8health.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;IM8 ambassado&lt;/a&gt;r and performance coach to 2025 US Open winner Aryna Sabalenka Jason Stacy..&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Most people are sitting in a sympathetic state a lot of the time, in this low-level stress, and that wears you out,” Stacy says “It can impact your ability to perform at your job, and it can impact your relationships with your family, friends, and loved ones.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“[When you improve your V02 max], there's less stress on your overall system. And when there's less stress on your overall system, it's much easier for you to manage your emotions. It's much easier for you to step back and make better decisions and see things for how they are, rather than being caught up in all the day-to-day stresses.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GQ</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 20:04:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxOSU4zV1dRQTNwNzF5WWwtblA3LXp2QXFOTmJZR2lKOVFMLVl2Qlc3Y2ljaWprQnFhU1JteFpIUUVsRmFZdEg5UkJ1ZzczemdGbS1kaGU5OFROdERobHQ0VkdaMm1PYUF1U3piTEl4TEhJQ002aVhjU3V2LThXbC05YzlKQ2RhSl9lNHZyX1VIY2dPMXFIak9kcnV3R2dtdzNhalNfczAtdmRwajg</guid></item><item><title>接种流感疫苗是否为时已晚？ “超级流感”在整个北卡罗来纳州蔓延的信息- Charlotte Observer</title><link>https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article314034720.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="" class="paper story-body"&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="trinityAudioPlaceholder trinity-player-iframe-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article314036264.html"&gt;flu cases&lt;/a&gt; have continued to rise across North Carolina, health experts have been urging residents to get vaccinated. But is it too late to get the shot now?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;State data from the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://covid19.ncdhhs.gov/dashboard"&gt;&lt;u&gt;N.C. Department of Health and Human Services&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (NCDHHS) show influenza-like illness made up just 1% of emergency department visits the week of Nov. 8, climbing steadily to 5% by Dec. 13. Hospital admissions for flu-like symptoms rose sharply over the same period, from 81 to 480 — &lt;b&gt;a 493% increase&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response, hospitals in &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/local/article314032075.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Charlotte&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.newsobserver.com/news/local/article314034350.html"&gt;Triangle&lt;/a&gt; have implemented restrictions barring young children or those with respiratory virus symptoms from interacting with patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-101" class="zone zone-el" index="2" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;What is the ‘super flu’?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data from the &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-50.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_2-u-s-virologic-surveillance"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (CDC) show one variant makes up nearly 9 in 10 cases in the U.S., and it’s been dubbed the “&lt;b&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article314036264.html"&gt;super flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6149781/"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Some research and surveillance reports&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; suggest that H3N2 strains tend to be associated with &lt;b&gt;more severe illness and higher rates of hospitalization and death&lt;/b&gt; compared to others, including H1N1 and influenza B, especially among older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. David Weber, an infectious disease specialist at UNC Health, told The Charlotte Observer that cases counts are expected to rise even more due to frequent large gatherings during the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We almost always have bumps, not only at our hospital, but in North Carolina and countrywide after Christmas and New Year’s,” said Weber. “People get together for religious observances, and obviously, family and others get together.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the anticipated bump in cases, have those who want to protect themselves from the flu missed the window? Here’s what you need to know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;Is it too late to get a flu vaccine?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;No&lt;/b&gt;, Weber told the Observer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It takes &lt;b&gt;one to three weeks to build immunity&lt;/b&gt; after vaccination, and with North Carolina’s flu season not expected to peak until late January, Weber said there’s still time to get the shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;NC flu vaccine rates&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;NCDHHS data show just &lt;b&gt;20%&lt;/b&gt; of North Carolina residents have been vaccinated against the flu during the 2025-26 season. Vaccination rates in Mecklenburg and Wake County are at 20% and 25%, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those rates are lower than in previous years, Weber said, noting that most counties are usually around 30–50% vaccinated by this point in the flu season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-106" class="zone zone-el" index="14" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It depends obviously on age and risk factors,” Weber said, referring to vaccination rates. “It’s not surprising that older people who are at higher risk are more likely to be immunized.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He attributed some of the drop to Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who is “not a vaccine advocate,” he said. Kennedy’s tenure has included &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.bmj.com/content/388/bmj.r389"&gt;&lt;u&gt;halting a CDC flu-promotion ad campaign&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and pausing meetings of major vaccine advisory groups, moves public health experts say could undermine confidence and uptake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;“Growing hesitancy”&lt;/b&gt; hasn’t affected just the flu, Weber said, noting that vaccination rates for measles, rubella and pertussis (whooping cough) have also declined in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-107" class="zone zone-el" index="17" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;Where to get a flu vaccine in NC&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s where to get a flu vaccine in NC:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pharmacies&lt;/b&gt;: Walk in or schedule appointments at national pharmacies like &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.cvs.com/immunizations/get-vaccinated"&gt;&lt;u&gt;CVS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.walgreens.com/findcare/schedule-vaccine"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Walgreens&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. You can also inquire with local neighborhood pharmacies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Grocery and big box stores&lt;/b&gt;: Walk in or schedule appointments at stores like &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.walmart.com/cp/flu-shots-immunizations/1228302"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Walmart&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.target.com/c/clinic/-/N-54x94"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Target&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.harristeeter.com/stores/covid-vaccine"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Harris Teeter&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.publix.com/Pharmacy/Pharmacy-Services/Vaccines"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Publix.&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your healthcare provider&lt;/b&gt;: Of course, you can contact your doctor for an appointment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="h2"&gt;How to avoid the flu&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are several ways to protect yourself from catching the flu, &lt;a target="_blank" rel="Follow" href="https://www.charlotteobserver.com/news/state/north-carolina/article313517551.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Observer previously reported&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Wear masks:&lt;/b&gt; The illness spreads through airborne particles, so masking is especially important indoors and in crowded spaces as cases rise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Get vaccinated:&lt;/b&gt; Though official guidance from the CDC has shifted, health professionals recommend that most people 6 months and older get the latest flu shots.. Older adults can also get a high-dose flu shot.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Use early treatments:&lt;/b&gt; Oral antivirals for flu work best when started quickly — within 48 hours of symptoms for flu.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Stick to basic precautions:&lt;/b&gt; Cover coughs and sneezes, wash your hands, improve airflow by opening windows and stay home when you’re sick.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-108" class="zone zone-el" index="23" issportsarticle="false" stnplayerkill="true" allowstnplayer="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="embed-infographic"&gt;  &lt;gray-box&gt;  &lt;h3&gt;Ask the North Carolina Service Journalism Team &lt;/h3&gt;  &lt;p&gt;Questions about life in North Carolina? Or have a tip or story idea you’d like to share? The service journalism teams at The News &amp;amp; Observer and The Charlotte Observer want to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can submit your question by &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSccVKD-gL7FQf5pkdkbdjLw965_FcrhM0VNSNc3CpkcOakHFg/viewform?usp=dialog" target="_blank" rel="Follow"&gt;filling out this form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/gray-box&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="related-stories story-module"&gt;  &lt;h5&gt; Read Next &lt;/h5&gt;  &lt;div class="grid"&gt;    &lt;article class="package"&gt;                  &lt;p class="time"&gt;        December 29, 2025 12:37 PM      &lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/article&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="related-stories story-module"&gt;  &lt;h5&gt; Read Next &lt;/h5&gt;  &lt;div class="grid"&gt;    &lt;article class="package"&gt;                  &lt;p class="time"&gt;        December 26, 2025 1:41 PM      &lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/article&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="summary gray"&gt;This story was originally published &lt;span class="inline-block"&gt;December 29, 2025 at 2:19 PM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="zone grid"&gt;&lt;div class="related-stories story-module"&gt;
        &lt;h5&gt;Related Stories from  Charlotte Observer&lt;/h5&gt;
        
        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="story-module"&gt;&lt;div class="author-card "&gt;
        
        &lt;div class="article-details"&gt;
            
                
                &lt;a class="author-name" href="/profile/256802412/"&gt;Evan Moore&lt;/a&gt;
                
                &lt;p&gt; 
                
                
                    
                    
                    &lt;span class="credit"&gt;The Charlotte Observer&lt;/span&gt;
                    
                
            &lt;/p&gt; 
            
            
                
                
                     
                
            
            
            

            

        &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;p class="author-description"&gt;

            &lt;span&gt;Evan Moore is a service journalism reporter for the Charlotte Observer. He grew up in Denver, North Carolina, where he previously worked as a reporter for the Denver Citizen, and is a UNC Charlotte graduate.&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="zone-el-16" class="zone-el"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Charlotte Observer</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:19:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNcUtsaTcyV2ZQUkZYOFo5OHJub21fN0JZWlU5MEQzTjdCNnF5MjhkbnN1bW1VSldLOUZQMkt0SGNlVm92TnZaN2tCc3Z2Z1lfZ3NWeUNZcnBfWUFzT1FOWUVpMFl0dnNRbTd5Z3ZWWllSSmhPQzFDN0lDbDFWdnJrcW1ON1pwU0Rh</guid></item><item><title>研究人员为机器人制造“神经形态”人造皮肤- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/12/researchers-make-neuromorphic-artificial-skin-for-robots/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
                      
                      
          &lt;p&gt;The nervous system does an astonishing job of tracking sensory information, and does so using signals that would drive many computer scientists insane: a noisy stream of activity spikes that may be transmitted to hundreds of additional neurons, where they are integrated with similar spike trains coming from still other neurons.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, researchers have used spiking circuitry to build an artificial robotic skin, adopting some of the principles of how signals from our sensory neurons are transmitted and integrated. While the system relies on a few decidedly not-neural features, it has the advantage that &lt;a href="https://arstechnica.com/science/2021/09/understanding-neuromorphic-computing-and-why-intels-excited-about-it/"&gt;we have chips&lt;/a&gt; that can run neural networks using spiking signals, which would allow this system to integrate smoothly with some energy-efficient hardware to run &lt;a href="https://arstechnica.com/ai/2025/12/scientists-built-an-ai-co-pilot-for-prosthetic-bionic-hands/"&gt;AI-based control software&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Location via spikes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The nervous system in our skin is remarkably complex. It has specialized sensors for different sensations: heat, cold, pressure, pain, and more. In most areas of the body, these feed into the spinal column, where some preliminary processing takes place, allowing reflex reactions to be triggered without even involving the brain. But signals do make their way along specialized neurons into the brain, allowing further processing and (potentially) conscious awareness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers behind the recent work, based in China, decided to implement something similar for an artificial skin that could be used to cover a robotic hand. They limited sensing to pressure, but implemented other things the nervous system does, including figuring out the location of input and injuries, and using multiple layers of processing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of this started out by making a flexible polymer skin with embedded pressure sensors that were linked up to the rest of the system via conductive polymers. The next layer of the system converted the inputs from the pressure sensors to a series of activity spikes—short pulses of electrical current.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are four ways that these trains of spikes can convey information: the shape of an individual pulse, through their magnitude, through the length of the spike, and through the frequency of the spikes. Spike frequency is the most commonly used means of conveying information in biological systems, and the researchers use that to convey the pressure experienced by a sensor. The remaining forms of information are used to create something akin to a bar code that helps identify which sensor the reading came from.&lt;/p&gt;

          
                      &lt;p class="ars-interlude-container in-content-interlude mx-auto max-w-xl"&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 19:00:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMingFBVV95cUxPdVFXUXA5alB5dTdNY0M1Yy03NnNtdjdtMDF0cExSMGVKZGZWLXl6Vk9tUm9xdkVBU09fdnNMTzViTGhyTXJINmFCbVRETTZMdDhUeUMzMEw1ZWNxUjA2S0FrbWRTM3FhcEF1dXlsYVZ1MDVxNUFGeTU0TE5qaExGOE0zT0RlZmQ5WkVSdzVHSlNfN3JtZDlJS1RpSWhEUQ</guid></item><item><title>解开谜团：科学家发现结直肠癌为何违反免疫系统规则- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/mystery-solved-scientists-discover-why-colorectal-cancer-defies-immune-system-rules/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:34:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxQT1pUdzZ6SThpLUNTSFQxT19JYkQ3X3RJWVpzZ1BEOXM4M0RJcHlnS1dQQ3lHdGNfeUlFYk5kWmVJXy1YaHB3MThkV2h3ZGFKTEFuNk1nUHBTSFVEcHBKclVVNmpCTkNWLV9zLVJtbUZndnVmQWcxWmptcDhYZ3dSWkM1Smd4UXVwTDI1NWRXUzFlNzN3a21XWmxTd2gtWlRpelp2cWV0akFhZTNhc3c</guid></item><item><title>根据新定义，超过75%的美国成年人可能符合肥胖标准：研究- ABC新闻</title><link>https://abcnews.go.com/Health/75-us-adults-meet-criteria-obesity-new-definition/story?id=128747616</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="xvlfx ZRifP TKoO eaKKC EcdEg bOdfO qXhdi NFNeu UyHES " data-testid="prism-article-body"&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao MvWXB TjIXL aGjvy ebVHC "&gt;A new definition of obesity could nearly double the prevalence of U.S. adults with the condition, according to a study published Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For decades, doctors have relied on body mass index (BMI) -- a tool that uses height and weight to estimate body fat -- to determine obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;A team of researchers from Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center, Harvard University, Yale University and Yale New Haven Health, found that BMI alone may significantly underestimate how many U.S adults have obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Using a new definition that includes waist-based measurements, the team found that more than 75% of adults may meet criteria for obesity compared to 40% when using BMI alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="oLzSq QrHMO fnRUo pvsTF EhJPu vPlOC zNYgW OsTsW RMeqy daRVX ISNQ sKyCY eRftA acPPc MENS nFwaT MCnQE mEeeY SmBjI xegrY rPLsU iulOd NIuqO zzscu lzDCc aHUBM IEgzD OjMNy eQqcx SVqKB GQmdz jaoD VWDdR ONJdw vrZxD OnRTz gbbfF roDbV GPGwb oMlSS gfNzt oJhud eXZcf zhVlX "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="InlineImage GpQCA lZur asrEW " data-testid="prism-inline-image"&gt;&lt;figure class="kzIjN GNmeK pYrtp dSqFO " data-testid="prism-figure"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;div class="nMMea bNYiy Mjgpa dGwha DDmxa jgKNG RGHCC aBIU PriDW lZur " data-testid="prism-caption"&gt;&lt;p class="HXPPJ barbu yKsXL IzgMt VcHIt uhSzI YGNMU cRAsZ xqMcl QtRul "&gt;&lt;span class="hsDdd OOSI GpQCA lZur VlFaz " data-testid="prism-truncate"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ "&gt;Stock photo of a person measuring their waist.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="qinlA IpWvx oqZz tylGM lyWxS nWcVF UhTug PPcLh YxlyB "&gt;&lt;span class="gtOSm FbbUW tUtYa vOCwz EQwFq yCufu eEak Qmvg nyTIa SRXVc vzLa jgBfc WXDas CiUCW kqbG zrdEG txGfn ygKVe BbezD UOtxr CVfpq xijV soGRS XgdC sEIlf daWqJ YNujN JGtjI aZFDu rkKLh "&gt;Kinga Krzeminska/STOCK PHOTO/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Earlier this year, The Lancet Diabetes &amp;amp; Endocrinology Commission -- a partnership between the medical journal and the health clinic King's Health Partners Diabetes, Endocrinology and Obesity -- &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/landia/article/PIIS2213-8587(25)00004-X/fulltext" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;proposed a revised obesity definition&lt;/a&gt; that included waist circumference, waist-to-hip ratio and waist-to-height ratio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;More than 70 medical organizations around the world have &lt;a class="zZygg UbGlr iFzkS qdXbA WCDhQ DbOXS tqUtK GpWVU iJYzE " data-testid="prism-linkbase" href="https://www.kingshealthpartners.org/our-work/clinical-academic-integration/diabetes-endocrinology-and-obesity/lancet-diabetes-and-endocrinology-commission-clinical-obesity" target="_blank" dir="ltr"&gt;endorsed the definition&lt;/a&gt; but its use in practice has not been evaluated, according to the study authors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"BMI is the standard measure for determining criteria for obesity. It's the most widely known metric," Dr. Erica Spatz, a cardiologist at Yale School of Medicine and co-author of the new study, told ABC News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt; She noted that BMI alone does not account for adipose tissue, which stores energy, insulates organs and produces hormones that regulate appetite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Spatz said adipose tissue is less visible than other types of fat but "is more associated with high blood pressure, diabetes and heart disease."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;For the study, published in JAMA Network Open, the team used data from the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey, a national survey run by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention that measures the health and nutrition of adults and children in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The team looked at data from more than 14,000 participants representing 237.7 million adults between 2017 and 2023, applying the Lancet Commission's proposed obesity criteria along with BMI.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;They found an estimated 75.2% of U.S. adults met criteria for obesity using BMI and additional body measurements compared to 40% when BMI alone was reviewed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Dr. Fatima Cody Stanford, an associate professor of medicine and pediatrics at Massachusetts General Hospital and Harvard Medical School, who was not involved in the study, told ABC News that the findings provide a sense of how significant obesity is in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;"We do have a major problem. Obesity is by far the most significant chronic disease in human history," she said. "And this Lancet Commission really gives us a sense of how significant it is and how much we need to be doing a better job of treating it, make sure that we have the clinicians that are trained to identify not only obesity itself, but the over 230 chronic diseases associated with it and making sure that we have a healthier society."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;Nearly four in 10 adults with a "normal" BMI were found to have excess body fat when waist-based measures were also applied. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The study also found that obesity prevalence increased sharply with age and was higher among Hispanic adults though rates were similar between men and women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The authors noted that the study has limitations. And because nearly all adults age 50 and older were classified as having obesity under the new definition, age-specific thresholds are needed as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;The authors did highlight the limitations of BMI as a standalone screening tool and suggest that incorporating waist measurements could improve obesity detection. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;They also stressed that because the new criteria will likely raise the current obesity estimates, more research should be done before broadly adopting the new definition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC TjIXL aGjvy "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ABC News' Dr.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;Veronica Danquah &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;contributed to this report.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="EkqkG IGXmU nlgHS yuUao lqtkC eTIW sUzSN "&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;Crystal Richards, MD, MS is a p&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;ediatric resident doctor at New-York Presbyterian Hospital Columbia University Medical Center&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em class=" "&gt;and a member of the ABC News Medical Unit.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ABC News</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:29:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxNbnp5bGItSlZ6Tl9admdlMFljbmE1QUQ2UXdQUzltVXNsa3ZJVkxINGctcG1FSjExdnFDOER1YmxZV3lNbGRGenlIbHMtRUVUN2s5cUt1cHQ1UE95WUw5Y0d6c2dhRjZDdVppZHhjVllOSmVqNUVPWUJRMEhnMWVxUDV1a1kwUFpQYVdTUWlzZVNGdFI5LV9qQkVtNzBvemfSAaQBQVVfeXFMTVFzRWtXYVZVNW9yR1FOVFlkZEY0TVRvbGh3d1BtcEh6eElrUnN4NW1FeXM2OGYzdzJLNWxubDdCb01XM2Etdjh2eElDdF9HSGVjYWVyaTNhUUgxU2pQT0YwV0VJRktZTGN6cGpFZWN4SEh2amJwVUtSQTFXbmlGQkNyYzVMQ0tXR2hZYlJ3OXZtS3JhZGwyNVRxcjFZWjg4Q3IwbV8</guid></item><item><title>意见：治愈阿尔茨海默氏症的奇迹？不再是不可能。- MarketWatch</title><link>https://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-miracle-of-curing-alzheimers-no-longer-an-impossibility-e385925f</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MarketWatch</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 18:21:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxQTk82RlE4X2V6VWhGaWRTZkg5TXJLeW9WRmhXaXlraDRnRUpDeXV6WU1TbUI1T2pPdW5ta3NsOFY4Z1gxNHdWWkpXejZmMG1RLU1mbmxHNkF1Y2twaFpfMHIwWHExYUlUOTJVbUhxQW91Y1I1a1daVGRNT29qQXktdEpMQWtLMUJ6OWFGTDVEYVlITC12TmN0NnRONTE0b1EyVGFEQQ</guid></item><item><title>50岁以后在家工作时可以缩小胃部突出的5种坐式练习-吃这个不是那个</title><link>https://www.eatthis.com/seated-exercises-shrink-stomach-overhang-work-from-home-after-50/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content single-post-content"&gt;
																			&lt;p class="tagline"&gt;Sitting all day? Do these 5 quick seated moves to tighten your waist after 50.&lt;/p&gt;
												
																			
																		
						
						
						&lt;p&gt;Look, I get it. You’ve been working from home, and that midsection isn’t cooperating like it used to. Here’s what’s really happening: as we age, we start &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/8361073/" target="_blank" data-citation="true" data-citation-type="ScholarlyArticle"&gt;losing muscle mass&lt;/a&gt;. And muscle is metabolically active, so when it goes, the body loses its ability to fight off fat the way it used to. Then you throw in working from home, sitting for hours, moving way less than you did when you had an office commute, snacking more because the kitchen is right there. Add in hormonal shifts, and suddenly that stomach overhang becomes this stubborn thing that won’t budge. But here’s the thing: you can actually start turning this around without leaving your chair. I’ve spent years helping people over 50 strengthen their core through &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="http://studiopilates.com" target="_blank"&gt;Studio Pilates International&lt;/a&gt;, and I’m going to show you five seated exercises that fit right into your workday. By the end of this, you’ll know exactly how to put them to work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You’re probably already sitting. You don’t even need to go anywhere to begin exercising. &lt;a rel="noopener noreferrer external" href="https://mavmatrix.uta.edu/kinesiology_studentwork/80/" target="_blank" data-citation="true" data-citation-type="Article"&gt;Exercising in the seated position&lt;/a&gt; can actually decrease the chances of adding in cheating movements, increasing the effectiveness of the workout.&lt;/p&gt;

	
	
&lt;figure id="894568" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-894568" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Lift Foot - Position 2" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-894568" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Lift Foot - Position 2" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-2-.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Copyright Jade Winter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt; Activates the deep lower abdominals and acts as a great warm up for your other exercises&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed karma_unit--halfpage"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit tall near the edge of your chair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gently draw your belly in (like zipping up snug pants)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lift one knee, lower, then alternate sides&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your torso still as your legs move&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Common mistakes:&lt;/b&gt; Don’t lean back, lift your shoulders, or hold your breath&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Repetitions:&lt;/b&gt; 20&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="seated-lateral-raises" class="o-slide-title" data-num="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seated Lateral Raises&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;figure id="894570" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-894570" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Seated Lateral Raise - Position 1" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-894570" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Seated Lateral Raise - Position 1" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seated-Lateral-Raise-Position-1-.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Copyright Jade Winter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt; Training the arms increases the amount of muscle mass you can gain, increasing your metabolic rate and fat burning capabilities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit tall with the arms straight, hands down next to the hips and holding onto small weights&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raise the arms sideways to shoulder height, then slowly lower the arms back down&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Common mistakes:&lt;/b&gt; Don’t move your arms too quickly or shrug your shoulders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Repetitions:&lt;/b&gt; 20&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="seated-side-bends" class="o-slide-title" data-num="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seated Side Bends&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;figure id="894571" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-894571" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Seat Side Bend -Position 2" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-894571" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Seat Side Bend -Position 2" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Seat-Side-Bend-Position-2-.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Copyright Jade Winter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt; Strengthens the lateral core and helps reduce side overhang&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit tall with the arms straight, hands down next to the hips. One hand is holding a weight. The heavier, the better for this one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gently bend to the side away from the weight, then straighten back up to sitting tall&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Common mistakes:&lt;/b&gt; Make sure you bend from the side of your waist, and don’t shrug your shoulders&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Repetitions:&lt;/b&gt; 20 (10 each side)&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;h2 id="sit-to-stand" class="o-slide-title" data-num="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sit to Stand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;figure id="891805" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-891805" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="woman exercising with hand weights in conference call from cellphone stay at home concept" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-891805" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="woman exercising with hand weights in conference call from cellphone stay at home concept" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/shutterstock_1717054042.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt; Challenges the legs and will train the legs, adding more muscle to your frame&lt;span aria-hidden="true"&gt;6254a4d1642c605c54bf1cab17d50f1e&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit near the edge, feet firmly connected to the floor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lean ever so slightly forward and stand up completely. Try not to use your arms at all&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower yourself down back to your seat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Common mistakes:&lt;/b&gt; Don’t use momentum or your arms to help yourself up&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Repetitions:&lt;/b&gt; 20&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;h2 id="seated-overhead-press" class="o-slide-title" data-num="5"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Seated Overhead Press&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
	
&lt;figure id="725521" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-725521" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="mature woman doing dumbbell overhead press, concept of strength exercises to stay fit in your 50s" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-725521" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="mature woman doing dumbbell overhead press, concept of strength exercises to stay fit in your 50s" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2023/04/mature-woman-dumbbell-overhead-press.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why it works:&lt;/b&gt; Works the arms but also requires great stabilisation through the core and upper back&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;How to do it:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sit tall. Hold onto some small weights, with the hands in front of the shoulders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press the arms directly overhead. Lower slowly back to the start position&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep your belly gently drawn in&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Common mistakes:&lt;/b&gt; Don’t tense your neck or arch your lower back&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Repetitions:&lt;/b&gt; 20&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How to Fit These Into Your Workday&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="879896" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-879896" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Smiling muscular sportswoman sitting on the chair in her apartment and doing fitness exercises for biceps with dumbbells." srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-879896" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Smiling muscular sportswoman sitting on the chair in her apartment and doing fitness exercises for biceps with dumbbells." data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/09/shutterstock_1943306899.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aim for 4 to 5 sessions per week, even if each session is only 5 to 10 minutes. Because these are seated and low impact, it’s easy to add them between meetings, before answering emails, or anytime you feel yourself slouching. If you can squeeze in a session multiple times a day, this work will accumulate quickly and give the muscles a lot of stimulation throughout the week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treat them as quick resets rather than full workouts. That mindset helps people stay consistent, which is what actually drives results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What Results You Can Expect in 4 to 6 Weeks&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="894572" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-894572" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Jade Winter. Lift Foot - Position 1" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-894572" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Jade Winter. Lift Foot - Position 1" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/12/Lift-Foot-Position-1-.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Copyright Jade Winter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While these exercises won’t spot reduce fat, people usually notice:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A flatter-looking midsection from improved posture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Better activation of the deep core muscles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increased stability and ease with daily movements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reduced bloating&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Less lower back tension from stronger support through the trunk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most people feel stronger and more supported within two weeks, and see subtle changes by the four week mark.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Simple Eating Changes That Boost Your Results&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;figure id="885803" class="alignnone"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-885803" src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Smiling active senior couple holding water bottles, drinking and jogging together in the park" srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="lazyload alignnone size-medium wp-image-885803" src="" xmlns='"http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"' viewbox='"0' data-src="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all&amp;amp;w=640" alt="Smiling active senior couple holding water bottles, drinking and jogging together in the park" data-srcset="https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1200w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=640,468&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 640w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=768,563&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 768w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=1024,750&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 1024w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=272,199&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 272w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=473,346&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 473w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=684,500&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 684w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=343,250&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 343w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=244,178&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 244w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=183,133&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 183w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=400,293&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 400w, https://www.eatthis.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/4/2025/10/shutterstock_2179070935.jpg?resize=800,586&amp;amp;quality=82&amp;amp;strip=all 800w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Small, sustainable shifts make a big difference:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="karma_unit karma_unit--distinct inline karma_unit--mobile hide-desktop karma_unit--sliding htlad-lazy-mob-square-fixed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include lean protein at every meal to support muscle maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Increase fiber through vegetables, berries, beans, and whole grains to reduce bloating&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stay well hydrated to support digestion and reduce water retention&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limit sugary or processed snacks, especially during long work from home days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Balance carbs with protein or healthy fats to keep blood sugar steady&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paired with consistent core work, these changes help the waistline look and feel more toned!&lt;/p&gt;

																		
																	&lt;/div&gt;
										&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio"&gt;
	&lt;p class="c-article-short-bio__name"&gt;Jade Winter&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class="c-article-short-bio__bio"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
		Jade Winter is a Co-Founder and CEO of Studio Pilates International.					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a class="c-article-short-bio__more" href="https://www.eatthis.com/author/jade-winter/"&gt;Read more about Jade &lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Eat This Not That</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:30:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxOdnZyMlVFSV9JN05LVUJPY1FXcGVzamt6WTIydmZ2Y09RWXJzUE1fWDBzUkJIN0JsWTQyNjNZVEQzWGhKQ2piUDlQcVA2LU1KOHJRcUkyUUEwcjlUR1lMT2wxZDd1czBYS0tlTEtPYktyVEVlVk1HSjlIZ3J1Q2s1QzRGMnVSbWV6bGhjTUVpSGxiZE0</guid></item><item><title>为什么机械分离牛肉在美国被禁止-外卖</title><link>https://www.thetakeout.com/2061238/why-mechanically-separated-beef-banned/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="content" class="article"&gt;
            

            &lt;article class="news-post"&gt;
    
    
    
                &lt;p class="news-article"&gt;
                &lt;h1 class="title-gallery" data-post-id="2061238" id="title-gallery" data-has-pixel-tags="1" data-pixel-tag="thetakeout" data-author="Ben Hillin" data-category="food-history-tto" data-content_type="Short Article" data-mod_date="2025-12-29" data-layout="Infinite" data-post_id="2061238" data-pub_date="2025-12-29" data-day="Monday" data-dayhour="Monday-12PM" data-pubhour="12PM" data-num_slides="2" data-num_words="500" data-pitcher="Trevor Lowry" data-trello_board="News" data-intent="evergreen" data-ideation="oo-hits"&gt;Why Mechanically Separated Beef Was Banned In America&lt;/h1&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;

    
                &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                                
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap lead-image-holder" data-post-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2061238/why-mechanically-separated-beef-banned/" data-post-title="Why Mechanically Separated Beef Was Banned In America" data-slide-num="0" data-post-id="2061238"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p723b17d5653e54718499785ea40c534a"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/why-mechanically-separated-beef-was-banned-in-america/intro-1760008374.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/why-mechanically-separated-beef-was-banned-in-america/intro-1760008374.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/why-mechanically-separated-beef-was-banned-in-america/intro-1760008374.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2061238/why-mechanically-separated-beef-banned/" data-post-id="2061238" data-slide-num="0" data-slide-title="Why Mechanically Separated Beef Was Banned In America: " alt="Very healthy cows in a field in France."&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Labellepatine/Shutterstock&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                
                
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/1933658/meats-illegal-us-now/" target="_blank"&gt;Banning different kinds of meat is somewhat common in the U.S&lt;/a&gt;., and it usually stems from two things: cultural norms or human safety. Mechanically separated meat definitely falls into the latter category, since chicken nuggets and various pork products are made via mechanical separation — meat goo, anyone? So &lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/1933658/meats-illegal-us-now/" target="_blank"&gt;why is mechanically separated beef banned&lt;/a&gt;? It all has to do with Bovine Spongiform Encephalopathy (BSE for short) — more commonly known as Mad Cow Disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For those who don't know, BSE is caused by a prion, which is a misshapen protein in the brain that begins to clump together with other proteins, which in turn misshape those proteins. In cattle, the proteins can no longer function, and the animals die. This prion can actually pass from one organism to another, so it is possible for the misshapen prion to jump from cows to humans via meat consumption only (i&lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/animal-veterinary/animal-health-literacy/all-about-bse-mad-cow-disease" target="_blank"&gt;t is not contagious in the everyday sense&lt;/a&gt;), or by eating brain and spine tissue — if that's your thing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In humans, it's called variant Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease (vCJD). It rapidly becomes a neurodegenerative disorder, often mimicking extreme forms of dementia. There are other types of vCJD, but they are uncommon. Since the disease could be contracted through meat, it quickly escalated into an international scandal.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;div class="news-article"&gt;
                
                &lt;h2 class=""&gt;Preventing BSE is a great thing, but the panic was wildly overstated&lt;/h2&gt;
                                &lt;div class="slide-key image-holder gallery-image-holder credit-image-wrap " data-post-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2061238/why-mechanically-separated-beef-banned/" data-post-title="Why Mechanically Separated Beef Was Banned In America" data-slide-num="1" data-post-id="2061238"&gt;
                                             &lt;picture id="p16a4eb31223169603514cc794fe5d174"&gt;
                                                    &lt;source media="(min-width: 429px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/why-mechanically-separated-beef-was-banned-in-america/preventing-bse-is-a-great-thing-but-the-panic-was-wildly-overstated-1760008377.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                            &lt;source media="(max-width: 428px)" srcset="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/why-mechanically-separated-beef-was-banned-in-america/preventing-bse-is-a-great-thing-but-the-panic-was-wildly-overstated-1760008377.sm.webp" type="image/webp"&gt;
                        &lt;img class="gallery-image " src="https://www.thetakeout.com/img/gallery/why-mechanically-separated-beef-was-banned-in-america/preventing-bse-is-a-great-thing-but-the-panic-was-wildly-overstated-1760008377.jpg" data-slide-url="https://www.thetakeout.com/2061238/why-mechanically-separated-beef-banned/" data-post-id="2061238" data-slide-num="1" data-slide-title="Why Mechanically Separated Beef Was Banned In America: Preventing BSE is a great thing, but the panic was wildly overstated" alt="Protestors in front of the Ministry of Agriculture and Food in London"&gt;
                    &lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
                    &lt;span class="gallery-image-credit"&gt;Mathieu Polak/Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;
				            &lt;div class="columns-holder "&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;While BSE had been known since the late 1980s, it had mostly been centered on ranches and farms in the U.K. and seemed to be passed on when cows were fed discarded parts from other animals. By the early 2000s, Japan and the U.S. had cattle that tested positive for BSE. While infections still continue to this day, it is extremely rare for humans to get it. Only 143 people in Britain were diagnosed with vCJD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To the surprise of many, especially today, the U.S. implemented several changes to how meat and cattle are regulated. The idea of the U.S. proactively regulating something seems like a bygone era. For example, cows that move across state lines have to be traceable for BSE. The ban on mechanically separated meat took effect in 2004, along with a ban on the &lt;a href="https://www.thetakeout.com/people-eating-brains-as-food-history-where-to-find-1849638067/" target="_blank"&gt;consumption of cow brains&lt;/a&gt;, tonsils, eyes, and spinal cords. This is all, arguably, a good thing. So then why would I claim it was way overblown?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC, only four cases of vCJD have been reported in the United States. Evidence suggests all four individuals were exposed abroad, with two cases likely linked to the U.K.Public concern created the impression that eating any beef could lead to brain degeneration. In reality, only four cases were confirmed among more than 300 million people in the United States. The widespread fear likely stemmed from the unsettling fact that a single misfolded protein could cause such severe neurological damage.&lt;/p&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;

    
&lt;/article&gt;                        
            
                            
                           &lt;p id="div-ad-1x1a" class="google-ad-placeholder clear placeholder placeholder-1-1" data-ad-height="any" data-ad-width="any" data-ad-pos="1x1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Takeout</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFByd2pHMEFoX1FreHpkNTJ1YnN3OFp4YlhDY3NxcWxwd2kwNVFDUXBiN2xZSUI5bm1YWFQ1WU1LS180V3RIN2dPS0k1cmVTN3hxelI1Ukl6TWNGRXJpSmE1d0QtTE5kTkpzRG8tRGstS0xraW9ERUY5V21pd21KNjA</guid></item><item><title>尽管拥有庞大的朋友圈，但年轻人仍会经历高度孤独- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/young-adults-experience-high-loneliness-despite-having-large-friend-networks/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A study analyzing data from two polls of U.S. residents found that social ill-being is highest in younger adults and lowest in older adults. Conversely, social well-being was higher in younger and older adults, and lower in middle-aged adults. The research was published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0334787"&gt;&lt;em&gt;PLOS One&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social well-being refers to the quality of a person’s relationships, sense of belonging, social support, and ability to function effectively within a community. It includes feeling accepted, valued, and connected to others, as well as having opportunities for meaningful social participation. Social well-being is supported by trust, reciprocity, social cohesion, and access to supportive networks. It also involves perceived fairness, inclusion, and the belief that society provides opportunities to meet basic needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social ill-being, in contrast, refers to conditions and experiences that undermine healthy social functioning and connectedness. It includes social isolation, loneliness, discrimination, marginalization, and chronic conflict. Social ill-being often arises from structural factors such as poverty, inequality, exclusionary institutions, or breakdowns in community trust. At the individual level, it may manifest as alienation, lack of support, or persistent interpersonal stress. Social ill-being can negatively affect mental and physical health, reducing resilience and increasing vulnerability to stress and illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study author Jeffrey A. Hall and his colleagues wanted to explore how social well-being and ill-being vary with age. They also wanted to know what social circumstances, life changes, and attitudes about relationships are typical of individuals with different social well-being and ill-being levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They analyzed data from two groups of American adults recruited by the Siena College Research Institute (SCRI), a national leader in public opinion polling. These groups were surveyed in 2022 and 2023. The 2022 group included 2,034 participants, while the 2023 group included 2,243 individuals. In the latter part of each year, these samples were complemented by university students, including a random sample of those aged 18–21 and students over the age of 22. With the addition of the students, the total number of participants whose data were used in this analysis was 4,812.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compared to the general population of the U.S., young adults were overrepresented and older adults were underrepresented in this group. The average age of participants was roughly 44 years. Approximately 57% were women, and 88% identified as heterosexual. Regarding relationship status, 31% were single, while 44% were married or cohabitating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this study, social ill-being was assessed by aggregating measures of loneliness and social disconnection. Social well-being was assessed using measures of social connection, companionship, perceived social support, and the number of friends (derived from a naming task in which participants listed their friends). Participants who named at least one friend also answered a number of questions about their relationships with those friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results showed that participants who reported higher levels of social well-being also reported less perceived stress and tended to have a higher number of friends. Individuals who reported higher levels of social ill-being tended to report lower levels of well-being and a somewhat lower number of friends. They were also more likely to report having lost touch with a friend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older individuals tended to report lower levels of social ill-being (disconnection and loneliness). On the other hand, indicators of social well-being were highest for younger and older adults, while being lower for middle-aged adults. The number of friends was highest in emerging adulthood, declined during the late 20s, and reached its lowest point in middle age (45–60). It then gradually increased in older individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The present manuscript suggests that loneliness among young adults is not bereft of connection, companionship, and friendship, but instead is characteristic of rapid life changes and a lack of relational permanence and routine,” the study authors concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study contributes to the scientific understanding of factors associated with social well-being. However, it should be noted that this was a cross-sectional, not a longitudinal study. This means that different ages were represented by different people, not the same people observed through their lifetimes. Because of this, it remains unknown whether the observed associations with age represent age-related changes or differences between generations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0334787"&gt;Lonely and connected in emerging adulthood: The ambivalence of sociality in a time of transitions,&lt;/a&gt;” was authored by Jeffrey A. Hall, Natalie Pennington, and Amanda J. Holmstrom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:15:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPMVRhT3F0NzlfYTROa1lUYmVlc2VaVnczb3FyQWs5Uk9rQ3FEV1kycGxsWFoxa2lReDdLWTk1cU5IVXhFUzUtVDNKUWhKeG84Vlp0UW56M3k3eGVEOVpQcl8tdXcteS1SN3l4MDhOREVlVFdWRlAyN3pHRE5hNUVCelBXYm1EQTd0UTlKQnVEdlVTMGlPa1RxT3l0V3ZhXzNqX2Y4</guid></item><item><title>当您同时服用维生素D和Omega-3时会发生什么？ -健康：值得信赖且富有同理心的健康与保健信息</title><link>https://www.health.com/omega-3-and-vitamin-d-11865471</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin D helps keep the bones and muscles healthy.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Omega-3 fatty acids support a healthy heart and improve the function of the immune system.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Combining the supplements may help reduce inflammation and manage certain health conditions.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-help-reduce-pain"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Some studies suggest that vitamin D supplements may help reduce cancer pain and muscle pain, especially in people with low vitamin D levels.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Omega-3 has been found to stop pain from worsening.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Taking vitamin D and omega-3 together can help prevent and manage chronic pain due to their inflammation-lowering effects.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; A 2022 study found that taking both supplements together reduced pain more effectively than taking either one alone.​&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, not all studies support the use of omega-3 fatty acids and vitamin D for pain reduction. A 2020 study observed that U.S. adults with chronic knee pain who took both omega-3 and vitamin D for more than five years did not see any significant decrease in pain.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-slow-aging"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Studies show that taking about 1 gram of omega-3 per day may slow down biological aging by up to four months.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; However, researchers have found that taking omega-3 and vitamin D together has even &lt;a href="https://www.health.com/supplements-for-longevity-8715067" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;greater benefits for biological aging&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Biological aging reflects the state of your organs and tissues and can predict your risk of diseases like Alzheimer's and stroke.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A 2025 study found that daily vitamin D supplementation of about 2,000 international units (IU) per day can reduce biological aging, with or without omega-3 fatty acids.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you are considering taking supplements for this purpose, consider talking to your healthcare provider. Taking omega-3 or vitamin D might be more beneficial than taking both, especially if you have an underlying condition.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-help-with-mood-disorders"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin D helps reduce inflammation in the brain and may help enhance cognition and mood.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Omega-3 is also a brain food and can &lt;a href="https://www.health.com/supplements-for-brain-fog-8709220" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;help boost cognition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; In addition, omega-3's inflammation-reducing properties may stabilize the nervous system and improve mood.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Taking both vitamin D and omega-3 supplements together may &lt;a href="https://www.health.com/vitamin-d-and-depression-8748323" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;improve depression and anxiety&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Both supplements work together to ease depression by reducing inflammation and balancing brain chemicals.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, if you live with depression or anxiety, talk to your healthcare provider, as supplements do not help treat the underlying cause of depression.  
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-help-you-sleep-better"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Studies suggest that vitamin D can &lt;a href="https://www.health.com/supplements-for-sleep-8777079" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;significantly improve sleep quality&lt;/a&gt;, especially in older adults and pregnant people.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Omega-3 has also been found to improve sleep quality.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A 2021 study found that taking &lt;a href="https://www.health.com/magnesium-vs-omega-3s-11691684" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;magnesium and omega-3 together&lt;/a&gt; helped improve sleep quality in women.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="18"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; However, there is not enough evidence to recommend taking omega-3 and vitamin D together to improve sleep quality. If you are concerned about your sleep quality, talk to your healthcare provider about supplement recommendations and other possible solutions.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-help-improve-heart-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Vitamin D can reduce the risk of heart attack in patients with heart disease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Omega-3 helps &lt;a href="https://www.health.com/triglycerides-7253673" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;lower triglyceride levels &lt;/a&gt;and reduce platelets from sticking together, which can help keep you healthy and protect your heart against stroke.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; There are mixed results on the heart health benefits of taking both supplements together. Some studies suggest taking both vitamin D and omega-3 together may help reduce the risk of health disease-related deaths in patients with heart attack, stroke, or heart failure.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Other studies have not found a significant benefit of taking both supplements together in preventing heart disease.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="22"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="21"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-improve-bone-health"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Omega-3 fatty acids may help enhance bone formation and prevent bone from breaking down.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Vitamin D helps your body absorb calcium, which can help you maintain strong bones.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Both omega-3 and vitamin D may help &lt;a href="https://www.health.com/reduce-bone-break-risk-osteoporosis-8576233" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;reduce the risk of osteoporosis&lt;/a&gt; (weak and brittle bones).
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Taking vitamin D and omega-3 fatty acids together may help enhance bone health and reduce fractures.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="30"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-may-help-reduce-blood-sugar"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Some research has shown that taking omega-3 fatty acids and vitamin D together can &lt;a href="https://www.health.com/ways-to-lower-your-blood-sugar-naturally-7556676" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;help lower blood sugar levels&lt;/a&gt;. A 2021 study found that taking vitamin D and omega-3 fatty acids for about six weeks effectively reduced blood sugar in women with gestational diabetes (a type of diabetes in pregnancy).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; However, omega-3 is not recommended in pregnancy without first talking to your healthcare provider.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-who-should-avoid-taking-omega-3-and-vitamin-d-together"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Combining omega-3 fatty acids and vitamin D is likely safe when used at recommended doses. However, this supplement combination may not be best for everyone, especially people living with certain conditions or taking certain medicines.​
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Do not take omega-3 and vitamin D without talking to your healthcare provider if you:&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;Have severe fish or shellfish allergies, as many omega-3 supplements are made with fish oil&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Have kidney or liver disease&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take medications that increase your risk of bleeding (e.g., warfarin), as omega-3 can increase your bleeding risk&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take medications like statins (atorvastatin or simvastatin) and thiazide diuretics (Hygroton and Microzide)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Are pregnant or breastfeeding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Health: Trusted and Empathetic Health and Wellness Information</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:12:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiY0FVX3lxTE9Ma0FMUFpLdkI5YVZMSmtTQVRNMmdRZ21PVUlOQ1BDdktUM3FGWXpzclBXVmR4WGlQSzByZVpVcTJ1Uzg5cGwzT3A4bjd2Q1dKNmR0MHdIcGoxUEIzOU1DN01fcw</guid></item><item><title>基因编辑对“圣杯”的追求导致了工具的爆炸式增长，但治愈的方法很少- Endpoints News</title><link>https://endpoints.news/as-gene-editing-tools-multiply-the-hunt-for-the-final-technology-continues/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="epn_content"&gt;
                            
                            &lt;p&gt;John Finn still re­mem­bers the twinge of jeal­ousy when he heard some­one else had in­vent­ed a long-sought form of gene edit­ing, one that might fi­nal­ly …&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="epn_limit" data-gt="r"&gt;
    &lt;img loading="lazy" src="https://endpoints.news/wp-content/themes/endpoints-rakia/assets/svg/epn_logo.svg" alt="Endpoints News"&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Sign up to read this article for free.&lt;/h3&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Get free access to a limited number of articles, plus choose newsletters to get straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

                            
                        &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Endpoints News</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 17:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOVmd4OTdpSm0yaXFTZTRuaFR6N2ZOYVV2bXZqaEpDZ2NXSDFXajZHOF9BLUpSOUQzbUctZkdqb25XRURPb2R6bXZGelhyb3NjNVpKMFVGMF9JQjNrS3p1S1pmWVhlMnVrNnJVYVNHX050UE5aZ0pSalhWamNrSTdDV3kxQXJqcUFnd3g3b2hvLVBySXE1OWs0UFBhSy1SOFE</guid></item><item><title>在阿尔茨海默氏症模型中显示出恢复记忆功能的天然存在的分子- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-12-naturally-molecule-shown-memory-function.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="success-screen" id="successScreen"&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-icon"&gt;✓&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;h2 class="success-title"&gt;Verification Complete&lt;/h2&gt;
            &lt;p class="success-subtext"&gt;This page will redirect in a moment...&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:20:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQV2ZrTGZGQjRGaFNmcnJVdmVXSWpabnVLbTJGNFlTcko3YTFoNnVuZHJXdjVtbE0zR0gwcnBYV0hUUmo5N25nX2Q1TVp3T2hGM2I1T0hoelZwdHQzSkdRYUJMTWVwVHNNMVhTTE04c3YyTG5WcXJ0WWFKR1IxSk5VUmxzMFA2MFdFSVdITA</guid></item><item><title>一种致命的疯牛病在北美鹿群中蔓延- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/a-deadly-mad-cow-like-disease-is-spreading-among-north-american-deer-2000703926</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl prose-science dark:prose-science"&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;We’re not ending 2025 without a last bit of awful news: Wildlife officials are sounding the alarm about a dangerous brain illness spreading among deer in North America.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Over the last several weeks, officials in Arkansas, Wisconsin, and Manitoba, Canada, have reported cases of chronic wasting disease (CWD) in new areas. The mad cow-like illness can spread easily between deer and has a 100% fatality rate. In addition to its ecological impact, the infection may also pose a potential health threat to humans, particularly hunters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;The zombie protein&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Prions are perhaps the strangest pathogen around.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They’re the misfolded form of a normally harmless protein found in the brain (also confusingly called the prion protein). When a rogue prion encounters its regular counterpart, it somehow forces the latter to misfold as well, almost like a zombie infection. Over time, this amassing army of bad prions will destroy the animal’s brain, leading to death.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Prion diseases have been found in many animals, humans included. The most infamous one might be bovine spongiform encephalopathy, better known as &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/what-happened-to-mad-cow-disease-history-prions-1851242160"&gt;mad cow disease&lt;/a&gt;. Much like mad cow, deer and related cervids afflicted with CWD will experience neurological symptoms like confusion, trouble walking, and rapid weight loss (the titular wasting).&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chronic-wasting/animals/index.html"&gt;CWD&lt;/a&gt; was first discovered in the U.S. over 50 years ago, though it took longer for scientists to determine that prions are behind it. And it’s been spreading further across North America ever since. Cases have now been &lt;a href="https://www.usgs.gov/media/images/distribution-chronic-wasting-disease-north-america-0"&gt;documented&lt;/a&gt; in at least 36 U.S. states and four Canadian provinces.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;In mid-December, the Arkansas Game and Fish Commission &lt;a href="https://www.agfc.com/news/cwd-positive-deer-found-in-grant-sevier-counties/"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; three cases of CWD in hunter-harvested white-tailed deer. These cases were found in Grant and Sevier counties, where CWD had never previously been detected (the first ever case in Arkansas was reported in 2016). Last week, the Wisconsin Department of Natural Resources &lt;a href="https://dnr.wisconsin.gov/newsroom/release/116586"&gt;confirmed&lt;/a&gt; its first positive CWD test result of a deer in La Crosse County. That same week, the Manitoba Natural Resources and Indigenous Futures &lt;a href="https://news.gov.mb.ca/news/index.html?item=72097&amp;amp;posted=2025-12-22"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; five new cases of CWD, two of which were in previously undetected areas (the first CWD case in Manitoba was documented in 2021).&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Why CWD matters&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The increasing presence of CWD in North America is concerning for several reasons.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;CWD can be transmitted relatively easily, compared to other prion diseases like mad cow and Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease (CJD), the most common, but still rare, prion disease that affects humans. CWD can spread directly through contact with infected animals and bodily fluids like saliva, and might also spread through prions left behind in the environment by urine or feces. That means CWD has the potential to cause sustained outbreaks of illness in both free-ranging and captive deer populations.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;There’s also the scary, if still only theoretical, danger of transmission to humans. Mad cow has sparked outbreaks of CJD in humans, caused by people eating contaminated beef. The possibility exists that a similar event could happen with hunters who eat CWD-tainted meat. Last year, for instance, a team of researchers &lt;a class="c-link c-link--focus-visible" href="https://gizmodo.com/chronic-wasting-disease-deer-meat-prions-hunter-deaths-1851423216" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" data-stringify-link="https://gizmodo.com/chronic-wasting-disease-deer-meat-prions-hunter-deaths-1851423216" data-sk="tooltip_parent"&gt;argued&lt;/a&gt; in a case report that two hunters who died from CJD may have been infected after consuming CWD-infected deer.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;These cases have not been conclusively tied to CWD, and other scientists have been &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/prions-venison-deer-meat-brain-disease-mad-cow-guide-1851547274"&gt;skeptical&lt;/a&gt; about the connection. Experimental studies have also provided mixed evidence for any transmission risk to people, at least for now.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;Still, CWD remains a real and growing threat to deer, as well as the human industries that rely on them. So even if CWD never directly harms us, it could cause a serious ecological disaster—large outbreaks could devastate local deer populations, which in turn would affect other species in the area, or cause the closure of deer farms, a $7.9 billion industry. To that end, Wisconsin officials have extended an existing baiting and feeding ban in La Crosse County (baits can attract large populations of deer to an area). Hunters, meanwhile, are advised against eating deer that are untested, or confirmed to have CWD.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:15:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAFBVV95cUxON1VOY3hGT0FUSkZYN0Jtc1M4dUhfTThLbENFODEwMkZuYUwwUTc4WEV0Zm16UkhsVHphNVZiOF9LR0FsQVZXQjRkVS1jTmJQc29FNHk4OUdMVFhnekFQaUVrM0dKSVlVLTBHWlFaVUtKaEJVRU5fVTI1dy1oMXlxQWNDUE5YZFhzUXAxakxlWnE4LWxXelVVRGxha3hPbnM0</guid></item><item><title>纽约州一周内出现最多的流感病例--Syracuse.com</title><link>https://www.syracuse.com/state/2025/12/new-york-state-sees-highest-number-of-flu-cases-ever-in-a-single-week.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4TBYOWMRV5BCBHEJ4JUK7W5YXI"&gt;The flu is spreading in record numbers, according to the New York State Health Department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="7LDO4QDIPBC6PK6KVTOIHHQSPA"&gt;“We are seeing the highest number of flu cases ever recorded in a single week in New York State,” NYS Health Commissioner Dr. James McDonald announced Friday. “We are closely reviewing hospital bed capacity data to better understand hospitalization trends and to guide any necessary response related to impacts from respiratory viral infections.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PMTRB5GRI5D6VCPKIPMYJO2PIA"&gt;According to the state health department, a total of 71,123 positive cases were reported for the seven days ending Dec. 20. That’s the most ever recorded in a single week since influenza was made reportable in 2004, and a rise of 38% from the previous week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2ZICDVKVLJF3FIWMJTH3QGEKCA"&gt;Hospitalizations due to influenza also climbed by 63 percent, up from 2,251 in the previous week to 3,666 across the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="F7UJMGBP7FBQNFQPQVVEGBY6HE"&gt;There have been 189,312 positive flu cases reported in New York this season to date. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WRBGTU337VH67IQXW3IN5KSIRY"&gt;The high numbers are likely due to fewer people getting the seasonal flu shot this year. Just 23.9% of New York state residents have gotten the influenza vaccine as of Dec. 24, according to &lt;a href="https://coronavirus.health.ny.gov/covid-19-and-influenza-vaccination-data" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://coronavirus.health.ny.gov/covid-19-and-influenza-vaccination-data"&gt;state data&lt;/a&gt;; in Onondaga County, it’s slightly higher at 29.9%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D4XGWYMQINANBKLJAZSVXXX7J4"&gt;More than half of Americans typically get the seasonal flu vaccine, according to federal data. Dr. Kathryn Anderson, the Onondaga County health commissioner, recently &lt;a href="https://www.syracuse.com/health/2025/12/onondaga-countys-top-doctor-frets-as-fewer-get-a-flu-shot-amid-vaccine-skepticism.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.syracuse.com/health/2025/12/onondaga-countys-top-doctor-frets-as-fewer-get-a-flu-shot-amid-vaccine-skepticism.html"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; more than 40% of county residents typically get their shots by early December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EBTDY57NO5H6VE47HOPXI7S6WA"&gt;National and local vaccination rates have declined since the Covid pandemic amid skepticism over vaccines. Statewide, nearly 4 million fewer residents have gotten their flu shots at this point compared to recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="CMSCTIHO2ZHVLCA26HTCVNK57Y"&gt;And infections could continue to grow as families gathered for the holidays, especially during the cold weather months. Flu season typically peaks in January, according to the state health department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="TM2WKXC6CREBXIYHQGUBUVDOLU"&gt;McDonald encouraged New Yorkers to protect themselves and those around them by getting vaccinated, staying home when sick, and “practicing everyday preventive measures. Flu is treatable for high-risk people with antiviral medicine, if taken within 48 hours of symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BMUQVZXT3NF33LOK3MQNODK7KE"&gt;Other tips include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="NBMYMWOISVAJVKJZDK5ZSK434I"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wash hands often with soap and water for at least 20 seconds. If soap and water are not available, use an alcohol-based hand sanitizer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="NQWFDF4FVFGMBOKVGKUI72OGRU"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Avoid touching eyes, nose and mouth with unwashed hands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="GL2ITWCW75FWTKIMWIXL4M3F2U"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Avoid close contact with people who are sick.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="AR6QSDAEFJFNVCDH6SDSMKVMUA"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stay home when sick.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="EL445XPEFVCGPMUXH5GDIMOUKQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Cover cough or sneeze with a tissue, then throw the tissue in the trash.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="5X2ASBGMLNFXZODUYTAK2K34YI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clean and disinfect frequently touched objects and surfaces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="662KOY4HQZCB3J2XGCAUM25ZIA"&gt;“It is not too late to get vaccinated against influenza, and the flu vaccine is widely available to those 6 months and older,” the health department said Friday. “Young children, pregnant women, people with certain chronic medical conditions and those ages 65 and older are most at risk of developing serious complications from flu.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VWK7UHNASNDN5MJYX5F4PSOMLY"&gt;The seasonal influenza vaccine remains the best protection against serious illness and death from the flu, the department added. Flu shots are available to New Yorkers ages 2 and older at health care provider’s office or at participating pharmacies without a prescription; children 6 months and older can receive the flu vaccine at a health care provider’s office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OGWOJP67MJDARB2XXT66DXJKFA"&gt;For more information, visit &lt;a href="https://www.health.ny.gov/diseases/communicable/influenza/seasonal/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.health.ny.gov/diseases/communicable/influenza/seasonal/"&gt;health.ny.gov&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Syracuse.com</author><pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 16:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxOT081NVk1VHNoSGpDeUxwelBnLXk4eEpWMGdQWjNyS0EwdEtldG1xZnpiallERldNYW45cmk5ZklfSlQyZ0VxMnJza2RxUUFldDZKTnhSRC1rWG9vOWdIRk1ZTkNJLXVNUmJ1dEtpeV9JUWNiVHRadmF3VVRvWlYyd3NnM1F1ZW5tOWluZkFDTU0yemJHMElVMTdEbTdqWEZtamZYMkRBUTNkUGJEMXNNOXc2RdIBxwFBVV95cUxQZ0RSRF9yQWV5TXdEZkphaV9xMFdMeXBHSUhYUVFpMjZMTldSNWJUdmJ6R0U1ODV2RUNBTkFrR2xVLWZINW9uem5qN2F5N3c5dFQ5MFNUelhuOXhPMERVb3VKLWRkcmlLRnJ2RjZmR0NKa2pVTlZ4NXpRSDdBaTBiMGFsWF9BVEhOZGJ5ODBfbHVMcVRjYnZfNzl5T01pdmZBZkN6M0ZDalFkazlkXzZIellNeFNPdE1kS25JWnNJWW9yazNzSkY4</guid></item></channel></rss>