<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>FDA负责人表示，预计更年期症状激素治疗的“黑匣子”警告将很快发生变化- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/02/health/menopause-hrt-warning-change-makary</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9fjumi000x26nq4lln7bmm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The US Food and Drug Administration plans to make changes soon to the lengthy black box warning on many hormone replacement products for women with menopause symptoms, Commissioner Dr. Martin Makary said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00042e6euz6hjv88@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “We are in serious discussions now about what to do about the black box warning, and I think you’ll hear something on it very soon,” Makary told CNN Chief Medical Correspondent Dr. Sanjay Gupta in the “&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/audio/podcasts/chasing-life"&gt;Chasing Life&lt;/a&gt;” podcast.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00052e6eqyl89zt1@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The black box warning is the strongest type of alert the FDA puts on a drug label. Since 2003, labels of &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/consumers/womens-health-topics/menopause" target="_blank"&gt;menopause treatments&lt;/a&gt; that contain estrogen – including pills, patches, sprays and creams – have warned that their use can increase the risk of uterine and breast cancers, as well as strokes and blood clots. The labels also warn about an increased risk of dementia for women over the age of 65.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00062e6eydtauwl4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The warning was added after &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/195120" target="_blank"&gt;a large government-funded study&lt;/a&gt; found that women taking estrogen pills after menopause had higher risks for some kinds of cancers, heart disease and stroke compared with women who took a placebo. The study participants had an average age of 63, so many were past menopause when they started the therapy.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00072e6erd0ydgwd@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            After the study and the label change, prescriptions for hormone replacement therapy drugs for women dropped by more than 70%, and doctors became reluctant to prescribe them.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00082e6e5s5y60wx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s really a tragedy.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;It’s&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;maybe one of the greatest screw-ups of modern medicine,” Makary said. “It’s resulted in 50 million women being denied this incredible therapy.”
    &lt;/p&gt;



    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji00092e6ekav5ajnm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The result has been undertreatment of symptoms that can be debilitating for women in midlife. In the late 1990s, more than 1 in 4 postmenopausal women were taking hormones to manage symptoms such as hot flashes, mood swings and night sweats. By 2020, that number had dropped to about 1 in 25, &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama-health-forum/fullarticle/2823976?utm_campaign=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_medium=articlePDFlink&amp;amp;utm_source=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_content=jamahealthforum.2024.3128" target="_blank"&gt;one study found&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000a2e6eeahhqn3l@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Newer analyses of the original study, called the Women’s Health Initiative, have since found that hormone therapy started in women younger than 60, or within 10 years of starting menopause, may safely help manage menopausal symptoms such as hot flashes and poor sleep as long as the women don’t have specific contraindications such as a history of hormone-sensitive breast or uterine cancer.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000b2e6eq8utzfsa@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Makary also said hormone replacement therapy may also have important benefits like reducing bone loss, heart disease risk and memory loss,
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000c2e6efzlmyczo@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Women live longer and feel better on hormone replacement therapy when started before age 60,” Makary told Gupta.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000d2e6el3zwtay9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The potential change follows a July &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/patients/fda-expert-panels/fda-expert-panel-menopause-and-hormone-replacement-therapy-women-07172025" target="_blank"&gt;meeting of experts&lt;/a&gt;, convened by the FDA, to discuss the benefits and risks of hormone replacement therapy for women. The panelists urged the agency to remove the warning label.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000e2e6e1gf8kh7p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I am begging the FDA, and all of us are begging, please remove the box label,” said Dr. JoAnn Pinkerton, a professor of obstetrics and gynecology at the University of Virginia School of Medicine. “And please stop harming women.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000f2e6e2vb3kdk4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some women’s health experts&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;say the FDA overstepped when it applied the boxed warning to all forms of estrogen replacement.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000g2e6ebps4216p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “That is a real mistake,” said Dr. JoAnn Manson, a professor at Harvard Medical School and one of the principal investigators of the Women’s Health Initiative study.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000h2e6ezlo35gk6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Some forms don’t raise estrogen levels in the blood, so they&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;aren’t likely to raise a woman’s cancer risk.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;For example, studies have found that low doses of estrogen delivered by tablets, creams or rings in the vagina can safely treat symptoms of dryness, painful sex and urinary tract infections in postmenopausal women, Manson said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000i2e6eo8ak6a09@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The black box warning, though, may stop women from using them.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000j2e6ep9nps398@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It scares them away. And even after they purchase the product, they just don’t take it,” Manson said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000k2e6evbrrtjuy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “This is really where women are being tremendously undertreated and are suffering unnecessarily due to a boxed warning that is just class labeling. All hormone therapy products get exactly the same boxed warning, and it is really harming women,” said Manson, who is chief of the Division of Preventive Medicine at Brigham and Women’s Hospital.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000l2e6e9ijl6hnx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Manson said it would also be reasonable for the FDA to consider removing the warnings on estrogen-containing therapies that are delivered through the skin in patches, sprays or creams to relieve the symptoms of menopause like hot flashes and night sweats. Those deliver hormones into the bloodstream, but observational studies suggest that they have a more favorable balance of risks and benefits than pills, she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000m2e6ehkbfxnpm@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Manson feels less certain about removing the boxed warning from estrogen-containing pills that are taken by mouth, however.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000n2e6e5thizgat@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I think that’s where it’s evidence-based and justified,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000o2e6esv56zmbx@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2797867" target="_blank"&gt;2022 review&lt;/a&gt; by the US Preventive Services Task Force concluded that, in women who are past menopause, there was no net benefit to taking either estrogen alone – prescribed for women who’ve had their uterus removed – or a combination of estrogen and progestin – which is typically prescribed for women who still have their uterus – to prevent chronic health conditions such as heart disease and dementia.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000p2e6e7a4xb2au@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            What’s less clear is whether a woman who starts hormone therapies in perimenopause need to stay on them long-term to get memory, heart and bone benefits.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000q2e6e33aad8en@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “It’s a very good question,” said Dr. Roberta Diaz Brinton, a neuroscientist who studies estrogen’s effects on the brain at the University of Arizona. “We need to answer that.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000r2e6em089svhi@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Other experts say there’s not enough scientific evidence to support long-term use of hormones to prevent heart disease, Alzheimer’s disease or osteoporosis.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000s2e6ek7txx1zv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://www.ahajournals.org/doi/10.1161/CIRCULATIONAHA.122.061559" target="_blank"&gt;Four medical societies&lt;/a&gt; — the American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists, the Menopause Society, the Endocrine Society, and the American Association of Clinical Endocrinology — support the use hormones to alleviate menopausal symptoms, but they don’t recommend continued use for preventing chronic conditions like heart disease.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000t2e6ew8v7t6p6@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Dr. Leslie Cho, who runs Cleveland Clinic’s Women’s Cardiovascular Center, said she’s supportive of the idea of lifting the warning from vaginal estrogen cream. “It’s never made sense on the cream,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000u2e6e83yb1330@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But Cho said she’s worried that some of the benefits being discussed are drawn from after-the-fact analyses of studies that weren’t designed to look at those outcomes in the first place.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000v2e6e30si3go3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I’m so glad to hear the FDA chair talk about this, because then, if that’s the case, they should do a study. They should fund a study,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000w2e6e178cjacs@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In a world where people can get hormones prescribed over the internet, Cho said she worries too many women could start taking hormones when they have risks like high blood pressure, obesity or high cholesterol that could overshadow the benefits. Even in younger women, studies show hormones may increase the risk of dangerous blood clots, she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmg9flcji000x2e6e9nbxedog@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Women have to talk to their physicians about hormone replacement therapy before they believe in all the hype that’s currently ongoing, because so much of it is hype,” she said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 14:41:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5ETk01UnNVZXZiSk5NbDhaekZrWmFvZkZnY2ptRXV2dkpfOFNwWGg4TGZVb3gxTUp5cWRRS21qQ1hlY0ZuN3dSU1lTaUZWaDZMQVBXNDQ5MG9weDhQQ2lIQ1VYZS1ZSzNTRXBLUHJzbWsyQUpnY3VFMFJuVmNHZw</guid></item><item><title>用手机上厕所的时间可能会给您带来真正的痛苦- CNET</title><link>https://www.cnet.com/tech/mobile/toilet-time-with-your-phone-could-give-you-a-real-pain-in-the-butt/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="c-ShortcodeContent c-ShortcodeContent-theme:default sm:u-col-2 md:u-col-6 lg:u-col-12"&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p1"&gt;We use &lt;a href="https://www.cnet.com/tech/mobile/best-phone/" target="_self"&gt;our smartphones&lt;/a&gt; just about everywhere, even in the bathroom, though we may not want to talk about that part. A &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0329983" target="_self"&gt;recent study&lt;/a&gt; of colonoscopy patients revealed that most used their phones on the toilet at least once a week -- and that those phone-on-the-toilet users showed a 46% increased risk for hemorrhoids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="u-speakableText-p2"&gt;The cause and effect are clear. Caught up in news or games or social media, bathroom users stay seated on the throne longer, with research showing phone users tend to spend more than 5 minutes doing their business. The study says that hemorrhoids are associated with prolonged sitting on the toilet, as well as constipation and increased straining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Don't miss any of our unbiased tech content and lab-based reviews. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=cnet.com#link=%7B%22role%22:%22standard%22,%22href%22:%22https://www.google.com/preferences/source?q=cnet.com%22,%22target%22:%22%22,%22absolute%22:%22%22,%22linkText%22:%22Add%20CNET%22%7D" target="_self"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Add CNET&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; as a preferred Google source.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 125 colonoscopy patients at Boston's Beth Israel Deaconess Medical Center Study who participated in the study answered questions about their bathroom phone habits, and endoscopists evaluated their hemorrhoids (just in case you think you have a bad job). Of all the respondents, 66% used smartphones while sitting on the toilet, and those participants tended to be younger than those who didn't. More than one-third (37.3%) of smartphone users spent more than 5 minutes sitting on the toilet per visit, while only 7.1% of those without smartphones spent that long seated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the numbers were adjusted for age, sex, BMI, exercise activity and "straining and fiber intake," results showed a 46% increased risk for hemorrhoids. Men were more likely than women to spend 6 minutes or more on the toilet, in case you wondered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who used smartphones while on the toilet also admitted to getting less exercise than those who didn't, which the researchers said "could signify a higher level of engagement with technology and a more sedentary lifestyle outside of the toileting environment." (Yes, "toileting environment." Otherwise known as just "the toilet.")&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-ad-callout="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common toilet phone activity was reading news, with 54.3% admitting to doing so, and 44.4% saying they were participating in social media while on the toilet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study didn't directly connect constipation with time spent on the toilet, but Dr. Eamonn Quigley, chairman of gastroenterology at Houston Methodist, &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/09/30/well/phone-use-toilet-hemorrhoids-constipation.html" target="_self"&gt;told The New York Times&lt;/a&gt; that it's likely those who sit hunched over their phones while on the toilet might be more likely to experience constipation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you're grossed out by the idea of your phone being in close connection with toilet time, you're not alone. Doctors told the NYT the obvious: Fecal material can get on your hands while you're wiping and be transferred to your phone, and flushing with the toilet lid open can also spray fecal matter onto your phone. Sure, you wash your hands, but now the stuff is on your phone, so it jumps right back on your hands after you dry them and start scrolling again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, you're probably going to scroll your phone while occupied in the bathroom. But this study notes that you should be aware that the phone's fun distractions might make you sit there longer than you planned, and that could have painful consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNET</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 13:27:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxNaW1LV0g3M29NcVROdGxzdy04SzhiVDhQM2JhMlRYWEhGdzEyWmVBb2JFczFHWXBETzlpOEpaXzdiY1ZjNUNmSUx6RGE2dmNtQVNqa0ZSOVh0aDd4Y1lyWU9BRFZlYmd1LXBqQm1Bc1JmVmRycjVnZ1U1M3VLNkZ4N05RZml4OXR5cm9PMEhVR0ItYkl1bFlFNXMtdlh1OW5ybEE</guid></item><item><title>新的疫苗接种图揭示了疫情爆发的风险。您的县受到保护吗？ -今日美国</title><link>https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/investigations/2025/10/02/vaccination-rates-drop-maps-outbreak-risks/86224099007/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="gnt_ar_b"&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Vaccination coverage is eroding across the United States at the same time measles cases are surging, according to new county-level data compiled from state health agencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Measles outbreaks are infecting more people this year than in any year since the early 1990s and have already killed three. So far in 2025, all but eight states have reported measles cases, a disease the U.S. declared eliminated in 2000. Nearly 92% of these cases were among the unvaccinated or people with unknown vaccination status. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Federal data released in July showed that childhood vaccination rates, which had remained steady for years, have declined, while the share of children exempted for religious and philosophical reasons has increased. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“What we see is that as trust erodes, as vaccination rates drop, the first thing that you see are measles outbreaks,” said Adam Ratner, a member of the American Academy of Pediatrics’ Committee on Infectious Diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Ratner said the outbreaks should act as a public health warning system, signaling that other diseases could follow. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“You have to look beyond that, because the diseases that are also vaccine-preventable, but maybe are a little less contagious than measles, are the ones that you'll see after that,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;To assess coverage at the local level, Johns Hopkins University compiled &lt;a href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/CSSEGISandData/MMR_data/refs/heads/main/mmr_data_sources.csv" data-type="link" data-id="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/CSSEGISandData/MMR_data/refs/heads/main/mmr_data_sources.csv" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;data&lt;/a&gt; from state health agencies that, in the absence of a federal database, sheds light on how vulnerable communities are to outbreaks. USA TODAY later expanded this effort by adding data for states missing from the university's database and filling gaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;An analysis of this combined data, covering counties in 41 states, showed that routine vaccine coverage among children has slipped in most counties, leaving more communities vulnerable today than before the pandemic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In at least three out of four counties, vaccination coverage is below 95%, an immunity threshold experts say is needed to prevent widespread outbreaks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“The fact that there are so many counties below this threshold means there is a lot of exposure risk,” said Lauren Gardner, director of Johns Hopkins University's Center for Systems Science and Engineering. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“It doesn’t mean there’s definitely going to be an outbreak, but the risk is higher if a case is introduced in a community,” she added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Experts also warn that when coverage falls below 90%, the risk of outbreaks rises sharply. Children who are immunocompromised or too young to be vaccinated rely on community immunity, they say. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Today, about 63% of counties meet that minimum threshold, compared to 84% before the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The data, together with interviews with public health experts, underscore that skepticism around the COVID-19 vaccine has seeped into broader attitudes toward immunization, worsened by the spread of misinformation and disinformation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Vaccine skeptics falsely claim that the measles vaccine causes autism, a &lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/2025/the-evidence-on-vaccines-and-autism" data-type="link" data-id="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/2025/the-evidence-on-vaccines-and-autism" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;claim repeatedly disproven by extensive scientific research&lt;/a&gt;. Regardless, rising vaccine skepticism has discouraged parents from vaccinating their children against dangerous diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;A September &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/public-opinion/new-kff-washington-post-survey-explores-parents-trust-in-and-confusion-about-childhood-vaccines-as-the-trump-administration-revamps-federal-policies/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.kff.org/state-health-policy-data/a-look-at-recent-changes-to-state-vaccine-requirements-for-school-children/" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Kaiser Family Foundation–Washington Post survey&lt;/a&gt; found that 9% of parents believe the false claim linking the MMR vaccine to autism, and nearly half are unsure what to believe. About one in six parents reported delaying or skipping vaccines (excluding seasonal flu and COVID-19), often citing safety concerns or distrust. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Parents who identify as Republican, younger, or homeschool their children are among the most likely to delay or skip vaccines, the survey found. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/hcp/vaccine-considerations/index.html" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/hcp/vaccine-considerations/index.html" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;recommends two doses of the MMR vaccine&lt;/a&gt; for children: first at 12–15 months, then at 4–6 years. The agency also recommends vaccines for polio, chickenpox, and hepatitis B, a viral infection affecting the liver. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Public health experts say these recommendations are facing challenges under Health Secretary &lt;a target="_blank" href="/news/politics/robert-f-kennedy-jr/" data-autotag="1eef402e-8d6b-4ca9-ae4b-46a1674522c3" rel="noopener" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;/a&gt;, an outspoken vaccine critic. Kennedy fired all 17 members of the CDC’s Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices (ACIP) in June, replacing some with vaccine skeptics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The ACIP has &lt;a href="/story/news/health/2025/09/18/rfk-vaccine-panel-hepatitis-b-mmrv-babies/86199355007/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/health/2025/09/18/rfk-vaccine-panel-hepatitis-b-mmrv-babies/86199355007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;already changed the MMRV (measles, mumps, rubella, and varicella) vaccine schedule&lt;/a&gt;, removing the recommendation for children under 4. The committee also considered changes to hepatitis B recommendations, but a vote was delayed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Experts warn these shifts could add confusion and further erode vaccination rates, even as clarity on vaccine safety and access remains critical. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;To that end, Ratner said, granular data collected by Johns Hopkins University and USA TODAY is important for identifying vulnerable populations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“Often people will look at state rates, which are important,” Ratner said. “But really what we find is that what matters is much more local rates — at the level of the county or even smaller.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The Johns Hopkins University-USA TODAY data is based on county-level vaccination compliance among kindergarteners — and, in a few cases, K–6 or K–12 students — covering either MMR vaccinations or all doses required for school enrollment.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;There are caveats: record collection varies by state, so state-by-state comparisons should be made cautiously. Because some agencies track students’ compliance with vaccine requirements — not actual vaccination status — the true vaccination rate could be lower than reported in those instances. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;For example, Oregon excludes exempted students in completion rates, while Wisconsin doesn’t. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“A student can be compliant with the school law either by being up to date on vaccines or by submitting a waiver, so school compliance rates could be higher than the vaccination rate of the school population,” said Jennifer Miller, spokesperson for the Wisconsin Department of Health Services. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Measles once sickened millions of Americans and killed hundreds each year. In the 1960s, the U.S. launched its vaccination program, eventually eradicating measles before the turn of the century. By 1980, all 50 states had adopted school vaccine mandates, requiring children to be vaccinated before enrollment. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Measles is particularly dangerous because it can spread before symptoms appear. Even with a low fatality rate, the virus can cause lasting complications, including brain damage, neurological problems, and blindness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;As of September 30 this year, the U.S. has reported nearly 1,550 measles cases, surpassing totals from any outbreak since the early 1990s. Only 2019, when the disease spread through unvaccinated communities in New York, comes close. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The first outbreak in 2025 occurred in the Mennonite community in Gaines County, Texas, where vaccination rates are low. The virus then spread across West Texas, New Mexico, and Oklahoma. Gaines County has reported 414 cases this year, nearly a quarter of the national total. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;There, vaccination coverage among kindergartners has averaged around 82.4% in recent years, 12.6 points below what experts call community immunity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Before the COVID-19 pandemic, 57% of counties were considered fully protected against outbreaks. That figure has since dropped to 25%.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;The decline in coverage spanned nearly three-quarters of counties, with each experiencing an average four-point drop. Only two states, Connecticut and Maryland, now have every county above the immunity threshold, while nine in 10 counties in Maine and New York meet it. No counties clear the bar in Alaska, Hawaii, Idaho, Utah, or Wisconsin — the same states with high exemption rates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;In July, the CDC estimated that &lt;a href="/story/life/health-wellness/2025/08/25/kids-back-to-school-vaccine-rates-exemptions/85629130007/" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/health-wellness/2025/08/25/kids-back-to-school-vaccine-rates-exemptions/85629130007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;nearly 286,000 kindergarteners lacked proof of completing the MMR vaccine&lt;/a&gt; series during the 2024–25 school year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Meanwhile, more parents are exempting their children from vaccination on religious or philosophical grounds, though medical exemptions have remained flat. Non-medical exemption rates rose to 3.4% in 2024–25, up from 2% a decade ago. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Even small increases can have a big impact, said Elizabeth Williams, senior policy manager at Kaiser Family Foundation’s Program on Medicaid and the Uninsured. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“Every increase reduces the ability to reach the threshold that scientists believe protects the community,” Williams said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Experts recommend keeping exemption rates below 5%, yet 17 states now exceed that level. Idaho leads at 15%, followed by Utah and Oregon at 10% each, and Arizona and Alaska at 9%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“Rising exemption rates are concerning; especially if you work under the assumption that a child who has an exemption on file with their school is unvaccinated,” said AJ McWhorter, a spokesperson for Idaho Department of Health and Welfare.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;“During a vaccine-preventable disease outbreak, then there are more children who would be at risk for contracting the disease and who would presumably need to be excluded from school,” McWhorter said.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Policy shifts may further lower vaccination rates. Many states have introduced changes that make it easier for families to obtain waivers. Florida &lt;a href="/story/news/politics/2025/09/03/ron-desantis-florida-vaccine-requirements/85956743007/" data-t-l=":b|e|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;plans to remove the mandate entirely&lt;/a&gt; from public schools. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Since 2021, lawmakers nationwide have &lt;a href="https://www.ncsl.org/state-legislatures-news/details/vaccine-policy-remains-a-topic-of-interest-for-state-legislatures" data-type="link" data-id="https://www.ncsl.org/state-legislatures-news/details/vaccine-policy-remains-a-topic-of-interest-for-state-legislatures" data-t-l=":b|z|k|⚑u" class="gnt_ar_b_a"&gt;introduced over 2,500 vaccine-related bills&lt;/a&gt;, almost half targeting requirements like mandates or school exemptions, according to the National Conference of State Legislatures.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;These state-level changes, alongside the shift in federal guidance, continued misinformation and access challenges, will make the situation worse, epidemiologists at the Oregon Health Authority said in an email. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_b_p"&gt;Public health is a community responsibility, Gardner, the Johns Hopkins expert, said. “Everyone has to be in on it, because otherwise it doesn't really work.”   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s0"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s50"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s75"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="gnt_ar_s gnt_ar_s100"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>USA Today</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 12:10:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxQbS1JbmVXYi0yMXRjalRVNFY0NDRudmhQZ2FOckdWajY1SzR0VDB4bElwVnJ1R3BDamk3N3BCV0ZYckt4d0o3MG05UnVub2lCRVJ3S2xDWTktSE5mWjJuSlV5R3pkV0NuLXN5ckh3WnBlYVItX2tidDBRa254Q3ZERDR3VnVIRDVtTjVMMTBVQXJnd2Q1UEtXbjFUNHlfTFhwLXZsRnV4dWkwckYwdTU3MWtRYnhOMjJy</guid></item><item><title>蔗糖实际上比高果糖玉米糖浆更健康吗？ - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/is-cane-sugar-healthier-than-high-fructose-corn-syrup_l_68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coca-Cola has announced it’s releasing&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/22/food/coca-cola-cane-sugar-launch-earnings" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name=" a new Coke product" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/22/food/coca-cola-cane-sugar-launch-earnings" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt; a new Coke product&lt;/a&gt; this fall that’s sweetened with cane sugar rather than high-fructose corn syrup. The announcement followed a July Truth Social post in which &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://truthsocial.com/@realDonaldTrump/posts/114864763487869986" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="President Donald Trump " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://truthsocial.com/@realDonaldTrump/posts/114864763487869986" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;&lt;span&gt;President Donald Trump &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;claimed he convinced Coke to change its product.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be fair, we don’t know whether Trump thinks cane sugar just tastes better, or whether he wanted to improve Coke’s nutritional profile, or if the decision was driven by political reasons. But regardless,&lt;span&gt; this move has been hailed as a victory by Health and Human Services Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. and his Make America Healthy Again Commission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;But is cane sugar really any better than high-fructose corn syrup (HCFS), from a nutritional perspective? The evidence strongly points to no. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s why: While HFCS definitely doesn’t do any favors for human health, neither does cane sugar. Too much added sugar — regardless of which type or what food it’s in — can cause spikes in blood sugar levels and has been linked with many different chronic health conditions, from type 2 diabetes to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002916524000017" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="heart disease" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0002916524000017" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;&lt;span&gt;heart disease&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(16)30617-1/abstract" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="obesity" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(16)30617-1/abstract" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;&lt;span&gt;obesity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Soda, which is loaded with added sugars, is an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://ajph.aphapublications.org/doi/full/10.2105/AJPH.2012.300974" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="unhealthy" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://ajph.aphapublications.org/doi/full/10.2105/AJPH.2012.300974" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;unhealthy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; food choice whether it’s sweetened with high-fructose corn syrup or cane sugar. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Maria Korneeva via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Maria Korneeva via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Coca-Cola has announced it's releasing&lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/22/food/coca-cola-cane-sugar-launch-earnings" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name=" a new Coke product" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cnn.com/2025/07/22/food/coca-cola-cane-sugar-launch-earnings" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt; a new Coke product&lt;/a&gt; this fall that’s sweetened with cane sugar rather than high-fructose corn syrup.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Replacing cane sugar with high-fructose corn syrup does not have any meaningful effect on health — including blood pressure, glucose metabolism or any measure of cardiometabolic health,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://nutritionwithmaddie.com/about" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Maddie Pasquariello" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://nutritionwithmaddie.com/about" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Maddie Pasquariello&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a New York City-based registered dietitian (RD).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Here’s what you need to know about cane sugar and HFCS — and why one isn’t really any healthier than the other, with expertise shared by registered dietitians. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s the difference between high-fructose corn syrup and cane sugar?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;From a chemistry standpoint, high-fructose corn syrup and cane sugar are both sugars, and they’re pretty similar, including containing the same number of calories &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;— about 4 per gram.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Let’s start with cane sugar. As the name implies, cane sugar is made from the sugarcane plant, and is made up of sucrose, the most common type of sugar. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/compound/sucrose" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Sucrose" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/compound/sucrose" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Sucrose&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; is formed through the joining of two simple sugars — glucose and fructose (both monosaccharides) — which makes it a disaccharide.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“Replacing cane sugar with high-fructose corn syrup does not have any meaningful effect on health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__attribution caption-cli"&gt;- Maddie Pasquariello, RD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/food-additives-petitions/high-fructose-corn-syrup-questions-and-answers" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="High-fructose corn syrup" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.fda.gov/food/food-additives-petitions/high-fructose-corn-syrup-questions-and-answers" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;High-fructose corn syrup&lt;/a&gt; is a sweetener made from corn syrup. Nutritionally, HFCS is very similar to table sugar (sucrose), which is also made of glucose and fructose in roughly a 50/50 split. &lt;span&gt;However, unlike sucrose, which is a disaccharide (where the two sugars are bonded together), HFCS contains glucose and fructose as individual monosaccharides. In high-fructose corn syrup, “the two are not bonded together and the ratio might be slightly different than 50/50 in the overall product,” Pasquariello said.&lt;/span&gt; Because of its sweetness, stability and low cost, HFCS is commonly used in the food industry, especially in sodas, packaged snacks, condiments and desserts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Are there health benefits to consuming drinks made with cane sugar rather than high-fructose corn syrup?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Despite any claims you may have heard from cane sugar advocates&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; — such as those &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1946694089954771123" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="calling" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://x.com/SecKennedy/status/1946694089954771123" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;&lt;span&gt;calling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; high-fructose corn syrup &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/07/22/coke-cane-sugar-health-rfk-jr/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="poison" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/07/22/coke-cane-sugar-health-rfk-jr/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;&lt;span&gt;poison&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, or suggesting it is uniquely harmful to the liver and more strongly linked to chronic illnesses like obesity and type 2 diabetes —&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span&gt;there aren’t any benefits to consuming cane sugar rather than HFCS. Both sweeteners have similar effects on the body when consumed in similar amounts. “Your body cannot tell the difference once they are broken down and enter the bloodstream,” Pasquariello said. “Calorically, metabolically — it doesn’t matter.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/food/food-additives-petitions/high-fructose-corn-syrup-questions-and-answers" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="the FDA" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.fda.gov/food/food-additives-petitions/high-fructose-corn-syrup-questions-and-answers" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt; &lt;span&gt;the FDA&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, high-fructose corn syrup isn’t any less safe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; in terms of how it’s metabolized by the body &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;than cane sugar and other common sweeteners like honey. Some critics have&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cspi.org/article/high-fructose-corn-syrup" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="blamed HFCS for rising obesity rates" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cspi.org/article/high-fructose-corn-syrup" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt; &lt;span&gt;blamed HFCS for rising obesity rates&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, pointing to a trend of rising obesity rates at the same time as increasing consumption of HFCS. But nutrition experts say that claim is unfounded. In the book “&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.awin1.com/cread.php?awinmid=92005&amp;amp;awinaffid=837483&amp;amp;campaign=&amp;amp;clickref=68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc&amp;amp;ued=https%3A%2F%2Fbookshop.org%2Fp%2Fbooks%2Funsavory-truth-how-food-companies-skew-the-science-of-what-we-eat-marion-nestle%2F12787680&amp;amp;platform=pl" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Unsavory Truth:" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.awin1.com/cread.php?awinmid=92005&amp;amp;awinaffid=837483&amp;amp;campaign=&amp;amp;clickref=68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc&amp;amp;ued=https%3A%2F%2Fbookshop.org%2Fp%2Fbooks%2Funsavory-truth-how-food-companies-skew-the-science-of-what-we-eat-marion-nestle%2F12787680&amp;amp;platform=pl" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Unsavory Truth:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; How Food Companies Skew the Science of What We Eat,” nutritionist and public health expert Marion Nestle pointed out that while the increasing use of high-fructose corn syrup in the food supply occurred alongside increasing obesity rates, this is an association, but not necessarily a cause. “In reality, both sucrose and HFCS are sugars,” she wrote. “Both are best consumed in small amounts.” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Added sugars contain calories, but other than that they’re &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4975866/" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="devoid of vitamins and minerals" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4975866/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="14"&gt;&lt;span&gt;devoid of vitamins and minerals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that support healthy bodily functioning. Consuming a beverage sweetened with 25 grams of added sugar from cane sugar has the same impact on the body as a beverage sweetened with 25 grams of added sugar from HFCS. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2161831322011085" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Research shows" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S2161831322011085" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="15"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Research shows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that when comparing cane sugar (sucrose) and high-fructose corn syrup, there aren’t significant differences in terms of the body’s metabolic or endocrine responses and adverse health outcomes like obesity. Because of this, removing HFCS from food production wouldn’t have a meaningful impact on the metabolism, health or obesity rates of Americans, explained RD &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.missouristate.edu/StrategicCommunication/profile-display.aspx?p=JaimeGnau" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Jaime Gnau" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.missouristate.edu/StrategicCommunication/profile-display.aspx?p=JaimeGnau" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="16"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Jaime Gnau&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, clinical assistant professor in the School of Health Sciences at Missouri State University. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“What makes a difference for health is your overall added sugar consumption on a long-term basis — not the source of the sugar,” Pasquariello said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Simply put: swapping out high-fructose corn syrup for cane sugar likely isn’t going to benefit your health. But cutting back on sugar-sweetened beverages and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://policysearch.ama-assn.org/policyfinder/detail/H-150.919%20?uri=%2FAMADoc%2FHOD.xml-H-150.919.xml" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="limiting added sugars" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://policysearch.ama-assn.org/policyfinder/detail/H-150.919%20?uri=%2FAMADoc%2FHOD.xml-H-150.919.xml" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;&lt;span&gt;limiting added sugars&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; will — and this includes any form of sugar, from cane sugar or HFCS to agave, honey, maple syrup or coconut sugar. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Switching to a beverage with less added sugar would be of much more benefit than changing the type of sugar in the drink,” said &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/mediaroom/expertslisting/kris-dilley" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Kristine Dilley" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://wexnermedical.osu.edu/mediaroom/expertslisting/kris-dilley" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="18"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Kristine Dilley&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, a registered dietitian nutritionist (RDN) at The Ohio State University Wexner Medical Center.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why does overall sugar intake matter?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;According to the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2021-11/DGA_FactSheet_AddedSugars_2021-06_508c.pdf" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dietary Guidelines for Americans" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.dietaryguidelines.gov/sites/default/files/2021-11/DGA_FactSheet_AddedSugars_2021-06_508c.pdf" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="19"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Dietary Guidelines for Americans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, added sugars should be limited to less than 10% of someone’s daily caloric intake, which amounts to about 50 grams of sugar per day for someone who’s eating a 2,000 calorie diet. And that’s the upper limit — they actually recommend aiming for even less. Meanwhile, the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/added-sugars" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="American Heart Association " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/sugar/added-sugars" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="20"&gt;&lt;span&gt;American Heart Association &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;suggests even stricter limits for added sugars — 24 grams per day for women and 36 grams per day for men.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry-support-huffpost-mid-article" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title default-title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;20 Years Of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Free&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Journalism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost__message--main"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__sub-headline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For two decades, HuffPost has been fearless, unflinching, and relentless in pursuit of the truth. Support our mission to keep us around for the next 20 — we can't do this without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="24"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="24"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support?utm_campaign=mid-article-web" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="23"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already contributed? &lt;a class="js-entry-link-no-impression" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fis-cane-sugar-healthier-than-high-fructose-corn-syrup_l_68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;And added sugars add up quickly. Just a 12-ounce can of Coca Cola contains &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.coca-cola.com/us/en/brands/coca-cola/products/original" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="39 grams" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.coca-cola.com/us/en/brands/coca-cola/products/original" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="21"&gt;&lt;span&gt;39 grams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; of added sugars, and rarely is that the only sugar someone is consuming in a day. Added sugar is found in high amounts in all sorts of processed foods, from cereal to yogurt to condiments. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Overconsumption of added sugar has negative outcomes for body weight, blood pressure, insulin sensitivity, and other cardiometabolic risk factors,” Pasquariello said. “The use of cane sugar in a sugar-sweetened beverage instead of HFCS doesn’t make it any less likely to be over-consumed.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Of course sugar isn’t always a bad thing. “Sugar provides fast energy and is a great tool for endurance athletes to perform their best,” Gnau said. “The more active you are, the more energy you need.” Still, most Americans are consuming too much sugar &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span&gt;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span&gt; not moving enough. According to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/active-people-healthy-nation/php/why-be-active/index.html" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="the CDC" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68cc1c8fe4b0aa8d99fe99fc" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.cdc.gov/active-people-healthy-nation/php/why-be-active/index.html" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="22"&gt;&lt;span&gt;the CDC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, just 1 in 4 Americans meet physical activity guidelines. And if you’re not moving enough and providing your body with a way to use energy from high added sugar intake, health risks rise, Gnau added. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxObkxWQVR3Z1FBWXQzVFFlWTE5RkY5Y1JraVpCRzVLakxOMWlBZzhLNVZnbUladGxET1N3bV9ZY3diUTJUbHJIcHFMLU9VSnU3VklwdmVSS0Z1M3didWxuYmRFZ096TDBubnFiVzFHTEFWdzJ2U0hINUVNZFEwaTVvOFlDZENMS0VybEJiNTVZVGdmSHJWaUU2bHhxSDhHdERYQ1pLaWIwUlVweGpoaEg2RdIBtgFBVV95cUxPUmRCc0NpMlJwb2MxREZrcXp2SHRhWVo1WFJUQk5teThXeGtKRlIxaWZXWTdYR2ZEZWo1R3NDQ215U3NEc2NRLUtCYjhWWDkxdmotWGxVTTlrQlRkVFdwSHFpcE5mY20xQ1l0OVVvakVnQms0dWV2TmJWZzd6QmxqZ2x4dk5rOUhySVlNU0pmQXROcExlN1B2STJUcEtzN093UnQ5SE94OE1xakpVVjBkTWhoOElpUQ</guid></item><item><title>在感冒和流感季节您可以做的最糟糕的事情- HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/worst-things-cold-flu-season_l_68d95052e4b040e2851e5164</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s officially fall, which means crisp air, cozy sweaters, autumn leaves ― and a fresh wave of colds and flu.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s almost inevitable that we will come into contact with at least one of the common respiratory viruses each cold and flu season,” &lt;a href="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1831552298/andrew-b-fleming" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Andrew Fleming" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://nyulangone.org/doctors/1831552298/andrew-b-fleming" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;Dr. Andrew Fleming&lt;/a&gt;, section chief of infectious diseases and immunology at New York University Langone Brooklyn, told HuffPost. “A well-maintained immune system can halt these viruses before an infection sets in.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between the unpleasant symptoms and schedule disruption, getting sick is hardly anyone’s idea of a good time. That’s why it’s crucial to do what you can to prevent the spread of germs, strengthen your body’s defenses and otherwise decrease your risk of infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While most people who get a cold or the flu ultimately do just fine, these illnesses can be deadly to others,” said &lt;a href="https://www.nationaljewish.org/doctors-departments/carrie-a-horn" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Carrie Horn" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.nationaljewish.org/doctors-departments/carrie-a-horn" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;Dr. Carrie Horn&lt;/a&gt;, the chief medical officer at National Jewish Health. “And sometimes even otherwise young and healthy people can develop complications from a simple cold like pneumonia that could become serious.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;With that in mind, acting with awareness about illness isn’t just about protecting yourself, but also protecting your community. In fact, it’s a matter of etiquette. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These protocols are not just about health ― they are about civility,” said &lt;a href="https://fromtheinsideoutsoe.com/about-founder/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Jackie Vernon-Thompson" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://fromtheinsideoutsoe.com/about-founder/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;Jackie Vernon-Thompson&lt;/a&gt;, the founder of From the Inside-Out School of Etiquette. “We never know how severely another person may be affected by a virus. Some may recover quickly, while others may face serious complications. Practicing mindfulness during this season reflects true etiquette: showing genuine concern for the well-being of others. Extending such care is not only proper etiquette ― it is kindness in action.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below, find doctors’ and etiquette experts’ breakdown of the things you want to avoid doing during cold and flu season ― and what you should do instead. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neglecting Rest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A primary mistake is to neglect rest and ‘power through’ when you feel symptoms emerging,” said &lt;a href="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/nora-zabel-tossounian/1316569" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Nora Tossounian" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/nora-zabel-tossounian/1316569" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Dr. Nora Tossounian&lt;/a&gt;, an internal medicine specialist with Hackensack Meridian Health. “Your immune system requires significant energy to fight off an infection, and depriving your body of sleep and recovery time severely compromises its ability to do so.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Fleming pointed to the many studies showing that sleep deprivation impairs components of the immune system that fight viruses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One study showed that those who got less than seven hours of sleep a night had an almost three times higher risk of getting the common cold compared to those who had eight or more hours of sleep,” he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting enough sleep is not just about fighting off an active infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When you’re run down, you’re more susceptible to getting sick,” said &lt;a href="https://www.webmd.com/bio/neha-pathak-md" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Neha Pathak" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.webmd.com/bio/neha-pathak-md" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Dr. Neha Pathak&lt;/a&gt;, WebMD’s chief physician editor of health and lifestyle medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Going Places While You’re Sick&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“One of the worst things you can do during cold and flu season is not to stay at home when you are sick, or to attend gatherings where you know others are sick,” said family medicine physician &lt;a href="https://familydoctor.org/media_ambassadors/michael-richardson/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Michael Richardson" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://familydoctor.org/media_ambassadors/michael-richardson/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;Dr. Michael Richardson&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going out in public ― whether it’s to your job, the grocery store or a social gathering ― while you know you’re sick exposes your whole community to your illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you have a fever, cough, runny nose, sore throat, or body aches, please stay home unless it is absolutely necessary that you go out,” Horn echoed. “Viral illnesses are contagious, and the best thing to do is limit the chance of spreading it to others.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a parent and health professional, Richardson also emphasized the importance of keeping sick kids out of school whenever possible. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s very difficult to prevent transmission in the school system,” he said. “And even if it’s inconvenient, it’s extremely important to keep your child home from school if they have a fever. Children may return to school 24 hours after the fever has subsided.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Forgetting To Wash Your Hands&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Germs spread so easily from surfaces to hands and then to your face,” Pathak said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s why skipping hand-washing is a bad idea, especially during cold and flu season. Instead, this should be a frequent practice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Hand-washing is one of the best ways to avoid getting sick,” Horn said. “Always wash your hands before you eat or after you have been out and about touching things in public.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overlooking Nutrition And Hydration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Poor nutrition and dehydration work against you,” Tossounian said. “Your body needs the vitamins, minerals, and hydration from a healthy diet to mount an effective defense, not the inflammatory effects of processed foods and sugar.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s why you should prioritize healthy eating with plenty of immunity-boosting nutrients like vitamin C. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t let yourself get dehydrated,” Horn advised, adding that it’s especially important to drink water and eat nourishing foods when you’re feeling sick. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fleming similarly pointed to the role of heavy alcohol consumption, which can be dehydrating and otherwise impact your immunity. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Both binge drinking and regular heavy alcohol use suppress the immune system and make us more susceptible to respiratory &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;viruses,” he said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: juanma hache via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;juanma hache via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;There are many things you can do to prevent the spread of germs, strengthen your body’s defenses and otherwise decrease your risk of infection.&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Frequently Touching Your Face&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“On the germ-spreading front, one of the most detrimental habits is infrequent handwashing combined with unconsciously touching your face,” Tossounian said. “Viruses enter your body through the mucous membranes of your eyes, nose and mouth, and your hands are the primary vehicle for getting them there.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Touching your face is a common habit that can be hard to break, but try to at least reduce the frequency with which you do it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s good to minimize touching your face,” Horn said, adding that you might also consider washing your hands before or after you touch your nose or mouth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ignoring Basic Cough And Sneeze Etiquette&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The most basic actions can really be effective,” said &lt;a href="https://providers.emoryhealthcare.org/provider/sarah-catherine-dupont/2287396" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Dr. Sarah Dupont" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://providers.emoryhealthcare.org/provider/sarah-catherine-dupont/2287396" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;Dr. Sarah Dupont&lt;/a&gt;, a family medicine physician at Emory Healthcare and assistant professor at Emory University School of Medicine. “Cover your cough, discard used tissues. All the things your mom taught you as a kid.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember the “vampire sneeze” and “vampire cough” tip. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Being mindful of others can help reduce transmission of viruses in many ways,” Fleming said. ”Cover your cough or sneeze with your elbow, even if you are not sure you are sick. Wash your hands after covering a cough or blowing your nose. ”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;This applies to your time in and out of your own home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“At home, disinfect surfaces often to reduce the risk of spreading germs to loved ones,” Vernon-Thompson advised. “This is often overlooked. However, be mindful of those in your home.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skipping Your Vaccines&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t skip the flu shot,” Dupont said. “Vaccination is the absolute best way to prevent the flu or make the infection less severe.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;To decrease your risk of getting the flu and transmitting it to others, the &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/best-time-flu-shot-2025_l_68c96720e4b056d71f628e99" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="recommended time to get your shot" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="68c96720e4b056d71f628e99" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;recommended time to get your shot&lt;/a&gt; is September or October. The vaccine can also help reduce the length of your illness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Flu shots are safe, offer an added boost of protection against getting the flu and reduce symptom severity and duration if you do contract the flu,” Richardson said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also recommended that adults get the latest COVID vaccine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Thankfully, I’m not seeing as much life-threatening illness as in years past, but COVID can still be debilitating, especially for people with pre-existing conditions like asthma,” Richardson noted. “I’ve seen patients with asthma who have had worsening symptoms that last for months beyond the infection.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Neglecting Masks And Hygiene When You Go Out&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you do have to go out and about while ill, please wear a mask to decrease the risk of transmitting anything to others,” Horn said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with weakened immune systems may want to get into the habit of wearing a mask in public places during cold and flu season. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Not everyone has paid sick leave or the ability to stay home from their jobs,” Smith said. “For those who must work, there are things you can do to mitigate and minimize the spread of any creeping crud.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She recommended taking medications to reduce your symptoms, being diligent about mask-wearing and handwashing, and warning those who work near you that you’re feeling under the weather so that they can keep their distance. Also, avoid sharing food or utensils. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Don’t visit grandma if you’re sick,” Dupont said. “Or, if you can’t visit at any other time, at least wear a mask, avoid hugs and kisses, and try to hang out in a well-ventilated area, like outside. Older adults, especially those living in communities with a lot of other older adults, are at much higher risk of being hospitalized if they catch the flu.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vernon-Thompson similarly recommended reconsidering physical greetings if you’re feeling a little under the weather or visiting someone else who is. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Instead of shaking hands, a gracious alternative is to place your right hand over your heart, offer a slight nod, and warmly say, ‘It is so nice to see (or meet) you,’” she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Not Going To The Doctor When You Aren’t Getting Better&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If a fever is lasting more than three days, if you are having trouble breathing, or if you have chronic medical conditions that could be worsened from a viral illness, it helps to go see your doctor earlier rather than later,” Horn said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have been feeling unwell without improvement, consider reaching out to a health care professional. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry-support-huffpost-mid-article" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title default-title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;20 Years Of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Free&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Journalism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;Your Support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Fuels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Our Mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost__message--main"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__sub-headline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For two decades, HuffPost has been fearless, unflinching, and relentless in pursuit of the truth. Support our mission to keep us around for the next 20 — we can't do this without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support?utm_campaign=mid-article-web" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already contributed? &lt;a class="js-entry-link-no-impression" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fworst-things-cold-flu-season_l_68d95052e4b040e2851e5164%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68d95052e4b040e2851e5164" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There are medications to treat the flu and COVID, and they work best when given early in the course of the illness,” Horn said. “They are most effective for people who are immune suppressed or have chronic underlying medical conditions, but they can shorten the duration of illness for everyone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOMVNIYkZWWVRYTVdvMlZ0bV9Cbk1OeFpGelRIWkJjLV91MUZWTVlybW9QSGNwVDloeHRSY1pZUktRb3VRUVpINnFfRTY5M3pWaUdOUVMyUUdQSUc5RjVhbjBXZG9vNzBIcW0yZXhQMktHRVVrZU9ZUjI2MDVoX3JwTjV1QU1WWmpsaFNYdFl3d9IBlAFBVV95cUxOY3B1d05ubXljZUNwRGFsQlJ1NnowZEs1ME5qQUJwNmhxU0w1bDVLTEFtbVo0U190cEdXOUtCdS1EOFcwR3ktRllEU05LMUs4bWFra2NXSnotblQxTzJIeng5LVk4eUc3Ry0yX3lBYzFNZlZuZ285aUZfT0x2Y29NYmFQeUg0U25wSUFkRTFTTUVYMkVZ</guid></item><item><title>解决前列腺癌治疗的斗争- Bloomberg.com</title><link>https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2025-10-02/focal-therapy-for-prostate-cancer-care-is-an-emerging-new-treatment</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="box main"&gt;
                &lt;h2 class="main__heading"&gt;We've detected unusual activity from your computer network&lt;/h2&gt;
                &lt;p class="continue"&gt;To continue, please click the box below to let us know you're not a robot.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p id="px-captcha"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/section&gt;
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bloomberg.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 09:00:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiugFBVV95cUxOWE1fWThrUW5sb3FYdVMxNXBDVDU1VDZyMEVJbjktODVuVG5JVDdwT2MyYUp6ZC0zMEJ5eFVwSDlLcWNyQ1p5UFN1dXpvd2dGUU9BdHY4Q1dYVDVySG5tb0UxSmdNVEpNZkN5NXMybW4yWUdaNGQ4YWtpV0ZDeDFKaXZIbEJlbXIzN29sTm8tVDNjWVlzUWQ5aUg4ZFRIU01GcDNOeWotVkpqeHhJbUxiUGoyaWt1ZUM3Ymc</guid></item><item><title>这种欧盟禁止的化学物质与帕金森病有关- Euronews.com</title><link>https://www.euronews.com/health/2025/10/02/industrial-chemical-banned-in-the-eu-linked-to-parkinsons-disease</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p&gt;S:E]���pQ�a��������p��K`pL�?L�v\����_����J��p�%��&amp;amp;\=��Is=�r����:@ -6��&amp;gt;���T9�_��-�I�~��/��˧c��?.�d����d�D]S}JS�ߌ�$�
�(�Cs�c�{��uz�������7��Qn��g2��t��hz�5�5/���H ɠ " �w���
� ��]wrh{��c,@2�4���8��pcJ�}��{�_�x�Ьa���DvԊ�\�&amp;lt;��hw����7�~���l��N"��8�!�&amp;gt;���W��g�� Y �b�"��;3$E�D�+*C��)��!u�i$�\���?�x�3�C
ݺ[���+�~�������$i��c���s��LG� t����}MA=n��*�35J���CYdj����ρ��YK��/�����U�"�R�s�dL����V� �3=C���yk; ��a������j��S3�Xe:{���m�F�ǀB`.o���o���߄x p���a�W��d1��Qt�o�l����/�e&amp;lt;�N� ��:R�F�~��&amp;lt; �AbM�����w0��`��B��u�ה�UQ���K���/����H�����[����A*&amp;amp;d��ם��z&amp;gt;י�Yѷ֨�#�c ��5A����C�[z?!=9��:���F}W�x���ܹCe�O���!�Io�M�?�﹆�:g����/㹠�Zw^YR���B�����I�QmK~%�&amp;lt;	�`Eb��ԯ����ZI����i���I�LE�(�h����4�l�0����OQ��"(�ѵ2��h��R�B|{��@�kb3���v4a�g?���
��}�UC�30q��H��d��{�@ �Ew�&amp;lt;���w,!����wg�辣eF��!��̏�;E�#�#���)�"�
w����s�f�i��F�QC=�%w]�3����QW�C#�r��h�k���5 ���+��Q�?��2p�σ�=�ڕW�q��#*t��d@�{�D�tG�(���nq��H(#|M�:��7	oE[e�����z2o!�Y������Xiuxz�%�A�^�@ZT3 ���g]Q#{ԪR�F�c��x���'�PF!�a[w;R�K�c #&amp;gt;^��J����v�N��� G��W�r���q���%�\tl�������tat�"g��A��j&amp;lt;��-�&amp;amp;�����N���8]���x:�I�f��h����I1�M�D���b*q"8�B.�I:��"��X��x6����U��9ð�:��L��q����e�l&amp;gt;�4���y���*��P�$���������&amp;lt;��5��&amp;amp;z���������ٕ�;�� ,�&lt;l&gt;&lt;/l&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Euronews.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 06:00:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPRV83Y2Jzazh5VFY5Z3MybFJxM0M4R3ZEWjJlY05KQUIyM3BaZGFIdlVod21kRkhsVEQ1cGg3cDFhRzVXVGpobHVPZXBXVXctYlVqdzBIek9lalNtdzdfWm1tNkxWVUpvcjExSVRybS12N0tJR1oxTG9QM0pqQ3ZSRGJwR3pRazhzQ0hZM3ExY3F1Ym0wamVKTHhvZ1BjT0lKWWdhU3hNTnVZU1dB</guid></item><item><title>男子说，多年“不必要的” UHCW化疗夺走了他的青春-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cdjzpllmke3o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;'Years of unnecessary chemotherapy stole my youth'&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 kSquvq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/272a/live/8a2bf180-9cfd-11f0-9297-a5fd92668561.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC A close-up on a man's face and neck. He has brown hair and stares into the camera. The background is blurred but a red-brick house is visible behind him, as are several cars on a drive." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Jonathan Jones was given chemotherapy tablets for 16 years, but NHS guidelines say they should usually only be taken for six months&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A brain cancer patient who says he was prescribed chemotherapy tablets for 16 years, even though NHS guidelines say they should usually only be taken for six months, has said he feels his youth was stolen from him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Jonathan Jones was diagnosed with anaplastic astrocytoma in 2007 when he was 17 and took temozolomide tablets until November 2023, when he was 33.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Since he has raised his case with lawyers, more than 30 other brain cancer patients at University Hospitals Coventry and Warwickshire (UHCW) have raised similar concerns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The NHS trust said it was committed to providing the safest possible care and had commissioned an independent inquiry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Prof Ian Brown, the oncologist who oversaw Mr Jones's care, is being investigated by the General Medical Council (GMC). The BBC has attempted to contact the retired professor several times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Jones, now aged 36, said: "I lost my freedom, I couldn't do anything at the time. I had 16, 17 years taken away from me."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;The landscape gardener from Lichfield, Staffordshire, said he had had dental problems, joint pain and anxiety issues since being diagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;'If you don't carry on, you'll die'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Talking about the impact on his life, he said: "I was off [work] every single month for seven days and I couldn't get employed, so financially that was a problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The pain I suffered at home… I'd stay in bed, I'd have panic attacks. Sickness, tiredness. I didn't really go out much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"It caused a lot of stress for my family as well." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Mr Jones was told he would need to stay on his tablets to stay alive, and when he questioned the treatment, he said the reply was: "Do you want to die? If you don't carry on taking the chemo, you'll die."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Guidelines say temozolomide should usually be taken post radiotherapy &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://products.mhra.gov.uk/search/?search=Temozolomide&amp;amp;page=2" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;for six cycles&lt;/a&gt;. This is usually over six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;There are a wide range of side effects associated with temozolomide, including muscle weakness, memory issues and, in rare cases, secondary cancers and liver damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Another patient, Samantha Smith from Bromsgrove, Worcestershire, says she took temozolomide for six-and-a-half years while under the direction of Prof Brown at UHCW.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She said she had suffered from teeth and gum decay, mobility issues and chronic fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Ms Smith said: "You never expect anybody to turn around and say to you 'by the way, you've had too much'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I get a lot more lethargic now. I can't move as much as I used to… it's difficult now to walk downstairs on my own. I fall a lot."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Samantha Smith said she was more lethargic and fell over a lot, after six-and-a-half years of taking temozolomide&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Law firm Brabners says it has obtained data, using Freedom of Information requests that shows UHCW spent more than £3.6m on temozolomide between 2009 and 2024 – more than 10 times that of comparable NHS hospitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In a statement, UHCW said: "The Trust is committed to providing the safest possible care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We have comprehensively reviewed and spoken to all individuals who were receiving temozolomide (TMZ) treatment at the end of 2023 to ensure appropriate support and care plans are in place."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;It added: "A high-grade brain tumour is an extremely complex condition and all modes of treatment – surgery, chemotherapy and radiotherapy – carry the risk of complications and side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"National Institute for Health and Care Excellence guidelines recognise that clinicians can exercise professional judgement appropriate to individual circumstances when offering treatment to patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"We have commissioned the Royal College of Physicians to conduct an independent review of a representative cohort of patients who received greater than 12 cycles of adjuvant TMZ between 2017 and 2023.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"As this process is ongoing, it would be inappropriate to comment further at this stage."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A statement from the GMC said: "Dr Ian Brown is currently registered with a licence to practise but with interim conditions on his registration pending the conclusion of a GMC investigation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"The interim restrictions were first imposed on Dr Brown's practice on 23 August 2024."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 05:11:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9zdTFySXVlajdTYlBtbmNvUEpzZHJpX2pDWmhRbVlUSV9YQklwWmtYeXNUSExYaXVCUE53bDNNdHdYNU9MS056b1dzZ25IdjRrd1kxNUl0bWZTQdIBX0FVX3lxTE80cklybUh6Q1ZuTU1JTVQwYTFHYnJmT0ZPbGhwcWZocTAwNW0xaHgxZW1iYTdHNmVoUnBuWmROWnJWVjFxeEI1Y0laX2ZmWHhTWGV3OU5FVGUyMEZsSnVR</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，当您睡眠不佳时，您的大脑看起来会变老- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/your-brain-looks-older-when-youve-slept-poorly-study-finds</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;We spend nearly a third of our lives asleep, yet sleep is anything but wasted time. Far from being passive downtime, it is an active and essential process that helps restore the body and protect the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When sleep is disrupted, the brain feels the consequences – sometimes in subtle ways that accumulate over years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.ebiom.2025.105941"&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt;, my colleagues and I examined sleep behaviour and detailed brain  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/magnetic-resonance-imaging" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73063" data-postid="176129" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;MRI&lt;/a&gt; scan data in more than 27,000 UK adults between the ages of 40 and 70. We found that people with poor sleep had brains that appeared significantly older than expected based on their actual age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/one-stage-of-sleep-seems-critical-for-reducing-risk-of-dementia"&gt;One Stage of Sleep Seems Critical For Reducing Risk of Dementia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does it mean for the brain to "look older"? While we all grow chronologically older at the same pace, some people's biological clocks can tick faster or slower than others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New advances in brain imaging and  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73092" data-postid="176129" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/a&gt; allow researchers to estimate a person's brain age based on patterns in brain MRI scans, such as loss of brain tissue, thinning of the cortex, and damage to blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In our study, brain age was estimated using over 1,000 different imaging markers from MRI scans. We first trained a  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/artificial-intelligence" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73092" data-postid="176129" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;machine learning&lt;/a&gt; model on the scans of the healthiest participants – people with no major diseases, whose brains should closely match their chronological age. Once the model "learned" what normal ageing looks like, we applied it to the full study population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176138" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176138" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/sleep_study_mri_scans_642.jpg" alt="mri scans of a brain" class="wp-image-176138 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/sleep_study_mri_scans_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/sleep_study_mri_scans_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176138" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Brain aging was estimated from over 1,000 different imaging markers. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MADnBGtNmtE/"&gt;LarisaBozhikova/Getty Images/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having a brain age higher than your actual age can be a signal of departure from healthy ageing. &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41380-018-0098-1"&gt;Previous research&lt;/a&gt; has linked an older-appearing brain to faster cognitive decline, greater dementia risk, and even higher risk of early death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleep is complex, and no single measure can tell the whole story of a person's sleep health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our study, therefore, focused on five aspects of sleep self-reported by the study participants: their chronotype ("morning" or "evening" person), how many hours they typically sleep (seven to eight hours is considered optimal), whether they experience insomnia, whether they snore, and whether they feel excessively sleepy during the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These characteristics can interact in synergistic ways. For example, someone with frequent insomnia may also feel more daytime sleepiness, and having a late chronotype may lead to shorter sleep duration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By integrating all five characteristics into a "healthy sleep score", we captured a fuller picture of overall sleep health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with four or five healthy traits had a "healthy" sleep profile, while those with two to three had an "intermediate" profile, and those with zero or one had a "poor" profile.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we compared brain age across different sleep profiles, the differences were clear. The gap between brain age and chronological age widened by about six months for every one point decrease in healthy sleep score.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On average, people with a poor sleep profile had brains that appeared nearly one year older than expected based on their chronological age, while those with a healthy sleep profile showed no such gap.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also considered the five sleep characteristics individually: late chronotype and abnormal sleep duration stood out as the biggest contributors to faster brain ageing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_176139" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-176139" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/working_late_night_642.jpg" alt="woman working late" class="wp-image-176139 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/working_late_night_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/working_late_night_642-600x374.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-176139" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Late chronotypes, or late owls, are at risk of faster ageing brains. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEJTZj5ENo/"&gt;M_a_y_a/Getty Images Signature/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A year may not sound like much, but in terms of brain health, it matters. Even small accelerations in brain ageing can compound over time, potentially increasing the risk of cognitive impairment, dementia, and other neurological conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that sleep habits are modifiable. While not all sleep problems are easily fixed, &lt;a href="https://newsinhealth.nih.gov/2021/04/good-sleep-good-health"&gt;simple strategies&lt;/a&gt;: keeping a regular sleep schedule; limiting  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/how-does-caffeine-wake-you-up" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73115" data-postid="176129" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;caffeine&lt;/a&gt;, alcohol, and screen use before bedtime; and creating a dark and quiet sleep environment can improve sleep health and may protect brain health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How exactly does the quality of a person's sleep affect their brain health?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/laneur/article/PIIS1474-4422(18)30450-2/abstract"&gt;One explanation&lt;/a&gt; may be inflammation. Increasing evidence suggests that sleep disturbances raise the level of inflammation in the body. In turn, inflammation can harm the brain in several ways: damaging blood vessels, triggering the buildup of toxic proteins, and speeding up brain cell death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/better-sleep-could-help-your-brain-flush-out-dementia-linked-toxins"&gt;Better Sleep Could Help Your Brain Flush Out Dementia-Linked Toxins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We were able to investigate the role of inflammation thanks to blood samples collected from participants at the beginning of the study. These samples contain a wealth of information about different inflammatory biomarkers circulating in the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we factored this into our analysis, we found that inflammation levels accounted for about 10% of the connection between sleep and brain ageing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Other processes may also play a role&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another explanation centres on the &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/sleep-ultimate-brainwasher"&gt;glymphatic system&lt;/a&gt; – the brain's built-in waste clearance network, which is mainly active during sleep. When sleep is disrupted or insufficient, this system may not function properly, allowing harmful substances to build up in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet another possibility is that poor sleep increases the risk of other health conditions that are themselves damaging for brain health, including &lt;a href="https://alz-journals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/alz.12482"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamapsychiatry/fullarticle/2797529"&gt;obesity&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurheartj/article/44/7/573/6964658"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our study is one of the largest and most comprehensive of its kind, benefiting from a very large study population, a multidimensional measure of sleep health, and a detailed estimation of brain age through thousands of brain MRI features.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/sleep/article-abstract/40/1/zsw032/2661823?redirectedFrom=fulltext"&gt;previous research&lt;/a&gt; connected poor sleep to cognitive decline and dementia, our study further demonstrated that poor sleep is tied to a measurably older-looking brain, and inflammation might explain this link.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brain ageing cannot be avoided, but our behaviour and lifestyle choices can shape how it unfolds. The implications of our research are clear: to keep the brain healthier for longer, it is important to make sleep a priority.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/265309/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/abigail-dove-2481902"&gt;Abigail Dove&lt;/a&gt;, Postdoctoral Researcher, Neuroepidemiology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/karolinska-institutet-1250"&gt;Karolinska Institutet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/poor-sleep-may-make-your-brain-age-faster-new-study-265309"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 01:28:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNcUw0VlJobGFUeWJ3R2tySXZ4ZGtIeHFWZElQR2N5VXFwMExydmdKRGlHOGpPR0tpM2NzSTV2a0Q2bjZ1S3Z6WU15UjdlMnRkbGtEc1Y3MkRRZFRDdEFidkk1YVJhMnRmRFFTUjlBM0t1bjRUODdvWVBOZXNYZGFYLTU0MzdsWWhRV2VlM3BvQ3U</guid></item><item><title>25%的男性前列腺增大50 ：现在可以做些什么来预防它-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/25-of-men-will-have-an-enlarged-prostate-by-50-what-can-be-done-now-to-prevent-it/photostory/124256849.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A healthy lifestyle, and hearty diet goes a long way in preventing &lt;a href="https://www.urologyhealth.org/urology-a-z/b/benign-prostatic-hyperplasia-(bph)%5B10"&gt;prostate&lt;/a&gt;. However, this must be adapted at a young age, since the condition cannot be reversed per se. Physical exercise helps maintain blood circulation and hormone equilibrium, which helps control prostate enlargement. A balanced weight achieved through proper eating habits decreases insulin resistance and inflammation, which are linked to BPH development. The reduction of caffeine and alcohol consumption together with spicy food intake, helps reduce urinary symptoms. Drinking enough water throughout the day helps control nighttime urination, but avoid drinking too much before bedtime. The management of stress together with sufficient sleep duration plays essential roles in maintaining prostate health. Basic changes in daily habits, create an effective method to protect prostate health naturally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi_AFBVV95cUxOUGFTVmxXYWRzNkRWNTRGZnQ5WHl4QTlJR3pGWGxrMGZlaVE5ZWd6R1ZSMnJqNE5TSVRLZzJBbW5Lb0lSY1h0Wm5QNGswbnBvczBMMFk5TERyOFR1V0FQZE5rdmFrMVhRTDZNdktoSVFvRWVGdEF2UWZXdnY5QUtEV2FTLXZuYk14RHZFYnhGZ2owNndmVk8zT0FueE1SMWVkZkh0b0ZEaGQycHYzeGtVMVdjUFhrQlhGNTRaS21EWXNvNmtnZXBsbnc3U2hwR3c0YlNnZnN5QnZOcDZWdUVIajFXSmJKaklSYzZMcVhwQTZPRm8zbDdfTHpxSXTSAYQCQVVfeXFMTWZHZ29OVWZuUFZYSG15QXJySm81ZUkySjlOakxpWU5tdFJJRjBNZlkta0o0cU16Mk9WUGcwWDN1R29ySXB1bjFnNllXaGdyeGRXYnI5MmNqanpsenlBRzN5dWVFSUVlMGlBYkkzU0JaZHpUWmlyQWVNeGJYQUVDSUFPNlBEampaSk96b09TS0RqMGhnZDJaU2ktbEU4Umc4dnlzWXV0aVNvQnFZcHowTWc3elFmNGM5NmhCdGM0ODJjMWpNRHIyVWZRbWhTV2xCQTBHUm40T2loTVpObXZ0dThRTWpLelp1cWpYS2diTEFUeXVWUW9CMlJqRVdEdk02VmxZU1g</guid></item><item><title>食用油：我应该用橄榄油煎炸吗？如何选择合适的瓶子- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cj3y7j2dz44o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Should I use olive oil for frying? How to choose the right cooking oil&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Assorted healthy vegetable oil bottle collection on wooden table in a old fashioned kitchen with low key illumination: Olive oil, hazelnut oil, almond oil, coconut oil and sesame oil" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Supermarket shelves are packed with oils from budget bottles of sunflower and vegetable oil to pricier olive, avocado and coconut oils claiming health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Oils and fats have been at the centre of nutritional debate for years and to understand why it matters, it helps to look at the different types of fat they contain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Not all fats behave the same way in the body - some raise cholesterol while others help lower it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Cholesterol is a natural fatty substance produced in the liver and can also be found in some of the foods we eat. Too much bad cholesterol can lead to a build-up of fatty deposits inside the walls of blood vessels, causing them to become narrowed or blocked. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;With so many shifting messages, knowing which product to pick can often feel overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Nita Forouhi, Professor of Population Health and Nutrition at the University of Cambridge, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/articles/5d6Xw8BbzfGb2s3SMJDdFMd/which-oils-should-we-be-using-for-cooking" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;tells the BBC's Sliced Bread podcast&lt;/a&gt; that no single oil holds the magic key to health and debunks three common myths about cooking oils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;1. Use sunflower and vegetable oil for cooking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Close-up of a shopper holding a bottle of cooking oil in a supermarket aisle, focusing on food choices, daily shopping, and consumer lifestyle." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Vegetable and sunflower oil is also a good budget option, costing around £2 a litre &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Rapeseed oil (commonly sold as vegetable oil) and sunflower oils often get bad press with some claiming they are ultra-processed and can cause inflammation which can be damaging to cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But, there isn't evidence to back this up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In fact, these oils contain a low amount - 5-10% -  of unhealthy saturated fats and are high in healthier mono- and polyunsaturated fats. Polyunsaturated fats (including omega-3 and omega-6) are essential for brain and heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Forouhi says that these oils are "absolutely good for us".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She explains that they can offer a reduction in disease risk "when saturated fats [which can raise bad cholesterol] like butter, lard or ghee are replaced with these oils".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At around £2 per litre in most supermarkets it's also a more budget friendly option  for cooking at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;2. Margarine can help reduce bad cholesterol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Stock photo shows a close up image of a knife running through margarine with a spot of sunlight pouring in." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Modern day margarines have close to zero amounts of trans fats in&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Margarine has had a bad reputation for years and many of us believe we should steer clear of it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That's because it used to contain harmful trans fats which are strongly linked with cardiovascular disease but modern day margarines "have close to zero amounts of trans fats" according to Forouhi. "So it can actually be part of a healthy diet and reduce the bad cholesterols."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Butter also isn't off the menu entirely. "If you love butter, for instance on your toast, by all means have it," says Forouhi. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;You can use both margarine and butter for cooking, but Forouhi recommends sometimes swapping them out for oil instead which has less saturated fat in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;UK health guidelines advise to keep your saturated fat intake below 10% of calories and this is easier to do if you're using oil to cook with instead of butter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;3. Olive oil isn't suitable for deep frying &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A stock photo shows a woman pouring a big bottle of sunflower oil into a deep wok pan on an electric hob with cooking ingredients all around her and her kitchen cabinets and oven in the background." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Use sunflower or vegetable oil if you're deep frying food &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Oils behave differently when heated which makes some of them unsuitable for frying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Extra virgin olive oil, for example, is packed with antioxidants and beneficial compounds but its low smoke point means it is better for salad dressings or drizzling over food rather than deep frying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A smoke point is the point at which the fats in the oil start to break down and nasty compounds are released which can make the oil taste bitter, burnt or unpleasant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Restaurateur Tim Hayward says for shallow frying he uses a basic olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But for deep frying something like chips or battered fish, vegetable or sunflower oil is best as they withstand higher temperatures without breaking down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Some studies have also shown that oils heated to above their smoke point release toxic chemical by-products. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But Professor Forouhi says that type of cooking in the home is not very common and that long-term health studies still show that vegetable oils "without exception are related with better outcomes for chronic diseases."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Which oils should I be using? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you're looking for a simple kitchen strategy:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For everyday cooking: Sunflower or rapeseed oil are affordable, healthy, and versatile. You could also use a basic olive oil&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For salads and finishing dishes: Extra virgin olive oil adds flavour and health benefits&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For deep frying: Stick with a high smoke point oil like vegetable or sunflower&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For flavour variety: While they may not have the same health benefits as olive oil, you could use sesame, coconut or avocado oils for cold dishes if you like the flavour&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Overall, Professor Forouhi says it is better to look at your whole diet rather than obsess over which bottle to buy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I would recommend going with what taste and cost considerations you have and experiment with different types of oil that will bring you some health benefits," she explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsletters/zyxfdnb" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt; to receive our weekly newsletter highlighting uplifting stories and remarkable people from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:06:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5tVHI1Rmhkbzk3V0JYem5PM01rMVBBZnNsc2F2LXNNZ01jOVlkZ204Um9wZVBMYkhwUUlkczJzbU1pdUJ5U2lHWmZXSE52aXdLa0w0UnpQeWk2Z9IBX0FVX3lxTE55dDVfT0JGZjZWNkMzOUdqYU4zMFprbW52VDVfWEhWd1Vxa1RleWxfVF80LU9PVXZ3UU1MQnM2WURpMEttMTNsRVF0NnVXNVhqSjJKbk9iaDA5NDVZemVF</guid></item><item><title>我应该使用橄榄油油炸吗？如何选择合适的食用油- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cj3y7j2dz44o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 jRDKjj"&gt;Should I use olive oil for frying? How to choose the right cooking oil&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 ERpRj"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cecb/live/f253c650-9dea-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images Assorted healthy vegetable oil bottle collection on wooden table in a old fashioned kitchen with low key illumination: Olive oil, hazelnut oil, almond oil, coconut oil and sesame oil" class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Supermarket shelves are packed with oils from budget bottles of sunflower and vegetable oil to pricier olive, avocado and coconut oils claiming health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Oils and fats have been at the centre of nutritional debate for years and to understand why it matters, it helps to look at the different types of fat they contain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Not all fats behave the same way in the body - some raise cholesterol while others help lower it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Cholesterol is a natural fatty substance produced in the liver and can also be found in some of the foods we eat. Too much bad cholesterol can lead to a build-up of fatty deposits inside the walls of blood vessels, causing them to become narrowed or blocked. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;With so many shifting messages, knowing which product to pick can often feel overwhelming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Nita Forouhi, Professor of Population Health and Nutrition at the University of Cambridge, &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/articles/5d6Xw8BbzfGb2s3SMJDdFMd/which-oils-should-we-be-using-for-cooking" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;tells the BBC's Sliced Bread podcast&lt;/a&gt; that no single oil holds the magic key to health and debunks three common myths about cooking oils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;1. Use sunflower and vegetable oil for cooking&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7744/live/e1651960-9deb-11f0-b3aa-f94b46cdf49f.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Close-up of a shopper holding a bottle of cooking oil in a supermarket aisle, focusing on food choices, daily shopping, and consumer lifestyle." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Vegetable and sunflower oil is also a good budget option, costing around £2 a litre &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Rapeseed oil (commonly sold as vegetable oil) and sunflower oils often get bad press with some claiming they are ultra-processed and can cause inflammation which can be damaging to cardiovascular health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But, there isn't evidence to back this up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;In fact, these oils contain a low amount - 5-10% -  of unhealthy saturated fats and are high in healthier mono- and polyunsaturated fats. Polyunsaturated fats (including omega-3 and omega-6) are essential for brain and heart health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Forouhi says that these oils are "absolutely good for us".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;She explains that they can offer a reduction in disease risk "when saturated fats [which can raise bad cholesterol] like butter, lard or ghee are replaced with these oils".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;At around £2 per litre in most supermarkets it's also a more budget friendly option  for cooking at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;2. Margarine can help reduce bad cholesterol&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/204f/live/dcc67a60-9ef0-11f0-928c-71dbb8619e94.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Stock photo shows a close up image of a knife running through margarine with a spot of sunlight pouring in." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Modern day margarines have close to zero amounts of trans fats in&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Margarine has had a bad reputation for years and many of us believe we should steer clear of it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;That's because it used to contain harmful trans fats which are strongly linked with cardiovascular disease but modern day margarines "have close to zero amounts of trans fats" according to Forouhi. "So it can actually be part of a healthy diet and reduce the bad cholesterols."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Butter also isn't off the menu entirely. "If you love butter, for instance on your toast, by all means have it," says Forouhi. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;You can use both margarine and butter for cooking, but Forouhi recommends sometimes swapping them out for oil instead which has less saturated fat in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;UK health guidelines advise to keep your saturated fat intake below 10% of calories and this is easier to do if you're using oil to cook with instead of butter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;3. Olive oil isn't suitable for deep frying &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jHorPx"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 ilsLtA"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250919-090805-05e5ba0164-web-2.30.1-2/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 hagXkB hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/4198/live/01c15600-9ef1-11f0-92db-77261a15b9d2.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A stock photo shows a woman pouring a big bottle of sunflower oil into a deep wok pan on an electric hob with cooking ingredients all around her and her kitchen cabinets and oven in the background." class="sc-5340b511-0 bGQwLJ"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 lha-dta"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 etSgSK"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 jFVvLh"&gt;Use sunflower or vegetable oil if you're deep frying food &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Oils behave differently when heated which makes some of them unsuitable for frying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Extra virgin olive oil, for example, is packed with antioxidants and beneficial compounds but its low smoke point means it is better for salad dressings or drizzling over food rather than deep frying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;A smoke point is the point at which the fats in the oil start to break down and nasty compounds are released which can make the oil taste bitter, burnt or unpleasant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Restaurateur Tim Hayward says for shallow frying he uses a basic olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But for deep frying something like chips or battered fish, vegetable or sunflower oil is best as they withstand higher temperatures without breaking down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Some studies have also shown that oils heated to above their smoke point release toxic chemical by-products. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;But Professor Forouhi says that type of cooking in the home is not very common and that long-term health studies still show that vegetable oils "without exception are related with better outcomes for chronic diseases."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 bPbmDW"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 fsBZby"&gt;Which oils should I be using? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;If you're looking for a simple kitchen strategy:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For everyday cooking: Sunflower or rapeseed oil are affordable, healthy, and versatile. You could also use a basic olive oil&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For salads and finishing dishes: Extra virgin olive oil adds flavour and health benefits&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For deep frying: Stick with a high smoke point oil like vegetable or sunflower&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="sc-6f869981-0 bYhyhr"&gt;&lt;li class="sc-734a601e-0 NnDUj"&gt;For flavour variety: While they may not have the same health benefits as olive oil, you could use sesame, coconut or avocado oils for cold dishes if you like the flavour&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;Overall, Professor Forouhi says it is better to look at your whole diet rather than obsess over which bottle to buy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;"I would recommend going with what taste and cost considerations you have and experiment with different types of oil that will bring you some health benefits," she explains. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jdlrvG"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 bJoRPJ"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsletters/zyxfdnb" class="sc-f9178328-0 jZoZnB"&gt;Sign up here&lt;/a&gt; to receive our weekly newsletter highlighting uplifting stories and remarkable people from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 23:06:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5tVHI1Rmhkbzk3V0JYem5PM01rMVBBZnNsc2F2LXNNZ01jOVlkZ204Um9wZVBMYkhwUUlkczJzbU1pdUJ5U2lHWmZXSE52aXdLa0w0UnpQeWk2Zw</guid></item><item><title>明尼苏达州报告了另外13例麻疹病例，将2025年的总数提高到18例- Star Tribune</title><link>https://www.startribune.com/minnesota-reports-13-more-measles-cases-raising-2025-total-to-18/601484655</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;“They did not travel together in a group or tour or anything like that,” she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;Griffith encouraged people to seek testing if they develop fevers and other measleslike symptoms after exposure to people who have the disease, or if they develop the infection’s characteristic rash. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;Unvaccinated people exposed to measles are generally asked to stay home from work and public indoor places for 21 days to prevent further spread of the infection. The measles virus is one of the most infectious agents on the planet, capable of lingering in the air and spreading to others for two hours after sick people have left the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;A two-dose vaccine is 97% effective at preventing measles, but the infectious disease is making a comeback in the United States as parents decline the shots for their children. The 1,500 U.S. cases this year represent the highest total since 1992.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;Minnesota had one of the best measles vaccination rates in the nation a decade ago, when 94% of children had received the shots in time for kindergarten. However, the state had the sixth-worst rate, 87%, at the start of the 2022-23 school year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box   article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;Three children in the recent Minnesota clusters were hospitalized, Griffith said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Star Tribune</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 22:26:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipAFBVV95cUxPY1RleEJXVzEtN3U3S1VyTDBlZ2dELV9sOVpzenlBUlRkRDVFZnNJODMzUHNzMzZTY3NqNy1Nb3ItVWpON2F1d2RadVV1V3BNcHh1bG1IdEVBZWNLNDB1SDlCM1U3U2NaVVZGOHdkSXo1eHladGJWZ3JOUGJpc0xRQTFPZGVRWEVKMnlVTTM2UC1pUFlaaDdiWUw1U3JQRk1nUnhMVA</guid></item><item><title>亚利桑那州犹他州公共卫生协调麻疹疫情应对-德撒律新闻</title><link>https://www.deseret.com/lifestyle/2025/10/01/utah-measles-case-count-keeps-rising-health-department/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="dn-article-body mt-4"&gt;&lt;div class="dn-article-body__key-points-list col-12"&gt;&lt;div class="key-points-list-content"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Utah confirmed 44 measles cases in 2025 compared to zero in 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Most cases are in southwest Utah near Arizona's ongoing measles outbreak.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Measles vaccine exemption rates for Utah kindergartners exceed 10%.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Utah has 44 confirmed measles cases so far in 2025, according to the &lt;a href="https://epi.utah.gov/measles-response/" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://epi.utah.gov/measles-response/"&gt;weekly update&lt;/a&gt; of the Utah Department of Health and Human Services measles dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;No cases were confirmed in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;According to the counts as of September 30, the majority of Utah cases — 30 — were in the southwest region near Arizona, a state that’s had 59 cases. The &lt;a href="https://www.azdhs.gov/preparedness/epidemiology-disease-control/measles/index.php" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.azdhs.gov/preparedness/epidemiology-disease-control/measles/index.php"&gt;Arizona Department of Health&lt;/a&gt; reports an ongoing outbreak of measles, with all but four of its cases in Mohave County.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The outbreak spanning northern Arizona and southwest Utah is among the largest in the U.S. at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Utah’s other 14 cases include four in northern Utah, three in southeast Utah and seven in Utah County. Measles detection in wastewater samples found virus shed in the same areas, but it doesn’t say how many people in each area had measles. The water detection result is the same for 1 or 100. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="Exposure-then-symptom-watch" class="dn-article-body__h3"&gt;Exposure then symptom watch&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;There are three active symptom watch periods, but they’re nearly over. People might have been exposed to measles at the Budge Clinic in Logan if they were there Sept. 15 between 3 p.m. and 6:30 p.m. The last day to watch for symptoms from that is Oct. 6.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Someone with measles was at Water Canyon High School in Hildale on Sept. 12, so others there at the same time have risk of exposure. That symptom watch ends Oct. 3.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Finally, folks at Chick-fil-A in Providence, Utah, Sept. 11 between 6:30 p.m. and 9:30 p.m. can stop checking for symptoms after Oct. 2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Eight other exposures are no longer being watched as enough time has passed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="About-measles" class="dn-article-body__h3"&gt;About measles&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Measles symptoms typically include a high fever (101°F or more), along with cough, runny nose, watery eyes and rash that starts at the hairline most of the time and then spreads down. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The viral illness can cause complications, some very serious. Those include pneumonia, hospitalization, brain swelling that can lead to deafness and other problems, pregnancy complications, seizures and a weakened immune system that can linger for a long time and increase the risk of infections. Some people die.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;There’s no specific treatment for measles; rather, symptoms are managed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="The-national-count" class="dn-article-body__h3"&gt;The national count&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;As of Sept. 30, the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt; reports 1,544 cases nationally. The CDC said it is also aware of probable cases, but its count only includes those that have been lab confirmed. In 2024, there were 285 cases of measles nationwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Of the 2025 measles cases, 21 were among international visitors. The other 1,523 cases were found in 42 jurisdictions: Alabama, Alaska, Arizona, Arkansas, California, Colorado, Florida, Georgia, Hawaii, Idaho, Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Kansas, Kentucky, Louisiana, Maryland, Michigan, Minnesota, Missouri, Montana, Nebraska, New Jersey, New Mexico, New York City, New York State, North Dakota, Ohio, Oklahoma, Oregon, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, South Carolina, South Dakota, Tennessee, Texas, Utah, Vermont, Virginia, Washington, Wisconsin and Wyoming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;The CDC said 4% of cases involved those who’d had one dose of measles, mumps, rubella (MMR) vaccine, and similarly, 4% were individuals who’d had both recommended doses. The other 92% were unvaccinated or their status wasn’t known. Nearly 40% of the cases were in the age 5 to 19 (school age) population, while 27% were in children younger than 5. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Twelve percent were hospitalized because of their measles symptom severity and three deaths have been attributed to measles this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 id="Vaccination-among-Utah-school-kids" class="dn-article-body__h3"&gt;Vaccination among Utah school kids&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Federal officials are urging parents to have their children vaccinated against measles. “Vaccines not only protect individual children from measles, but also contribute to community immunity,” acting CDC director Jim O’Neill said. He is also deputy secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;According to the Utah Department of Health and Human Services, during the 2024-25 school year:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;About 10% of in-person kindergarten students in Utah had an exemption for the MMR vaccine or were missing documentation to show they were vaccinated against measles.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;9.0% of in-person kindergarten students in Utah had an exemption to any school-required vaccine.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;10.1% of all students in Utah had an exemption to any school-required vaccine, including students in online schools.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/measles-outbreak-utah-arizona-vaccines-data-schools-rcna232399" target="_blank" rel="" title="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/measles-outbreak-utah-arizona-vaccines-data-schools-rcna232399"&gt;NBC News and Stanford&lt;/a&gt; looked at vaccine rates for communicable diseases like measles. NBC reported that in Washington County, Utah, near the Arizona border, about 79% of kindergartners are vaccinated against measles — just a bit higher than the rate in Gaines County, Texas, which was the heart of the 2025 outbreak earlier this year. To get herd immunity protection, 95% need to be vaccinated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;“I’ve worked for this health department for about 18 years, and we’ve never seen a case of measles that I know of up until this point,” David Heaton, the public information officer for the Southwest Utah Public Health Department, told NBC. “We are just at that low rate of (vaccine) uptake that does leave us open for this kind of an outbreak.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph"&gt;Arizona and Utah health officials are reportedly working collaboratively to respond to the outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Deseret News</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 21:06:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxQWjkwdWhBMUZBNGwzNWV4d2pWSVk3SUJJejJvaGYzM2JmdHJBTkZ3OEhiaDRBRG15MDhqeTNsdVpQanRMSUktT1lySUFqVTlRWUhxOWRvTFNLRy1ER2hLQUQ3X0xYeGc3Q1MyaElNRm1lYzZrb3dxYXJuUHpsN3dBcVVpM0wzdl9nZFQ1YTZyRFlUcEtZbmI2T09NVURDZXRNakE</guid></item><item><title>卫生部长警告性传播疾病和糖尿病发病率上升--特立尼达和多巴哥新闻日</title><link>https://newsday.co.tt/2025/10/01/tha-health-secretary-warns-of-rise-in-stis-diabetes/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="article-content"&gt;


	&lt;a class="article-category" href="https://newsday.co.tt/category/news"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;header&gt;
	&lt;h1&gt;THA health secretary warns of rise in STIs, diabetes&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;/header&gt;



&lt;address class="article-author"&gt;
	&lt;a rel="author" href="https://newsday.co.tt/reporter/newsday_reporter"&gt;
		Newsday Reporter								
	&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/address&gt;



&lt;time class="date-time" pubdate datetime="2025-10-01" title="Wednesday 1 October 2025"&gt;5 Hrs Ago&lt;/time&gt;

&lt;figure id="article-featured-image" class="article-featured-image"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" src="https://newsday.co.tt/wp-content/uploads/2025/10/23227615.jpg" alt="THA Health Secretary Dr Faith Brebnor - "&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;THA Health Secretary Dr Faith Brebnor - &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;p&gt;THA Secretary of Health, Wellness and Social Protection has reported an increase in sexually transmitted infections (STIs) and diabetes cases on the island.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the launch of a health and wellness campaign titled “Play Mas, Live Well” on September 29 at the Hochoy Charles Administrative Complex in Calder Hall, Dr Faith Brebnor made the startling revelation as she encouraged people to take charge of their health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“This was a good opportunity to say to the people of Tobago, to the people of TT, that we need us – all of us – to really be healthy – head to toe, and head to toe includes those...private parts.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She said before becoming health secretary, she along with others spoke publicly on the issue of contracting HIV and being able to live a long, healthy life with medication.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We really are seeing increased rates of almost all of the STIs throughout the island.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="ad-manager-half-page-mobile-ad-300x600 ad-space-centered" id="div-gpt-ad-1550239531467-0"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"So way back when, when we started talking about HIV and the thing that we were looking at, or the images that we looked at included people looking very sick, and then we went through that wave and then we recognised that there was medication that was available for us and that you did not have to die from HIV but you could live a very long, healthy life with HIV, and then somehow we stopped talking.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;She noted that with these concerning statistics will be addressed in the “Play Mas, Live Well” campaign and accompanying initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We stopped talking about STIs and we stopped talking about all of the other things, about consent and those areas, and we decided that this was a great opportunity because those things, we are seeing the numbers raised again. This was a good opportunity to say to the people of Tobago, to the people of Trinidad and Tobago, that we really need all of us to be healthy.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using information shared by a health practitioner, she said people in their thirties are reporting HbA1c (blood glucose) readings over 14 per cent. Readings below 5.7 per cent are considered normal, while prediabetes is between 5.7 per cent and 6.4 per cent. Diabetes is diagnosed with readings 6.5 per cent or higher.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We now have significantly younger people who are having long-term (diabetes), because HbA1c is not because you drank something and your sugar is high now, it is because you have had uncontrolled high sugar, in essence, in your system for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"So this means we have increased numbers of young people (with diabetes), because this used to be what happened to the older people who are treating with these issues.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The launch ended with the first aerobic burnout session.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;



&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Trinidad and Tobago Newsday</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:29:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxPUEt0QzQxMm5zeTBjR2JYM1RtdkYzM1RKU2s2VXdXeTNjNmpHa2lKRkxzUnB3T3NRXzB0LWlyUnJHMWhRcmJxcDktU3VvdU1OVFlYOEZuRTJIWUw5R3p6V0FCQnB4WUZMVVZ5T0ttS2tyZFF2blVtcjVxQUNWby1MdGI1U0ltaFk5c3RiS213</guid></item><item><title>女性在撰写自己的讣告后变得病毒式轰动- WHIO TV</title><link>https://www.whio.com/news/local/woman-becomes-viral-sensation-after-writing-her-own-obituary/WP4SVUSZRZCNDFZMRN3I4M4EGQ/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;BOYLSTON, MASS. — Linda Murphy, a Massachusetts woman who battled ALS, has become a posthumous viral sensation for her humorous self-written obituary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Murphy, who was raised in Framingham and lived in Boylston, passed away after a battle with Bulbar ALS, leaving behind a legacy of humor and resilience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;“She was the life of the party. She was the party,” said her daughter, Justine Hastings, reflecting on her mother’s vibrant personality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[DOWNLOAD: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://www.whio.com/mobile-apps/"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free WHIO-TV News app for alerts as news breaks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRENDING STORIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Murphy was diagnosed with Bulbar ALS after experiencing symptoms like slurred speech and trouble swallowing. She had initially approached doctors at Massachusetts General Hospital, confident in her self-diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;In addition to her battle with ALS, Murphy was a breast cancer survivor, having been diagnosed in 2012. Her experience with cancer inspired her to write a book titled ‘F-Off Cancer,’ which aimed to show that life could still be enjoyed despite the illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Murphy’s obituary, written six months before her death, is filled with her characteristic humor. She begins it with, ‘Well, if you are reading this, then it looks like I am dead. Wow. It actually happened. I died of FOMO due to complications of ALS.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Despite her struggles, Murphy maintained her sense of humor, writing about her ‘superpowers’ and the challenges of living with ALS. She lamented the inability to enjoy food and drink, a sentiment she expressed with wit in her obituary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Murphy’s obituary also included a call for kindness, urging people to be nice to everyone they encounter and suggesting that instead of flowers, people should buy scratch tickets and give them to strangers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;In her final act of generosity, Murphy donated her brain and spinal cord for ALS research, hoping to contribute to a better understanding of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;Murphy’s self-penned obituary not only captured her humor and spirit but also left a lasting impact by encouraging kindness and supporting ALS research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;a href="https://mccarthyfh.com/tribute/linda-murphy-21-476/" target="_self" rel="" title="https://mccarthyfh.com/tribute/linda-murphy-21-476/"&gt;You can read her full obituary here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters" target="_self" rel="" title="https://membercenter.whio.com/newsletters"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WHIO-TV Daily Headlines Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 lofITx body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHIO TV</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:25:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivAFBVV95cUxPNHNjS0lHaVNkcFgzMG1mU2x6bE1WMzZEdlR5amRfclZaam5vajI1QWFDd2tHanRkUThYVWJjUG9VV0JIWkxlRWIyVmZydWxSOW5Sb2pJY0J2N01XemZNWXlCakZ4TjJ1RjNBWDFudklzaV8xOExDX1JEQVhCYzUzUVFlRDhIWW5jVVlUb29raDhHRy0wejNrWkllSFcwenhhc0hqYnRocXRwWmZJZC1CbVgwMmZSZTlMV1BicNIB0AFBVV95cUxQWERCUVZoV0g4MTJhclVLbmVBa1NIdkY5U2M0T0xWVElsTGNzNlpPcGFtaTV0aXB3djdmMkQxS2lUdHlFWEdkSE10cmcwTEwwRlZLNXNpSmY5ZTB4Q1BsQXZoTlVObVdnZXhmZGFubC13ZkJCaXFiVjMxNm5IWlhYOWwzazBZdVdxekdhb1hCb2RuS19WUndFeE44WHNPdGliNVNqS25yVTU3V2k0UjEyTE5oVEI4ZFZmSWZpVzNSOGlaSktKNDZTa1E4aDA0cDNU</guid></item><item><title>长寿研究：饮食压力支持健康衰老- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-longevity-dietary-stress-healthy-aging.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
									    
&lt;div class="article-gallery lightGallery"&gt;
    &lt;div data-thumb="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/tmb/2025/longevity-research-die.jpg" data-src="https://scx2.b-cdn.net/gfx/news/hires/2025/longevity-research-die.jpg" data-sub-html="A balanced diet keeps the nematode C. elegans (pictured) fit and healthy in old age. Credit: Jachen Solinger, Biozentrum, University of Basel"&gt;
        &lt;figure class="article-img"&gt;
            &lt;img src="https://scx1.b-cdn.net/csz/news/800a/2025/longevity-research-die.jpg" alt="Longevity research: Dietary stress supports healthy aging" title="A balanced diet keeps the nematode C. elegans (pictured) fit and healthy in old age. Credit: Jachen Solinger, Biozentrum, University of Basel"&gt;
             &lt;figcaption class="text-darken text-low-up text-truncate-js text-truncate mt-3"&gt;
                A balanced diet keeps the nematode C. elegans (pictured) fit and healthy in old age. Credit: Jachen Solinger, Biozentrum, University of Basel
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;        &lt;/figure&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain nutrients in food can trigger a mild stress response in nematodes. But instead of making them sick, this actually helps them stay healthier as they age, according to researchers at the University of Basel, Switzerland.&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                                                                &lt;p class="w-100 my-4 d-print-none"&gt;
     
     
     &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7587637799"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
     
&lt;/p&gt;  
                                         

                                                                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;The results of their study have been &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-025-63987-x" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;i&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;People are living longer than ever, but a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/long+life/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;long life&lt;/a&gt; doesn't necessarily mean a healthy one. For many, the question isn't so much "How old do I want to get?" but rather "How do I want to get old?" While lifespan refers to the years we live from birth to death, "healthspan" describes the number of years we spend in good health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Healthy aging is also a question of diet. It's long been known that not just the quantity, but also the individual nutrients impact how we age. Using the tiny worm Caenorhabditis elegans, corresponding author Anne Spang's team has now demonstrated that certain RNA molecules in food have a positive effect on the worm's fitness in old age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"These molecules prevent the formation of harmful protein aggregates that are typically linked with aging and disease," says Spang.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How diet shapes aging&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With age, the body becomes less efficient at removing altered and damaged proteins. These can accumulate and form harmful protein aggregates in cells. Such protein aggregates are considered drivers of aging and are associated with multiple &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/age-related+diseases/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;age-related diseases&lt;/a&gt; including muscular and &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/neurodegenerative+diseases/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;neurodegenerative diseases&lt;/a&gt; such as Alzheimer's and Parkinson's disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers have discovered that a &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/balanced+diet/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;balanced diet&lt;/a&gt; promotes healthspan, and specific components in the nematode's diet exert a protective effect. The &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/worms/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;worms&lt;/a&gt; feed mainly on bacteria that contain double-stranded RNA molecules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"These dietary RNAs are absorbed in the gut and activate quality-control mechanisms to protect from &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/cellular+stress/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;cellular stress&lt;/a&gt;," explains Emmanouil Kyriakakis, the study's first author. "This low-level stress essentially trains the body to cope with protein damage more effectively."&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                        
    &lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
          
        
        &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7099578867"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                                                                                                                                &lt;h2&gt;Diet-dependent mechanisms slow cellular aging&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Diet activates autophagy—a cellular cleanup process that degrades and recycles damaged proteins. This mechanism reduces harmful protein aggregation and thus slows down cell aging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We were surprised to find that the gut communicates with other organs," says Kyriakakis. "We observed protective effects not only locally, but also in muscles and throughout the whole organism."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Healthier aging—even in worms&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, the worms exposed to a balanced diet were more active and healthier in old age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The dietary-RNA species elicit a systemic stress response that protects the worms from &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/protein/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;protein&lt;/a&gt; aggregation during aging," says Kyriakakis, "thereby extending their healthspan."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The findings confirm that diet strongly influences health in old age.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Specific food components can stimulate the body's own protective mechanisms," adds Spang. "So, a little stress can be good for you."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whether individual nutrients can also spark beneficial effects in humans—and potentially help prevent age-related diseases—remains to be investigated. But it's certainly conceivable. What is clear already: What we eat can shape the way we age.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                    
                                                                                
                                        											&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
												                                                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
                                                    Emmanouil Kyriakakis et al, Bacterial RNA promotes proteostasis through inter-tissue communication in C. elegans, &lt;i&gt;Nature Communications&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41467-025-63987-x" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1038/s41467-025-63987-x&lt;/a&gt;
																								
																								&lt;/p&gt;
																							&lt;/div&gt;
                                        											
																					
                                                                                                                        
                                        
                                        &lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
                                                 &lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
                                                 Longevity research: Dietary stress supports healthy aging (2025, October 1)
                                                 retrieved 2 October 2025
                                                 from https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-10-longevity-dietary-stress-healthy-aging.html
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
                                            This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
                                            part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 19:10:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQZFdPOFB5T1N4WkJmeFVkLXhXeno5YV9sQ2EwVkR5ZGEySVBhZGJKUnJZMEVuZTZ6NmpGUWV4Y3VaYXk2akJPVTFRM0JGNWEwV2s3TG1VU1RxMzk3cjlxU2lHSUk5TGZaazZxdEkzdmRmbHR1OHBOMnpRblIxem5iVWE1SnVWUk1fNHc</guid></item><item><title>科学家研究了自我诊断患有多动症的人。他们的发现揭示了什么- Gizmodo</title><link>https://gizmodo.com/scientists-studied-people-with-self-diagnosed-adhd-what-they-found-was-revealing-2000666179</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-xl "&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;New research out today shows that there are key differences between people who self-diagnose themselves with attention-deficit/hyperactivity disorder and those diagnosed by a doctor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Scientists at Michigan State University examined hundreds of thousands of Reddit posts from users of a forum dedicated to ADHD. Among other things, they found that self-diagnosed individuals were more likely to have a negative self-image than people clinically diagnosed with ADHD; they also tended to seek out validation online and from their loved ones more often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-5 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The findings suggest it’s important to recognize how people’s identity surrounding ADHD can be shaped by the origin of their diagnosis, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;A Reddit analysis&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The study authors initially analyzed over 450,000 posts on the subreddit r/ADHD, made over a 14-year span between 2009 and 2023.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They ultimately studied a subset of 211,000 posts, made by 15,432 unique users, that clearly indicated a person’s diagnosis status. In one example of self-diagnosis cited by the authors, the user stated that they were “undiagnosed but suspecting things.” They analyzed the language of these posts, looking for signs of validation-seeking, negative self-image, and internalized stigma (one example of the latter: “I avoided treatment for years because of the shame of the source”).&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;All in all, they found that people with self-diagnosed ADHD were more likely to look down on themselves and to express internalized stigma in these posts than those with clinically diagnosed ADHD. They were also more likely to express wanting validation of their condition, both social (from their real-life peers) and media (from mass media portrayals or large online communities like r/ADHD).&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;At the same time, having social validation was associated with people having both negative and positive self-images. And while people with clinically diagnosed ADHD sought validation less often, the link between validation and a person’s self-image and internalized stigma was actually stronger in this group than in people with self-diagnosed ADHD.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;What to take away&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The findings appear to reaffirm a concept in psychology known as &lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2011-21802-002"&gt;self-verification theory&lt;/a&gt;, the researchers say, which argues that we prefer other people to see us the same way as we see ourselves.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In this particular case, they argue, people with self-diagnosed ADHD are more motivated to seek confirmation of their issues in online communities like Reddit since they lack formal recognition from a doctor. But while being validated might improve a person’s outlook in some ways, it can also reinforce a person’s negative self-perceptions and belief in stereotypes associated with having that condition, which then contributes to internalized shame and stigma.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The major, if perhaps obvious, takeaway here is that online communities and social media can greatly shape how individuals with ADHD view themselves, the researchers say. And ideally, these communities should share accurate information about the condition that can support a positive self-image and reduce stigma.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;“Collaboration with mental health organizations is essential to ensure the dissemination of evidence-based content, which can strengthen social support networks and promote positive mental health outcomes for the ADHD community,” the authors wrote in their paper, &lt;a href="http://plos.io/4plEDJz"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; Wednesday in PLOS-One.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, that might be easier said than done. Other studies have suggested that misinformation about ADHD is rampant online. A study this past March, for instance, found that nearly half of the most popular ADHD-related videos on TikTok &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0319335"&gt;contained&lt;/a&gt; misleading claims about the condition; the researchers also noted that the more people watched this kind of content, the more likely they were to overestimate how many Americans are thought to have ADHD (it’s estimated about 6% of adults and 11% of children are &lt;a href="https://chadd.org/about-adhd/general-prevalence/"&gt;currently diagnosed&lt;/a&gt; with ADHD).&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;It’s also worth noting that even experts in the field are still &lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/why-are-adhd-rates-so-much-higher-in-the-u-s-2000595804"&gt;debating&lt;/a&gt; over just how common ADHD truly is among the general public.&lt;/p&gt;      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 18:00:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxNTW10bEVGc25ZSFJ6WFdsU2dESmNNSlFDUVpKNHdZV2p4cVJtSS1USGtFMWJvLXo5R3hYZ05KYkViczdaNTVqWFVkRjROQWZDbUd0U3U4anRzaTJSTnpOUXJ0VDhWUmZCSG1odEVTbFJnSTBRaDBSQ3hyZmdjUDROYVluWXpOa0tnbnpvZTdHWEktV1RPUzJlekVZejFFbUctQ0g0WjhmejNRRzZEYWRMYQ</guid></item><item><title>州警方称146号公路的所有车道都开放- WJAR</title><link>https://turnto10.com/news/local/crashes-disrupting-traffic-on-route-146-north-and-south</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="index-module_storyColumn__EZ7G" id="js-Story-Content-0"&gt;&lt;p class="StoryTags-module_tagWrapperLine__Jfav"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="StoryText-module_storyText__FWhP"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rhode Island State Police said Wednesday that both directions of Route 146 were open again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The highway was shut down earlier north of Route 99 because of low-hanging power lines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier, the Rhode Island Department of Transportation reported that two separate crashes were disrupting traffic on Route 146 in Lincoln and North Smithfield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;RIDOT said on X at about 2:15 p.m. that a crash had been cleared from Route 146 north at Interstate 295 in Lincoln.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a separate post, RIDOT said a second crash was cleared from the travel lanes of Route 146 south at Sayles Hill Road in North Smithfield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No additional information was immediately available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WJAR</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:26:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNTnE2a2RLZXFzZTdvMWlFTGpTSHg1dkRrWXB2cUczN3JrUWZySUZ6LVB5V25KWldocC1ySGxGTkFTUFZRamxRNkh5Z1RXeGRTcG5Sb2Z6UHVUY0F2c0RRbmRXeWxwTTROZkRvLXlqVUZ1YzhyM0hVT2tVZnJLWXBpUnF2ZTJDYWhzM3F6RTdMaHQ</guid></item><item><title>Bexar县卫生官员表示， Fox狂犬病检测呈阳性- KSAT</title><link>https://www.ksat.com/news/local/2025/10/01/fox-tests-positive-for-rabies-bexar-county-health-officials-say/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 fURyTV iQviKm articleBody" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BEXAR COUNTY, Texas&lt;/strong&gt; – The Bexar County Public Health Department confirmed a fox tested positive for rabies on Tuesday. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;County health officials said a homeowner saw the fox behaving abnormally on their north Bexar County property located in the 27000 block of Mark Wayne. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;According to the county, the homeowner killed the fox and reported the incident to Bexar County Animal Control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;A test conducted by the Texas Department of State Health Services determined that the fox had rabies, but it did not interact with any other humans or pets. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 kNAFkD cuqaEv article-text"&gt;Health officials said rabies is most often transmitted by rabid animal bites. Additionally, rabies can be transmitted when a rabid animal’s saliva touches a human or mammal’s eyes, nose, mouth or a break in the skin. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;“Thankfully no human contact was involved in this positive rabies incident,” Bexar County Public Health Department Director Dr. Andrea Guerrero said in a statement. “However, wild animals such as foxes and raccoons can infect pets. It underscores the importance of ensuring that all dogs and cats are vaccinated against the rabies virus. I encourage Bexar County residents to reach out to Bexar County Animal Care for information on how to access resources for rabies vaccination.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__FlexBase-sc-1fnzlkn-1 jGlKin adWrapper" aria-label="Advertisement"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;The county said this week’s rabies case is the 15th in Bexar County so far this year. Bexar County health officials are encouraging residents to take the following precautions: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 kDvXdO font_openSans articleList"&gt;&lt;li class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 ecGWWE iQviKm"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 hxqFXA fYWDEy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 6 6" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;circle cx="3" cy="3" r="3" fill="#212121"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;span class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 gJUqRf"&gt;Avoiding contact with wildlife and unknown animals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 ecGWWE iQviKm"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 hxqFXA fYWDEy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 6 6" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;circle cx="3" cy="3" r="3" fill="#212121"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;span class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 gJUqRf"&gt;People bitten, scratched, or exposed to a rabid animal should immediately wash the wound with soap and water and talk to a healthcare provider&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 ecGWWE iQviKm"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 hxqFXA fYWDEy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 6 6" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;circle cx="3" cy="3" r="3" fill="#212121"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;span class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 gJUqRf"&gt;The location of the rabid animal, if known, should be reported as soon as possible&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 ecGWWE iQviKm"&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__StackBase-sc-1fnzlkn-7 hxqFXA fYWDEy"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 6 6" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" aria-hidden="true" role="presentation"&gt;&lt;circle cx="3" cy="3" r="3" fill="#212121"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;span class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 gJUqRf"&gt;Pet owners should ensure their dogs and cats have their rabies vaccinations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 bYFsJw cuqaEv article-text"&gt;&lt;b&gt;More recent local health coverage on KSAT: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;p class="dist__Box-sc-1fnzlkn-0 dist__TextBase-sc-1fnzlkn-3 nALdY copyright"&gt;Copyright 2025 by KSAT - All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSAT</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:16:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPTGpfM1FsZTM2NUZ0d245aHBNbkhkSU5YSXZQWXItd2ZTVUlLaVNwR2I1c3BfTHdvLUl6RGtaYldMbl9qNG9FWTBubmpjdlZUR3p1Sld3RTN6bGdUS1BaV09xT09VYjlyTmQwa0g2SU5pbm55SThMNi1KOXA5bWpGbVQyRC1FU2ppV2p4QlR0dzg2bjI3VkluXzVMNl8tZ2tRdGtNX0t4Z3E3V0E</guid></item><item><title>因水果饮食而饿死的英国大学毕业生恳求对症状的帮助- The Mirror</title><link>https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/world-news/uk-university-graduate-who-starved-35998554</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article id="article-body" class="ArticleBody_article__AwrJE" data-testid="body"&gt;&lt;h1 class="HeadingOne_heading-one__mmNWJ  __className_4d0286" publication="mirror"&gt;UK university graduate who starved to death from fruit diet pleaded for help over symptoms&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;h2 class="LeadText_lead-text__wd_PA __className_1cc836" data-testid="leadtext" publication="mirror"&gt;Leeds University graduate Karolina Krzyak dropped to as little as 4.2 stone after consuming only raw fruit until she was so weak that she could not even turn over in bed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;button class="LightboxBtn_lightbox-btn__eoxYS" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX ImageEmbed_image-lead__Ti3qQ" data-testid="leadimage" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="35995121"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Karolina Krzyzak was found dead in her Bali hotel room in December 2024&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: carolina.mariie/Instagram)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;A UK university graduate who starved to death from a raw fruit diet made a plea for help over her crumbling yellow nails and rotting teeth, it has emerged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/uk-news/woman-27-starves-death-bali-35995285" target="_self" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;Tragic ex-Leeds University student Karolina Krzyak &lt;/a&gt;exclusively consumed raw&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/7-million-taking-cholesterol-drug-35981459" target="_blank" aria-label=" fruitLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt; fruit&lt;/a&gt; when she was 19 after she became obsessed with "clean eating." But the&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/poland" target="_blank" aria-label=" PolishLink opens in a new tab." tabindex="0"&gt; Polish&lt;/a&gt; native's health dramatically deteriorated she could hardly turn over in bed during a trip to Bali in December 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;Staff at the Sumberkima Hill resort on the Indonesian island said she appeared "emaciated," with sunken eyes. The 27-year-old was even so weak that the night clerk had to support her as Karolina could not even carry her own weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image-group"&gt;&lt;button class="LightboxBtn_lightbox-btn__eoxYS" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-35998729" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="35998729" data-tmdatatrack-type="image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Karolina died three days into her stay at a hotel in Bali &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: carolina.mariie/Instagram)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_c7f578"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.dailystar.co.uk/news/latest-news/woman-27-starves-death-bali-35997921" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="35997921" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;Woman, 27, starves to death in Bali hotel room after weighing 3.5 stone on 'fruitarian' diet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="readmore" class="ReadMore_readmore-prefix__xS44r __className_c7f578"&gt;READ MORE: &lt;span class="ReadMore_readmore-link__eF9pN"&gt;&lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/news/health/exact-date-brits-most-likely-32969935" data-tmdatatrack="read-more" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="32969935" data-tmdatatrack-source="editorial" tabindex="0"&gt;Exact date Brits most likely to kickstart healthy eating push in time for summer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;Just three days into her stay, Karolina's body was found in her room, reports The Cut. But the fruitarian's death came after years of health problems, including complaining her teeth had started to rot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;An online friend of Karolina revealed she had suffered from developed osteoporosis and albumin deficiency, which resulted in oedema and swelling of her feet. Karlolina shared her concerns in a social media group dedicated to raw veganism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BoxStyles_box-container__Qk3WH BoxStyles_non-commercial__aiWwo undefined" data-testid="non-commercial-1" publication="mirror"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;In an October 22, 2022, post shared to The Healthiest Raw Vegan Diet &lt;a class="TextLink_text-link__dBSS0 TextLink_enabled__dJF3l" href="https://www.mirror.co.uk/all-about/facebook" target="" aria-label="" tabindex="0"&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; group, she made plea for help after noticing her nails were yellowing and crumbling. She said: "I know seeking 'diagnosis' or advice here based on photos may not be the ideal but maybe someone knows/ has experienced something similar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image-group"&gt;&lt;button class="LightboxBtn_lightbox-btn__eoxYS" aria-label="Open image viewer" aria-haspopup="dialog" aria-controls="image-lightbox"&gt;&lt;div class="ImageEmbed_image-embed__0T8WX false" data-testid="imageembed-35998730" data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-articleid="35998730" data-tmdatatrack-type="image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="ImageEmbed_fig-caption__qotOK"&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_camera-style__Qjeby"&gt;&lt;svg viewbox="0 0 16 16" fill="none" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg"&gt;&lt;g clip-path="url(#clip0_209_94274)"&gt;&lt;path opacity="0.16" fill-rule="evenodd" clip-rule="evenodd" d="M14 4H2V10.6667C2 11.403 2.59695 12 3.33333 12H12.6667C13.403 12 14 11.403 14 10.6667V4ZM8 10C9.10457 10 10 9.10457 10 8C10 6.89543 9.10457 6 8 6C6.89543 6 6 6.89543 6 8C6 9.10457 6.89543 10 8 10Z" fill="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M2 3.33331H14V11.3333C14 12.0697 13.403 12.6666 12.6667 12.6666H3.33333C2.59695 12.6666 2 12.0697 2 11.3333V3.33331Z" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;circle cx="8" cy="8" r="2" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/circle&gt;&lt;path d="M11.3332 1.33331L12.6665 1.33331" stroke="var(--color-sem-icon-primary-default)" stroke-width="1.33333" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;defs&gt;&lt;clippath id="clip0_209_94274"&gt;&lt;rect fill="white"&gt;&lt;/rect&gt;&lt;/clippath&gt;&lt;/defs&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-title__FSINC"&gt;Karolina studied at Leeds University &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ImageEmbed_caption-credit__uNiU6"&gt;(Image: carolina.mariie/Instagram)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;"Do you think it's parasites? I do feel a lot of itchiness lately and very bad bloating. Of course, that just part of a while bigger picture of my health history but just got the first glance do you think this may be some kind of fungus?"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;Despite her weight falling, Karolina expressed how she believed veganism "opened her eyes" to "so many things" and that she was "grateful" for the experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;"She needed medical and psychological help, and the community often validated her behaviours instead," a friend said. One fruitarian health coach noticed Karolina due to her low weight and estimated she could not have weighed more than 4.2 stone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Paragraph_paragraph-text__PVKlh " data-tmdatatrack="content-unit" data-tmdatatrack-type="paragraph" publication="mirror"&gt;Following a few months, friends reported she could barely maintain her balance and needed to walk slowly to avoid hitting objects. Karolina approached health coaches with the intention of seeking assistance for her illness but was adamant any treatment would need to include a raw vegan diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mirror</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 17:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxOTUtLMTlRelA3Wk1hcWQ0ajhuYkowd0RZU2JmQ3ZHZ3UxU2F6TGlJejJkc0VVSVc2X3NteVNrVDcxMzNNVXBWc2Mxc2o0QW9LRk1EZWR6V1RmajdBemJuMFJjVGJXRjJGU1RfVndsWGR1WUJqUnBqTVd1cGNUSEJNLTd2eG82a2UxbXlPWdIBkgFBVV95cUxPYWdZbm11aVM0d3FBLTRDeDEtU3FqR3c2TVZLZ0o3SlB0WUZLVG1KYS1jWGZfamtFOVo4M0k5MHFKb3hKNjE2U1YzdjFvTDNiSjYyc2VlWF9vZi11VUVST2VXR2JpVFpMZU90MlQybW1CYW9Ldkx2SkM5WmFwT1hJdFM2N01BclBUNS0wQzE1a3d2UQ</guid></item><item><title>心脏病专家揭示了实际有效的降低胆固醇的3个简单变化-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/cardiologist-reveals-3-simple-changes-to-lower-cholesterol-that-actually-work/photostory/124263476.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients who show up with stubbornly high cholesterol usually expect a genetic explanation. Dr. Shailesh Singh, an interventional cardiologist, cuts through that expectation on Twitter: “Your cholesterol isn't high because of genetics. It's high because you eat like s***, don't move, and pretend you'll 'start Monday.'” He goes on to name three repeatable choices that, he says, drive most of what he treats in clinic. The claim is blunt, but it’s worth asking whether the evidence lines up with the bluntness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 16:44:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihwJBVV95cUxOODI2bkN3Zl9yVEtCeFh4eExBR1pZQUtxMHA2RHpuNzV1X0Exc1hqNmd0QWc5X3U2QnlLcWppOXd4R2hjU1JqX2FhM0phckxmX1JWMkpuRWpQWGdlMWRpYmFCY2dqd0ZMQ2RzNlppVnFsU1JzZzRibnNwR0hvOHBuX2U2YTJ3NVFLdkRjVHQ4UVlJRzA0eWhXSlk3Z2RlUHA5TGo5RVh4dmE3dUpJNnBKaTlJeGZib3RkR0JlUlAyTF93SW9JaTZRTlk1NVNqZk1TdlJRWmVyMlpZVzBKMV9DUUxWS20yckU3UG1pb2RTZWNnZ2RCUmFkYjYtWmM2cmJXQjBRV0w2NNIBjwJBVV95cUxPeWdZUjVwdE5Zb2VwMnZpT3l0bHdzVVJFTVpGNlZ5dXo2Ukd0Sl9ZOFMzdkhIZHN4LXNhT0hWYXR3ZkRnUS0teWJBaVhhbFgxNndTdF9aRmx1aTVXTUtDOHpEc3R2eXFKbU0wS2hMMjc3cWVCeVNIcWFPOVVPb2lWSmMza20tSWJGLXp6a3JNelU5cHFMdnFiTUdKRjl6aWkwSzA3TU5nNmxJTXVrQTdrZ2VMVlFaTk0wcm5pQ0RPX3NMRDRMOXg2ZDNXU3FCVXBqWFZVQy1BZElaOU15YUJwa2ZQdTQ4SXpXY1hnN1JSRE5jYWVMSmFXQktXUFJ0U2FqRThFOFVGMDJHaDg0SU9Z</guid></item></channel></rss>