<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>随着危险病毒的传播，世界卫生组织警告疫情威胁： “我们看到历史在重演” - yahoo.com</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/world-health-organization-warns-epidemic-030000069.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Officials with the World Health Organization are &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/world-health-organization-raises-concern-about-spread-mosquito-borne-chikungunya-2025-07-22/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:alerting;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;alerting&lt;/a&gt; the public to a potential revival of epidemic proportions. New reports show the chikungunya virus is spreading outside of its typical distribution, according to Reuters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Chikungunya is a virus that was first &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/chikungunya" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:identified;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;identified&lt;/a&gt; in the United Republic of Tanzania in 1952. Since then, it's emerged across Africa and Asia, particularly in the Indian Ocean region. It's spread by mosquitoes, most commonly by the species &lt;a href="https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/disease-vectors/facts/mosquito-factsheets/aedes-aegypti" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Aedes aegypti;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Aedes aegypti&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/disease-vectors/facts/mosquito-factsheets/aedes-albopictus" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Aedes albopictus;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Aedes albopictus&lt;/a&gt;. Once bitten, an infected person can expect to experience fever and severe joint pain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Right now, an estimated 5.6 billion people across 119 countries are &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/world-health-organization-raises-concern-about-spread-mosquito-borne-chikungunya-2025-07-22/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:at risk;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;at risk&lt;/a&gt; of contracting the virus as it spreads to Europe and other continents, per Reuters. WHO officials are concerned that the pattern is similar to an epidemic of the disease that happened between 2004 and 2005 and impacted nearly half a million people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We are seeing history repeating itself," &lt;a href="https://www.reuters.com/business/healthcare-pharmaceuticals/world-health-organization-raises-concern-about-spread-mosquito-borne-chikungunya-2025-07-22/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:said;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Diana Rojas Alvarez, a medical officer at the WHO, per Reuters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why are mosquito-borne illnesses important?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;According to the WHO, mosquitoes are the &lt;a href="http://newprairiepress.org/cgi/viewcontent.cgi?article=2299&amp;amp;context=jac#:~:text=Funding%20for%20this%20study%20was%20provided%20by,caused%20nearly%20800%2C000%20deaths%20worldwide%20each%20year." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:most common;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;most common&lt;/a&gt; vector of disease. Illnesses such as chikungunya, malaria, and West Nile cause nearly 800,000 deaths each year worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Humans are more likely to be infected where mosquitoes &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mosquitoes/about/where-mosquitoes-live_1.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:thrive;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;thrive&lt;/a&gt; in warm, wet climates. With global temperatures &lt;a href="https://www.climate.gov/news-features/understanding-climate/climate-change-global-temperature" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:on the rise;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;on the rise&lt;/a&gt;, the insect's habitat is expanding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about mosquito-borne illnesses?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There are &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chikungunya/about/index.html#:~:text=There%20are%20currently%20no%20medicines%20to%20treat%20chikungunya" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:no medicines;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;no medicines&lt;/a&gt; currently known to treat chikungunya, though two types of &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chikungunya/vaccines/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:vaccines;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;vaccines&lt;/a&gt; are available in the United States and &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/chikungunya/symptoms-diagnosis-treatment/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:acetaminophen or paracetamol;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;acetaminophen or paracetamol&lt;/a&gt; can alleviate symptoms, per the CDC. With this, as with many mosquito-borne illnesses, prevention is key.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Mosquito-borne illnesses are easily preventable by controlling the insect population and preventing them from breeding. In California, vector district officials are working to sterilize male mosquitoes in an effort to control populations. Scientists in Burkina Faso have developed a mosquito-killing fungus to be introduced to the insects during mating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?recXRbhoAbElbd9sJ" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>yahoo.com</author><pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 03:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNMlVuNEp3ZlFkQk9UdnR6NkZHNWNtZ3UyVURuNEthQkFBNzg0bUVqQjdVXzA0LVBaa2EyRXFHLU1UMnl4YlViakY0aDEyay15T1MzQ0RhWUVONjM1RVlUaWdmYmtJaDdXbmdMYzcya0t1blBKQWZ3UENONkxxOF90dV9fZm9jc0puaXBSTnZxal8yTE04U0E</guid></item><item><title>我从1865年开始尝试世界上第一种减肥饮食......以下是它与当今饮食趋势的比较-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15019255/banting-diet-weight-loss-low-carb.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While low-carb diets are all the rage today, they can be traced back to one man who is said to have birthed the stripped back way of eating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;William Banting, who was a funeral director living in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/london/index.html" id="mol-9c0d0d50-7e06-11f0-89a6-d1f846923610"&gt;London&lt;/a&gt; during the mid-19th century, claimed to have lost 52 pounds and &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-15024677/Hidden-body-fat-skinny-ageing-heart.html"&gt;more than 13 inches&lt;/a&gt; from his waist in one year by adhering to a low-carb diet after three decades of struggling with his weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His diet, however, while low in carbs, included some items that doctors today say to avoid to drop pounds, including &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/alcohol/index.html" id="mol-b6bafb00-7f94-11f0-adb8-e302dd2c8f29"&gt;alcohol&lt;/a&gt; and whipped cream.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;By 1862, at the age of 64, Banting was obese - weighing 202lbs at 5ft 5in with a BMI of 33.6 - so he decided to give up bread, butter, milk, sugar, beer and potatoes and live on mainly animal protein, fruit and non-starchy vegetables. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Astounded by the results, he printed his &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-1b65f430-7e08-11f0-89a6-d1f846923610" class=""&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt; secrets in a booklet titled 'Letter On Corpulence, Addressed To The Public,' which is considered one of the first diet guides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://youtu.be/wvZf9x_G_Jk?si=ifX4LkEdtk5dxY5t"&gt;To see how Banting's &lt;/a&gt;diet holds up in the 21st century, fitness YouTuber William Tennyson decided to give it a go for one day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In a &lt;a target="_self" href="/sciencetech/youtube/index.html" id="mol-6fcbf100-7e08-11f0-89a6-d1f846923610"&gt;YouTube&lt;/a&gt; video, Tennyson starts his day off with Banting's 'Corrective cordial' which comprises a quarter of a gallon of blackberry juice, 1lb of sugar, 0.5oz of grated nutmeg, 0.5oz of powdered cinnamon, 0.25oz of all spice, 0.25oz of cloves and one pint of brandy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One tablespoon of this solution is then diluted in a glass of water. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Commenting on the concoction, which he says 'tastes like Christmas', Tennyson said: 'I think in the 19th century every single day when you wake up you just you could probably die of 14 different diseases. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;While low-carb diets are all the rage today, they can be traced back to one man who is said to have birthed this stripped back way of eating; William Banting. To see how Banting's diet holds up in the 21st century, fitness YouTuber William Tennyson (pictured) decided to give it a go&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So, ideally, you'd want your immune system to just be absolutely 100 percent. I don't think this [drink] would do it. I think this is just an excuse to have sugar and alcohol in the morning. Dare I say an energy drink is healthier.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Moving on to breakfast, Tennyson rustles up a feast in line with what Banting would have eaten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In his diet book, Banting wrote: 'For breakfast, I take four or five ounces of beef, mutton, kidneys, broiled fish, bacon, or cold meat of any kind except pork; a large cup of tea (without milk or sugar), a little biscuit, or one ounce of dry toast.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This restriction of pork stemmed from a belief at the time that it contained starch and saccharine matter, which Banting and his medical adviser, William Harvey, believed contributed to the creation of fat and hindered weight loss. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tennyson said that it is easy to understand why Banting lost weight with such a 'sad looking' breakfast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He said the mutton (aged lamb) tastes 'very earthy' and 'like I'm licking a barn door.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, he noted he was happy to see some protein on his plate to kick off the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies consistently show that increasing your protein intake is one of the most effective strategies for promoting satiety and helping with weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, some carbohydrates such as pastries and pasta, don't keep you full because they are refined or processed, causing rapid blood sugar spikes and crashes that lead to hunger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the 19th century, what is now called lunch was generally known as dinner, and it was the largest meal of the day, served in the early afternoon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In his food diary, Banting said for 'dinner' he enjoyed: 'Five or six ounces of any fish except salmon, any meat except pork, any vegetable except potato, one ounce of dry toast, fruit out of a pudding, any kind of poultry or game, and two or three glasses of good claret, sherry, or Madeira - champagne, port and beer forbidden.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Banting excluded salmon as it is considered one of the fattiest fish. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Mirroring this medley, Tennyson made a meal with cod, Brussel sprouts, and a piece of dry toast. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For dessert, he interpreted 'fruit out of a pudding' as a dish made with strawberries and whipped cream and as a drink, he opts for sherry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While most modern-day diets generally recommend limiting or avoiding alcohol, Tennyson was surprised to see that alcohol is a running theme with the Banting diet, with up to seven glasses permitted per day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The calorie count of wine varies significantly based on its alcohol content and sweetness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, a standard five ounce (150ml) glass of dry table wine typically ranges from 120 to 130 calories, while dessert wines and fortified wines like sherry can have a much higher calorie density. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dry sherries are low in sugar and calories, while sweet or cream sherries are much higher. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As he sipped the sherry, Tennyson mused: 'Dude has the priorities of a seasoned pirate. Or you want to know what? Maybe this was safer to drink than water.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;For breakfast, Tennyson dined on mutton, a biscuit and tea without milk and sugar&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;William Banting, who was an funeral director living in London during the mid-19th century, claimed to have lost 52 pounds by adhering to a low-carb diet. Astounded by the results, he printed his weight loss secrets in a booklet titled Letter On Corpulence&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;After his midday meal, Tennyson went for a 'gentle walk' before returning home for  'tea' which comprised 'two or three ounces of fruit, a rusk (a light, dry biscuit) or two, and a cup of tea without milk or sugar.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Banting diet was mainly concerned with food intake, with meals every three to four hours, and there is little focus on working out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Considering he ate less calories than he usually would, Tennyson said he was surprised how satisfied felt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For his final meal of the day, 'supper,'  Tennyson opts for chicken in line with Banting's meal plan ('three or four ounces of meat or fish') and this is paired with a 'glass or two' of sherry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The YouTuber said he likes the light protein before bed but the alcohol leaves him feeling a little light headed, as it did so earlier in the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Before bed, Banting recommended a 'tumbler of grog (gin, whiskey, or brandy, without sugar) or a glass or two of claret or sherry.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tennyson opted to have a glass of gin, which made him feel even more woozy. He said: '[Banting] may have lost waist size, but man, that liver. So he says that this [alcohol] attributes to the perfect night's sleep. I mean, yeah, probably because I'm going to be unconscious.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol creates an illusion of restful sleep by initially acting as a sedative, but it disrupts the natural sleep cycle, leading to less REM (Rapid Eye Movement) sleep and more light sleep, causing fragmented rest and frequent awakenings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the end of the day and alcohol aside, the YouTuber said he can see why the Banting diet can be effective when it comes to shedding weight as it is very low carb and it is less than the recommended calorie intake. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He explained: 'Other than the alcohol, I will say it's actually kind of debatable that this diet is better than a lot of current diets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'[This is] because there's just a lot of single ingredient foods. No additives, no chemicals, just the food for what it is, which we need more of in today's day and age. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Tennyson makes a lunch with cod, Brussel sprouts, and a piece of dry toast. For dessert, he interprets 'fruit out of a pudding' as a dish made with strawberries and whipped cream and as a drink, he opts for sherry&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'So, while there's a lot of things that we should stay away from today, there's a lot of things that we should probably bring back and adopt.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tennyson used a food tracking app while on the Banting diet and in one day, it came out to &lt;span&gt;1,714 calories, 115g of protein, 31g of fat, &lt;/span&gt;and 68g of carbs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For men, the recommended calorie intake per day is 2,500 calories and when it comes to macronutrients, the USDA recommends consuming 10 percent to 35 percent of calories from protein, 45 percent to 65 percent from carbohydrates, and 20 percent to 35 percent from fat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tennyson said that the Banting diet is so low in carbs, 'most people are going to lose &lt;span&gt;some weight.'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;New York-based nutritionist Laura Cipullo told DailyMail.com that the Banting diet is a precursor to today's keto diet, which involves consuming a very low amount of carbohydrates and replacing them with fat to help your body burn fat for energy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="art-ins mol-factbox floatRHS health" data-version="2" id="mol-5919c3d0-7eb0-11f0-8976-bb5db4900e1d" data-permabox-url="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15019255/banting-diet-weight-loss-low-carb.html"&gt; &lt;h3 class="mol-factbox-title"&gt;THE BANTING DIET &lt;/h3&gt; &lt;div class="ins cleared mol-factbox-body"&gt;&lt;ul class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;For dinner, five or six ounces of any fish except salmon, any meat except pork, any vegetable except potato, one ounce of dry toast, fruit out of a pudding, any kind of poultry or game, and two or three glasses of good claret, sherry, or Madeira—champagne, port and beer forbidden.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;For tea, two or three ounces of fruit, a rusk or two, and a cup of tea without milk or sugar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;For supper, three or four ounces of meat or fish, similar to dinner, with a glass or two of claret.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;ul class="mol-bullets-with-font"&gt;&lt;li class=""&gt;For nightcap, if required, a tumbler of grog—(gin, whiskey, or brandy, without sugar)—or a glass or two of claret or sherry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;span&gt;She says: '&lt;/span&gt;The Banting or keto diet macronutrient distribution typically ranges from approximately 55 percent to 60 percent fat, 30 percent to 35 percent protein, and five percent to 10 percent carbohydrates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'While you will dehydrate and lose all water related to glycogen stores immediately, you will then start to utilize fat and protein for energy. The goal is to use fat as the primary source.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'One should exercise when attempting a low-carb diet to preserve muscle mass and hypertrophy.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, personal trainer and fitness expert Natalya &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="http://trainer-nyc.com/"&gt;Alexeyenko&lt;/a&gt; says she is not a fan of such restrictive approaches to dieting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This is because from her observations, she believes strict approaches usually bring 'only temporary results, and eventually, most people end up rebounding'. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Revealing her preferred approach, she says: 'What works much better long-term is having a clear understanding of how to manage your calories, protein, fats, and carbs according to your current goals without feeling like you have to cut things out completely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Carbs in particular, play an important role in building and maintaining muscle. With diets that cut them too low, someone might see the number on the scale go down, but in reality they’re often losing muscle instead of fat leading to that “skinny fat” look or simply not having a toned body.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Looking at the future of dieting, the personal trainer thinks there will be 'less focus on rigid plans and more emphasis on personalized nutrition plans built around someone’s lifestyle, preferences, and health needs, instead of strict rules that are hard to follow long-term'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 23:18:48 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOSTJ3Xzg5RFQ3cElLUEJDcmVGRlVmLUpSZkU1cVE2NmtzTk9ldER4SXNGVW1mOHZ1djJBUFJtZWRfS0ZZR0w3UWlCNm5mWkdZY083aGNVQVc1cldrSms0ZEpRcVIzX3VzNk9nazcxUUxna1A2R3lNdUktRVB4SDZSbkJDLS1lc29SaGNoOFZ3RnVFWjZa0gGaAUFVX3lxTFBaanFUd1VPX3RtZFdEZ3hhSTBNaFpXTGhhX0tSRExKclkzbWtDVnhTdUxPXzRINkRUdy1YaDltSmMyVFRERldrb21Hb3UwV1ZQdXV3RjVuZTY4Rk5MWEg1QzJwUkFnQzkwTXI1dmVGWk5SREFVR1lweEdGOV9RdFdzeGdOYlFSa3NWSVVhYVVQcTBLWjh3aGR0S0E</guid></item><item><title>超过40万人的研究将肠道细菌与失眠风险联系起来- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/study-of-over-400000-people-links-gut-bacteria-with-insomnia-risk</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;We're learning more and more about how parts of our bodies are linked &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-remarkable-connection-discovered-between-our-heart-and-brain"&gt;and working together&lt;/a&gt; – and now a new study reveals connections between gut bacteria and the risk of insomnia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research, from scientists in China and the US, suggests that being &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cognitive-shuffling-really-could-help-insomniacs-get-to-sleep"&gt;unable to sleep at night&lt;/a&gt; could be at least partly down to the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-people-in-your-life-are-sharing-their-gut-microbes-with-you"&gt;mix of microbes&lt;/a&gt; in our digestive system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, the relationship appears to go both ways: poor sleep can disrupt the gut's microbial balance, creating a feedback loop that could make insomnia harder to shake. With further investigation, we may be able to develop treatments based on these findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/screen-time-in-bed-may-increase-insomnia-odds-study-suggests"&gt;Screen Time In Bed May Increase Insomnia Odds, Study Suggests&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Changes in the composition and function of the gut microbiota are commonly noted in patients with insomnia," &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1136/gpsych-2024-101855"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers in their published paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"However, their causal connections to insomnia phenotypes are far from being clear."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team, led by psychiatrist Shangyun Shi of Nanjing Medical University, used a statistical approach called &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mendelian_randomization"&gt;Mendelian randomization&lt;/a&gt;. This method looks at genetic variations – which are set at birth and unaffected by lifestyle and other factors – to help determine whether one factor is truly influencing another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By analyzing genetic and health data from more than 400,000 people, the researchers found several clear matches. Certain types of bacteria were associated with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/chronic-insomnia-linked-to-ultra-processed-foods-study-finds"&gt;increased insomnia risk&lt;/a&gt;, while others seemed to lower the odds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The strongest evidence pointed to the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clostridium_innocuum"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Clostridium innocuum&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; group of bacteria being linked to a greater risk of insomnia. It's not normally a dangerous kind of bacteria, but it appears to be contributing to sleepless nights for some.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We identified a total of 14 and 8 bacterial taxa, respectively, as positively and negatively correlated with insomnia," &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1136/gpsych-2024-101855"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers. "In addition, there were reverse effects of insomnia correlated with 19 identified microbial taxa."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_171453" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-171453" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/InsomniaBacteria.jpg" alt="Insomnia and bacteria" class="wp-image-171453 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/InsomniaBacteria.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/InsomniaBacteria-477x415.jpg 477w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/InsomniaBacteria-600x522.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-171453" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The team found signs of gut bacteria affecting insomnia, as well as insomnia affecting gut bacteria. (Shi et al., &lt;em&gt;Gen. Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists already know the gut-brain axis works in two directions, and previous research has linked it to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/want-to-lower-your-stress-it-may-just-take-4-weeks-of-eating-these-kinds-of-food"&gt;stress levels&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/parkinsons-gut-bacteria-link-suggests-an-unexpected-simple-treatment"&gt;neurodegenerative diseases&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-identifies-gut-microbe-imbalances-that-predict-autism-and-adhd"&gt;conditions such as autism and ADHD&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers behind this study think that some of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/fasting-style-diet-seems-to-result-in-dynamic-changes-in-human-brains"&gt;the chemical reactions&lt;/a&gt; that certain bacteria start or stop might explain the new findings. We're still at the early stages here, and further studies are going to be required in diverse populations – all the participants in this study were of European descent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's worth noting that gut microbes are only one piece of the insomnia puzzle. Other factors can contribute, from stress at work to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/drinking-and-insomnia-often-go-together-and-this-could-be-why"&gt;drinking habits&lt;/a&gt;. But it appears that gut bacteria are definitely a factor to look at in more detail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eventually, &lt;a href="https://gutscharity.org.uk/advice-and-information/health-and-lifestyle/prebiotics-probiotics/"&gt;prebiotics and probiotics&lt;/a&gt; could be developed to take advantage of this link, and poop transplants might also work as a way of treating insomnia – something that's being looked at &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/transplanting-feces-from-one-person-to-another-could-ease-parkinsons-symptoms"&gt;for multiple conditions&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Overall, the intertwined effects of insomnia on gut microbiota and vice versa represent a complex bidirectional relationship involving immune regulation, inflammatory response, release of neurotransmitters, and other molecular and cellular pathways," &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1136/gpsych-2024-101855"&gt;write&lt;/a&gt; the researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1136/gpsych-2024-101855"&gt;&lt;em&gt;General Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 19:01:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPRTdXWlVhYXI2djVqbU9tbFg0eGdzYjNZWFhaZmhBWUJtOEFoSzNfRm05WlpKNF9tQlNkWnBqZXFidHI5VEh2eVFtUHRMNDMySl9pa0d2V2lEY25NTG9acU5uN2VERFNwYjZlX0FieWprRDE2LTZvVUNlRVNIcDNib0ZjSkUwZmM5d0lacUZvcFVQU2liT0Z1MUt3</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法，减肥时不应避免的5种“坏”饮料- EatingWell</title><link>https://www.eatingwell.com/bad-drinks-you-shouldnt-avoid-for-weight-loss-11796212</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowing what to eat and drink when trying to lose weight can be confusing.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Drinks that you might think are "off-limits" can absolutely fit into a weight loss plan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dairy milk, soy milk and 100% pomegranate juice are a few drinks that can fit into your plan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Figuring out the best beverages for weight loss can be exhausting. With the evolving research and pseudo-science influencers sharing misinformation online, it’s challenging to determine what, if anything, aside from water, can be consumed in a meal plan when weight loss is the goal.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Unfortunately, thinking in absolutes can really derail your goals, especially if you’re someone who enjoys a cup of juice with breakfast or milk in their cereal. Here at&lt;em&gt; EatingWell&lt;/em&gt;, we believe all foods—drinks included—can fit into a healthy, balanced diet. Here are five “bad” drinks that are fine to consume, whether you want to lose weight or not.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-cows-milk"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Cow’s Milk &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Despite the headlines that have deemed milk as “bad” for weight loss, demonizing its (natural) sugar content as the culprit, research has found the opposite to be true. For example, one study suggests that drinking whole milk is associated with lower body weight, BMI and risk of obesity.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Milk has a lot of benefits. The high-quality, bioavailable protein in milk, like leucine, stimulates muscle growth, which can optimize maintaining lean muscle mass,” says sports dietitian &lt;a href="https://sarahkoszyk.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Sarah Koszyk, RDN&lt;/a&gt;. “When people are trying to lose weight, they want to focus on preserving and maintaining their lean muscle mass and, instead, burn the fat."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re looking for a quick protein fix, milk offers just that. A 1-cup serving of skim milk delivers 8 grams of protein for just 90 calories.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Whether you enjoy it on its own for a quick and nutrient-rich snack, in a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/261428/chocolate-peanut-butter-protein-shake/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;protein shake with fruit&lt;/a&gt; for an on-the-go meal, or in a bowl of cereal, there’s no shame in adding dairy milk into your meal plan.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-fortified-soy-milk"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Fortified Soy Milk &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Soy foods, including soy milk, are a great addition to your weight-loss eating plan. One review found that studies suggest that eating plenty of protein can aid in weight loss, and this includes soy protein.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The point being: Soy protein does not stand in the way of weight loss—and may even help.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Soy milk can also help you consume a healthier diet. “Including soy milk in your diet is a fabulous way to up your protein, fiber and vitamin and mineral intake to meet your nutrient needs while losing weight,” says &lt;a href="https://nutritionstarringyou.com/about/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Lauren Harris-Pincus, M.S., RDN&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; For reference, a 1-cup serving of fortified, unsweetened soy milk contains 7 grams of protein and 80 calories.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Plus, it also packs vitamin B12, a nutrient often lacking in plant-based diets.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-naturally-sweetened-coffee"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Naturally Sweetened Coffee &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Flavored coffee tends to get a bad rap. Even when the benefits of caffeine are highlighted for weight loss, the second a sweetener enters the picture, coffee gets canceled.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; But, that doesn't have to be the case. “There are some coffee creamers that are high in ‘empty’ calories from sugars and saturated fats,” says Koszyk. “Coffee isn’t meant to be a high-caloric drink, but drinking black coffee doesn’t always appeal to everyone’s taste buds. Choosing the right coffee creamer that is low in sugar and saturated fat can offer satisfaction while still aligning with one’s weight-loss goals.” 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; With this in mind, it's important to consider what will satisfy your taste buds while fitting into your weight-loss goals. That’s where naturally derived sweeteners, like monk fruit, or no-added-sugar coffee creamers come into play, says Koszyk. Or drizzle a little honey or maple syrup into &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/8069479/is-coffee-good-for-you/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;your coffee&lt;/a&gt; for a truly natural sweet addition.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-100-pomegranate-juice"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; 100% Pomegranate Juice &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; A juice made from 100% fruit juice, like 100% pomegranate juice, can be a wonderful way to add flavor and nutrients to plain water. “Sometimes we need a little extra incentive to increase our water intake,” says Harris-Pincus. You can add a splash of the sweet and slightly tart juice to water or seltzer to encourage drinking more H20 without added sugar, she says.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/7882893/health-benefits-of-pomegranates/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Pomegranate&lt;/a&gt; consumption has also been shown to be beneficial in reducing body weight, blood pressure, blood sugar and other markers of cardiovascular health.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; The fruit is rich in polyphenols, good-for-you antioxidant compounds that help rid your body of free radicals and help decrease inflammation. For a nice twist on iced tea, try our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/249903/hibiscus-pomegranate-iced-tea/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Hibiscus-Pomegranate Iced Tea&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-low-calorie-lower-sugar-sodas"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Low-Calorie, Lower-Sugar Sodas &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Diet soda is a love-it or hate-it&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;item for many,” says Harris-Pincus. However, switching from full-sugar soda to zero-calorie soda can significantly decrease the number of calories you consume in a day and assist with weight loss, she says. While it is probably safe in moderation, the downside is that diet soda doesn’t contain anything beneficial for your health, adds Harris-Pincus.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_35-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; At &lt;em&gt;EatingWell&lt;/em&gt;, we suggest first &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/article/290448/is-drinking-soda-bad-for-weight-loss/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;switching to diet soda&lt;/a&gt; if you typically drink regular, then, over time, phase soda out completely (other than on occasion). Swapping soda for sparkling water and infusing it with fruit and herbs, like we do with our &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/recipe/265887/lemon-cucumber-mint-infused-water/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Lemon, Cucumber &amp;amp; Mint Infused Water&lt;/a&gt;, can help you make the switch less painfully.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_36-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-can-drinks-help-with-weight-loss"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_37-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How Can Drinks Help with Weight Loss? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_38-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Staying well-hydrated may help keep your hunger at bay, while also simultaneously reducing the tendency to mindlessly munch. “Hydration is important because it helps us feel full and can reduce our hunger levels,” says Koszyk. Sometimes we think we are hungry, but in reality, we’re thirsty and dehydrated. “A refreshing drink can fill up the stomach while also sending a signal to the brain that you are full,” she explains.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_39-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_40-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Plus, when you provide your body with the right kind of fluids, you’ll also keep your gastrointestinal tract moving. And good digestive health is something that can lead to successful weight maintenance in the long term.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Of course, most drinks beyond water contain calories, which does matter for weight loss. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_41-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_42-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Still, that doesn’t mean you have to avoid calorie-containing drinks—even when you’re aiming to lose weight. “The right drinks can minimize hunger and increase satiety. Focus on staying hydrated with drinks that work with your needs so you enjoy life while reaching your goals,” says Koszyk.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_43-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-know-if-a-drink-is-good-for-weight-loss"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_44-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How to Know If a Drink Is Good for Weight Loss &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_45-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Love a beverage not listed in the five above? Don’t worry! Here are a few tips Koszyk and Harris-Pincus use to evaluate if a drink can fit within someone’s weight-loss goals:
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_46-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul id="mntl-sc-block_47-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Check the calorie content. &lt;/strong&gt;Be mindful of how many calories the drink provides. Ideally, avoid drinking calories that are worth more than a regular meal. Make sure that a meal-substitute drink has a protein or fiber source so you feel full and satisfied after drinking it.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitor the added sugar content. &lt;/strong&gt;Added sugars come from sweet ingredients like honey, agave, syrups and sugar, and they add calories but don’t fill us up. The American Heart Association recommends limiting daily added sugar intake to 24 grams (6 teaspoons) for women and 36 grams (9 teaspoons) for men.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Evaluate the total nutrition. &lt;/strong&gt;Does the drink have more calories than you’d typically enjoy, but offer nutrients, like dietary fiber, protein and calcium? Then it may be a worthwhile addition to your day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_48-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_49-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-spotlight--1-2-post mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight--1-2-post mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight mntl-block theme-1-2-post"&gt;&lt;h3 id="mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight__heading_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block-universal-spotlight__heading mntl-text-block"&gt;Healthy Drink Recipes for Weight Loss&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_50-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_51-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_52-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Contrary to what you may have heard, you don’t have to just rely on water for your fluid intake if you’re on a weight-loss plan. You can include drinks, like cow’s milk, soy milk, 100% pomegranate juice and others you like. “Any weight-loss plan should be sustainable in the long term. It’s important to include foods and beverages that are enjoyable while allowing you to remain in a caloric deficit,” says Harris-Pincus. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_53-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_54-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Remember, nutrition and your individual needs are unique. Working with a registered dietitian one-on-one is the best way to tailor a &lt;a href="https://www.eatingwell.com/30-day-high-protein-high-fiber-meal-plan-for-weight-loss-8695433" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="internalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;meal plan&lt;/a&gt; that includes the drinks you love that work with your weight-loss goals.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQWFdqQVlzelJzOWdUNkgtQkdSSHNoaDJGa1YtczlYWFg5VWZodmozMEt1aWJwOW1TaDFpYm95NnIxM1NkbW1NQ3BGenlhOEQ3bGUtdjA3d2JXaURldmR4RUcwa25EaWdrWWxlSjZtZzY0LUlEc0QzSUhWNUNrRUxuMEVPZmg4elpI</guid></item><item><title>定义他的破折号：当地人的遗产，他太谦虚了，看不到- KSL.com</title><link>https://www.ksl.com/article/51364706/the-dash-that-defined-him-local-mans-legacy-that-he-was-too-humble-to-see</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="articleContainer"&gt;&lt;p&gt;BLACKFOOT, Idaho – When Scott Hancock died of cancer in May, his wife Colleen knew his story was much more than a date of birth and a date of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If Scott had written his own obituary, it would have been simple: Born November 18, 1946 – Died May 18, 2025," said Colleen. "I asked him, 'What about the dash?' His real story lies in the dash between those two dates."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Hancock never believed he made much of a difference in his life. However, now that he's gone, his wife has made it her mission to let people know that he did make a difference. A huge one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He grew up in Pocatello in the 1950s. At age 4, he went to bed one night a perfectly healthy, happy little boy. The next morning, he woke up unable to walk. His parents rushed him to St. Anthony Hospital, where doctors, fresh from training at a polio clinic back east, recognized the signs immediately. The polio virus had attacked the nerves in his legs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was sent to the Elks Rehabilitation Center for Polio in Boise, where he was fitted with leg braces to help support his weight and returned home. Despite this drastic and unexpected life change, his parents refused to treat him differently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He was the youngest of five children," Colleen Hancock said. "He was expected to do his chores just like his brothers and sister, behave appropriately, and not complain. He believed that made him the man he became — a regular person who just happened to have a disability."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He learned to live resourcefully at a young age. As a little boy, he sold worms, dug for Island Park fishermen, shined his brother's shoes for a nickel, and fixed roller skates for neighborhood kids — all to buy small gifts for his mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back then, Pocatello schools weren't sure how to accommodate students with disabilities, and some people feared they might catch polio by touching someone who had survived it. His mother fought for her son's right to an education. She eventually helped establish the Handicapped School at Idaho State University for Scott and many other students.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He returned to public school in seventh grade, using his crutches and a wheelchair to get around. He went on to graduate from Highland High School's very first graduating class in 1964, later enrolling at Idaho State University as an art major.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Seeing Scott Hancock riding a motorcycle from his wheelchair was a sight that turned heads, but it was something that gave him much pleasure in life. (Photo: Family photo)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was only the beginning of his long list of accomplishments, according to Colleen Hancock. He helped write Idaho's Americans with Disabilities Act legislation and served on multiple state councils for people with disabilities. He directed a senior program in northern Idaho, traveling the state to set up meal services and secure financial help for seniors in need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Later, he shifted gears into construction. For 34 years, he built and remodeled homes across northern Idaho doing much of the work crawling on the ground or from his wheelchair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He found a different way of solving problems. He kept a marble in his pocket while he was building houses. He put the marble on the floor to see if it rolled to determine if the floors were straight," said Colleen. "He never let being in a wheelchair stop him from doing the things he wanted to do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He made friends with kids who had fast cars, hitching rides until he could afford his own vehicle. When he finally bought one, he retrofitted it with hand controls and drove it hunting and fishing in Island Park and throughout southeast Idaho.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of his greatest joys was riding his Honda Gold Wing motorcycle retrofitted so he could drive it from his wheelchair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also wrote extensively, contributing to the Island Park News, Blackfoot Morning News and publishing in Idaho Magazine, American Motorcyclist and Sports Afield.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet he often dismissed his work as insignificant. "There are so many others who do a much better job," he would say. "These are just silly little stories anyone could write."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Author and Island Park News columnist Scott Hancock at a book signing in Island Park with his friend and fellow author EC Stilson of Pocatello. (Photo: Family photo)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was asked many times to write a book about his life, but always said, "Nobody would believe I really did those things."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the Hancocks eventually returned to southeast Idaho, settling in Blackfoot, he reluctantly "retired." That's when he began writing the "little stories" about his life that grew into two volumes of "Tales from the High Lonesome." They were so well received that he began writing a third volume before his death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colleen Hancock has since published Volume 3, now available on Amazon, fulfilling the promise she made to her husband to publish it. She plans to combine his remaining writings into a fourth book, creating one final large collection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott's books are available through Amazon, Barnes &amp;amp; Noble and at Kesler's Market in Blackfoot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But she emphasizes that writing was just a small part of his accomplishments and who he was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"He raised children who were not his own and loved them as if they were. He gave from his heart, made friends everywhere, and loved being with people," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Colleen Hancock, sharing his legacy is about honoring the impact he never fully saw in himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I am not the writer. My husband was. His story is one of resilience. I can only try to express what I saw and learned from him and share some of his dash with you," she concluded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="kt_disclaimer"&gt;
                                    The Key Takeaways for this article were generated with the assistance of large language models and reviewed by our editorial team. The article, itself, is solely human-written.
                                &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KSL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 16:47:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxNc3VydUFvQ2kxeTFfVURXR3RxcUlqZVVRLXpWNW5kMnJSZU5JVW12LWJORlRoRFd0enZDVlZvZHpVNk5URnlFV3BJdWtXZ1ZwaWR2OC1odmlyMnRuakhoRHd4Z0hzb0VjQWliM2lHemVRLXdVcVZINlVDdnFkNzlNTWRsRTRkU05OTkRjWjdROFZtR1NMSThTSWRSQVEzOWlxUW04cXItOWxRSkQ3ZlVn</guid></item><item><title>警告：致命的牛源性超级细菌正在传播给人类-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-15026091/deadly-cattle-borne-superbug-spreading-humans.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A dangerous superbug commonly found in cattle can jump to humans, and researchers warn that infections may soon become untreatable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A team from Penn State University discovered that Salmonella Dublin has become increasingly resistant to antibiotics and is spreading to humans through contaminated beef, milk, or cheese, or through direct &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-15014833/Frankenstein-rabbit-outbreak-threat-humans.html"&gt;contact with infected cows&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers studied 2,150 &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-14891037/FDA-issues-urgent-recall-cucumbers-contamination.html"&gt;Salmonella Dublin&lt;/a&gt; strains from cattle, humans, and the environment and found they were all genetically similar, making it easier for the bacteria to spread across species.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This bacterium typically causes &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-14816895/Urgent-recall-popular-cereal-contain-pieces-METAL.html"&gt;severe illness or death&lt;/a&gt; among cows, but it can also result in serious blood infections among people, especially those in close contact with farm animals. In severe cases, Salmonella Dublin can kill people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Making matters worse, the new study revealed that cattle strains have the highest levels of antibiotic resistance, particularly to drugs meant for treating infections, such as tetracycline and cephalosporins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The increasing antibiotic resistance means that infections may become harder to treat, potentially leading to longer illnesses or more severe symptoms for people and animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If treatments become less effective, human infections could become more dangerous, especially for vulnerable groups like the elderly, children, or those with weak immune systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Study authors added that the US, being a major beef and dairy-producing country, is at an even greater risk of this superbug turning into a widespread health emergency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Cattle are the main carriers of a superbug called Salmonella Dublin, an antibiotic-resistant bacterium (Stock Image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Penn State researchers (pictured) found that the bacteria was present in cows, people, and in both food and farm surfaces&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers used data from two public sources: the National Center for Biotechnology Information Pathogen Isolate Browser and the National Antimicrobial Resistance Monitoring System.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These provided whole-genome sequences of Salmonella Dublin, which allowed the team to examine each strain's genes in detail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They compared 581 samples from cattle, 664 from humans, and 905 from the environment (food and farm areas) to identify patterns in how the bacteria's genes cause severe disease and resist antibiotics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The bacteria from cows, people, and the environment were incredibly similar, with 72 percent of the 2,150 strains differing by only a few DNA changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Although cow strains had the most genes that were resistant to medication, those found contaminating food and surfaces had more DNA mutations linked to quinolone resistance, a drug used to treat humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, the study published in &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://journals.asm.org/doi/10.1128/aem.00689-25"&gt;Applied and Environmental Microbiology&lt;/a&gt; warned that each strain examined had similar genes that make them dangerous, like those helping them stick to cells or invade the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These genes were present in almost every strain in cows, people, or food, meaning the bacteria are consistently harmful no matter where it's found. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Study leader Erika Ganda, an associate professor of food animal microbiomes, said in a &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.psu.edu/news/research/story/bacteria-strains-infecting-cattle-and-humans-us-are-highly-similar"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt;: 'That's important, because it shows that Salmonella Dublin is highly connected across humans, animals and the environment — so efforts to control it need to consider all three.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Contaminated beef can make people sick with Salmonella Dublin, leading to blood infections (Stock Image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Direct contact on farms can also transmit the bacteria from cattle to people (Stock Image)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (&lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://wwwnc.cdc.gov/eid/article/23/9/17-0136_article"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;) has estimated that Salmonella bacteria, including Dublin, cause about 1.2 million illnesses every year in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Salmonella Dublin infections have been particularly severe due to their tendency to cause bloodstream infections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Between 2005 and 2013, a staggering 78 percent of Salmonella Dublin infections required hospitalization, and 4.2 percent resulted in death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The Food and Drug Administration (FDA) treats Salmonella outbreaks, including those involving Dublin, as high-risk health emergencies, often issuing urgent recalls to prevent their spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One incident in 2019 saw 34,222 pounds of contaminated ground beef from Central Valley Meat Company in California recalled to prevent a large-scale outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, 13 people were infected with Salmonella Dublin in the state, and one died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Now that the bacterium has become resistant to antibiotics, the threat to humans is greater than ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The CDC has said that antibiotic-resistant infections, including those from Salmonella, cause over 2.8 million illnesses and more than 35,000 deaths each year in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers emphasized the need for a 'One Health' approach, combining efforts in human, animal, and environmental health to control the superbug's spread and reduce antibiotic use in livestock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:54:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxOT2w1UndYdVBKM1pQc2hYXzd1ZzkzWUVoWElndXBmcUZrSmR3RURNTW16c0xTc0JnNnZ3ZzdkWlM1QXBmMjlNbjAxWFNzWXI5MFpxelBOQlFCclJ3MFRVcjBqanMwWWRPSXY2bE12Ri1wTHd3dnp3Zzk3WlpjbHMzUllhS05nX3dhMXRFQWNRZGFPMWFPUVRtY0M2LWNneGZ2cW9HVHAySjJ1TmfSAbABQVVfeXFMTUQwSVdHNVp3eEhrc1VEcEZzaEExRmNCUTl0aTRua3QwWktyRF9UdkRESlRGRGphNUtFcjE3b2pweXNnem5ZQXl4VmtWWUd0Y2tEal9VX19ncFdOdnMyQTVGbDBVS013dEJBS3QyS2tySHpEUGpielFLaXk4YlJKM0tfYmhTSnphNjlHMWFDMElJdW9sTWdrTmtjcW1KbWpjblBFU0N0bjY3SVBoNXZ6d0g</guid></item><item><title>患有麻疹的乘客可能在新泽西州的火车上暴露了其他人。这是他们旅行的时候。- NJ.com</title><link>https://www.nj.com/news/2025/08/rider-with-measles-may-have-exposed-others-on-nj-trains-heres-when-they-traveled.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N24GEXL2T5B5FHQCL7LXD6OQCM"&gt;A Hudson County resident with measles could have exposed other riders while traveling recently on several NJ Transit trains, the &lt;a href="https://www.nj.gov/health/news/2025/approved/20250822a.shtml" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;state Health Department announced&lt;/a&gt; Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VERJ4RLCLZCQ5BVK7O24LLZ6H4"&gt;Anyone who traveled on these transit line during the dates and times could have been exposed to measles and should monitor for symptoms that could appear as late as Sept. 11, health officials said:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="TP5ZYNNIMFDGNL6XPDVXLOI4E4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;NJ Transit Hudson-Bergen Light Rail, 8th street, Bayonne to Hoboken branch between 9:00 a.m. and 11:00 a.m. and between 6:00 p.m. and 9:00 p.m. on Aug. 13, 14, and 15.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="NU6IEWHH2RD2FJXH2UY4XUKJQ4"&gt;&lt;span&gt;8th street light rail station in Bayonne between 9:00 a.m. and 11:00 a.m. and between 6:00 p.m. and 9:00 p.m. on Aug. 13, 14, and 15.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="2IUQSFFDUJCR3LMCFM3LI3NRZQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;PATH Newark on the World Trade Center Line between 9:15 a.m. and 11:45 a.m. and between 5:45 p.m. and 8:30 p.m. on Aug. 13, 14, and 15.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="6RZYCCPFSVGCHAXULSZ6BWZHJY"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Exchange place station in Jersey City between 9:15 a.m. and 11:45 a.m. and between 5:45 p.m. and 8:30 p.m. on Aug. 13, 14, and 15.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QMQE5WTAIFGNFBJRHHTEUHKRWA"&gt;People at risk include those who have not been fully vaccinated or have not had measles in the past. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NPIUJYROG5FPZF7P3CTLTHFJMA"&gt;There have been seven reported cases of measles so far in 2025, according to the U.S. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="OX7TDYSC5RDMPJJEYHVKXD6JGY"&gt;The person presented with measles following close contact with an out-of-state resident who also had a confirmed case of measles, the New Jersey Health Department said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LMMA4NG7PFG5RDBUJ3K4JAG5TQ"&gt;This case is unrelated to previously reported cases of measles in the state, the department said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZMG2HXBJBJGJPC7HLMXDI46UCM"&gt;The state is not experiencing a measles outbreak, which is defined as three or more related cases &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html#cdc_data_surveillance_section_10-measles-cases-in-2025" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;by the CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VIPGAQY6QJB5LGTQP6BM2DCKAY"&gt;Symptoms of measles include a high fever, cough, runny nose, watery red eyes and a red rash that begins at the hair, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZPY6ROFMDFHDBMZ3AJ3UQODA2I"&gt;The rash usually starts three to five days after the other symptoms. People can spread measles to others from four days before through four days after the rash appears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="4E6EKS3NIVFGFAN3A4YXYGLLPA"&gt;Anyone who suspects an exposure is urged to call their local health department or a health care provider before going to any medical office or emergency department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="LLAG6YFU2ZGHZNVZNHOBG655MU"&gt;Ninety-seven percent of the cases reported in the United States for 2025 are among people who had not received the measles-mumps-rubella vaccine or have unknown vaccination status, according to the state Department of Health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="C5M3NEA5VNGULLIBFKM2AK26FE"&gt;As of Aug. 19, a total of 1,375 confirmed measles cases were reported by 42 states, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HZ5C24FASBHGTFSOYLTB2SMBSY"&gt;That marks the highest annual measles case tally in 33 years, when officials recorded more than 2,100 infections in 1992. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:XSWK2X3KXJBEDOIX3GFSH54XHM" data-fusion-component="XSWK2X3KXJBEDOIX3GFSH54XHM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:XSWK2X3KXJBEDOIX3GFSH54XHM" data-fusion-component="XSWK2X3KXJBEDOIX3GFSH54XHM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="MVPTWRUV7JBBVKV7C7FYTULYVM"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thank you for relying on us to provide the local news you can trust. Please consider supporting &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;NJ.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; with a subscription.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="YAC3TWPVZZAJXCAAP5ZGOSD65Y"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/staff/victoria-gladstone/posts.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;Victoria Gladstone&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; may be reached at vgladstone@njadvancemedia.com. Follow her on Twitter&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://x.com/TorigNJAM" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt; @TorigNJAM&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;. Find&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/NJ.com" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt; NJ.com on Facebook&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:25:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxOSWxyMG5jQVR1QVF3U2NDdFZyeXYzaTVjY2EtemdhQWs4QkEwOUpUbkdIUEd2UGRPclJpU1FraGw0RjJwVWdBQWRqVjhtRW1QR0VRWUhScnRVeDVmMmo3WTMwSy1NM2FkZnpXaXEzejZxZTVfUkZObzdjLWJOSzRPdDNsOWdyeUliY3NyNTdjejNDeEVpQ1BTZFR1T1MwM2FXSUhOSzdmNURUclZnYVRiREZPRG9neGxn0gHMAUFVX3lxTE9kYlFjTkhLMW9vOUR5eUJjTVZ5dUZVY1JHbE54VlNHNmV5R0RKWGgxNjZsYkVZQW9nRVBxdDZDZERoWkpVd1BRRU1VUlJZc2c5dDUxM2hIcU5JajFLMVhkVGdTZFpUTWlrYzFyd1dhbndHMWRJNDRyLUNxekxhdVBSdkRXbTZlTDloaW1SU1pmV29BM05lbE5UVGJTd2dScHd1UzIzMFQ2U1FjLUdJOC1YQXh4cDlPYlZScFpvaHJ5MjlmemxpYmc1am93Vw</guid></item><item><title>潮热？盗汗？绝经期激素治疗的注意事项-美联社新闻</title><link>https://apnews.com/article/hormone-therapy-estrogen-hot-flashes-fda-5b1f29a73553c142f67b1f88b6656428</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="LeaderBoardAd-Mobile "&gt;
                                    
                                        
                                            
                                        
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
                            
                            
                                
                                
                                    &lt;div class="RichTextStoryBody RichTextBody"&gt;
                                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/menopause-dental-dry-mouth-estrogen-414c39e119f4d3f17e9be289c9dd6914"&gt;Menopause&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can usher in a host of &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/menopause-work-benefit-hot-flash-insomnia-support-c91eb76a8802c3dbbd5a0fdef219086c"&gt;disruptive symptoms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; like hot flashes, night sweats and sleep problems. Hormone therapy promises relief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But many women wonder about taking it. That’s because the treatment, subject of a recent expert panel convened by the &lt;span class="LinkEnhancement"&gt;&lt;a class="Link AnClick-LinkEnhancement" data-gtm-enhancement-style="LinkEnhancementA" href="https://apnews.com/article/fda-kennedy-antidepressants-hormones-meetings-experts-afbd525b29ca5e2585b79548a075be75"&gt;Food and Drug Administration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, has long been shrouded in uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was once used routinely. But in 2002, research testing one type was stopped early because of concerns about increased risks of breast cancer and blood clots. Concerns lingered even though later studies showed the benefits of today’s hormone therapies outweigh the risks for many women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“There is still a lot of confusion and a lot of fear,” said Grayson Leverenz, a 50-year-old from Durham, North Carolina, who hesitated to take it but is glad she did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others increasingly are also giving hormone therapy a second look. But experts continue to disagree about how to present the treatment’s pros and cons. The FDA-assembled panel stressed the benefits and suggested health warnings be removed from at least some versions — prompting dozens of experts to call for more input before making any changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors say hormone therapy is a great option for many, but not all, menopausal women — and it’s important to understand the nuanced reality of these treatments before deciding what’s best.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
&lt;h2&gt;How hormone therapy works &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It treats symptoms that can arise when menstruation winds down and ends, causing levels of estrogen and progesterone to drop very low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One type is low-dose vaginal estrogen therapy. Because it’s applied into the vagina, very little circulates in the blood and the risks are far lower. Doctors say it’s a good option for women whose biggest complaint is vaginal dryness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whole-body therapy includes pills, patches, sprays, gels or a vaginal ring that deliver doses of hormones into the bloodstream at levels high enough to have significant effects on symptoms like hot flashes. Such systemic hormones include estrogens and progestogens.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;p&gt;Jennifer Zwink, a nurse in Castle Rock, Colorado, began using an estrogen patch more than a year ago and also has an IUD, which gives her progesterone. The treatment has relieved her hot flashes, improved her sleep and eased her joint pain and bloating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s not like a 100% magic wand,” she said. “But it definitely has made a significant difference.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Menopause Society says hormone therapy can lower the risk of cardiovascular disease if started within 10 years of reaching menopause. It may also reduce the risk of Type 2 diabetes and maintain bone density for longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They might have a drop in their bone density at age 60" instead of at age 50, said Dr. MargEva Morris Cole, an OB-GYN with Duke University.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Hormone therapy carries some risks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Leverenz was first prescribed hormone therapy last year, she kept worrying about the risks she’d heard about — then finally decided: “I can’t live like this anymore.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a combination of three medications, her anxiety lifted, her sleep improved, her joint pain and hot flashes went away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I just feel like myself again,” she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors say many patients hesitate to try hormones, and they try to reassure them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women can use estrogen therapy for seven years – and estrogen-progestogen therapy for three to five years – before breast cancer risk goes up, according to the Menopause Society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group says both estrogen therapy and estrogen-progestogen therapy increase the risk of stroke, which goes away soon after stopping hormones. The risk of blood clots rises if you take hormones by mouth, but may be lower if you use a patch, gel or spray. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A lot of these risks are small,” said Dr. Nanette Santoro, an OB-GYN at the University of Colorado. “And they have to be weighed against the benefit of symptom relief.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Age, medical history and how long women stay on the hormones are also considerations. Many women take them for around five years, and those who’ve had a stroke or certain other conditions may be advised against using them at all.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Debate on changing warnings on hormone medications&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors are divided over whether there should be changes in “black box” health warnings on some hormone treatments. All estrogen drugs still carry boxed warnings about the higher rates of stroke, blood clots and cognitive problems among women taking the medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the physicians at the recent expert panel meeting convened by the FDA prescribe the hormones or are involved with a pharmaceutical industry campaign opposing the warning label. A letter signed by 76 doctors and researchers argues that “removing label warnings without adequate scientific assessment puts patients at risk,” and asked the agency to hold an advisory committee meeting with a public hearing before making any changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the meantime, doctors urge people to be wary of misinformation, like false claims on social media posts that hormones will prevent dementia and ensure a healthy old age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We can’t say that you are going to live a longer, healthier life because you took hormones,” Duke’s Cole said. “I don’t want the pendulum to go so far that people feel that it is promising health for the next 30 to 40 years.”&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;h2&gt;Alternatives to hormone therapy for menopause &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Santoro pointed to a new non-hormonal medication called fezolinetant, marketed as Veozah, for hot flashes and night sweats. The anti-epileptic medication gabapentin, in low doses, can also be used for hot flashes and a moisturizer can improve vaginal dryness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts also say regular exercise and a healthy diet can help manage symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Santoro urged against the “wild proliferation” of supplements claiming to be menopause cure-alls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Everybody is in on the menopause gold rush,” she said. “If it looks too good to be true, it probably is.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="optimizelyHubpeekId" class="optimizelyHubpeekClass"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Associated Press Health and Science Department receives support from the Howard Hughes Medical Institute’s Department of Science Education and the Robert Wood Johnson Foundation. The AP is solely responsible for all content.&lt;/p&gt;
                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                            

                            
                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AP News</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPMHJaNVZWQVFSbHNsSmNETW1HUHhFVGt1cDVGa2R5cXZNazhYbUpsaVd4cHZvWE1FckFUVmkyZmpNMldSd2JXOS1ZSjJ4QV9NYWJ2Wm8xS3FyV0htSlU3d0N5R0RtRVJYR3dUR0tvWXU3dHVxcmVhRTEtcjJEZ244a3ZiQ0Nld042UlhlQkFPemxvWkRaOGEyQmtFcTNvOFBBTEE</guid></item><item><title>纽约市报告2025年首例人类西尼罗河病例-哥谭市</title><link>https://gothamist.com/news/nyc-reports-first-human-west-nile-cases-of-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="streamfield-paragraph rte-text"&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="lraxb"&gt;Two Queens residents contracted West Nile Virus, marking New York City's first human cases in 2025, the health department said Friday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="eh6i9"&gt;Officials also said the virus was also detected in blood donations from two other individuals, one residing in Brooklyn and the other on Staten Island. However, neither donor "met the criteria to be considered a case," once interviewed, health department spokesperson Laura Brahm said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="f5lch"&gt;The health department said it is also investigating reports about further cases in Brooklyn. Brahm said officials expect to have more information on those cases within two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="2v8o4"&gt;Human cases of West Nile virus are the result of individuals being bitten by infected mosquitoes, which are present in the city from May to October. The virus has been detected in mosquitoes &lt;a href="https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/health/health-topics/west-nile-virus-activity.page" rel="noopener" target="_blank"&gt;across all five boroughs&lt;/a&gt; since July, and peak season for the virus is in the months of August and September, according to the department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="bjcfc"&gt;The virus can be fatal in some cases, with pronounced risks for elderly and immunocompromised people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="vam5"&gt;Health officials are warning New Yorkers to use repellent and wear long-sleeved shirts and pants during the dawn and dusk hours. Those with weakened immune systems are being instructed to avoid going outdoors during those time periods altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="6nngk"&gt;“West Nile virus can cause serious illness, especially among people over 55 and with weakened immune systems,” Acting Health Commissioner Dr. Michelle Morse said in a statement from the department.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="30lau"&gt;According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, the mortality rate for people at least 70 years old is about 20%, but just 2% for those under 50. The mortality rate is between 30% and 40% for people with certain blood cancers, recipients of stem cell and solid organ transplants, and people undergoing certain antibody therapies, per the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="f2rk9"&gt;Most people infected with the virus do not develop any symptoms, though some may experience fever, headaches, muscle aches, rash and extreme fatigue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="ffnt2"&gt;One of the two confirmed human cases of West Nile virus this season has already been discharged since being briefly hospitalized, according to the health department. The second individual is currently hospitalized with encephalitis, a form of brain inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="6nupg"&gt;There have been 988 positive mosquito pools across the city since Aug. 22, which is fewer than reported at this time in 2024, according to the health department. It said the city is treating infected mosquito populations with spray operations, aerial, catch basis and ground-based larviciding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="epo4o"&gt;Mosquito control &lt;a href="https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/health/health-topics/west-nile-virus-spray.page" rel="noopener" target="_blank"&gt;sprayings are scheduled&lt;/a&gt; Monday through Wednesday in the Bronx, Manhattan and Staten Island.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="1i667"&gt;The city is urging anyone who suspects they may have contracted the virus to contact their health care provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="26cqo"&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story has been updated with more information.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gothamist</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 13:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE9iSnV6N1VybzF5aHI0dE5OY001c3oxNGdyVlQ3RW5qaFBIOHBwbTVxdWR0SnVlSWQ5NEg1c0RmbXJDZjdtZkpITU9sYmdZc011RGM2UFE4T1RaZGYyR3Q1NzJYMzRhcGptYWlNZ010dWswdVNSX0tQQ1BOc0J4Y1E</guid></item><item><title>新泽西州警告PATH ，轻轨车手可能接触麻疹- Gothamist</title><link>https://gothamist.com/news/nj-warns-path-light-rail-riders-of-possible-measles-exposure</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="streamfield-paragraph rte-text"&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="co3xn"&gt;New Jersey health officials are asking transit riders to be wary of potential exposure to measles after an infected rider rode the rails last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="b4ifv"&gt;The state department of health &lt;a href="https://www.nj.gov/health/news/2025/approved/20250822a.shtml" rel="noopener" target="_blank"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; that a Hudson County resident with a confirmed case of measles rode the PATH train and Light Rail between August 13 and 15. Officials urged riders to make certain they have received their measles, mumps, and rubella (MMR) shots, the department says, and stay vigilant for the symptoms of measles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="bbk6c"&gt;Those symptoms include high fever, cough, red eyes, a runny nose, and a distinctive rash which appears a few days after symptoms begin, usually beginning with red spots at the hairline. But measles symptoms may not appear for 10 or 14 days after exposure .&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="6lj7p"&gt;The person with measles rode during morning and evening commute hours on the three days they used public transit. They took the Hudson-Bergen Light Rail, specifically using the 8th Street station and also rode PATH Newark - World Trade Center Line and spent time at Exchange Place Station in Jersey City.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="61o9"&gt;Though New Jersey does not yet have an official measles outbreak, other states across the country are seeing a recent surge in the virus which can be spread when an infected person coughs, sneezes or talks, releasing tiny droplets into the air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="cremp"&gt;Measles was declared eliminated in the U.S. in 2000, but many Americans began opting out of vaccinations, based on medically dubious claims about their potential side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-block-key="eg6s0"&gt;The Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health reports in 2025 so far there have been&lt;a href="https://publichealth.jhu.edu/ivac/resources/us-measles-tracker" rel="noopener" target="_blank"&gt; 1,378 cases&lt;/a&gt; more than any year since 1992. Measles can cause ear infections, diarrhea and pneumonia, according to the school, and in severe cases can result in brain damage and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gothamist</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 13:42:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQa1laQlJmNVRmaDY3UGRDdjhTMnFEc0l2RFJfRGZUdk9ndXJzQmZZdTZIeElsWC1aSEgxSE5ydDlnaFM2V2NnMmRvc3J4c2R2dy1WWC1YcUJXTUFURWxpZjZXODc5ZUpaMDRrOTVWbHdSajdON3BtR2lLeFZJZlRJOVRQU25wRnJ6UUN2ODBoUEQ</guid></item><item><title>餐厅老板中风后无法恢复功能。新技术改变了一切。- CBS新闻</title><link>https://www.cbsnews.com/news/tommy-fello-cleveland-clinic-vivistim-system-stroke-recovery-technology/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Restaurateur Tommy Fello was driving from his Ohio establishment to his house on Christmas Eve when he started veering off the road. Fello, then 71, had been awake since 4 a.m. local time preparing a holiday buffet for his family. He chalked the disturbance up to a flat tire. Driving slowly and relying on the vehicle's autocorrect feature, he was able to complete his journey home safely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when Fello stepped out of the truck, he couldn't get his balance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I finally realized it wasn't the truck that was veering. It was me that was veering," Fello said. He went indoors and talked to his wife and daughter, who said he looked unwell. About five minutes later, they called 911. Paramedics took him to an area hospital, where he lost all movement in his left arm and leg. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"They were literally just like appendages on me. I could not feel them and could not do anything," Fello said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A clot-busting drug reversed the stroke, but the numbness on the left side of his body, including his face, remained. He struggled to swallow, eat or drink. Physical and occupational therapy produced only minor improvements. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/21/96db0061-c4a4-45d0-90b8-1c781b55967b/thumbnail/620x1110/d367b7d971e358b86c75d5d43ae8be88/screenshot-2025-08-21-at-12-35-53-pm.png#" alt="screenshot-2025-08-21-at-12-35-53-pm.png " srcset="https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/21/96db0061-c4a4-45d0-90b8-1c781b55967b/thumbnail/620x1110/d367b7d971e358b86c75d5d43ae8be88/screenshot-2025-08-21-at-12-35-53-pm.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Tommy Fello walks during a rehabilitative therapy session before his surgery.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Thomas Fello

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Sharon Covey, Fello's occupational therapist and the founder of the Center for Stroke and Hand Recovery, Inc., told CBS News that his arm was essentially stuck in a bent position with his fingers curled when he met her in January 2024. The position and tension in the limb caused Fello constant pain. Working in his restaurant was out of the question.  &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It was very scary. You take for granted so many of the things you do, and even the common, simplest things become like a chore," Fello said. "We mark all these small victories ... Being able to lift up your arm or pick up a cup is a gigantic accomplishment. Those little accomplishments are gigantic to a stroke victim. They encouraged me to keep going on. But there was always a thought in the back of my mind: 'Is this as good as it's going to get?'" &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A "first-of-its-kind technology"  &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One day, another recovering stroke patient suggested Fello look into an implant called the &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/stroke-treatment-vivistim/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Vivistim System&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The &lt;a href="https://www.accessdata.fda.gov/cdrh_docs/pdf21/P210007B.pdf" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;FDA-approved&lt;/a&gt; implant, developed by the medical device company MicroTransponder Inc., uses vagus nerve stimulation during rehabilitation to improve hand and arm function for stroke victims. The vagus nerves are the body's longest cranial nerve, with one on each side of the body, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/body/22279-vagus-nerve" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;according to the Cleveland Clinic&lt;/a&gt;. They regulate the body's involuntary functions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Vivistim Therapy system involves a physical or occupational therapist sending wireless signals to the device. That signal delivers a brief, gentle pulse to the vagus nerve while the stroke patient performs rehabilitative tasks. The stroke patient also does at-home exercises. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Erez Nossek, a neurosurgeon and director of the cranial bypass program at NYU Langone, told CBS News that the vagus nerve stimulation can enhance the brain's ability to rewire itself, known as neuroplasticity. That increased neuroplasticity can result in "greater and faster improvements in motor function for stroke survivors," Nossek said in emailed remarks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/21/e87ef1a2-9a34-4844-b5bf-b648058cc411/thumbnail/620x478/e84b9c383372d652da61e31c2f7fca34/vivistim-paired-vns-system-implant-diagram-callout-labels.png#" alt="vivistim-paired-vns-system-implant-diagram-callout-labels.png " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/21/e87ef1a2-9a34-4844-b5bf-b648058cc411/thumbnail/620x478/e84b9c383372d652da61e31c2f7fca34/vivistim-paired-vns-system-implant-diagram-callout-labels.png 1x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;An illustration from MicroTransponder, Inc. shows the positioning of the Vivistim System device.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                MicroTransponder, Inc.

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"There is no other FDA-approved technology proven to boost neuroplasticity for stroke survivors, creating new connections in the brain, which is theirs to keep, even after the device is no longer in use," Nossek said. "This is (a) first-of-its-kind technology that is redefining what is possible for this patient population." &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc3" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A 108-person trial &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(21)00475-X/abstract" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;published in The Lancet in 2021&lt;/a&gt; found that the device generated two to three times greater improvement in hand and arm function for stroke survivors when compared with just rehab. Stroke patients who have limited hand and arm function six months or more after their stroke and are considered to have "moderate to severe deficits" qualify for the device, the company &lt;a href="https://microtransponder.showpad.com/share/D0VkrCHvDXiqoQf11CiVP" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;said in a fact sheet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Implant aids in recovery&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fello turned to the Cleveland Clinic, where he met cerebrovascular neurosurgeon Dr. Mark Bain. He studies stroke recovery, especially in the cases of patients like Fello, whose rehab progress has plateaued months after the stroke. Bain determined that Fello was a candidate for the Vivistim System. Fello became the first Cleveland Clinic patient to receive the implant on April 29, 2025. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It didn't really scare me to try and do it. I was anxious to see how it worked," Fello said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The device was placed during an hour-long procedure. The vagus nerve sits just below the carotid artery, so Bain and his surgical team made a small incision to place the leads of the implant and hid the scar in a fold of Fello's neck. The key-fob sized implant was placed under Fello's clavicle. Bain said the procedure itself is low-risk, with "less than 1% chance of any complications." Two weeks after the surgery, the device was turned on and Fello returned to his rehabilitative work with Covey. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/22/3ad9dc62-30bb-4504-af89-f482b4fdee94/thumbnail/620x414/2c1024061356dac66ee1d41a4017a683/g0wywdkq.jpg#" alt="g0wywdkq.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/22/3ad9dc62-30bb-4504-af89-f482b4fdee94/thumbnail/620x414/2c1024061356dac66ee1d41a4017a683/g0wywdkq.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/22/3ad9dc62-30bb-4504-af89-f482b4fdee94/thumbnail/1240x828/7b1115fbf8254fd1b8aa021a68c05117/g0wywdkq.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Tommy Fello and Dr. Sharon Covey during a therapy session.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Cleveland Clinic

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Covey said Fello has made huge progress since the device was implanted four months ago. She said he has no pain or tension in the limb, and is beginning to practice using his left arm to carry items. The task is difficult, she said, but isn't "something he could have done before." Fello, now 72, said he's been thrilled by the progress he's made in a short time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I'm very, very happy to do it, very proud to do it, and I'm glad I did it," he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;"The sky's the limit"&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 800,000 people in the United States experience an ischemic stroke each year, Bain said. Vivistim and &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/philadelphia/video/robotic-coach-offer-new-hope-for-stroke-patients-on-the-road-to-recovery/?intcid=CNM-00-10abd1h" target="_blank" rel="nofollow" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;other new technologies&lt;/a&gt; may offer hope to the patients like Fello who struggle to recover with just rehabilitation, Bain said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="mpu-flex-inc4" data-ad="mpu-flex-inc" class="ad-mpu-flex-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["mpu-flex-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I think over the next probably five to 10 years, what you're going to see is an explosion of procedures, devices and things in rehab that will help people, once they've had strokes, to get their lives back," Bain said. "In the future, I think the sky's the limit for what we can expect for stroke recovery." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time of his conversation with CBS News, Bain had given seven other stroke patients a Vivistim implant. Covey said at her practice, there are eight patients with the implant receiving the paired therapy course. MicroTransponder Inc. declined to say how many patients have received the implant, but &lt;a href="https://www.vivistim.com/find-a-provider/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noopener"&gt;shared a map&lt;/a&gt; that shows dozens of surgeons and rehabilitation therapists that provide the therapy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think this is the newest, most effective strategy for people getting their affected limbs back," Covey said. "This is the first real technique that has been available, at least in the last 20 years, for stroke rehab. The theories that we use as practitioners to increase somebody's use of their affected arm are 50 to 75 years old. So this is a new technology that's really going to turn the stroke recovery world upside down." &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
                  
    

    


    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 13:00:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxONUtvWVBVeU9lZFVCd212UjJJbjJGa05BZFBUNERhT2ZjUkQ1ejJTc1NiUG9vWW42ZVk2akE0Mjk3ZW5RQk5hNjdmbE1oX1ZySkhYSDAtbHVDQS1IbHRrTXItb3RfS3pYMEJPbF92WGlMREtmbUZsRG9xZ25hV3Rfa0NrQWRoODdlUVhSWkpqQ0dkYWNTZDF2MWtBZWJFLWRUR3Qw0gGoAUFVX3lxTFBYSXNvSGJPYnNXSVRRRnQ0cFZoOVhCSXhndjZjWmttUFdCaHBvRjNqLXdmVDRhdm1nQWJJTWpkVkkyaWgzQ0FmQ0N6M24tdVlpRDU0UEFqUVUtbmtPTFd4Mm5pRS0ycUZwVGNaZm5rcnI5akR3N2xzZFNwR2QyR1hsanJaa1BET1RHLVFrM2hOZHl3bXdxUEtCOUpkMGpQYkxidmxDMTVvNA</guid></item><item><title>随着年龄的增长，大脑的某些层实际上会变得更强壮- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/some-layers-of-your-brain-actually-get-stronger-as-you-age</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;You might expect that with age comes a natural progression of brain degeneration, but new research shows that this might not be the case for all regions of the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new analysis of mouse and human brains suggests that some parts of the somatosensory cortex – the part of the brain that processes sensory information – aren't just exempt from the thinning found in other parts, they actually grow stronger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This result suggests that the brain's ability to adapt and change continues, even into older age – and that the more you use it, the stronger your brain could be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/study-finds-humans-age-faster-at-2-sharp-peaks-heres-when"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Study Finds Humans Age Faster at 2 Sharp Peaks – Here's When&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Until now, it had not been considered that the primary somatosensory cortex consists of a stack of several extremely thin layers of tissue, each with its own architecture and function. We have now found that these layers age differently," &lt;a href="https://www.dzne.de/en/news/press-releases/press/the-cerebral-cortex-ages-less-than-thought"&gt;explains neuroscientist Esther Kühn&lt;/a&gt; of the German Center for Neurodegenerative Diseases and the Hertie Institute for Clinical Brain Research in Germany.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Although the cerebral cortex becomes thinner overall, some of its layers remain stable or, surprisingly, are even thicker with age. Presumably because they are particularly solicited and thus retain their functionality. We therefore see evidence for neuroplasticity, that is, adaptability, even in senior people."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_171357" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-171357" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/study-schematic.jpg" alt="" class="size-full wp-image-171357" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/study-schematic.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/08/study-schematic-600x333.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-171357" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;An overview of the human portion of the study. (Liu et al., &lt;em&gt;Nat. Neurosci.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neuroplasticity is the brain's ability to adapt to changing circumstances and requirements, reorganizing and rewiring its neural connections to support evolving needs. The assumption is that neuroplasticity peaks when you're young, and gradually declines with age; however, this assumption is &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.18632/aging.101514"&gt;not necessarily supported&lt;/a&gt; by &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.brs.2020.09.004"&gt;robust evidence&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Led by neuroscientists Peng Liu and Juliane Doehler of &lt;span&gt;Otto von Guericke University &lt;/span&gt;Magdeburg in Germany, a team of researchers undertook a study of possible age-related changes in the human cerebral cortex, a folded region of the brain that usually thins with age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It is generally assumed that less brain volume means reduced function," &lt;a href="https://www.dzne.de/en/news/press-releases/press/the-cerebral-cortex-ages-less-than-thought"&gt;Kühn says&lt;/a&gt;. "However, little is known about how exactly the cortex actually ages. This is remarkable, given that many of our daily activities depend on a functioning cortex. That's why we examined the situation with high-resolution brain scans."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers took particularly sensitive  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/magnetic-resonance-imaging" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73063" data-postid="171348" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;MRI&lt;/a&gt; brain scans of 61 adults between the ages of 21 and 80, focusing on a small region at the top of the brain called the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Primary_somatosensory_cortex"&gt;primary somatosensory cortex&lt;/a&gt;, which receives tactile sensory information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that this region is structured a little bit like a stack of crepes: multiple layers of extremely thin, delicate tissue, each with its own role. These layers, the brain scans revealed, present differently depending on a person's age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some are thinner in older people, as expected; but the middle and upper layers were found to be thicker in older people than the same layers seen in younger people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The middle layer is effectively the gateway for &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haptic_perception"&gt;haptic&lt;/a&gt; [touch] stimuli. In the layers above, further processing occurs," &lt;a href="https://www.dzne.de/en/news/press-releases/press/the-cerebral-cortex-ages-less-than-thought"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Kühn. "For example, in the case of sensory stimuli from the hand, the upper layers are particularly involved in the interaction between neighboring fingers. This is important when grasping objects."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lower layers, by contrast, were thinner in the older patients. These are the layers that handle modulation, where tactile signals are amplified or suppressed, depending on context. For example, you don't tend to feel your clothing unless you're thinking about it – similar to the way &lt;a href="https://www.ceenta.com/news-blog/why-cant-i-see-my-nose"&gt;your brain edits out your nose&lt;/a&gt; from your field of vision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As to why different layers thicken or thin with age, the team suggests it could come down to the old adage of "use it or lose it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The middle and upper layers of the cortex are most directly exposed to external stimuli. They are permanently active because we have constant contact with our environment," &lt;a href="https://www.dzne.de/en/news/press-releases/press/the-cerebral-cortex-ages-less-than-thought"&gt;Kühn says&lt;/a&gt;. "The neural circuits in the lower layers are stimulated to a lesser extent, especially in later life. I therefore see our findings as an indication that the brain preserves what is used intensively. That's a feature of neuroplasticity."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, although the lower layers shrink, they may compensate for any cellular degeneration. Their myelin content was found to increase in response to an increase in a certain type of neuron that amplifies the modulation signal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is another sign of adaptability, and the researchers hope that, in future research, they may be able to find a way to promote these adaptive mechanisms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Together, our findings are consistent with the general idea that we can do something good for our brains with appropriate stimulation. I think it's an optimistic notion that we can influence our aging process to a certain degree," &lt;a href="https://www.dzne.de/en/news/press-releases/press/the-cerebral-cortex-ages-less-than-thought"&gt;Kühn says&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s41593-025-02013-1"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 12:01:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNUDlhMk02QVRfVHVoTVpWQWoxYmJ4SG9GbjB3dHA4cmp0WW1BUng3Z1M5alFnaDdGLW5IRlZTNmdhbmxXM1hTWU1qaDhsbDd5OXFCeTBLSHNmMy0yRENSREp3SFNuTDJUMkpIajNkRzZtd1FjdURmZmlGc1Y1NlFCSGhVanFtc2R4elIyNUp6cDU</guid></item><item><title>我婆婆告诉我，你可以对孕妇说的最糟糕的事情之一。我是Aghast. - Slate</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOS08yOUx1X3NNVWpvSVVURjJXSkJmMU85Tkd5dE9lTEp6YXIwc2NqN3lLUmNLNnBibjB6a0tuMTVXWUc4dkRCeTZwbFY4cDhDZUZzRzNsRmpXbXVBdWlxTUtLcjk3ZFhZSFZ2MHlzNFB1bEU4ckM4MjgzbnZQV2VTWTV2aGY1N3hjTnlz?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="16" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmemylwhz006urdm6zbklpg4z@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen4gn0l001a3b79lybvs2hz@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="45" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen5drax001m3b79qe5ze9am@published"&gt;My husband and I are expecting our first child in October, and my sister is throwing a baby shower for me in a few weeks. Since my husband’s mother found out, she has made it her personal mission to put a halt to the event.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="118" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen5dsn9001r3b79sdr98tgt@published"&gt;She claims that we are “inviting disaster” by holding it and accepting gifts for our baby before he arrives. I have told her that if she is not comfortable attending, that’s fine, but she doesn’t get to decide for me. Her response has been to tell me to go ahead, but “don’t be surprised when the baby is stillborn.” I’ve had enough. She is really starting to cast a pall over what should be a happy occasion. My husband tells me she’s always been superstitious and to just ignore her. Easy for him to say—he’s not the one who’s pregnant! How can I convince him that he needs to get his mother to keep her opinions to herself?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen5dvaf001w3b79vwtto8es@published"&gt;—Shower Stress&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen5dwjo00213b797h0gdzoj@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Shower,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="61" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen5dy9t00263b79imx4n65h@published"&gt;You can’t. Or, at any rate, I wouldn’t bother, because even if you convinced &lt;em&gt;him&lt;/em&gt;, he’d still have to convince her. (And if his response to you is that you ought to ignore her—presumably that’s what he does—I am pretty sure he knows he won’t be able to convince her. Not to mention that he doesn’t want to be bothered trying.)&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="99" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen5e00e002b3b79lkvjal5n@published"&gt;How about you take the bull by the horns yourself? You’ve already told her where you stand; she’s blown right by that &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; escalated things. Someone who tells you your baby is going to be stillborn is not someone you need to hear from. So stop speaking to her altogether until after the baby is born. I wouldn’t even make a production of it: I’d just say, “Oh, sorry, can’t talk now” whenever she calls—or not pick up the phone when you see it’s her. If she stops in for a visit, you’ll be just on your way out.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="125" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen5e29q002g3b799sfnmmnz@published"&gt;Do not invite her over; do not accept her invitations. If she complains about your freeze-out to her son—and she will—that’s his chance to say something to her, which is what you wanted in the first place. If nothing else, he can explain &lt;em&gt;why&lt;/em&gt; you’re icing her out. That conversation will be good for both of them. Will it change her? Doubtful. But the most important outcome of this is that you won’t have to listen to the dreadful things she has to say anymore. And you can keep this strategy in your back pocket for after the baby is born, if she tries to get under your skin then too. You are under no obligation to put up with her (or anyone’s) bad behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen4he0e001g3b79jud6i9fd@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Michelle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmen30log000q3b79b3kpblbe@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmen30goy000f3b790ps61sqd@published"&gt;My friend’s kids don’t know that they’re adopted. My very good friend, let’s call her Stacy, was married years ago, to a man whose niece had a daughter at 16. My friend and her husband stepped up and took care of the baby most days for 18 months, until the birth mother came to them and announced that she just couldn’t do it anymore. They ended up adopting the baby. A couple years later, the birth mom came to them with the fact that she was pregnant again. Stacy and her husband adopted this baby at birth. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2020/03/adoption-disclosure-teenagers-care-and-feeding.html"&gt;They raised both girls for the next two years before divorcing.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmemylwhz006xrdm6djmq9e7n@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;The latest sex, parenting, and money advice from our columnists delivered to your inbox three times a week.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxOS08yOUx1X3NNVWpvSVVURjJXSkJmMU85Tkd5dE9lTEp6YXIwc2NqN3lLUmNLNnBibjB6a0tuMTVXWUc4dkRCeTZwbFY4cDhDZUZzRzNsRmpXbXVBdWlxTUtLcjk3ZFhZSFZ2MHlzNFB1bEU4ckM4MjgzbnZQV2VTWTV2aGY1N3hjTnlz</guid></item><item><title>50多岁时最常见的性问题（以及如何处理） - HuffPost</title><link>https://www.huffpost.com/entry/sex-after-50-goog_l_68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="entry__content-list js-entry-content js-cet-subunit"&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Living in an ageist culture that equates &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/topic/sex" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="sex" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/topic/sex" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="0"&gt;sex&lt;/a&gt; with youth, you may believe things fizzle out in the bedroom after you hit a certain age. But in many cases, that’s just not true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, 43% of Americans over age 50 say their sex life is “just as or more adventurous” than it was in their younger days, &lt;a href="https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/allthemoms/2019/05/24/why-adults-over-50-have-more-adventurous-sex-as-std-rates-rise-lumen-survey/1197575001/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="according to one 2019 survey" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.usatoday.com/story/life/allthemoms/2019/05/24/why-adults-over-50-have-more-adventurous-sex-as-std-rates-rise-lumen-survey/1197575001/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="1"&gt;according to one 2019 survey&lt;/a&gt;. Another survey from 2021 found that 35% of people in this age group say their &lt;a href="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=Zb4jl9GtVeY&amp;amp;mid=41168&amp;amp;u1=68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495&amp;amp;murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lelo.com%2Fblog%2Fsenior-sex-study%2F" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="sex drive is higher now" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://click.linksynergy.com/deeplink?id=Zb4jl9GtVeY&amp;amp;mid=41168&amp;amp;u1=68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495&amp;amp;murl=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lelo.com%2Fblog%2Fsenior-sex-study%2F" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="2"&gt;sex drive is higher now&lt;/a&gt; than when they were younger. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, our bodies and lives change as we age, which can result in some shifts in the bedroom, too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“It is extremely important to note, however, that while &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;changes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; in sexual feeling and function as we age are normal, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;problems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; are not, though we sometimes assume they are,” clinical sexologist and sexuality educator &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/lawrence-siegel-a9b18810/?src=aff-lilpar&amp;amp;veh=aff_src.aff-lilpar_c.partners_pkw.10078_plc.Skimbit%20Ltd._pcrid.huffpost.com_learning&amp;amp;trk=aff_src.aff-lilpar_c.partners_pkw.10078_plc.Skimbit%20Ltd._pcrid.huffpost.com_learning&amp;amp;clickid=Uu13%3AfUiOxyITQCWPAUhD043UkGRj1UtITt8Uc0&amp;amp;mcid=6851962469594763264&amp;amp;irgwc=1" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Lawrence Siegel" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.linkedin.com/in/lawrence-siegel-a9b18810/?src=aff-lilpar&amp;amp;veh=aff_src.aff-lilpar_c.partners_pkw.10078_plc.Skimbit%20Ltd._pcrid.huffpost.com_learning&amp;amp;trk=aff_src.aff-lilpar_c.partners_pkw.10078_plc.Skimbit%20Ltd._pcrid.huffpost.com_learning&amp;amp;clickid=Uu13%3AfUiOxyITQCWPAUhD043UkGRj1UtITt8Uc0&amp;amp;mcid=6851962469594763264&amp;amp;irgwc=1" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="3"&gt;Lawrence Siegel&lt;/a&gt; told HuffPost. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we get older, we need to establish new norms for ourselves, adjusting our expectations as time passes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A 55-year-old should not be trying to maintain the same level of interest or stamina as a 25-year-old,” Siegel said. “While things seem to work automatically when we’re younger, we have to provide more effort and awareness to them when we get older.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;To that end, we asked Siegel and other sex therapists which bedroom issues people commonly encounter in this phase of life and how to address them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Negative Beliefs About Sexuality And Aging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Tetra Images via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Tetra Images via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Approaching sex as you age with a negative mindset can get in the way of a satisfying bedroom life. &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our mindset around sex as we age has a huge impact on our sex lives. And negative beliefs in this area are a “much bigger problem than most people realize,” said psychotherapist and sex therapist &lt;a href="https://askdoctornan.com/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Nan Wise" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://askdoctornan.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="4"&gt;Nan Wise&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“We need to debunk some of the more pernicious myths and misconceptions about our sexuality as we mature. Yes, hormonal changes can negatively impact us as our bodies adjust to the shifting sands of time, but this is greatly exacerbated by our culture’s hangups about sex in general and, even more so, about sex as people age,” Wise,&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;author of &lt;a href="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07FKB3PWC/ref=dp-kindle-redirect?tag=kelseyborresen-20%26ascsubtag%3D68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" target="_blank" role="link" data-amazon-link="true" data-aps-asin="B07FKB3PWC" data-aps-asc-tag="kelseyborresen-20" data-aps-asc-subtag="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495,-1,-1,d,0,0,hp-fil-am=0,0:0,0,0,0" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="“Why Good Sex Matters,”" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://r.bttn.io?btn_ref=org-677cb81987ed72f9&amp;amp;btn_url=https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07FKB3PWC/ref=dp-kindle-redirect?tag=kelseyborresen-20%26ascsubtag%3D68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495%252C-1%252C-1%252Cd%252C0%252C0%252Chp-fil-am%253D0%252C0%253A0%252C0%252C0%252C0" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="5"&gt;“Why Good Sex Matters,”&lt;/a&gt; told HuffPost. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;People in their 50s have to “get past the societal stigma that they are less sexual due to their age,” said psychologist and sex therapist &lt;a href="https://drshannonchavez.com/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="Shannon Chavez" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://drshannonchavez.com/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="6"&gt;Shannon Chavez&lt;/a&gt;. In her practice, she found that many people in this age group have better sex than when they were younger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They are more clear on what they want and how to express it,” she told HuffPost. “Sex in your 50s is often more connected and comfortable with less performance anxiety and sexual hangups from the past. Most people in this age group are more confident and have had experience to know what they want and can be much more assertive towards a partner.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Vaginal Dryness&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drop in estrogen levels that occurs with menopause can cause vaginal dryness — which, in turn, can impact sexual functioning. It’s estimated that &lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/womens-health/dont-ignore-vaginal-dryness-and-pain" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="about half of " data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.health.harvard.edu/womens-health/dont-ignore-vaginal-dryness-and-pain" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="7"&gt;about half of &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/womens-health/dont-ignore-vaginal-dryness-and-pain" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="post-menopausal women" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.health.harvard.edu/womens-health/dont-ignore-vaginal-dryness-and-pain" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="8"&gt;post-menopausal women&lt;/a&gt; deal with this condition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“This can lead to painful or uncomfortable sexual experiences for some, which is why all women over 50 should &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/best-personal-lube-sex-experts_l_628e815ee4b0cda85db9ba01" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="have a good lube on hand" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="628e815ee4b0cda85db9ba01" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="9"&gt;have a good lube on hand&lt;/a&gt;,” Siegel said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Spending &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/best-foreplay-tips-havent-heard-before_l_60a85464e4b09604b5227711" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="more time on foreplay" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="60a85464e4b09604b5227711" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="10"&gt;more time on foreplay&lt;/a&gt; may also be helpful. Being more aroused can &lt;a href="https://www.prevention.com/sex/a20507070/sex-after-menopause/" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="increase vaginal lubrication" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.prevention.com/sex/a20507070/sex-after-menopause/" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="11"&gt;increase vaginal lubrication&lt;/a&gt;, making sex feel more pleasurable. If vaginal penetration is too painful, other activities, such as oral sex or using sex toys, might feel more enjoyable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s worth noting that many women go through menopause without “any real issues,” Siegel said, “other than a sense of liberation from the chance of getting pregnant.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Erection And Ejaculation Challenges &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;As men age, things change in the erection department — and that’s normal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“They will not have the same kinds of spontaneous or reflexive erections the way they used to,” Siegel said. “And they will find that they may need more and varied stimulation in order to get or maintain an erection. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;In addition, they may also find that their erections are not as hard or robust as they used to be.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having erection trouble from time to time is not unusual. But if you’re unable to develop or sustain an erection most times you try to have sex, you &lt;a href="https://www.urologyhealth.org/urology-a-z/e/erectile-dysfunction-(ed)" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="might be dealing with erectile dysfunction." data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.urologyhealth.org/urology-a-z/e/erectile-dysfunction-(ed)" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="12"&gt;might be dealing with erectile dysfunction.&lt;/a&gt; Speak with your doctor, as this can be a &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/erectile-dysfunction/symptoms-causes/syc-20355776" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-external-link" data-vars-item-name="sign of an underlying health condition" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="https://www.mayoclinic.org/diseases-conditions/erectile-dysfunction/symptoms-causes/syc-20355776" data-vars-target-content-type="url" data-vars-type="web_external_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="13"&gt;sign of an underlying health condition&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, the volume of ejaculate and the force with which it’s released may be “significantly less” than what they’re accustomed to, Siegel said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="cli cli-pullquote"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-pullquote__content"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__quote accent-cli"&gt;“While things seem to work automatically when we’re younger, we have to provide more effort and awareness to them when we get older.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-pullquote__attribution caption-cli"&gt;- Lawrence Siegel, clinical sexologist and sexuality educator&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men are socialized to think their sexual vitality “hinges on the unfailingly consistent performance of their penises,” said Wise, which can be “a recipe for problems as men age.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is also one of the most common issues that impact erectile challenges,” she said. “Even young men experience erectile dysfunction as they become preoccupied with the state of their penises during lovemaking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;To combat this, Siegel said the most important thing is to relieve performance pressure and change the objective of sex in the first place. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“If we approach sexual encounters with the idea that we are simply wanting to share this pleasurable experience, and if ejaculation occurs, great; if it doesn’t, it can still be sharing a great, pleasurable experience,” he said. “Our intimate and erotic experiences can be greatly increased if we look at orgasm less as a goal and more as a nice side effect of sharing pleasure.” &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Lower Sexual Desire &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stress, physical health problems, mental health issues, medication side effects and declining hormone levels can all contribute to &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/what-to-do-when-libidos-dont-match_n_5ba00288e4b013b0977d9e25" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="decreased libido" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="5ba00288e4b013b0977d9e25" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="14"&gt;decreased libido&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prevalent issues for those in their 50s include&lt;span&gt; “dealing with changes in their physical body and energy levels which can lead to low desire,” Chavez said, noting that menopause and other hormonal shifts are common during this time. “The hormonal shifts not only affect physiology and sexual desire but can also impact mental health, including fatigue and changes in mood,” Chavez added.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;She suggested getting a hormone panel to see how to balance your hormones and reduce unwanted symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Most hormonal changes are very manageable with the right support,” she said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Siegel said, “it’s perfectly normal” to have less interest in sex as we age. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For some, hormone-replacement therapy might be appropriate,” he said. &lt;br&gt;“For others, more naturalistic things like yoga, meditation, and supplements can be helpful.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="cli cli-image js-no-inject"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-image__spacer"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__source-wrapper"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-image__credit" aria-label="Image Credit: Marilyn Nieves via Getty Images"&gt;&lt;p class="credit-container"&gt;&lt;span class="credit"&gt;Marilyn Nieves via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="cli-image__caption caption-cli"&gt;Finding ways to reduce stress in your life can improve your libido and your overall well-being. &lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finding ways to alleviate stress may increase your desire for sex and make you happier and healthier overall. For example, Wise recommends daily breathing exercises to “access the healing power of the parasympathetic ‘restorative’ state.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“Most of us spend most of our time in ‘fight-or-flight,’ which is when the body pumps out stress hormones that aren’t meant to be flooding us so consistently,” she said. “This perpetual state of hormonal stress erodes our sense of well-being and can put a kibosh on our sex drives, to boot.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take five minutes once or twice a day to do this practice. First, find a quiet spot to sit and “give yourself permission to be exactly as you are and for the moment to be exactly as it is,” Wise said. This is also known as &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/entry/what-is-radical-acceptance-how-it-helps-pandemic_l_5eda9f83c5b640424ef71891" target="_blank" role="link" class=" js-entry-link cet-internal-link" data-vars-item-name="radical acceptance" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="5eda9f83c5b640424ef71891" data-vars-target-content-type="buzz" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="article_body" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="15"&gt;radical acceptance&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“By giving yourself permission to start from where you are, you can loosen and soften a whole lot of the stress we accumulate when we resist what is,” she said. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then take a long, smooth inhalation through your nose and a long soft exhalation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div id="support-huffpost-entry-support-huffpost-mid-article" class="cli support-huffpost-mid-article primary-cli cli cli-text cli-support-huffpost hidden"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__content-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title default-title"&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--first"&gt;20 Years Of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--second"&gt;Free&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="cli-support-huffpost__title--third"&gt;Journalism&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title contributor-once-variation"&gt;Your Support Fuels Our Mission&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__title contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;Your Support Fuels Our Mission&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message-container"&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message support-huffpost__message--main"&gt;&lt;p&gt;For two decades, HuffPost has been fearless, unflinching, and relentless in pursuit of the truth. Support our mission to keep us around for the next 20 — we can't do this without you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cli-support-huffpost__sub-headline"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-once-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="cli-support-huffpost__message variation contributor-canceled-variation"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We remain committed to providing you with the unflinching, fact-based journalism everyone deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you again for your support along the way. We’re truly grateful for readers like you! Your initial support helped get us here and bolstered our newsroom, which kept us strong during uncertain times. Now as we continue, we need your help more than ever. &lt;a href="https://www.huffpost.com/support" class="cli-support-huffpost__message__link js-entry-link" data-vars-item-name="we're offering an ad-free experience" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="17"&gt;We hope you will join us once again&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a class="cli-support-huffpost__support-button accent-button" href="https://www.huffpost.com/support?utm_campaign=mid-article-web" data-vars-item-name-overwritable="support-huffpost" data-vars-item-name="Support HuffPost" data-vars-item-type="button" data-vars-unit-name="main" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/support" data-vars-target-content-type="feed" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component" data-vars-position-in-subunit="16"&gt;Support HuffPost&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="support-huffpost-login"&gt;Already contributed? &lt;a class="js-entry-link-no-impression" href="https://login.huffpost.com/login?dest=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.huffpost.com%2Fentry%2Fsex-after-50-goog_l_68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495%3Fhp_auth_done%3D1" data-vars-item-name="Log in to hide these messages" data-vars-item-type="text" data-vars-unit-name="68a86f74e4b0ab862cb25495" data-vars-unit-type="buzz_body" data-vars-target-content-id="/login" data-vars-target-content-type="utility" data-vars-type="web_internal_link" data-vars-subunit-name="support-huffpost-mid-article" data-vars-subunit-type="component"&gt;Log in to hide these messages.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“When you make your exhalation longer than the inhalation, your brilliant body shifts your nervous system into the restorative mode, your heart slows down, and your stress hormones decrease,” Wise said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;When stress crops up throughout the day, consider that your cue to slow your breathing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="primary-cli cli cli-text "&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“You may find that this simple practice becomes a wonderful new habit that enhances overall well-being and helps you tune into your lust for life — both in and out of the bedroom,” Wise said. ”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Remember, pleasure isn’t a luxury. It’s a necessity for a healthy mind and body and a life worth living!” &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>HuffPost</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 11:00:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigAFBVV95cUxNWVZRaFg1cVBaR3Z5ZGRDN3loaWxfMFlpckhTWkZuWnlUc3ZPSWR5QjM3R25oaGlPM29HMEpJZEg5b3JKNVlBVlJLbkdGbUR3Yk5JQUNtUXRvUWkzcjViT3pXZ1BNYlFPZzJITXY1ZWswZ2R1OVJSb3ZEYWVsR01QVtIBhgFBVV95cUxONm1vN1F4SWdjMlBPSFp5eXM3M0p3RGZ0M2V0dFA5cWkzVHVFWXoxQjJDM0syM1IxNWNwSVpRTWlpTWNBY01YS0xGUll6UFd0azR0NEl1c0Y0UEFvazRhWWM0aTVWRzM1S0xHc1ZhbmsyaFJ5THFYWVg1WjMwMndsVkFVd0wxdw</guid></item><item><title>根据营养师的说法，吃香蕉以最大限度吸收钾的最佳时间- EatingWell</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiekFVX3lxTE9CZy1FNTJUUFZTQkxnbGd3bnB1bmxxS3luUVFsZFZCaTRqeFhqbU1KYk1tMEViZVdLbjY1Q254MTJMbFE3eUd3NF9IRHlTTVRZdnZwLTZRWk53eEkwZXR0UFpiN213YVVtQjB4V1hOVnB3MXIxTEhSaUFB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key Points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Potassium absorption isn't significantly affected by when you eat a banana.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The body naturally balances potassium levels based on intake and current needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A varied, nutrient-rich diet is more important than banana timing for potassium benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Bananas are a go-to snack for good reason: they’re convenient, tasty and packed with nutrients. There’s no denying that bananas are an excellent source of potassium. A medium-sized banana is loaded with around 420 mg of potassium, which is about 12 to 16 percent of your daily needs (2,600 mg for females and 3,400 mg for males).&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Potassium is a mineral and electrolyte that plays some very important roles in supporting overall health. It helps keep your body hydrated, supports cell and nerve functioning and maintains healthy muscle and heart function, yet most Americans don’t get enough of it each day.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; But if you’re aiming to get the biggest potassium benefit from your banana, does the &lt;em&gt;timing&lt;/em&gt; of when you eat it actually matter? We asked registered dietitians to weigh in—and the answer might surprise you.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-optimal-timing-for-banana-intake"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Optimal Timing for Banana Intake &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Truth be told, there is no single “best time” or “worst time” to eat a banana for maximum potassium intake. This is because timing doesn’t have much of an impact on potassium absorption, as opposed to other nutrients. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; “Our body absorbs potassium passively, like a sponge,” says &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/diane-han-mph-rdn-ld-3351911a5/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Diane Han, M.P.H., RD&lt;/a&gt;. “Once it has absorbed enough or reached an optimal level, absorption becomes limited.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In other words, your body’s pretty good at figuring out what it needs, regardless of when you eat potassium-rich foods. When you eat a banana, your body will figure out what to do that’s best in the moment to maintain a nutritional equilibrium so you don’t experience any negative symptoms, like low blood pressure, dizziness or muscle aches,” says &lt;a href="https://tracynutrition.com/about" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Tracy Lockwood Beckerman, M.S., RD, CDN&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-what-influences-potassium-absorption"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; What Influences Potassium Absorption? &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_18-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Potassium is absorbed in the small intestine, and your body generally does a good job of using what you consume. But certain factors can affect potassium levels—like high sodium intake, some medications, vomiting or diarrhea and underlying health conditions that impact how your body retains or excretes potassium.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Think of potassium levels like a see-saw, Beckerman says. “If you are eating foods that are putting too much potassium into your body, excretion will be high, so levels remain stable,” she says. “If intake is too low, excretion will be low, so it is conserved in the body.”
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The kidneys do much of this balancing act. If your potassium stores are low, your body will hold on to the necessary amount of potassium when you eat potassium-rich foods. But if your potassium levels are appropriate, your body will excrete the excess through the urine.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="3"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The other nutrients you eat with bananas don't have much of an impact on potassium absorption. “Potassium acts alone as an electrolyte that does its own thing, regardless if it’s ingested with other macronutrients like proteins, fat and carbohydrates,” Beckerman says.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-how-to-get-the-most-potassium-from-your-bananas"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; How to Get the Most Potassium from Your Bananas &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Instead of stressing over banana timing, focus on building a nutrient-rich eating pattern. “Eating a variety of whole plant foods supports a balanced diet that promotes heart and overall health, while also helping regulate healthy potassium levels in conjunction with other nutrients,” Han says. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_28-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Plus, bananas aren’t the only potassium heroes. Other potassium-rich foods to include are potatoes, Swiss chard and spinach.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Another tip: keep your sodium in check. Potassium and sodium work together in the body, so maintaining a healthy sodium level can help your body maintain the right balance between sodium and potassium in the body.&lt;span class="ql-inline-citation" data-cite="5"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;span class="heading-toc" id="toc-our-expert-take"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;h2 id="mntl-sc-block_33-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block eatingwell-sc-block-heading mntl-sc-block-heading"&gt; &lt;span class="mntl-sc-block-heading__text"&gt; Our Expert Take &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_34-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If you’re aiming to get the best potassium benefit from eating bananas, the time you choose to eat one does not really matter. Potassium absorption tends to be efficient regardless of timing. Bananas can help support your body’s potassium needs, whether you eat them morning, evening, or mid-day. Rather than stressing over the perfect time to eat a banana for maximum potassium benefits, focus on getting enough potassium-rich foods in your diet.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>EatingWell</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiekFVX3lxTE9CZy1FNTJUUFZTQkxnbGd3bnB1bmxxS3luUVFsZFZCaTRqeFhqbU1KYk1tMEViZVdLbjY1Q254MTJMbFE3eUd3NF9IRHlTTVRZdnZwLTZRWk53eEkwZXR0UFpiN213YVVtQjB4V1hOVnB3MXIxTEhSaUFB</guid></item><item><title>气候变化正在将军团病带到您附近的城镇- WIRED</title><link>https://www.wired.com/story/this-deadly-bacteria-was-once-an-only-in-new-york-problem-not-anymore/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;This story originally&lt;/span&gt; appeared on &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.vox.com/climate/458413/legionnaires-disease-signs-symptoms-cooling-towers-nyc" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.vox.com/climate/458413/legionnaires-disease-signs-symptoms-cooling-towers-nyc"}' href="https://www.vox.com/climate/458413/legionnaires-disease-signs-symptoms-cooling-towers-nyc" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Vox&lt;/a&gt; and is part of the &lt;a href="https://www.climatedesk.org/"&gt;Climate Desk&lt;/a&gt; collaboration.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Air conditioners have been working overtime this hot summer, from those tiny window units to the massive AC towers that serve the tightly packed apartment buildings in major cities. And while they bring the relief of cool air, these contraptions also create the conditions for dangerous bacteria to multiply and spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;One particularly nasty bacteria-borne illness is currently spreading in New York City using those enormous cooling units as its vector: Legionnaire’s disease. The bacterial pneumonia, which usually recurs each summer in the US’s largest city, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/health/health-topics/legionnaires-disease.page" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/health/health-topics/legionnaires-disease.page"}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.nyc.gov/site/doh/health/health-topics/legionnaires-disease.page" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;has sickened&lt;/a&gt; more than 100 people and killed &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://nypost.com/2025/08/19/us-news/fifth-person-dies-in-legionnaires-disease-outbreak-in-harlem-as-cases-rise-to-108/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://nypost.com/2025/08/19/us-news/fifth-person-dies-in-legionnaires-disease-outbreak-in-harlem-as-cases-rise-to-108/"}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://nypost.com/2025/08/19/us-news/fifth-person-dies-in-legionnaires-disease-outbreak-in-harlem-as-cases-rise-to-108/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;five&lt;/a&gt; in a growing outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;If you don’t live in New York City or the Northeast, you may never have heard of Legionnaire’s, but this niche public health threat may not be niche for much longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Climate change is helping to make Legionnaire’s disease both more plentiful in the places where it already exists and creating the potential for it to move to new places where the population may not be accustomed to it. Cities in the Northeast and Midwest, where hotter weather meets older infrastructure, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/php/surveillance/index.html" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/php/surveillance/index.html"}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/php/surveillance/index.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;have reported more cases&lt;/a&gt; in recent years. Recently, &lt;em&gt;Legionella&lt;/em&gt; bacteria was &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cbsnews.com/detroit/news/legionella-bacteria-found-water-system-dearborn-allegria-village/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cbsnews.com/detroit/news/legionella-bacteria-found-water-system-dearborn-allegria-village/"}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cbsnews.com/detroit/news/legionella-bacteria-found-water-system-dearborn-allegria-village/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;discovered&lt;/a&gt; in a nursing home’s water system in Dearborn, Michigan—one of the states, along with &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/health-depts/surv-reporting/2018-19-surv-report-508.pdf" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/health-depts/surv-reporting/2018-19-surv-report-508.pdf"}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/health-depts/surv-reporting/2018-19-surv-report-508.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Ohio, Pennsylvania, Illinois, and Wisconsin&lt;/a&gt;, that have &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.msms.org/About-MSMS/News-Media/michigan-experiencing-increase-in-legionnaires-disease" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.msms.org/About-MSMS/News-Media/michigan-experiencing-increase-in-legionnaires-disease"}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.msms.org/About-MSMS/News-Media/michigan-experiencing-increase-in-legionnaires-disease" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;seen more activity in the past few years&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Anyone can contract Legionnaire’s disease by inhaling tiny drops containing the bacteria, and the symptoms—fever, headache, shortness of breath—appear within days. It can cause a severe lung infection, with &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/hcp/clinical-signs/index.html%23:~:text=Hospitalization%20is%20common.,fatality%20rate%20is%20extremely%20low." class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/hcp/clinical-signs/index.html%23:~:text=Hospitalization%20is%20common.,fatality%20rate%20is%20extremely%20low."}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.cdc.gov/legionella/hcp/clinical-signs/index.html%23:~:text=Hospitalization%20is%20common.,fatality%20rate%20is%20extremely%20low." rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;a death rate of around 10 percent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;While healthier people often experience few symptoms, the more vulnerable—young children, the elderly, pregnant people, and those with compromised immune systems—face serious danger from the illness. Around 5,000 people die every year in the United States from Legionnaire’s disease, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2025/08/06/legionnaires-disease-nyc-outbreak-ac/85531559007/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2025/08/06/legionnaires-disease-nyc-outbreak-ac/85531559007/"}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/nation/2025/08/06/legionnaires-disease-nyc-outbreak-ac/85531559007/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;many of them&lt;/a&gt; living in low-income housing with outdated cooling equipment where the bacteria can more readily grow and spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Legionnaire’s disease is a microcosm of climate change’s impact on low-income communities. As warmer temperatures facilitate the spread of disease, the most socially vulnerable populations are going to pay the steepest price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;The Collision of Legionnaire’s Disease, Climate Change, and Economic Disparities&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Legionnaire’s disease was first &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC358030/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC358030/"}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC358030/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;documented&lt;/a&gt; after an unusually aggressive pneumonia outbreak during an American Legion conference in Philadelphia in 1976. Soon, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention scientists confirmed the cause of the mysterious illness: a previously unknown bacteria that was accordingly named &lt;em&gt;Legionella&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;em&gt;Legionella&lt;/em&gt;, unfortunately, is everywhere—in streams, lakes, and water pipes across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;But usually, it occurs in such low concentrations and is so remote that it doesn’t pose a threat to humans. &lt;em&gt;Usually.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Now, city health officials have found the bacteria in the large cooling tanks that serve massive apartment buildings across New York City, particularly in Harlem. Cooling tanks are ideal places for Legionnaire’s to grow and spread. They’re filled with stagnant, warm water that is more hospitable to bacterial growth. Like an evaporative cooler, the systems convert warm stagnant water into cool air for apartment dwellers. They can spray mists laden with the bacteria into the open air, dispersing it across the surrounding air, where it can enter a person’s lungs when they inhale. According to the &lt;a data-offer-url="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.epa.gov/sites/default/files/2014-08/documents/climate_and_microbial_iaq.pdf" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.epa.gov/sites/default/files/2014-08/documents/climate_and_microbial_iaq.pdf"}' href="https://archive.is/o/eVGir/https://www.epa.gov/sites/default/files/2014-08/documents/climate_and_microbial_iaq.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Environmental Protection Agency&lt;/a&gt;, 80 percent of Legionnaire’s cases are linked to potable water systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQU2xxWmhjSVBOTzdBN0pBa1FNMWx0WU1DSHlTZE5WQWdQcEFmX3kxRkg2V252clVocDZOUi1UUzBOSUxWTEhDQlRCTmJFVzE1SkpxVlZ6TTFmVVRUTUJRRUNxQ3ZDZmZRcHhLeGpLSXhabkl4OGpYVGYyMUEyNEp3cVlnRE02M2hWZUpSb0FpaE1GSHZEWm4xZl9xSUdoeVk</guid></item><item><title>5种可以自然提高维生素D水平的素食-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/5-vegetarian-foods-that-can-naturally-boost-vitamin-d-levels/photostory/123469964.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin D has become something of a quiet obsession in urban households. Doctors flag it during routine check-ups, health apps warn about its deficiency, and pharmacies are stocked with pills and drops promising quick fixes. Yet, step back, and the irony is hard to miss: this is the one vitamin our bodies are perfectly capable of making, provided we get enough sunlight. But modern life doesn’t always allow for it. Between long hours indoors, sunscreen use, pollution, and lifestyle shifts, vitamin D deficiency has become one of the most widespread nutritional gaps of our time. While sunlight remains the gold standard, food can play a critical supporting role. For vegetarians, who don’t have access to fish or other animal-heavy sources, the options are fewer but not absent. Here are some vegetarian-friendly ways to sneak vitamin D onto the plate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2gFBVV95cUxPdFFUODljUDFsbnMzeXE5X1NiOXFhOGQ5a09Bc21wbEZ5V3hmeWdwajFQY1cxVW52UVVxd1J5SldoWWxrNjZlcjd0ODUzMTdtOG13OG9EdnBpQWtKUWhOSGZTRXRpY1FaTDNMdWJ5T3d4c0VodjlsZ0FWdjg1T2NiMjJhc01fWFVGRmlJNXlrQlRrRmYySEZlN21CUXRIUTRtLURVTTY1R2Q5eTlRY2NVT2RzaE1ib0dHc0kwSkFSRy1rZ28zV0huSjFUUTR5cXB1dVhNQ1F1alJlQdIB4gFBVV95cUxQeHdLWWdnOU9zN2NwTkpwNEZTZl9jRlhxOWgtdEtsZkJrajJKLWNUZXFQS3djUU1EX01lR0hlMi1COFA4STBBT2RBOXBzZlNYRWcwRkI0Um1qTGJidFhRbTJ5RUx1amI2c045RkIwbzR6eElBaEowT0ZXUHFXWGcyS2JqWmVnUWcwa0NHWlIzTlYwa0dKR25NUzdJbVZEMExpdG5TNWcta0xXVmZKcGl3d1JQSlcyQVduRFJMZVFxT1JlUFoyVGlTME5NNER1VnZGdGRYV3d1ZTZEZ1BSZk9VSEZn</guid></item><item><title>没有激光的LASIK ？科学家可能已经找到了一种方法- Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPRmtJWW80VmxXdHRGS1p5M2U3SnRNNmVyQVRuNXRFZEczc0JQM0RRNTJ3UkM5STZTUmk4bzlHVzBKN2RXMzZpcG5pSEQ4QlBfS0Jqb05xRlM4ckRlUVVEODMzSDBnakREOGJzNHF4aXB5Y1Vya1NObjBOa3pxRkZyRkJLOGt1S1ZkSm1Z?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none "&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;What if you could fix your damaged eye without having to shoot a laser at it? Scientists have potentially discovered a novel method of repairing the cornea, similar to LASIK, that wouldn’t require a laser or other invasive surgical tool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-4 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Researchers at Occidental College and the University of California, Irvine, created the technique, which aims to temporarily make the cornea malleable. In experiments with rabbit eyeballs, their method appeared to work while also leaving corneal cells alive. More research is needed to vet the procedure, but if all goes well, it could become a preferred alternative to LASIK, the researchers claim.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“There’s a long road between what we’ve done and the clinic. But, if we get there, this technique is widely applicable, vastly cheaper and potentially even reversible,” said lead researcher Michael Hill, a professor of chemistry at Occidental College, in a &lt;a href="https://www.acs.org/pressroom/presspacs/2025/august/an-alternative-to-lasik-without-the-lasers.html"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; from the American Chemical Society.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;h2&gt;Why some people avoid LASIK&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/tests-procedures/lasik-eye-surgery/about/pac-20384774"&gt;LASIK&lt;/a&gt; is routinely used to treat conditions like myopia, farsightedness, or astigmatism. It reshapes the cornea—the transparent, outer layer of the eye that captures and focuses light onto the retina—using a precise cutting laser.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Though generally safe and effective, the surgery does permanently weaken the structural integrity of the cornea. People will also commonly experience side effects like dry eye and visual disturbances like halos; a small few will even &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8319231/"&gt;develop&lt;/a&gt; serious, if rare, complications like chronic nerve pain. Ideally, the team’s method would avoid these risks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;A potentially safer method&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;The technique is called electromechanical reshaping. Some of the authors had previously used it to manipulate other parts of the body that contain collagen and water, such as &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5008912/"&gt;ears&lt;/a&gt;. It works by altering the pH of the tissue via short bursts of electricity, briefly allowing it to be molded as desired. Once the proper pH is restored, the tissue returns to its original rigid state.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;The researchers used the technique on rabbit eyeballs in the lab, some of which were intended to represent myopia in humans. Special contact lenses made from platinum were placed over the extracted eyes. These lenses served as an electrode, providing a base for how the cornea should be correctly reshaped.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Once the researchers lightly zapped the eye, the cornea became flexible and contoured to the shape of the lens. Not only did the cornea fill out as the researchers wanted, but the procedure didn’t seem to kill any corneal cells or otherwise affect the cornea’s stability. A YouTube video describing the team’s approach, from the American Chemical Society, can be &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RUbJWbUt0m0"&gt;seen&lt;/a&gt; below.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p class="not-prose video-container"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;iframe title="Surgery without scalpels | Headline Science" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/RUbJWbUt0m0?feature=oembed" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" allowfullscreen&gt;VIDEO&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The team’s results, &lt;a href="https://acs.digitellinc.com/live/35/session/563514"&gt;presented&lt;/a&gt; this week at the fall conference of the American Chemical Society, are still preliminary. The researchers admit that it will take more research in animals before they can even think about testing their method in humans. Their next planned step is to try out the procedure on living rabbits.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But the potential for the team’s work is certainly there, and it may extend beyond treating myopia. The researchers are also hoping to explore whether electromechanical reshaping can help repair farsightedness, astigmatism, and possibly even some forms of cloudy vision.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, as has been the &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/content/article/odds-winning-nih-grants-plummet-new-funding-policy-and-spending-delays-bite"&gt;case for many scientists&lt;/a&gt; during the second Trump administration, the researchers say their work has been delayed over concerns in securing additional funding.&lt;/p&gt;
              
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:00:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxPRmtJWW80VmxXdHRGS1p5M2U3SnRNNmVyQVRuNXRFZEczc0JQM0RRNTJ3UkM5STZTUmk4bzlHVzBKN2RXMzZpcG5pSEQ4QlBfS0Jqb05xRlM4ckRlUVVEODMzSDBnakREOGJzNHF4aXB5Y1Vya1NObjBOa3pxRkZyRkJLOGt1S1ZkSm1Z</guid></item><item><title>为什么咖啡因戒断头痛如此疼痛？ - Live Science</title><link>https://www.livescience.com/health/why-do-caffeine-withdrawal-headaches-hurt-so-much</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p id="19a955fe-676b-4680-ae59-0ca1ec76fecc"&gt;Missing your morning coffee is a headache — literally. Though caffeine is often used to kick-start a day or deliver an energy boost, a sudden drop in consumption can cause painful headaches. And for those trying to kick a coffee habit entirely, the pain can be particularly agonizing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Caffeine withdrawal headaches can be surprisingly intense," &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/provider/nolan-pearson-5036486.html" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.cedars-sinai.org/provider/nolan-pearson-5036486.html" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Nolan Pearson&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a neurologist and headache specialist at Cedars-Sinai Medical Center in Los Angeles, told Live Science. "It can trigger a migraine-type headache, so it can be pulsing, pounding, throbbing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="19a955fe-676b-4680-ae59-0ca1ec76fecc-2"&gt;But why is caffeine withdrawal so excruciating? Neurologists still aren't entirely sure, but they have a few theories and some tips on how to treat these nasty headaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mid-article-leaderboard" class="ad-unit sm:hidden block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="8e1f1892-402e-4817-b8d8-98d85bc05a5f"&gt;Caffeine withdrawal headaches occur after a person consumes more than 200 milligrams of caffeine — the amount in about two cups of coffee — per day for more than two weeks and then abruptly stops, according to the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://ichd-3.org/8-headache-attributed-to-a-substance-or-its-withdrawal/8-3-headache-attributed-to-substance-withdrawal/8-3-1-caffeine-withdrawal-headache/" target="_blank" data-url="https://ichd-3.org/8-headache-attributed-to-a-substance-or-its-withdrawal/8-3-headache-attributed-to-substance-withdrawal/8-3-1-caffeine-withdrawal-headache/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;International Classification of Headache Disorders&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (ICHD-3). The headaches usually appear within 24 hours without caffeine, and typically go away within one week or when caffeine is consumed again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why withdrawal headaches are so painful remains somewhat unclear. Because caffeine affects many parts of the body, experts haven't been able to pin down a single overarching cause. But the pain likely comes, in part, from dilated &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/veins-and-arteries" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/veins-and-arteries"&gt;&lt;u&gt;blood vessels&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="f2e9421c-28e6-4477-9f0f-ea482efeb276"&gt;Caffeine constricts blood vessels — which is part of the reason why the drug can also, paradoxically, be used to relieve some types of headaches, according to the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.mayoclinichealthsystem.org/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/does-caffeine-treat-or-trigger-headaches" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.mayoclinichealthsystem.org/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/does-caffeine-treat-or-trigger-headaches" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. When caffeine use stops, those blood vessels swell, causing more blood flow and, therefore, pain. But &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://physiciandirectory.brighamandwomens.org/details/13897/brian-mcgeeney-neurology-boston-jamaica_plain" target="_blank" data-url="https://physiciandirectory.brighamandwomens.org/details/13897/brian-mcgeeney-neurology-boston-jamaica_plain" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dr. Brian McGeeney&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a neurologist and headache specialist at Boston's Brigham and Women's Hospital, said that's just one contributing cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's involved, but it's not the whole story," he told Live Science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/health/food-diet/does-caffeine-help-or-cause-headaches" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/health/food-diet/does-caffeine-help-or-cause-headaches"&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Does caffeine help or cause headaches?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another explanation for caffeine withdrawal headaches has to do with adenosine receptors. The drug blocks adenosine, a building block of RNA, from attaching to receptors scattered across the central nervous system. This causes neurons to fire more quickly and blood vessels to constrict, which, in turn, makes people feel more alert and awake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When someone stops consuming caffeine, the sudden buildup of adenosine in the body can &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-3425/7/3/30" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.mdpi.com/2076-3425/7/3/30" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;contribute to withdrawal headaches&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. This is also why caffeine is commonly used to treat headaches: By blocking adenosine receptors, it prevents blood vessel dilation from the outset. In fact, caffeine can make painkillers like &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/42205-ibuprofen.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/42205-ibuprofen.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;ibuprofen&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/42785-acetaminophen.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/42785-acetaminophen.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;acetaminophen&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; work more efficiently, according to the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.mayoclinichealthsystem.org/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/does-caffeine-treat-or-trigger-headaches#:~:text=Also%2C%20when%20caffeine%20is%20taken,medication%20to%20provide%20faster%20relief." target="_blank" data-url="https://www.mayoclinichealthsystem.org/hometown-health/speaking-of-health/does-caffeine-treat-or-trigger-headaches#:~:text=Also%2C%20when%20caffeine%20is%20taken,medication%20to%20provide%20faster%20relief." referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;Mayo Clinic&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, as Pearson noted, much of caffeine withdrawal is yet to be explained. "We certainly don't know, but these are all reasons why it might be causing headaches," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Caffeine withdrawal often &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0278691521002611" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0278691521002611" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;happens in hospital settings&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; when patients have to quit their coffee habit to undergo a medical procedure. Some studies also show caffeine withdrawal symptoms in people who fast, &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0278691521002611" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0278691521002611" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;such as Muslims observing Ramadan&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"When life is interrupted unpredictably, like you end up in the emergency room or get admitted to hospital, you see a lot of caffeine withdrawal," McGeeney said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="14e124de-9b23-4a64-bee2-5ef125afdd98"&gt;Caffeine is usually &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/wellness-and-prevention/9-reasons-why-the-right-amount-of-coffee-is-good-for-you" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/health/wellness-and-prevention/9-reasons-why-the-right-amount-of-coffee-is-good-for-you" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;safe in moderation&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. But when someone is looking to reduce or eliminate their caffeine intake, experts agree that the best strategy is to cut down gradually. Drink a little less each day, or substitute lower-caffeine alternatives, like tea, to make the transition easier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"If somebody's using caffeine chronically and they want to cut back, I would do it quite gradually," Pearson said. "So no faster than about 25 to 50 milligrams of caffeine reduced per day — that's a quarter to half a cup of coffee."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a headache lasts longer than a week, Pearson recommended seeking medical care, as that time frame suggests the headache may be triggered by something other than caffeine withdrawal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-freeText-Gqdx774KcPGQZTxVgY7G3n-9FCA4TIhP6d0IDjtS129ixg77mOhVGIk" class="slice-container freeText-wrapper freeText-Gqdx774KcPGQZTxVgY7G3n-9FCA4TIhP6d0IDjtS129ixg77mOhVGIk slice-container-freeText"&gt;&lt;div class="info-block"&gt;&lt;p class="infoDisclaimer"&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and is not meant to offer medical advice.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQbHBNblNoQ1hHMk9DV2llWWdZUC1kQmxYbFh5Skg4T2lBeDBUamltT0FCb1g4dElxb01Xcm15eW1zcTJHN2RHenJNYm44Q2M5ZUd4U0dXYTZMdV9WTENxZU1MNUNlcVd0RXgtU0RjYjVfeU5qQ3JxYWVlRW1YUTZBSzIxWlk4YS1JdDBfVw</guid></item><item><title>根据哈佛科学家的说法，这种缺失的营养素可能是阻止阿尔茨海默氏症的关键- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/according-to-harvard-scientists-this-missing-nutrient-may-be-the-key-to-stopping-alzheimers/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content cf entry-content content-spacious"&gt;

		
				
		&lt;figure id="attachment_483370" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-483370" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers.jpg"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-483370" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers-777x477.jpg" alt="Erasing Brain Dementia Alzheimer's" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers-777x477.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers-400x246.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers-768x472.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers-1536x944.jpg 1536w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers-150x92.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers-450x277.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers-1200x737.jpg 1200w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Erasing-Brain-Dementia-Alzheimers.jpg 2000w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-483370" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Harvard researchers report that the brain naturally contains lithium and that its early loss may spark the cascade that becomes Alzheimer’s. In human tissue, lithium levels drop at the earliest stages, and in mice, forming amyloid appears to sequester lithium; a brain-available, amyloid-evading lithium compound restored memory and reversed pathology. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Study finds that lithium loss triggers &lt;span class="glossaryLink" aria-describedby="tt" data-cmtooltip="&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemTitle&amp;gt;Alzheimer’s&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemBody&amp;gt;Alzheimer&amp;amp;#039;s disease is a progressive neurological disorder that primarily affects older adults, leading to memory loss, cognitive decline, and behavioral changes. It is the most common cause of dementia. The disease is characterized by the buildup of amyloid plaques and tau tangles in the brain, which disrupt cell function and communication. There is currently no cure, and treatments focus on managing symptoms and improving quality of life.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;" data-gt-translate-attributes='[{"attribute":"data-cmtooltip", "format":"html"}]' tabindex="0" role="link"&gt;Alzheimer’s&lt;/span&gt;, but a lithium-based compound reverses the disease in mice.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What sets off the earliest chain of events that leads to Alzheimer’s disease? And why do some people who show Alzheimer’s-like brain changes never progress to dementia? These unresolved questions have challenged scientists for decades.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at Harvard Medical School now believe they may have an explanation: a deficiency of lithium in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their study, published on August 6 in Nature, demonstrates for the first time that lithium is naturally present in the brain, where it protects against neurodegeneration and supports the normal functioning of all major brain cell types. The findings — a decade in the making — draw on mouse experiments as well as analyses of human brain tissue and blood samples from people at different stages of cognitive health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_490370" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-490370" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-vs.-Normal-Lithium-Levels.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-490370" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-vs.-Normal-Lithium-Levels-777x398.jpg" alt="Lithium Deficiency vs. Normal Lithium Levels" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-vs.-Normal-Lithium-Levels-777x398.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-vs.-Normal-Lithium-Levels-400x205.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-vs.-Normal-Lithium-Levels-768x393.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-vs.-Normal-Lithium-Levels-150x77.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-vs.-Normal-Lithium-Levels-450x230.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-vs.-Normal-Lithium-Levels.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-490370" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Top row: In a mouse model of Alzheimer’s disease, lithium deficiency (right) dramatically increased amyloid beta deposits in the brain compared with mice that had normal physiological levels of lithium (left). Bottom row: The same was true for the Alzheimer’s neurofibrillary tangle protein tau. Credit: Yankner Lab&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team discovered that loss of lithium in the human brain is among the earliest alterations linked to Alzheimer’s, while in mice, reduced lithium sped up both brain damage and memory decline. They traced this decline to lithium binding with amyloid plaques and reduced absorption in the brain. In follow-up experiments, they showed that a new lithium compound resistant to amyloid capture restored memory in mice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Together, the results bring coherence to decades of patient observations and introduce a new framework for understanding the disease, offering potential paths for early diagnosis, prevention, and treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Filling gaps in Alzheimer’s research&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s disease, which affects an estimated 400 million people worldwide, is marked by a range of brain abnormalities. These include clumps of the protein amyloid beta, tangles of the protein tau, and the loss of a protective protein called REST. Yet none of these features fully account for the disease. Some individuals with such changes show no cognitive impairment, and drugs designed to target amyloid beta often fail to restore memory and provide only limited slowing of decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is also well established that both genetic and environmental influences shape a person’s risk, but researchers have long struggled to explain why people with the same risk factors can experience such different outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new study suggests that lithium may represent a missing link.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_490369" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-490369" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mass-Spectroscopy-of-Human-Brain-Tissue.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-full wp-image-490369" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mass-Spectroscopy-of-Human-Brain-Tissue.jpg" alt="Mass Spectroscopy of Human Brain Tissue" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mass-Spectroscopy-of-Human-Brain-Tissue.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mass-Spectroscopy-of-Human-Brain-Tissue-400x315.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mass-Spectroscopy-of-Human-Brain-Tissue-768x604.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mass-Spectroscopy-of-Human-Brain-Tissue-150x118.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Mass-Spectroscopy-of-Human-Brain-Tissue-450x354.jpg 450w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-490369" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Lithium was the only metal that differed significantly between people with and without mild cognitive impairment, often a precursor to Alzheimer’s disease. Credit: Aron et al, ‘Lithium deficiency and the onset of Alzheimer’s disease’, Nature&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“The idea that lithium deficiency could be a cause of Alzheimer’s disease is new and suggests a different therapeutic approach,” said senior author Bruce Yankner, professor of genetics and neurology in the Blavatnik Institute at HMS, who in the 1990s was the first to demonstrate that amyloid beta is toxic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Yankner, the findings open the possibility that lithium could eventually be used to treat the disease as a whole rather than targeting only one aspect, such as amyloid beta or tau.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Amyloid beta binds lithium&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A key finding from the study is that during the early stages of dementia, amyloid beta begins forming deposits that bind to lithium in both humans and mouse models. This binding reduces lithium’s availability in the brain, lowering its function across all major brain cell types. In mice, the drop in lithium levels triggered changes that mirrored Alzheimer’s disease, including memory impairment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers identified a group of lithium compounds capable of avoiding capture by amyloid beta. Among them, lithium orotate proved the most effective: in mice, it reversed Alzheimer’s-like pathology, protected brain cells from damage, and restored memory function.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While these results must still be validated in humans through clinical trials, they suggest that monitoring lithium levels could help detect Alzheimer’s at an early stage. They also highlight the potential of amyloid-resistant lithium compounds as candidates for treatment or prevention.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_490368" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-490368" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-Thins-Myelin-Sheaths.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-490368" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-Thins-Myelin-Sheaths-777x364.jpg" alt="Lithium Deficiency Thins Myelin Sheaths" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-Thins-Myelin-Sheaths-777x364.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-Thins-Myelin-Sheaths-400x188.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-Thins-Myelin-Sheaths-768x360.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-Thins-Myelin-Sheaths-150x70.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-Thins-Myelin-Sheaths-450x211.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Lithium-Deficiency-Thins-Myelin-Sheaths.jpg 840w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-490368" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Lithium deficiency thinned the myelin that coats neurons (right) compared to normal mice (left). Credit: Yankner Lab&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lithium-based drugs are already prescribed for conditions such as bipolar disorder and major depression, but those therapies require doses high enough to be toxic, particularly in older adults. In contrast, Yankner’s team showed that lithium orotate works at a concentration about one-thousandth of the clinical dose — enough to replicate natural brain lithium levels. Mice given this compound for nearly their entire lifespan showed no signs of toxicity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“You have to be careful about extrapolating from mouse models, and you never know until you try it in a controlled human clinical trial,” Yankner said. “But so far the results are very encouraging.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Lithium depletion is an early sign of Alzheimer’s&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yankner’s interest in lithium began while studying its relationship to REST, a protein known for its neuroprotective role. Determining whether lithium naturally exists in the human brain, and whether its levels shift during the progression of neurodegeneration, required access to brain tissue — something not possible to obtain from living individuals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To address this, the lab partnered with the Rush Memory and Aging Project in Chicago, which maintains a collection of postmortem brain samples donated by thousands of participants spanning the full spectrum of cognitive health and decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This breadth of material was essential. Studying advanced Alzheimer’s is, as Yankner described it, “like looking at a battlefield after a war,” where extensive damage obscures the origins of the disease. In contrast, examining early stages allows researchers to find “important clues before the brain is badly damaged.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Under the leadership of first author Liviu Aron, senior research associate in the Yankner Lab, the team used advanced mass spectroscopy to measure trace levels of about 30 metals in brain and blood samples from individuals who were cognitively healthy, those with mild cognitive impairment, and those with advanced Alzheimer’s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure id="attachment_490367" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-490367" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Comparison-of-Amyloid-and-Tau-in-Treated-Mice.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-490367" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Comparison-of-Amyloid-and-Tau-in-Treated-Mice-777x398.jpg" alt="Comparison of Amyloid and Tau in Treated Mice" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Comparison-of-Amyloid-and-Tau-in-Treated-Mice-777x398.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Comparison-of-Amyloid-and-Tau-in-Treated-Mice-400x205.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Comparison-of-Amyloid-and-Tau-in-Treated-Mice-768x393.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Comparison-of-Amyloid-and-Tau-in-Treated-Mice-150x77.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Comparison-of-Amyloid-and-Tau-in-Treated-Mice-450x230.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Comparison-of-Amyloid-and-Tau-in-Treated-Mice.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-490367" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Treating mice with the amyloid-evading lithium orotate (top row) reduced amyloid beta (left) and tau (right) much more effectively than lithium carbonate (bottom row). Credit: Yankner Lab&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lithium was the only metal that showed clear differences among groups and declined at the earliest stages of memory loss. Healthy donors had higher lithium levels, while those with mild impairment or full Alzheimer’s exhibited substantially reduced levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The team confirmed these results with additional samples from brain banks across the United States.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This observation aligned with earlier population studies that linked higher environmental lithium — such as lithium naturally occurring in drinking water — with lower rates of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crucially, however, the new research went further by directly detecting lithium in the brains of individuals who had never received it as a therapy, establishing a normal physiological range and showing that lithium is vital for brain function.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Lithium turns out to be like other nutrients we get from the environment, such as iron and vitamin C,” Yankner said. “It’s the first time anyone’s shown that lithium exists at a natural level that’s biologically meaningful without giving it as a drug.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then Yankner and colleagues took things a step further. They demonstrated in mice that lithium depletion isn’t merely linked to Alzheimer’s disease — it helps drive it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Loss of lithium causes the range of Alzheimer’s-related changes&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that feeding healthy mice a lithium-restricted diet brought their brain lithium levels down to a level similar to that in patients with Alzheimer’s disease. This appeared to accelerate the aging process, giving rise to brain inflammation, loss of synaptic connections between neurons, and cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In Alzheimer’s mouse models, depleted lithium dramatically accelerated the formation of amyloid-beta plaques and structures that resemble neurofibrillary tangles. Lithium depletion also activated inflammatory cells in the brain called microglia, impairing their ability to degrade amyloid; caused the loss of synapses, axons, and neuron-protecting myelin; and accelerated cognitive decline and memory loss — all hallmarks of Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mouse experiments further revealed that lithium altered the activity of genes known to raise or lower risk of Alzheimer’s, including the most well-known, &lt;em&gt;APOE&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Replenishing lithium by giving the mice lithium orotate in their water reversed the disease-related damage and restored memory function, even in older mice with advanced disease. Notably, maintaining stable lithium levels in early life prevented Alzheimer’s onset — a finding that confirmed that lithium fuels the disease process.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What impresses me the most about lithium is the widespread effect it has on the various manifestations of Alzheimer’s. I really have not seen anything quite like it all my years of working on this disease,” said Yankner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;A promising avenue for Alzheimer’s treatment&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A few limited clinical trials of lithium for Alzheimer’s disease have shown some efficacy, but the lithium compounds they used — such as the clinical standard, lithium carbonate — can be toxic to aging people at the high doses normally used in the clinic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new research explains why: Amyloid beta was sequestering these other lithium compounds before they could work. Yankner and colleagues found lithium orotate by developing a screening platform that searches a library of compounds for those that might bypass amyloid beta. Other researchers can now use the platform to seek additional amyloid-evading lithium compounds that might be even more effective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“One of the most galvanizing findings for us was that there were profound effects at this exquisitely low dose,” Yankner said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If replicated in further studies, the researchers say lithium screening through routine blood tests may one day may offer a way to identify individuals at risk for Alzheimer’s who would benefit from treatment to prevent or delay disease onset.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Studying lithium levels in people who are resistant to Alzheimer’s as they age might help scientists establish a target level that they could help patients maintain to prevent onset of the disease, Yankner said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Since lithium has not yet been shown to be safe or effective in protecting against neurodegeneration in humans, Yankner emphasizes that people should not take lithium compounds on their own. But he expressed cautious optimism that lithium orotate or a similar compound will move forward into clinical trials in the near future and could ultimately change the story of Alzheimer’s treatment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My hope is that lithium will do something more fundamental than anti-amyloid or anti-tau therapies, not just lessening but reversing cognitive decline and improving patients’ lives,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference: “Lithium deficiency and the onset of Alzheimer’s disease” by Liviu Aron, Zhen Kai Ngian, Chenxi Qiu, Jaejoon Choi, Marianna Liang, Derek M. Drake, Sara E. Hamplova, Ella K. Lacey, Perle Roche, Monlan Yuan, Saba S. Hazaveh, Eunjung A. Lee, David A. Bennett and Bruce A. Yankner, 6 August 2025, &lt;i&gt;Nature&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-09335-x"&gt;DOI: 10.1038/s41586-025-09335-x&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This work was supported by the &lt;span class="glossaryLink" aria-describedby="tt" data-cmtooltip="&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemTitle&amp;gt;National Institutes of Health&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemBody&amp;gt;The National Institutes of Health (NIH) is the primary agency of the United States government responsible for biomedical and public health research. Founded in 1887, it is a part of the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services. The NIH conducts its own scientific research through its Intramural Research Program (IRP) and provides major biomedical research funding to non-NIH research facilities through its Extramural Research Program. With 27 different institutes and centers under its umbrella, the NIH covers a broad spectrum of health-related research, including specific diseases, population health, clinical research, and fundamental biological processes. Its mission is to seek fundamental knowledge about the nature and behavior of living systems and the application of that knowledge to enhance health, lengthen life, and reduce illness and disability.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;" data-gt-translate-attributes='[{"attribute":"data-cmtooltip", "format":"html"}]' tabindex="0" role="link"&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/span&gt; (grants R01AG046174, R01AG069042, K01AG051791, DP2AG072437, P30AG10161, P30AG72975, R01AG15819, R01AG17917, U01AG46152, and U01AG61356), the Ludwig Family Foundation, the Glenn Foundation for Medical Research, and the Aging Mind Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Never miss a breakthrough: &lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/newsletter/"&gt;Join the SciTechDaily newsletter.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				
		
		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:47:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuAFBVV95cUxNcF9YUkFTbGVwaXN1VWdlcXB6NXpLVzNJMGVoY21pMFJSTG9DQWxjaWplZVhtLUxWTUdhaTB6VktRWVVlZ0VRY0NWSGs0NjBYTFI4SC1aWWpqTl8zOHBqVFlZcmRtU0VkZGZsUkwxSVE0N18yZmZfbFYtcmltdE9DaHdzb3JKdHVsRGs4d3RiSXZoUU5hRWJuZVJseDJJTU5qbXdoMmZ0U002NmtMUkVFWUtGWkRjZmp4</guid></item><item><title>22岁的法学院毕业生在CT扫描期间发生严重过敏反应后死亡，家人向“充满活力的女孩”致敬-美国太阳报</title><link>https://www.the-sun.com/news/15032445/law-graduate-dies-allergic-reaction-ct-scan/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A YOUNG law graduate has tragically died after suffering a severe allergic reaction following a CT scan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leticia Paul, 22, was undergoing a routine check-up for kidney stones when she reacted to a special dye used in scans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-container-placeholder lazyload" data-name="news" data-value="The US Sun" data-login-link="https://login.the-sun.com" data-isgeneric="true" data-widget-name="newsletter"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="article__media"&gt;&lt;div class="article__media-img-container open-gallery" data-index="1"&gt;&lt;a href="#"&gt;&lt;img alt="Portrait of Letícia Paul." data-credit="Jam Press" data-img="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?strip=all&amp;amp;w=960" data-caption="Leticia Paul passed away during a medical checkup" sizes="(max-width: 375px) 335px, (max-width: 520px) 480px, (max-width: 660px) 620px, 940px" srcset="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=940 940w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=335 335w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=480 480w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=620 620w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=1880 1880w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=670 670w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=960 960w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=1240 1240w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=2820 2820w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=1005 1005w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=1440 1440w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=1860 1860w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=3760 3760w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=1340 1340w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=1920 1920w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?w=2480 2480w" loading="lazy" src="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742687.jpg?strip=all&amp;amp;w=960" role="img"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="article__gallery-count"&gt;&lt;span class="article__gallery-count-value"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="article__media-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="article__media-span"&gt;Leticia Paul passed away during a medical checkup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="article__credit"&gt;Credit: Jam Press&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure class="article__media"&gt;&lt;div class="article__media-img-container open-gallery" data-index="2"&gt;&lt;a href="#"&gt;&lt;img alt="Photo of Letícia Paul, a law graduate who died from an allergic reaction." data-credit="Jam Press" data-img="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?strip=all&amp;amp;w=764" data-caption="The young law graduate reportedly went into anaphylactic shock after receiving a contrast agent" sizes="(max-width: 375px) 335px, (max-width: 520px) 480px, (max-width: 660px) 620px, 940px" srcset="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=940 940w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=335 335w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=480 480w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=620 620w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=1880 1880w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=670 670w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=960 960w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=1240 1240w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=2820 2820w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=1005 1005w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=1440 1440w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=1860 1860w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=3760 3760w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=1340 1340w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=1920 1920w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?w=2480 2480w" loading="lazy" src="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742672.jpg?strip=all&amp;amp;w=764" role="img"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="article__gallery-count"&gt;&lt;span class="article__gallery-count-value"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="article__media-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="article__media-span"&gt;The young law graduate reportedly went into anaphylactic shock after receiving a contrast agent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="article__credit"&gt;Credit: Jam Press&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The young woman suffered a serious reaction after receiving a contrast agent - a special dye used in CT and MRI scans to make organs and tissues more visible on medical images.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;She had a &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/history/"&gt;history&lt;/a&gt; of kidney stones and was undergoing the scan as part of a routine&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;check at the Alto Vale &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/hospital/"&gt;hospital&lt;/a&gt; in Rio do Sul, Brazil&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leticia had a &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/law/"&gt;law&lt;/a&gt; degree and was pursuing postgraduate studies in Law and Real Estate &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/business/"&gt;Business&lt;/a&gt;, according to the national outlet &lt;a href="https://g1.globo.com/sc/santa-catarina/noticia/2025/08/22/jovem-22-anos-morre-reacao-alergica-durante-tomografia-com-contraste-sc.ghtml"&gt;g1&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She was laid to rest on Thursday at Casa Mortuária Jardim Primavera in Rio do Sul before being transported to Crematório Vaticano in Balneário Camboriú, the Mirror reports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aunt Sandra Paul, told&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://g1.globo.com/sc/santa-catarina/" rel="nofollow"&gt;g1&lt;/a&gt;:  "She was a vibrant girl, with a lot of personality. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"She loved law, she was so studious. She dreamed big, and I'm sure she would be a well-known name in the legal world." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hospital said: “We regret this loss and extend our heartfelt sympathies to the &lt;span id="56999c7b-686e-43df-b1b0-0e0f97d0ab4f" class="suggested-link"&gt;family&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We reaffirm our commitment to ethics, transparency, and patient safety, emphasising that all procedures are conducted in accordance with recommended clinical protocols.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iodinated contrast is injected into a vein to make organs and tissues more visible during a CT scan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; It is widely used in medicine and is generally considered safe, but in rare cases it can trigger severe reactions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical studies show that severe reactions to iodinated contrast are very rare, occurring in roughly one in 5,000 to one in 10,000 scans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Healthcare facilities are typically prepared for such cases, but there are situations where even immediate medical care may not be enough. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people experience only mild symptoms, such as warmth, nausea, or itching. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It comes after a &lt;a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/health/33066526/mum-bloating-died-allergic-reaction-ct-scan-kidney-disease/" rel=""&gt;mum suffering from severe bloating died after she had a suspected allergic reaction&lt;/a&gt; to a CT scan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yvonne Graham, 66, went into cardiac arrest minutes after medics at &lt;a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/topic/northampton/"&gt;Northampton&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.the-sun.com/topic/general-hospital/"&gt;General Hospital&lt;/a&gt; injected dye - called contrast medium - ahead of a scan to investigate a &lt;a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/wellness/28954544/foods-puffy-face-bloated-belly-swaps/"&gt;bloated stomach&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two hours later, retired-butcher Yvonne died after suffering a &lt;a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/sport/32078429/cricket-death-cardiac-arrest/"&gt;cardiac arrest&lt;/a&gt;, leaving her family devastated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="article__media"&gt;&lt;div class="article__media-img-container open-gallery" data-index="3"&gt;&lt;a href="#"&gt;&lt;img alt="Hospital Regional Alto Vale in Rio do Sul, Brazil." data-credit="Jam Press" data-img="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?strip=all&amp;amp;w=960" data-caption="Hospital Regional Alto Vale where the young law graduate died" sizes="(max-width: 375px) 335px, (max-width: 520px) 480px, (max-width: 660px) 620px, 940px" srcset="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=940 940w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=335 335w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=480 480w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=620 620w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=1880 1880w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=670 670w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=960 960w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=1240 1240w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=2820 2820w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=1005 1005w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=1440 1440w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=1860 1860w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=3760 3760w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=1340 1340w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=1920 1920w, https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?w=2480 2480w" loading="lazy" src="https://www.the-sun.com/wp-content/uploads/sites/6/2025/08/less-24-hours-later-let-1017742750.jpg?strip=all&amp;amp;w=960" role="img"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="article__gallery-count"&gt;&lt;span class="article__gallery-count-value"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="article__media-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="article__media-span"&gt;Hospital Regional Alto Vale where the young law graduate died&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="article__credit"&gt;Credit: Jam Press&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her daughter Yolanda, 39, believes her mum shouldn't have been given the dye because Yvonne suffered from stage three &lt;a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/tv/32938169/coronation-street-bosses-slammed-kidney-charity-itv/"&gt;kidney disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also thinks her Yvonne would have survived if there had been an &lt;a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/health/32052508/son-mild-nut-allergy-severe-anaphylaxis-epipen/"&gt;EpiPen&lt;/a&gt; in the scan room.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/topic/nhs/"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; website advises patients to tell their hospital if they have kidney or thyroid problems ahead of a scan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The use of contrast dye can be necessary to enhance tests like&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.thesun.co.uk/health/23695656/hospitals-out-of-date-mri-ct-scanners/"&gt;CT scans and MRIs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;, but sometimes they may lead to kidney problems or cause problems in patients who already have kidney disease, according to the&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kidney.org/kidney-topics/contrast-dye-and-kidneys" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener"&gt;National Kidney Foundation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The NHS UK website says: "Complications of a CT scan are rare. Some people can have an allergic reaction to the contrast medium [dye].&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This can cause weakness, sweating and difficulty breathing."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-boxout"&gt;&lt;p class="article-boxout__header t-p-background-color"&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-boxout__headline t-s-border-color"&gt;Rare reactions to contrast dyes&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-boxout__content theme__background-color-rgba-20"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are two rare but serious disorders associated with contrast dyes and the kidneys:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contrast induced nephropathy (CIN)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nephrogenic systemic fibrosis (NSF)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;CIN is a rare disorder and occurs when kidney problems are caused by the use of certain contrast dyes. It can cause a sharp decrease in kidney function over a period of 48 to 72 hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The symptoms can be similar to those of kidney disease, which include feeling more tired, poor appetite, swelling in the feet and ankles, puffiness around the eyes, or dry and itchy skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In many cases, CIN is reversible and people can recover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, in some cases, CIN can lead to more serious kidney problems and possible heart and blood vessel problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In most cases contrast dyes used in tests, such as CT scans and angiograms, have no reported problems, with about 2 per cent of people receiving dyes developing CIN.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the risk for CIN can increase for people with diabetes, a history of heart and blood diseases, and chronic kidney disease (CKD).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NSF is a rare but serious disease affecting the skin and other organs, affecting some patients with advanced CKD after exposure to gadolinium-containing contrast dyes that are used in MRIs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It affects about 4 per cent of patients with advanced CKD. People with acute kidney injury (AKI) are also at higher risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NSF has not been reported in people with mild kidney damage or normal kidney function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NSF can be painful, debilitating, or even fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms and signs of NSF can include burning and itching of the skin, red or dark patches on the skin, joint stiffness, or muscle weakness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease can develop within 24 hours up to around three months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Source: &lt;a href="https://www.kidney.org/kidney-topics/contrast-dye-and-kidneys" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;National Kidney Fo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.kidney.org/kidney-topics/contrast-dye-and-kidneys"&gt;undation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The US Sun</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:42:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxNVEk1a2FVQS04bml2UEtqSmhJWkFpeTE4Nmg4S3BKdm5NV2RKLV8tcUY5NHR3MjV4WGw4VkxSN0F5SGJ6dmNXcUdkdldPdkZ1QUtrRkJia1J6aHVJcHEyV0lDTW0xVjFtb2FGMS1sS01JWTBqd0RmUXpJVmVKU05ZRTVhVEkxSVJnSEE</guid></item><item><title>3个简单的习惯长寿医生，将他的生物年龄扭转了11年发誓-商业内幕</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMipwFBVV95cUxOczhTdExMWEZFYUdrTHhOYmFTT1R5T2VZZ0ticjRHUkRfVWd5RUthcTIwRWZYOUUtOFluU3djVGpuLTk2VzVETzJVVFg0RGRMR1pjWG5lU2xZTDhCY2poNjFXSk5RTEI4N0FFdFR0NndfVTZscHRaUm1UeWEyNk4tUUFJeEQ2emZlaWdidDdOVW1Nd0t2ZkFCUDE5UExQcjRpSGlCZ0VYOA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="post-body-content post-story-body-content" data-component-type="post-body-content" data-load-strategy="exclude" data-track-content="" data-post-type="story" data-track-marfeel="post-body-content"&gt;
            
                &lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/simple-food-rules-stay-in-shape-live-longer-longevity-doctor-2025-7" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Dr. Kurt Hong&lt;/a&gt;, an obesity doctor, nutrition researcher, and professor of medicine and aging, takes leading a healthy lifestyle seriously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, it's working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 52-year-old father of three leads a full life and has no chronic health conditions. He told Business Insider that his most recent "&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/what-is-the-maximum-age-of-humans-115-or-older-2023-3" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;biological age&lt;/a&gt;" tests, taken around 18 months ago, said he was 41, or 11 years younger than his chronological age. There's no consensus on how to define or measure biological age, but Hong used the PhenoAge algorithm, which measures nine biomarkers associated with aging, including &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/anti-inflammatory-foods-to-help-prevent-chronic-inflammation-2023-11" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;inflammation levels&lt;/a&gt; and metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"A lot of the age-related chronic diseases are directly related to what you eat and your weight," he said. "The key is really to be proactive."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong follows a Mediterranean diet, which is packed with fresh produce and is widely considered the healthiest way to eat for a longer life. He also leads an active lifestyle to maintain a healthy weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He shared three daily habits he's established in the hopes of living a long, healthy life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="b833f27f-2f6e-4fef-a00d-9e14d2a05150" data-toc-id="b833f27f-2f6e-4fef-a00d-9e14d2a05150"&gt;Cardio and resistance training&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Hong loves to do his cardio outdoors.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Randy rebo Berton/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;Hong, who is the chief medical officer of Lifeforce, a concierge &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/rich-people-obsessed-longevity-luxury-hotels-iv-drips-mri-scans-2024-10" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;preventive medicine&lt;/a&gt; company based in Los Angeles, does a mixture of aerobic exercise, or cardio, and resistance training each week. "They contribute to different things," he said.&lt;/p&gt;
              
              
              &lt;section class="dad-related-posts-component at-inline related-posts" data-component-type="dad-related-posts" data-delay-third-party-scripts="true" data-size="2" data-min-size="2" data-container-index="in_content_recirc_1" data-included-verticals="health" data-placement="inline" data-track-marfeel="dad-related-posts-inline" data-excluded-verticals="bi-video" data-root-margin="250px 0px" data-track-view='{"event":"module_in_view","element_name":"in_content_recirc","subscription_experience":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"in_content_recirc_1"}'&gt;
                  &lt;p class="content-recommendations-title-container"&gt;
                    &lt;h2 class="content-recommendations-title display-xs ignore-typography"&gt;
                      Related stories
                    &lt;/h2&gt;
                  &lt;/p&gt;
            
                &lt;div class="dad-related-posts-container" data-track-click-shared='{"element_name":"in_content_recirc","product_field":"in_content_recirc_1","click_text":"Read next","event":"tout_click"}'&gt;
                    &lt;div class="related-posts-container"&gt;
                      
                      
                      
                      &lt;article data-component-type="tout" data-load-strategy="exclude" class="tout style-loading as-horizontal as-placeholder with-ungrouped-text" data-post-id="post"&gt;
                       
                          
                            &lt;span class="tout-image"&gt;        &lt;/span&gt;
                        
                      
                      
                          &lt;h3 class="tout-title font-weight-garnett-500"&gt;
                            &lt;span class="tout-title-link"&gt;Business Insider tells the innovative stories you want to know&lt;/span&gt;
                          &lt;/h3&gt;
                      
                      
                      
                      &lt;/article&gt;          
                      
                      
                      &lt;article data-component-type="tout" data-load-strategy="exclude" class="tout style-loading as-horizontal as-placeholder with-ungrouped-text" data-post-id="post"&gt;
                       
                          
                            &lt;span class="tout-image"&gt;        &lt;/span&gt;
                        
                      
                      
                          &lt;h3 class="tout-title font-weight-garnett-500"&gt;
                            &lt;span class="tout-title-link"&gt;Business Insider tells the innovative stories you want to know&lt;/span&gt;
                          &lt;/h3&gt;
                      
                      
                      
                      &lt;/article&gt;        &lt;/div&gt;
                &lt;/div&gt;
              &lt;/section&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;"Aerobic exercise without question really contributes to your cardiovascular fitness and health," he said. Strength training helps &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/stay-fit-maintain-muscle-simple-celebrity-trainer-magnus-lygdback-2025-1" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;build and maintain muscle&lt;/a&gt; and bone density.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For cardio, Hong likes running, hiking, and swimming in the summertime. He makes the most of the SoCal weather and exercises outside as much as possible. "My aerobic stuff I like to do outside the gym," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also has a gym membership and uses the weight machines for 45 minutes a few times a week. "There are some people who will be at the gym for two, three hours. For me, I'm getting in and out of there," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong tells his patients to find a physical activity they enjoy and to start by doing it twice a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His "anything's better than nothing" approach to exercise reflects the findings of a &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/57/15/979" data-track-click='{"click_type":"other","element_name":"body_link","event":"outbound_click"}' rel=" nofollow"&gt;large 2023 study&lt;/a&gt;, published in the British Journal of Medicine Sports. The systematic review looked at self-reported data from more than 30 million people and found that those who exercised an average of 2.5 hours a week had a lower risk of early death, cardiovascular disease, and cancer than their sedentary peers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study found that people who exercised up to 2.5 hours longer than the average gained even more health benefits. But even working out for an hour and 15 minutes — half the recommended time of 2.5 hours — lowered the risk of early death, cardiovascular disease, and cancer, compared with no exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="4ce33b4e-7007-4965-b5ed-8fb74a1593e8" data-toc-id="4ce33b4e-7007-4965-b5ed-8fb74a1593e8"&gt;Vitamin D&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong doesn't believe in taking stacks of buzzy supplements, but said they can be useful for people with certain deficiencies or health conditions. "I only take one," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He takes a &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/longevity-doctor-supplements-every-day-lost-50-pounds-2025-5" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;vitamin D supplement &lt;/a&gt;each day for bone health as he ages and because testing revealed that his levels are low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vitamin D helps the body absorb calcium, which is crucial for bone density, which naturally starts to decline around the time we hit 35. Many biohackers and &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/vitamin-d-and-longevity-anti-aging-2023-9" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;longevity researchers take vitamin D&lt;/a&gt; because of the beneficial effects it can have on bones, the immune system, and on cancer risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="aa9e0d53-7b5b-42ce-a477-18fc96ce3802" data-toc-id="aa9e0d53-7b5b-42ce-a477-18fc96ce3802"&gt;Challenge your brain&lt;/h2&gt;
              &lt;figure class="figure image-figure-image   " data-type="img" data-e2e-name="image-figure-image" data-media-container="image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;
              
              
              
                
              
              &lt;span class="image-source-caption "&gt;
                    &lt;figcaption class="image-caption headline-semibold" data-e2e-name="image-caption"&gt;
                      Hong challenges his brain for at least an hour or two each day.
                      
              &lt;span class="image-source headline-regular" data-e2e-name="image-source" itemprop="creditText"&gt;
              
              Carol Yepes/Getty Images
              
              &lt;/span&gt;
                    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
                  &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figure&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;To keep his mind sharp, for an hour or two each day, Hong makes sure he does something that challenges his brain. "Your brain's like a muscle — if you don't use it, you lose it" he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Often, work will be enough stimulation for him, but on the weekends, for example, he might play a game of chess or checkers with his kids, or read. Screentime doesn't count, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mental stimulation can't prevent the brain from aging, but evidence suggests it can help build resilience against &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.businessinsider.com/facing-early-onset-alzheimers-how-family-copes-with-genetic-fate-2025-2" data-track-click='{"element_name":"body_link","event":"tout_click","index":"bi_value_unassigned","product_field":"bi_value_unassigned"}' rel=""&gt;Alzheimer's disease symptoms&lt;/a&gt; such as forgetfulness. This resilience is known as cognitive reserve, and studies have found that people with larger reserves, which are built through cognitive activity, developed Alzheimer's disease later in life and had fewer symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The most important thing I tell all my patients is age is really a number," Hong said. "Your body may tell you you're 52 years old, but you can behave or you can feel like a 35-year-old. And it can also be the other way around."&lt;/p&gt;
            
            
            &lt;/section&gt;
            
            
            
            
              &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Business Insider</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:37:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxOczhTdExMWEZFYUdrTHhOYmFTT1R5T2VZZ0ticjRHUkRfVWd5RUthcTIwRWZYOUUtOFluU3djVGpuLTk2VzVETzJVVFg0RGRMR1pjWG5lU2xZTDhCY2poNjFXSk5RTEI4N0FFdFR0NndfVTZscHRaUm1UeWEyNk4tUUFJeEQ2emZlaWdidDdOVW1Nd0t2ZkFCUDE5UExQcjRpSGlCZ0VYOA</guid></item><item><title>阻断这种蛋白质可恢复衰老的大脑- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/blocking-this-one-protein-restores-aging-brains/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content cf entry-content content-spacious"&gt;

		
				
		&lt;figure id="attachment_490410" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-490410" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves.jpg"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-490410" src="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves-777x518.jpg" alt="Dementia Mental Health Recovery Tree Head Leaves" srcset="https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves-777x518.jpg 777w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves-400x267.jpg 400w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves-768x512.jpg 768w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves-1536x1024.jpg 1536w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves-150x100.jpg 150w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves-450x300.jpg 450w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves-1200x800.jpg 1200w, https://scitechdaily.com/images/Dementia-Mental-Health-Recovery-Tree-Head-Leaves.jpg 2000w" sizes="(max-width: 777px) 100vw, 777px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-490410" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;A single protein was found to fuel brain aging, and shutting it down reversed memory loss. Credit: Shutterstock&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Researchers at UC San Francisco have uncovered a surprising culprit in brain aging: a protein called FTL1.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;In aging mice, too much of this protein weakened memory and disrupted neural connections. But when scientists blocked FTL1, the mice’s brains regained youthful function, and their memory tests dramatically improved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Aging Hits the Hippocampus Hard&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aging takes a heavy toll on the hippocampus, the part of the brain that drives learning and memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists at UC San Francisco have now pinpointed a single protein, FTL1, that appears to play a central role in this age-related decline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By studying how genes and proteins in the hippocampus change over time in mice, the team found that only one stood out as consistently different between young and old animals: FTL1.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Mimicking Old Age in Young Brains&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Older mice showed higher levels of FTL1, fewer connections between hippocampal neurons, and weaker memory performance. When researchers artificially boosted FTL1 in young mice, their brains and behavior quickly started to resemble those of much older animals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In cell culture experiments, neurons engineered to produce large amounts of FTL1 developed abnormally. Instead of growing complex, branching neurites, they formed only simple, single-armed extensions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Reversing Memory Decline by Lowering FTL1&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When scientists reduced FTL1 in the hippocampus of aged mice, the results flipped. Their neurons made more connections, and the animals significantly improved on memory tests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“It is truly a reversal of impairments,” said Saul Villeda, PhD, associate director of the UCSF Bakar Aging Research Institute and senior author of the paper, which appears in &lt;em&gt;Nature Aging&lt;/em&gt; on August 19. “It’s much more than merely delaying or preventing symptoms.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Metabolism, FTL1, and Hope for Therapies&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In old mice, FTL1 also slowed down metabolism in the cells of the hippocampus. But treating the cells with a compound that stimulates metabolism prevented these effects.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Villeda is optimistic that the work could lead to therapies that block the effects of FTL1 in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We’re seeing more opportunities to alleviate the worst consequences of old age,” he said. “It’s a hopeful time to be working on the biology of aging.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Reference: “Targeting iron-associated protein Ftl1 in the brain of old mice improves age-related cognitive impairment” by Laura Remesal, Juliana Sucharov-Costa, Yuting Wu, Karishma J. B. Pratt, Gregor Bieri, Amber Philp, Mason Phan, Turan Aghayev, Charles W. White III, Elizabeth G. Wheatley, Bende Zou, Brandon R. Desousa, Julien Couthouis, Isha H. Jian, Xinmin S. Xie, Yi Lu, Jason C. Maynard, Alma L. Burlingame and Saul A. Villeda, 19 August 2025, &lt;i&gt;Nature Aging&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43587-025-00940-z"&gt;DOI: 10.1038/s43587-025-00940-z&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Authors: Other UCSF authors are Laura Remesal, PhD, Juliana Sucharov-Costa, Karishma J.B. Pratt, PhD, Gregor Bieri, PhD, Amber Philp, PhD, Mason Phan, Turan Aghayev, MD, PhD, Charles W. White III, PhD, Elizabeth G. Wheatley, PhD, Brandon R. Desousa, Isha H. Jian, Jason C. Maynard, PhD, and Alma L. Burlingame, PhD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Funding: This work was funded in part by the Simons Foundation, Bakar Family Foundation, National Science Foundation, Hillblom Foundation, Bakar Aging Research Institute, Marc and Lynne Benioff, and the &lt;span class="glossaryLink" aria-describedby="tt" data-cmtooltip="&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemTitle&amp;gt;National Institutes of Health&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;&amp;lt;div class=glossaryItemBody&amp;gt;The National Institutes of Health (NIH) is the primary agency of the United States government responsible for biomedical and public health research. Founded in 1887, it is a part of the U.S. Department of Health and Human Services. The NIH conducts its own scientific research through its Intramural Research Program (IRP) and provides major biomedical research funding to non-NIH research facilities through its Extramural Research Program. With 27 different institutes and centers under its umbrella, the NIH covers a broad spectrum of health-related research, including specific diseases, population health, clinical research, and fundamental biological processes. Its mission is to seek fundamental knowledge about the nature and behavior of living systems and the application of that knowledge to enhance health, lengthen life, and reduce illness and disability.&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;" data-gt-translate-attributes='[{"attribute":"data-cmtooltip", "format":"html"}]' tabindex="0" role="link"&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/span&gt; (AG081038, AG067740, AG062357, P30 DK063720).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Never miss a breakthrough: &lt;a href="https://scitechdaily.com/newsletter/"&gt;Join the SciTechDaily newsletter.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				
		
		
		
	&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:22:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifkFVX3lxTE5SRlptNHZKZjBwTi1uN2ZvVVlBVTJrY3d0U1A0em5LUWp5RDc2SzExVVNPZDIwWjJWYUJUS2pxOUZNNFRvcjd4M1kzWlRYc2J1ejJUbmx3UExRZWxfU2VUaW5HY1dkdFFjdE5RN3FKWjhaRDJoMzBvZVR6STRFdw</guid></item><item><title>可以预防阿尔茨海默氏症的常见英国水果-《独立报》</title><link>https://www.independent.co.uk/news/health/cherries-cherry-powder-fruit-alzheimers-prevention-kent-b2812918.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-jbiisr-0 gryCYY sc-jbiisr-1" id="main"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0" data-component="SupportNSCNative" data-loading="lazy" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;aside class="sc-hez36s-0 dFpFuY"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-1 dmMyEN"&gt;&lt;h3 data-testid="support-nsc-title" class="sc-hez36s-2 fXvmgM"&gt;Your support helps us to tell the story&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-8 juUDRT"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-hez36s-13 cqPbFA"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-0 rAFIl sc-hez36s-16 jZSKtc"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-aja53j-6 PdmgT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content-container" class="sc-aja53j-5 hJPJVF"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-collapsed-content" class="sc-aja53j-4 lcJUSj"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="support-nsc-collapsed-content-tablet" class="sc-hez36s-7 laZbyn"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 cKWiEj"&gt;From reproductive rights to climate change to Big Tech, The Independent is on the ground when the story is developing. Whether it's investigating the financials of Elon Musk's pro-Trump PAC or producing our latest documentary, 'The A Word', which shines a light on the American women fighting for reproductive rights, we know how important it is to parse out the facts from the messaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 cKWiEj"&gt;At such a critical moment in US history, we need reporters on the ground. Your donation allows us to keep sending journalists to speak to both sides of the story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-1uza6dc-0 cKWiEj"&gt;The Independent is trusted by Americans across the entire political spectrum. And unlike many other quality news outlets, we choose not to lock Americans out of our reporting and analysis with paywalls. We believe quality journalism should be available to everyone, paid for by those who can afford it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;strong class="sc-1uza6dc-1 huxBsk"&gt;Your support makes all the difference.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;button class="sc-aja53j-1 dLkuvY sc-aja53j-7 eMEmGu"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="dropdown-with-gradient-dropdown-tablet" class="sc-aja53j-3 dHXFkr"&gt;&lt;span data-action-type="Read more" class="sc-aja53j-2 jrwZqm"&gt;Read more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;svg class="sc-eaj12q-0 hUgQwJ sc-culv3z-0 eifaJK sc-a5wy94-0 hyKPon"&gt;&lt;use href="#ee6613da15642019"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eating cherries turned into a powder rather than a juice could help prevent &lt;a href="/topic/alzheimers"&gt;Alzheimer’s disease,&lt;/a&gt; while also tackling &lt;a href="/voices/food-waste-fund-autumn-budget-2024-b2636044.html"&gt;food waste&lt;/a&gt;, according to new research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The red stone fruits are known for being naturally rich in anthocyanins and quercetin - pigments known for their antioxidant and anti-inflammatory properties. Some studies have previously suggested anthocyanins can help combat dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And now a new study from researchers at the &lt;a href="/topic/university-of-kent"&gt;University of Kent&lt;/a&gt;, published in &lt;em&gt;Antioxidants&lt;/em&gt;, has said the most effective way to use cherries to boost anthocyanins is not to juice them, but instead to turn them into a powder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="article-im-prompt"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using cherries that otherwise would have been discarded, researchers analysed cherry juice, pulp and pomace’s retention of anthocyanin. They found “greater biological activity” in developing the powder, which they suggested may bring more health benefits than extracts or supplements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="sc-awdjp1-2 cbpRGD sc-awdjp1-3 image align-center"&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-1cbdeug-0 cXcwgU"&gt;&lt;div data-gallery-length="2" class="sc-awdjp1-0 gofEvQ"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/07/22/09/21104644-b7d71ceb-0f20-4f02-b85b-65f387a92617.jpg" srcset="https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/07/22/09/21104644-b7d71ceb-0f20-4f02-b85b-65f387a92617.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=320&amp;amp;auto=webp 320w, https://static.independent.co.uk/2025/07/22/09/21104644-b7d71ceb-0f20-4f02-b85b-65f387a92617.jpg?quality=75&amp;amp;width=640&amp;amp;auto=webp 640w" loading="lazy" alt="Scientists took cherries that otherwise would have been thrown out (Place UK/ PA)" class="sc-1mc30lb-0 ggpMaE inline-gallery-btn"&gt;&lt;p class="hydrate-root sc-10wlkbs-0 sc-awdjp1-1 bMDiiD" data-component="AutoGalleryButton" data-theme-name="base"&gt;&lt;button class="sc-1uf4o3q-0 dkRtZs inline-gallery-btn" id="trigger-autogallery-18800"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-1uf4o3q-1 hwVecx"&gt;open image in gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/button&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-1cbdeug-1 sc-1cbdeug-3 bpFomM hgzWpY"&gt;Scientists took cherries that otherwise would have been thrown out (Place UK/ PA)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.kent.ac.uk/biosciences/people/2081/ezcurra-marina"&gt;Dr Marina Ezcurra&lt;/a&gt;, the project’s lead researcher based in Kent’s &lt;a rel="nofollow" target="_blank" href="https://www.kent.ac.uk/school-of-natural-sciences"&gt;School of Natural Sciences&lt;/a&gt;, said: ‘Working with local growers has been key to this success. Together we are showing that agricultural by-products don’t need to go to waste – they can become part of the solution to producing sustainable and accessible healthy foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-mid-article-thumbnails-ii" class="sc-looa6c-0 cPCVUJ"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;‘Our newly discovered innovation is a scientific approach that could be adopted at scale in Kent and other agricultural regions, and we look forward to carrying out further research to help drive this forward.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sarah Blackburn, first author of the study, said the research showed how food waste could be turned into health supplements: “What makes this work exciting is that we combined detailed analytical approaches with health measurements in inexpensive laboratory models that provide insights into human health,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This allows us to demonstrate the potential of food waste to provide benefits for both people and the environment.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around one million people are living with dementia in the UK - a number that is expected to rise significantly to around 1.4 million by 2040. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous studies have shown that people who consume more foods rich in flavonoids, such as berries, tea, red wine and dark chocolate, could lower their risk of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href="/health-and-wellbeing/demntia-cure-red-wine-chocolate-b2614396.html"&gt;2024 paper&lt;/a&gt; from teams at Queen’s University Belfast found increasing your intake of flavonoid-rich foods and drinks could help reduce the risk of developing the incurable illness by 28 per cent. Flavonoids are understood to have antioxidant, anti-inflammatory and anti-cancer properties that can boost your chances against dementia. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Independent</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 08:20:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxONzcyWk5BX0hXS2xrT3RiRDE0aFlDNURSZGRmQVhXT05seHVraC11WTF6TjJ0STJhUWNVZldZQmlzMGFFZDdEbG9KRXVsTjBsM0hjYmY3bU1FUlN2aFdVb0pvVXpRanVpQ24wVHFLQjNlUUVXY3BJYmcxN2NJSlg2d2xCd3pPazllNlZqSnl1OFNXY2ZmckJ5dFFlQjVTQ0RtWjhPR2RJUlFvdlZzd1V1ZA</guid></item><item><title>父亲希望能治愈影响其他300人的儿子罕见病--英国广播公司</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5URHQxcXZxdHlZTG9waWhxeUhxV091Zy1RT2plYWxNQm1xb3BnNm1VWXFOa1hoaXBUTGhta1B6Sm1zLXpYcUZRaXk5cjAyRFV5X0RFVkJ3ZHlCQdIBX0FVX3lxTFBmYXVjQzctN0N3cjVlaXRJWXYyNENJVXhoZ2NLci1MWDVnZW85RjREX3lrc3p1dTA0NlNKTnlHeTcydmdhNlktclBjSWFhZ0c0Sm9EWUtIWUpxZjR6bnNv?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;Dad's hope to find cure for son's rare condition&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-801dd632-0 eSlECZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-801dd632-12 bwIYVa"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-801dd632-5 kRoBHa"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-801dd632-7 lasLGY"&gt;James McCarthy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-801dd632-8 hwLppI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BBC News, West of England&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-801dd632-5 kRoBHa"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-801dd632-7 lasLGY"&gt;Clara Bullock&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-801dd632-8 hwLppI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BBC News, Somerset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250814-092707-b0ec5bc3fc-web-2.27.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/43a7/live/9e3e4040-7fea-11f0-9faa-4582154214b0.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/43a7/live/9e3e4040-7fea-11f0-9faa-4582154214b0.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/43a7/live/9e3e4040-7fea-11f0-9faa-4582154214b0.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/43a7/live/9e3e4040-7fea-11f0-9faa-4582154214b0.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/43a7/live/9e3e4040-7fea-11f0-9faa-4582154214b0.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/43a7/live/9e3e4040-7fea-11f0-9faa-4582154214b0.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/43a7/live/9e3e4040-7fea-11f0-9faa-4582154214b0.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/43a7/live/9e3e4040-7fea-11f0-9faa-4582154214b0.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Supplied by family Tom is holding is son Jenson in his arms, their faces are touching and they are both smiling at the camera." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Supplied by family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Tom hopes a cure or life-changing therapies can be found for his son Jenson&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A father whose son has been diagnosed with a condition only 300 people have in the world has launched a mission to find a "cure or life-changing therapy". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Within days of Jenson's birth he collapsed and was not expected to live. He was put on life support at Bristol Children's Hospital where he spent the first few weeks of his life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He was later diagnosed with incurable Phelan-McDermid Syndrome (PMS) which causes developmental delays. Since then his father Tom has been raising money for PMS research charity CureShank, and in June he ran nine marathons in nine days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He said: "I hope they find a cure or life-changing therapy that significantly improves Jenson's quality of life."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"We were told he had very little chance of survival but he powered through," said Tom, from Bath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He and his wife Kim noticed that Jenson, now aged four, was not smiling, pointing, waving, sitting or crawling during his early years and he was eventually diagnosed with the rare condition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;PMS leads to a range of developmental and physical issues such as intellectual disability, delayed or absent speech, and symptoms of autism. It is caused by a mutation or deletion of the Shank3 gene found on chromosome 22.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250814-092707-b0ec5bc3fc-web-2.27.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/bc4e/live/69ec9cd0-79f8-11f0-abec-f3f54a291b20.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/bc4e/live/69ec9cd0-79f8-11f0-abec-f3f54a291b20.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bc4e/live/69ec9cd0-79f8-11f0-abec-f3f54a291b20.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/bc4e/live/69ec9cd0-79f8-11f0-abec-f3f54a291b20.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/bc4e/live/69ec9cd0-79f8-11f0-abec-f3f54a291b20.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/bc4e/live/69ec9cd0-79f8-11f0-abec-f3f54a291b20.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/bc4e/live/69ec9cd0-79f8-11f0-abec-f3f54a291b20.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/bc4e/live/69ec9cd0-79f8-11f0-abec-f3f54a291b20.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Supplied by family Baby Jenson in hospital after his collapse" class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Supplied by family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Days after he was born, baby Jenson collapsed and was taken back into hospital&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Jenson was also found to have Ring 22, which has similar characteristics to PMS, and a heart disorder. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;According to Tom, about 3,500 people in the world have PMS, and only 300 have both PMS and Ring 22.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;He said: "We were lucky to get a diagnosis as quickly as we did because some parents don't get one for a long time."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;It was difficult to get information as doctors knew little about how Jenson would be affected, Tom added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The 34-year-old, who runs a sports agency, said: "He is still not walking or talking or eating by himself but we are trying to get him the right therapy and make sure he hits those milestones."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hoQmHM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250814-092707-b0ec5bc3fc-web-2.27.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/545f/live/60a72c90-7a01-11f0-815f-b9007f63c56a.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/545f/live/60a72c90-7a01-11f0-815f-b9007f63c56a.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/545f/live/60a72c90-7a01-11f0-815f-b9007f63c56a.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/545f/live/60a72c90-7a01-11f0-815f-b9007f63c56a.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/545f/live/60a72c90-7a01-11f0-815f-b9007f63c56a.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/545f/live/60a72c90-7a01-11f0-815f-b9007f63c56a.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/545f/live/60a72c90-7a01-11f0-815f-b9007f63c56a.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/545f/live/60a72c90-7a01-11f0-815f-b9007f63c56a.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt='Supplied by family Tom and his children on a beach with a banner reading "Run for Jenson"' class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Supplied by family&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;Tom has been supported by his family raising money for CureShank&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Tom said Jenson was "funny, handsome and obsessed with cars, tractors and bikes".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"He has a smile that would light up a room," he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Tom completed his challenge to run nine marathons over nine days, starting on 27 June, raising £25,000 for Cureshank, which supports research into PMS. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dHQIrb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 06:34:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE5URHQxcXZxdHlZTG9waWhxeUhxV091Zy1RT2plYWxNQm1xb3BnNm1VWXFOa1hoaXBUTGhta1B6Sm1zLXpYcUZRaXk5cjAyRFV5X0RFVkJ3ZHlCQdIBX0FVX3lxTFBmYXVjQzctN0N3cjVlaXRJWXYyNENJVXhoZ2NLci1MWDVnZW85RjREX3lrc3p1dTA0NlNKTnlHeTcydmdhNlktclBjSWFhZ0c0Sm9EWUtIWUpxZjR6bnNv</guid></item><item><title>糖尿病：姜黄补充剂可以帮助减肥吗？ - MedicalNewsToday</title><link>https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/for-better-weight-control-in-diabetes-turmeric-may-be-the-answer</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-yhe8zq"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/turmeric-weight-GettyImages-1393397612-Header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/turmeric-weight-GettyImages-1393397612-Header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/turmeric-weight-GettyImages-1393397612-Header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/turmeric-weight-GettyImages-1393397612-Header-1024x575.jpg" alt="slices of turmeric" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Ffor-better-weight-control-in-diabetes-turmeric-may-be-the-answer&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F08%2Fturmeric-weight-GettyImages-1393397612-Header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Diabetes%3A%20Can%20turmeric%20supplements%20help%20with%20weight%20loss%3F" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/turmeric-weight-GettyImages-1393397612-Header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-13b3g0x"&gt;Turmeric are supplements linked to better weight control in diabetes, evidence suggests. Image credit: Bahadur Ali/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Type 2 diabetes is a major global health concern — in 2017, around 6.28% of the world’s population lived with the condition, a proportion that is expected to rise to 7% by 2030.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There are several treatments for the condition, but the global cost of treating type 2 diabetes is projected to be more than $1 trillion by 2030.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new study has found that turmeric, or its active component curcumin, may help people with prediabetes or type 2 diabetes lose weight, potentially reducing their need for costly medications.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of people with &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/317462" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt; — a condition where a person cannot regulate their blood glucose — is rising rapidly. In 2017, around &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7310804/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;462 million people&lt;/a&gt;, or 6.28% of the world’s population lived with the condition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;By 2024, the &lt;hl-trusted-source source="World Health Organization" rationale="Highly respected international organization"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/13-11-2024-urgent-action-needed-as-global-diabetes-cases-increase-four-fold-over-past-decades" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;World Health Organization (WHO)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; reported that the number of people living with diabetes worldwide had risen to more than 800 million, of whom 95% had type 2 diabetes. And the condition can lead to complications such as cardiovascular disease, vision problems and kidney disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Obesity and overweight are common in people with prediabetes and type 2 diabetes, and losing weight can help manage symptoms, or even &lt;a href="https://bmjgroup.com/losing-weight-can-reverse-type-2-diabetes-but-is-rarely-achieved-or-recorded/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;reverse the condition&lt;/a&gt; in some. Now, a study suggests that &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/318405#faq" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;turmeric or curcumin&lt;/a&gt; supplements might help people with these conditions on their weight-loss journey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The review of 20 randomized controlled trials, published in &lt;hl-trusted-source source="Nature" rationale="Highly respected journal,Expert written journal,Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41387-025-00386-7" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Nutrition &amp;amp; Diabetes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;, found that turmeric or curcumin — the active component of turmeric — had a beneficial effect on some indicators of obesity, and might therefore help with weight management in people with prediabetes and type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.rushu.rush.edu/faculty/thomas-m-holland-md-ms" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Thomas M. Holland&lt;/a&gt;, MD, MS, physician-scientist and assistant professor at the RUSH Institute for Healthy Aging, RUSH University, College of Health Sciences, not involved in this study, commented to &lt;em&gt;Medical News Today&lt;/em&gt; that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The findings are modest but noteworthy. The meta-analysis showed that turmeric/curcumin supplementation led to small but significant reductions in body weight, waist circumference, fat mass percentage, and hip circumference in people with type 2 diabetes and &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/311240" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;prediabetes&lt;/a&gt;. From a scientific standpoint, these changes, about 2 kg (5 lbs) of weight loss and [approximately] 2–3 cm (about an inch) off the waist, may seem small, but in population health even minor improvements in central obesity can reduce metabolic and cardiovascular risk.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turmeric has long been used to add flavor and color to foods, and can also be taken as a supplement. &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9881416/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Studies&lt;/a&gt; suggest that it may have antioxidant, antimicrobial and anti-inflammatory effects, and that it is generally &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/318405#adverse-effects" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;safe and well tolerated&lt;/a&gt; at the dosages found in food, although may have some side effects at higher dosages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;This latest review investigated the effects of turmeric/curcumin supplementation on measures of body size, including body weight, &lt;hl-trusted-source source="National Heart Lung and Blood Institute " rationale="Governmental authority"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/calculate-your-bmi" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;body mass index (BMI)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;, percentage of fat mass, waist circumference, waist-to-hip ratio, and hip circumference, in 20 different studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;All were randomized controlled trials comparing supplementation with placebo, carried out in adults with prediabetes or type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants in the studies were given dosages ranging from 80 milligrams per day (mg/day) to 2,100 mg/day, for 8– 36 weeks. The researchers noted that adverse events, such as stomachache, itching, vertigo, constipation, hot flashes, and nausea, were reported in only 3 of the 20 studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In people with type 2 diabetes, turmeric/curcumin supplementation led to improvements in body weight, waist circumference, body fat percentage, and hip circumference, but not BMI or waist-to-hip ratio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For those with prediabetes, supplements significantly reduced body weight and waist circumference, but again had no effect on BMI.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers also found significant associations between dosage and waist circumference, and between duration of supplementation and body weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two of the study authors, &lt;a href="https://cv.tums.ac.ir/en/cv/Leila_Azadbakht" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Leila Azadbakht&lt;/a&gt;, PhD, professor of nutritional Sciences, and &lt;a href="https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Mohammadreza-Baniasadi" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Mohammadreza Moradi Baniasadi&lt;/a&gt;, MSc in the Department of Community Nutrition at the School of Nutritional Sciences and Dietetics, both at Tehran University of Medical Sciences, Iran, commented on their findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;They told &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; that “the most useful finding is the dose-response relationship: Supplementation for [more than] 22 weeks significantly reduced body weight —[weighted mean difference of] -2.5 kg — and doses [of more than] 15,00 mg/day lowered waist circumference — [weighted mean difference of] -1.8 cm — in [type 2 diabetes] patients.”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This provides practical guidance for clinicians on optimal dosing and duration to achieve meaningful effects, highlighting the potential of turmeric/curcumin as an adjunct to lifestyle interventions for weight control in diabetes management,” they added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pure.atu.ie/en/persons/eamon-laird" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Eamon Laird&lt;/a&gt;, PhD, assistant lecturer in Human Nutrition at Atlantic Technological University Sligo, and adjunct assistant professor at Trinity College Dublin, not involved in the study explained for &lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; that:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Turmeric/curcumin could influence metabolism, reducing inflammation, and potentially impacting (reducing) appetite. Some studies suggest curcumin can enhance thermogenesis (calorie burning for heat production), which could contribute to weight loss over time. Additionally, curcumin’s anti-inflammatory properties may help counteract some of the inflammation (cytokines) associated with obesity and diabetes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/does-turmeric-help-you-lose-weight#research" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Several studies&lt;/a&gt; have suggested that turmeric may help with weight loss, but there is little clear evidence as to how it has its effects, as Azadbakht and Baniasadi told us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“While the precise mechanism remains somewhat enigmatic, we believe the activation of &lt;hl-trusted-source source="Nature" rationale="Highly respected journal,Expert written journal,Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nrm.2017.95" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;AMPK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; and the anti-inflammatory properties are the most likely primary modes, as they directly link to improved insulin sensitivity, reduced chronic inflammation — common in [type 2 diabetes] and prediabetes‚ and enhanced fat metabolism,” the study authors explained.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Laird welcomed the study as interesting but highlighted “significant limitations to consider before getting too excited.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Firstly,” he told &lt;em&gt;MNT,&lt;/em&gt; “out of the 20 studies in the analysis 13 are from the same country (Iran). This limits the potential effects/applicability to the general public as there could be just something unique about that population whether it be genetics or just other dietary or other components not controlled for.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Moreover, there was a wide range of doses and forms of the product used, wide variations in the study duration whilst the majority of the studies were in mostly older female adults,” he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Azadbakht and Baniasadi outlined how they hope to address these issues, noting: “We are considering further research to address limitations in the current evidence base. This includes larger, longer-term [&lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/280574" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;randomized controlled trials&lt;/a&gt;] focusing on high-absorption formulations and combinations with lifestyle interventions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We also aim to explore effects in diverse populations (e.g. varying ethnicities or comorbidities) and investigate mechanistic pathways more deeply […] to better predict responders and optimize safety.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This research is encouraging, but we need to be cautious. The overall effect sizes are small, and the certainty of evidence is low to moderate, meaning stronger, larger trials are still needed. […] For patients, the takeaway is that turmeric can be a helpful addition to a healthy lifestyle, but it’s not a shortcut to weight loss. Clinicians should frame it as a ‘supportive therapy’ alongside established treatments, like lifestyle and medications, for diabetes and obesity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;– Thomas M. Holland, MD, MS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>MedicalNewsToday</author><pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 05:30:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxPZmxSajNMa0s5OUZzbWF5MDNsMkNucmo5VTRfWDFsTFg3TDVtMGNvN0xNRGVvWVVsSW00eGRMMncyb0o2WkhXcUdnU3FydExER1AxeXl2SVpIWjVoMVpjbkZfV0FiN05MelFFb0N2YWpTZ29WWHhxZXVlTTN5TTdzOVFqZnVxZ2lKUjZxelFxZlRSV1VRRXVSaTA2VlpxOWZKRkRFYTFIX3FmQQ</guid></item></channel></rss>