<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>显示一种膳食补充剂可减少高达28%的攻击性- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/one-dietary-supplement-was-shown-to-reduce-aggression-by-up-to-28</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Keep calm and try &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Omega-3_fatty_acid"&gt;omega-3&lt;/a&gt;. The fatty acids, available as dietary supplements via fish oil capsules and thought to help with mental and physical well-being, could also cut down on aggression, according to a 2024 study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These findings haven't come out of nowhere: omega-3 has previously been linked to &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/fish-oil-helps-at-risk-teenagers-avoid-schizophrenia-even-8-years-later"&gt;preventing schizophrenia&lt;/a&gt;, while aggression and antisocial behavior are thought in part to stem from a &lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/190990"&gt;lack of nutrition&lt;/a&gt;. What we eat can influence our brain's chemistry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers from the University of Pennsylvania built on earlier, smaller studies of omega-3 supplementation effects on aggression. Their  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/meta-analysis" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73088" data-postid="179839" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; looked at 29 randomized controlled trials across 3,918 participants in total.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/angry-outbursts-could-literally-be-putting-some-peoples-heart-at-risk"&gt;Angry Outbursts Could Literally Be Putting Some People's Heart at Risk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Across all the trials, a modest but noticeable short-term effect was found, translating to up to a 28 percent &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/venting-doesnt-reduce-anger-but-something-else-does-study-finds"&gt;reduction in aggression&lt;/a&gt; across multiple different variables (including age, gender, medical diagnosis, and length and dosage of treatment).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I think the time has come to implement omega-3 supplementation to reduce aggression, irrespective of whether the setting is the community, the clinic, or the criminal justice system," &lt;a href="https://penntoday.upenn.edu/news/time-has-come-implement-omega-3-supplementation-reduce-aggression"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; neurocriminologist Adrian Raine when the meta-analysis was published.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_149438" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-149438" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/FowDiagramDetailingProcessOfReview.jpg" alt="Flow diagram detailing steps of review process." class="wp-image-149438 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/FowDiagramDetailingProcessOfReview.jpg 673w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/FowDiagramDetailingProcessOfReview-642x495.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/FowDiagramDetailingProcessOfReview-538x415.jpg 538w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/FowDiagramDetailingProcessOfReview-600x463.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 673px) 100vw, 673px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-149438" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Flow diagram of literature search leading to 28 suitable papers. (Raine &amp;amp; Brodrick, &lt;em&gt;Aggression and Violent Behavior&lt;/em&gt;, 2024)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trials included in the study, carried out between 1996 and 2024, ran for an average of 16 weeks. They covered a variety of demographics, from &lt;a href="https://acamh.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/jcpp.12314"&gt;children aged 16 and under&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/abs/10.1080/10284150290007119"&gt;older people aged between 50 and 60&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, the reductions in aggression included both reactive aggression (in response to provocation) and proactive aggression (behavior planned in advance). Before this study, it wasn't clear if omega-3 could help with these different types of aggression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While larger studies across longer periods of time are going to be needed to further establish this relationship, it adds to our understanding of how fish oil pills and the omega-3 in them might be &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/some-kids-with-adhd-may-see-improvement-with-fish-oil-pills-but-results-are-mixed"&gt;beneficial for the brain&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"At the very least, parents seeking treatment for an aggressive child should know that in addition to any other treatment that their child receives, an extra portion or two of fish each week could also help," Raine &lt;a href="https://penntoday.upenn.edu/news/time-has-come-implement-omega-3-supplementation-reduce-aggression"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_149436" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-149436" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/10/ExamplesOfFoodsThatHaveOmega3-e1736917333981.jpeg" alt="One Dietary Supplement Found to Reduce Aggression by Up to 28%" class="size-full wp-image-149436" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-149436" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Natural sources of omega-3 in foods. (Ekaterina Kapranova/iStock/Getty Images Plus)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers think something in the way that omega-3 &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0952327816302198"&gt;reduces inflammation&lt;/a&gt; and keeps vital brain processes &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/nrn3820"&gt;ticking over&lt;/a&gt; might be helping regulate aggression. There are still a lot of unanswered questions, but the team suggests there's enough evidence to look into this further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add in &lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2072-6643/13/7/2154"&gt;the studies that show&lt;/a&gt; that medications derived from fish oil can help reduce the risk of fatal heart attacks, strokes, and other heart health problems, and there seems to be plenty of upside to adding some omega-3 to your diet.&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Omega-3 is not a magic bullet that is going to completely solve the problem of violence in society," &lt;a href="https://penntoday.upenn.edu/news/time-has-come-implement-omega-3-supplementation-reduce-aggression"&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Raine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"But can it help? Based on these findings, we firmly believe it can, and we should start to act on the new knowledge we have."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1359178924000466"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Aggression and Violent Behavior&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i data-stringify-type="italic"&gt;An earlier version of this article was published in June 2024.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:02:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQYnZUMXlQdDR6ODgwaUFYVHdZSm9wdEt2T0ViLWpVTU1KNHNkU1ZqcjVIUmNRblE1dFd4LWlZNldqUnM4ZWc5ZmhSSmpNaUNucWUxMF9vWWU5LTJYenVQTncyQ093U1B3MFhydldScDVfeEhObUNzUHBwbmpjaTFob3lkMTJwU1h3aTNrNzQtSDhwTmJjbFBDaC1B</guid></item><item><title>长期使用与心力衰竭和死亡风险增加相关的褪黑激素补充剂- News-Medical</title><link>https://www.news-medical.net/news/20251103/Long-term-use-of-melatonin-supplements-linked-to-higher-risk-of-heart-failure-and-death.aspx</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="body-e0b46078-fc92-4b73-988a-e16f1894d9ea" class="page-content clearfix" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
            &lt;p id="mobile-top-promo-spot" class="mobile-promo-wrap mobile-promo-leaderboard-320"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span itemprop="author" itemscope itemtype="http://schema.org/Organization"&gt;&lt;meta itemprop="name" content="News Medical"&gt;&lt;meta itemprop="url" content="https://www.news-medical.net/"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Long-term use of melatonin supplements, often used to promote sleep and address insomnia, was associated with a higher risk of heart failure diagnosis, heart failure hospitalization and death from any cause in chronic insomnia, according to a preliminary study to be presented at the American Heart Association's Scientific Sessions 2025. The meeting, Nov. 7-10, in New Orleans, is a premier global exchange of the latest scientific advancements, research and evidence-based clinical practice updates in cardiovascular science.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Melatonin is a hormone naturally produced in the body by the pineal gland, and it helps regulate the body's sleep-wake cycle. Melatonin levels increase during darkness and decrease during daylight. Chemically identical synthetic versions of the hormone are often used to treat insomnia (difficulty falling and/or staying asleep) and jet lag. The supplements are widely available over the counter in many countries, including the U.S. In the U.S., over-the-counter supplements are not regulated, so each brand of supplement can vary in strength, purity, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this study, researchers classified people who had used melatonin long-term (with long-term use defined as a year or more documented in their electronic health records) as part of the "melatonin group." In contrast, those who never had melatonin recorded anywhere in their medical records were classified as the "non-melatonin group."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Melatonin supplements may not be as harmless as commonly assumed. If our study is confirmed, this could affect how doctors counsel patients about sleep aids."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ekenedilichukwu Nnadi, M.D., lead author of the study and chief resident in internal medicine at SUNY Downstate/Kings County Primary Care in Brooklyn, New York&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Melatonin supplements are promoted and marketed as a safe sleep aid; however, data demonstrating their long-term cardiovascular safety are lacking, which prompted the researchers to examine whether melatonin use alters the risk of heart failure, specifically in chronic insomnia patients. According to the American Heart Association's 2025 Heart Disease and Stroke Statistics, heart failure occurs when the heart can't pump enough oxygen-rich blood to the body's organs for them to function properly and is a common condition that affects 6.7 million adults in the U.S.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using a large international database (the TriNetX Global Research Network), the researchers reviewed 5 years of electronic health records for adults with chronic insomnia who had melatonin recorded in their health records and used it for more than a year. They were matched with peers in the database who also had insomnia but never had melatonin recorded in their health records. People were excluded from the analysis if they had previously been diagnosed with heart failure or had been prescribed other sleep medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mobile-middle-mrec-promo-spot" class="mobile-promo-wrap mobile-promo-mrec"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;The main analysis found:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Among adults with insomnia, those whose electronic health records indicated long-term melatonin use (12 months or more) had about a 90% higher chance of incident heart failure over 5 years compared with matched non-users (4.6% vs. 2.7%, respectively).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;There was a similar result (82% higher) when researchers analyzed people who had at least 2 melatonin prescriptions filled at least 90 days apart. (Melatonin is only available by prescription in the United Kingdom.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A secondary analysis found:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Participants taking melatonin were nearly 3.5 times as likely to be hospitalized for heart failure when compared to those not taking melatonin (19.0% vs. 6.6%, respectively).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Participants in the melatonin group were nearly twice as likely to die from any cause than those in the non-melatonin group (7.8% vs. 4.3%, respectively) over the 5-year period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p id="trendmd-conditional-suggestions" class="related-content-embed"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Melatonin supplements are widely thought of as a safe and 'natural' option to support better sleep, so it was striking to see such consistent and significant increases in serious health outcomes, even after balancing for many other risk factors," Nnadi said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"I'm surprised that physicians would prescribe melatonin for insomnia and have patients use it for more than 365 days, since melatonin, at least in the U.S., is not indicated for the treatment of insomnia. In the U.S., melatonin can be taken as an over-the-counter supplement and people should be aware that it should not be taken chronically without a proper indication," said Marie-Pierre St-Onge, Ph.D., C.C.S.H., FAHA, chair of the writing group for the American Heart Association's 2025 scientific statement, Multidimensional Sleep Health: Definitions and Implications for Cardiometabolic Health. St-Onge, who was not involved in this study, is a professor of nutritional medicine in the division of general medicine and director of the Center of Excellence for Sleep &amp;amp; Circadian Research in the department of medicine at Columbia University Irving Medical Center in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study has several limitations. First, the database includes countries that require a prescription for melatonin (such as the United Kingdom) and countries that don't (such as the United States), and patient locations were not part of the de-identified data available to the researchers. Since melatonin use in the study was based only on those identified from medication entries in the electronic health record, everyone taking it as an over-the-counter supplement in the U.S. or other countries that don't require a prescription would have been in the non-melatonin group; therefore, the analyses may not accurately reflect this. Hospitalization figures were also higher than those for initial diagnosis of heart failure because a range of related diagnostic codes may be entered for the hospitalization, and they may not always include the code for a new diagnosis of heart failure. The researchers also lacked information on the severity of insomnia and the presence of other psychiatric disorders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;"Worse insomnia, depression/anxiety or the use of other sleep-enhancing medicines might be linked to both melatonin use and heart risk," Nnadi said. "Also, while the association we found raises safety concerns about the widely used supplement, our study cannot prove a direct cause-and-effect relationship. This means more research is needed to test melatonin's safety for the heart."&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Study details, background and design:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The study included 130,828 adults (average age of 55.7 years; 61.4% women) diagnosed with insomnia.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The study data was from TriNetX, established in 2013, a growing global network of real-world, de-identified patient data available for research.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;65,414 participants had been prescribed melatonin at least once and reported taking it for at least a year.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A second group of people were examined for comparison (control group) - those who had never been prescribed melatonin and were matched to the group taking melatonin on 40 factors including demographic information, health conditions and medications. &lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Participants were excluded if they had already been diagnosed with heart failure or had been prescribed other types of sleeping pills such as benzodiazepines.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The melatonin and control groups were matched for age, sex, race/ethnicity, heart and &lt;a href="https://www.news-medical.net/health/What-is-the-Nervous-System.aspx" class="linked-term"&gt;nervous system&lt;/a&gt; diseases, medications for heart and nervous system diseases, blood pressure and body mass index. Researchers looked at electronic medical records from the five years after the matching date.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;For the main findings, records were searched for codes related to an initial diagnosis of heart failure. Secondary findings included codes for hospitalization related to heart failure or death.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Following the initial analyses, researchers validated the credibility of their findings by conducting a sensitivity analysis. This involved slightly changing the criteria: they required participants in the melatonin group to have filled at least two melatonin prescriptions that were at least 90 days apart. This adjustment aimed to determine whether the extended duration of confirmed melatonin prescriptions influenced the outcomes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p id="mobile-bottom-promo-spot" class="mobile-promo-wrap mobile-promo-leaderboard-320"&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
        
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>News-Medical</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0AFBVV95cUxQeXktOUs1TDBCRFZWYy1EaklCLThRaGJBcEozQW9LTnlmSlBmdnBiYzB1WTdhNnVWMnBqLVBNajVfNFVpZjZQMERpWEdNUEFKSEZsS3FBNXlOd09tNHZuZEdEMGFRU2RzNjZobFpWUHFtbjh0ZENEN0lnVXdiNDM3QjNMcUZUM0VZWUZDUnZFcWtmLV9YdnNGNXNfTEtBOVYxWVJRUXljVDJHejVobGlDcVFOOFZ1R1RpLWpIaHFsNkVVSlhNbllJZ1piQW5zcFp0</guid></item><item><title>Yuen ：为什么每个人都在谈论更年期—为什么是时候了- Star Tribune</title><link>https://www.startribune.com/menopause-conference-hrt-sharon-malone/601507395</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;Menopause is no joke, even if our society has treated it as such. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;The cliché of a woman furiously fanning herself in the middle of a hot flash has long been the standard image that comes to mind of a person struggling with menopause. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;But these days, the floodgates to information about menopause have swung open. Women have taken to TikTok and Instagram to detail their various symptoms, ranging from weight gain to sleep disruptions. Hormone replacement therapy, while not for everyone, is shedding some of its stigma from a previous generation. Hollywood stars from Naomi Watts to Halle Berry are speaking up about their experiences with menopause, signaling that a growing number of women are refusing to suffer in silence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;And now, Minnesotans have a chance to hear more about menopause and perimenopause — the years leading up to a woman’s final period — at a conference Thursday. The Change Summit is convening nationally renowned voices, including Dr. Sharon Malone, to educate health care providers, insurance companies and everyday women about this historically overlooked stage of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;Malone is an OB/GYN, chief medical adviser at &lt;a href="https://www.myalloy.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Alloy Health&lt;/a&gt;, host of the new podcast &lt;a href="https://www.drsharonmalone.com/podcast"&gt;The Second Opinion&lt;/a&gt; and author of the New York Times best-selling book "&lt;a href="https://www.drsharonmalone.com/book" target="_blank"&gt;Grown Woman Talk&lt;/a&gt;." (She’s also a close friend of Michelle Obama and is the wife of former U.S. Attorney General Eric Holder.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;Here’s a snippet of my conversation with Malone, edited for clarity and length.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box  pb-5 article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Q: Why is menopause having a moment &lt;/b&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;now?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="article-body-item" class="rt-Box   article-body-rich-text"&gt;&lt;div class="rt-Box w-full"&gt;&lt;p class="rt-Text"&gt;&lt;b&gt;A:&lt;/b&gt; The explosion of social media is what has changed things for us. I have been having this same conversation in my office for 30-plus years. There’s not a lot of brand new information; this is just getting the information out to the general public. Millennials are the first generation that hasn’t heard all the negativity [about hormone replacement therapy]. They’re demanding different answers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Star Tribune</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:00:44 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxPSzZGYTRFaVJDeU5VbXpiak9SR0IwZ3dOV25DNWFhLWt1aFk0TnJyNWJ3Rk1sYlZWZHcwMjJzOWtNZ3NMLUdFTE5VSnVsWGZtcFdKbFZoenA4empHZ01YcmJEa2d1V0xvaWVyektnS0kweXpxd2dzS0ljRVFOVFFCc1VR</guid></item><item><title>科学让花生过敏全错了–直到科学方法正确- CNN</title><link>https://www.cnn.com/2025/11/03/health/peanut-allergy-researcher</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" data-editable="content" itemprop="articleBody" data-reorderable="content"&gt;
                
    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0003356nzti48g0s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It was a question Dr. Gideon Lack asked often, when giving lectures to fellow allergists and pediatricians on the topic of food allergies: How many doctors in the room had a patient allergic to peanuts?
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0004356nrwj3r31f@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Normally, “virtually every doctor would have put up their hand,” Lack said. Peanut allergy is one of the most common food allergies, affecting more than 2% of US children, with a similar &lt;a href="https://www.allergyuk.org/resources/peanut-allergy-factsheet/" target="_blank"&gt;prevalence&lt;/a&gt; in the United Kingdom, where Lack was practicing.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0005356nbenw5p9s@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But at a lecture in Tel Aviv, Israel, about 25 years ago, the audience’s response took Lack by surprise. Only two or three out of about 200 raised their hand.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0006356nz8q0prs0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I said, ‘Wait, this doesn’t make sense,’ ” he recalled recently. “I was practicing in London, which has a big Jewish community, and I was seeing a high frequency of peanut allergy amongst Jewish children who share similar ancestral background.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0007356n0i6tol41@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lack and his colleagues’ investigations into why, which played out over the next 15 years, led to last month’s remarkable &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/10/20/health/peanut-allergy-guidance-change-wellness"&gt;finding&lt;/a&gt; that the incidence of peanut allergies in the US – after a precipitous rise – appeared to have fallen dramatically.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0008356nxbol2yoe@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It turned out that the guidance parents and pediatricians – and Lack himself – had been following, to avoid giving peanuts to babies and young children to try to prevent the development of dangerous allergies, was completely backward.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0009356nbecgiuzw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “By thinking we were protecting them, we were actually causing the problem,” Lack told CNN.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000a356nup77hdz5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The story of how he and his colleagues proved that was the case is a primer in the &lt;a href="https://www.amnh.org/explore/videos/the-scientific-process" target="_blank"&gt;scientific process&lt;/a&gt;.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000c356nehco6urw@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            There’s a joke in Israel that the first three words babies learn are “mother,” “father” and “Bamba,” Lack said – for the peanut puff snacks that Israeli parents give babies when they’re very young.&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000d356n2m8tlcn5@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “They’ve sort of become a national snack,” he noted, pointing out that the joke is actually “a truism.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000e356nn1bx6z2o@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            As he had conversations with the doctors there, as well as parents of young children, “They all told me one very clear thing: ‘We give peanut snacks to our babies from between 4 and 6 months of age.’ ”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000f356nl23044wu@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Bambas contain “vast amounts of peanut protein,” Lack said. And he came to suspect that, just by “happenstance … this product was developed in Israel and protected the Israeli population.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000g356n0l3c1h2d@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But that was an observation, something he’d learned at a lecture, Lack emphasized. “That’s not really proof of anything.” Could there be other differences Israeli children experience - weather, sunshine, vitamin D exposure - that could have contributed?
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000h356ncm7bqm4y@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            So he and a team of colleagues set out to study it. They looked at about 5,000 schoolchildren in Israel and 5,000 Jewish schoolchildren in London who shared a similar ancestral background – to control for genetic differences – and compared their rates of peanut allergy.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000i356n4chbnj5z@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “In the UK, it was tenfold higher”: almost 2% of kids, Lack said, whereas in Israel, it “virtually didn’t exist.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000j356naz22rqr0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Examining the children’s diets, including when peanuts were introduced in the first year of life, revealed an obvious difference: UK babies were consuming a median zero grams of peanut per week. Israeli babies were eating about 2 grams – equivalent, in Bambas form, to about 10 weekly peanuts.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000k356nle88cvc7@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The kids were eating this with great relish,” Lack noted; it’s a “very popular snack.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000l356nyammts9j@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But “at the time when I suggested this hypothesis, it was virtually impossible to get funding,” he said. He and his team turned to the &lt;a href="https://nationalpeanutboard.org/" target="_blank"&gt;National Peanut Board&lt;/a&gt;, the group representing American peanut farmers. He said the study was criticized for who funded it but emphasized that it had no bearing on the outcome.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000m356ndhlnsp6p@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The idea of eating peanuts was felt to be preposterous, that we would be putting babies at risk and causing peanut allergy based on the old thinking we had, and that it would even be an unethical thing to do,” he recalled.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000n356nbjh8egus@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The results suggested otherwise. But&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;the work was only beginning.
    &lt;/p&gt;



  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000p356nj098zwo9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            What Lack and his colleagues had shown with that study, which was &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/19000582/" target="_blank"&gt;published&lt;/a&gt; in the Journal of Allergy and Clinical Immunology in 2008, was an &lt;em&gt;association &lt;/em&gt;between eating peanuts early in infancy and a lower likelihood of developing peanut allergy.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000q356nkwm14gk2@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            What they wanted to prove was that early introduction of peanuts was the &lt;em&gt;cause &lt;/em&gt;of those reduced allergy rates.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000r356nj6jzhklq@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            For that, they’d need to run a randomized controlled trial, in which they randomly separated participants – in this case, infants with severe eczema, egg allergy or both, putting them at higher risk of peanut allergy – into two groups. One set was directed to consume foods with peanut - such as Bambas peanut puffs - starting between 4 and 11 months of age, and the other was told to avoid them until they turned 5 years old.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000s356nft4nkr3w@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            This time, Lack and his colleagues received funding from the US National Institutes of Health, specifically the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Diseases, which Lack called “patient and generous.” It was not an overnight result. It took two years to recruit the 640 infants into the trial, Lack said, and then they were followed for five years.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000t356nurmayp96@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The results were stark. Of the 530 kids who didn’t start out with a sensitivity to peanut, 13.7% developed peanut allergy by age 5 if they avoided peanuts. In the group that consumed peanuts starting before age 1, 1.9% developed peanut allergy. Among kids who’d shown signs of sensitivity to start with, 35.3% who avoided peanuts developed the allergy, versus 10.6% of those who ate them.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000u356nitg99pjk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “I was hoping for an effect, but I was not expecting to see a more than 80% reduction,” Lack said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000v356njoh2j59c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            When the biostatisticians called him and colleague Dr. George Du Toit with the results, “we toasted the good news to whiskey and roasted peanuts,” Lack recalled. They published the &lt;a href="https://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMoa1414850" target="_blank"&gt;findings &lt;/a&gt;from the trial, called the LEAP study, in 2015 in the New England Journal of Medicine.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000x356nmgxc59af@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            It wasn’t clear, though, whether the message would resonate with parents and pediatricians – if they could change course and do the opposite of what they’d been told for so long.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000y356n3lfz2iu9@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/10920165/" target="_blank"&gt;Guidelines&lt;/a&gt; had been issued in 2000 by the American Academy of Pediatrics, and although they’re often described now without nuance, they were anything but definitive.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd000z356npbcbd90q@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Conclusive studies are not yet available to permit definitive recommendations,” the academy’s Committee on Nutrition wrote in a document about hypoallergenic infant formulas. For infants at high risk of developing allergies, the committee continued, “the following recommendations seem reasonable at this time” – including delaying introduction of dairy products until 1 year, eggs until 2 years and peanuts, nuts and fish until age 3.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0010356nwt58cge3@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lack himself followed the avoidance guidance with his own sons, which of course, “in retrospect, was the wrong advice.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0011356nc95eahk0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            But he emphasizes that the scientific process of proving it was the way medicine should work.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0012356nlo1xv0p4@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “The history of medicine is a series of zigzags,” he said. “It’s not one linear, perfect progression, and people forget that.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

  





    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0013356n0kjzok2u@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            In 2008, the American Academy of Pediatrics &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6157280/#:~:text=In%202008%2C%20the%20AAP%20partially,for%20introducing%20peanut%2Dcontaining%20foods." target="_blank"&gt;withdrew&lt;/a&gt; its guidance that said potential allergens should be avoided for high-risk babies, but didn’t have enough data to recommend introducing them early.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhf734ly0001356nf3pzsyow@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            After the LEAP study was published in 2015, the guidance was updated in what researchers now refer to as a landmark move, and the recommendations were expanded in 2017 and 2021.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0014356nmk27clxb@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            A &lt;a href="https://publications.aap.org/pediatrics/article/doi/10.1542/peds.2024-070516/204636/Guidelines-for-Early-Food-Introduction-and" target="_blank"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published last month in the journal Pediatrics found that rates of peanut allergies among US kids 3 and under declined 33% after the 2015 recommendation and fell 43% after 2017 – and peanut allergies slipped from being the most prevalent to the second-most, behind eggs.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0015356n2yy7pubv@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Study leader Dr. David Hill of Children’s Hospital of Philadelphia notes that those reductions, extrapolated to the number of US kids under age 3, suggest that almost 40,000 children may have avoided peanut allergy diagnoses since the guidelines changed.
    &lt;/p&gt;

  

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0017356n1zf60kgk@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Lack’s work continues. He’s currently co-leading another trial funded by the NIH, called the &lt;a href="https://reporter.nih.gov/project-details/10825608" target="_blank"&gt;SEAL study&lt;/a&gt;. It seeks to test another question that once seemed backward: Could treating eczema early in a baby’s life prevent the development of food allergies?
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0018356n75arbqh0@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “For years, we used to think that food allergies cause eczema,” Lack said. “Now we know it’s the reverse.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd0019356nfkjih8ij@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The idea is referred to as the dual-exposure hypothesis, and Hill noted that it’s supported by decades of research, including from the LEAP trial.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd001a356np9v7aguy@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            “Early exposure to food proteins through the gut promotes tolerance, teaching the immune system that these foods are safe,” he told CNN. “In contrast, exposure through inflamed or disrupted skin – as often occurs in infants with eczema – can sensitize the immune system and increase the likelihood of developing food allergy.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd001b356n6pxmqr5c@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            Babies might encounter food proteins through their skin if they have eczema just from their parents eating those foods, Lack said.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd001c356n8477qzys@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            He put the hypothesis another way: “If I were to knock on your front door and ask for directions, you’d probably greet me in a civil way. But if I were to break into one of the windows, you might greet me in a different way.”
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd001d356nsqyrqben@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            The SEAL study aims to &lt;a href="https://clinicaltrials.gov/study/NCT03742414" target="_blank"&gt;treat &lt;/a&gt;dry or red, flaky skin in the first 12 weeks of life, before babies have developed allergies, using moisturizers and topical steroids, and give babies more time to be exposed to foods by eating them. The goal: see if that helps reduce the likelihood they develop food allergies.
    &lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p class="paragraph-elevate inline-placeholder vossi-paragraph" data-uri="cms.cnn.com/_components/paragraph/instances/cmhe1f4sd001e356n0w9w1nea@published" data-editable="text" data-component-name="paragraph" data-article-gutter="true"&gt;
            If they’re right, it could change medicine again.
    &lt;/p&gt;

              &lt;/div&gt;
                  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CNN</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 11:00:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE9ranZHUV93ZGJIU3hWSEZuSGlURjdhVlNWcEJoV01rY1JsT1pDTlFWQWVEek0zUmRkUFVpRkFfMTdVaF9OUEVNNzFId2FNaHZCU3VjYmNsWUxqOGktbFhvQUtHNTlFSU1SQzhZX09OWS0</guid></item><item><title>Apple Watch数据与人工智能合作揭示心脏损伤-英国《金融时报》</title><link>https://www.ft.com/content/4766c95e-9a87-4ec8-9f18-1f54df0ba713</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="o-grid-row details-section o3-type-body-base css-pmzbjb"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Access to eight surprising articles a day, hand-picked by FT editors. For seamless reading, access content via the FT Edit page on FT.com and receive the FT Edit newsletter.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Financial Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 10:00:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMicEFVX3lxTE4wRUhKT3Ric1hjcGJUVWRSbUxEMHZUdzh2eXV4TUQ4QkZKX3V1SUFTcWdUeEd3OU9SeG1jWlh4MXNubHllSkpySDhHUDJGMUI2LVFhbTBYdmdpRXFNeERlNWIyV2dpVkEwVFFwRnlIMk8</guid></item><item><title>服用褪黑激素可以揭示您的心脏健康状况- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/taking-melatonin-reveal-heart-health-rcna241132</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7eace9" class="body-graf"&gt;Taking melatonin for long periods of time could be a sign of underlying heart problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d6ba4f" class="body-graf"&gt;Long-term use of the popular over-the-counter sleep aid has been linked to a higher risk of &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/heart-health/lillys-tirzepatide-cuts-heart-failure-risks-company-says-rcna164587" target="_blank"&gt;heart failure&lt;/a&gt; and early death in &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/mental-health/sleep-profile-sheds-light-health-lifestyle-cognition-new-study-shows-rcna235901" target="_blank"&gt;adults with insomnia&lt;/a&gt;, according to research released Monday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f0b33a" class="body-graf"&gt;There’s no evidence that melatonin supplements themselves cause heart problems, the researchers said. But a need to take them on a regular basis to help with falling and staying asleep could be a signal that the body is &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/beating-insomnia-lower-risk-heart-attack-rcna72016" target="_blank"&gt;experiencing cardiac issues&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b15016" class="body-graf"&gt;“Insomnia can increase blood pressure, stress hormones and inflammation,” said Dr. Ekenedilichukwu Nnadi, lead author of the new study and an internal medicine resident at SUNY Downstate/Kings County Primary Care in New York City.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d0b648" class="body-graf"&gt;Nnadi and colleagues looked at five years of electronic health records from 130,828 adults, average age 56, finding that people who took melatonin regularly for at least a year were nearly twice as likely to develop heart failure compared to those who didn’t use the supplement, though the actual rates were relatively low: 4.6% of people in the melatonin group developed heart failure, compared to 2.7% among those who didn’t take melatonin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c0249d" class="body-graf"&gt;They were more than three times as likely to be hospitalized for the condition (19% versus 6.6%), and nearly twice as likely to die during the study period, compared to people who didn’t take melatonin regularly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7706af" class="body-graf"&gt;It’s unclear, however, whether the data captured outcomes of all people in the U.S. who take melatonin long term. Researchers identified people as chronic users of melatonin based on medical records only — that is, if they’d been prescribed the supplement. In the U.S., the supplement is available over the counter and isn’t often reflected in medical records.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7f47f0" class="body-graf"&gt;“I caution people against drawing concrete conclusions based on this study alone,” said Dr. Nishant Shah, a preventive cardiologist at Duke University Medical Center in Durham, North Carolina, who wasn’t involved with the study. “But now that we have this observation, this is prime time to figure out whether there’s actually a direct association of harm with sleep agents. That would be practice-changing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3e813e" class="body-graf"&gt;Nnadi’s research is scheduled to be presented in New Orleans at an upcoming meeting of the American Heart Association. It has not been published in a peer-reviewed journal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-60e9c7" class="body-graf"&gt;Heart failure occurs when the heart can’t pump enough oxygen-rich blood to the body’s organs for them to function properly. Nearly 7 million Americans have the condition, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/heart-disease/about/heart-failure.html#" target="_blank"&gt;Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-097025" class="body-graf"&gt;While the study found that long-term melatonin use was an indicator of potential heart problems — and not causing the problems itself — experts agreed more research is needed into the supplements’ possible side effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b8b9da" class="body-graf"&gt;“We have patients using all kinds of supplements without understanding the risks,” said Dr. Martha Gulati, a preventive cardiologist and the incoming director of the Davis Women’s Heart Center at Houston Methodist DeBakey Heart and Vascular Institute in Texas. “If there is harm from a supplement, it means the cost could be far more than simply expensive urine.” Gulati was not involved with the new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f35619" class="body-graf"&gt;Melatonin is a hormone made naturally by the body that helps regulate sleep and wake cycles. Synthetic versions, sold widely over the counter as dietary supplements, are marketed to help people &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/aging/falling-asleep-time-may-safest-heart-new-study-shows-rcna4887" target="_blank"&gt;fall asleep faster&lt;/a&gt; or overcome jet lag. Because supplements aren’t regulated by the Food and Drug Administration, doses and purity can vary widely among brands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-457ac4" class="body-graf"&gt;Use of the supplement has increased in recent years. A 2022 &lt;a href="http://sleepfoundation.org" target="_blank"&gt;Sleep Foundation survey&lt;/a&gt; found that up to 27% of U.S. adults take melatonin, as well as 4% of kids. The new study &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/reports-melatonin-poisoning-kids-increased-rcna31741" target="_blank"&gt;didn’t include children&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c323a7" class="body-graf"&gt;People taking melatonin for sleep for more than a year should talk with their doctor, experts said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-56d3cf" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;“People should be aware that it should not be taken chronically without a proper indication,” Marie-Pierre St-Onge, director of the Center of Excellence for Sleep &amp;amp; Circadian Research at Columbia University Irving Medical Center in New York, said in a press release. St-Onge was not involved with the new research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxOR2gwbk1kcjhEMjN1aUxwMU93akhsQl9rZWNrQmdfZnRuZ1JrcW1Wc1NuNk90VGVud0w3Mml1Q203X2dvNV9iUk42NHkyX3dSMlhGUThmQ1NuVjBlekNOQWNNOXVYNjFLMXlJVlVtX1ZXR3NKTTh4UlpNcmlMSUp4ekhXa200QXFaTTV3dl9NM19sMEI00gFWQVVfeXFMT3FfNS1VUl81MFl3MnF6WVBPcWJCWTZieG1MQUp1eXZGbldTV0lmencyRktraXJhN1N3YVhaNWM4VGZndlJOa001ZjNGTHhpODFlS0FCVFE</guid></item><item><title>为了优化健康，请将您的习惯与您的生物钟同步。具体操作方法如下： NPR</title><link>https://www.npr.org/2025/11/03/nx-s1-5590198/health-habits-circadian-rhythms-body-clock</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storytext" class="storytext storylocation linkLocation"&gt;
      &lt;div id="resg-s1-96090" class="bucketwrap image large"&gt;
            
&lt;div class="credit-caption"&gt;
    &lt;div class="caption-wrap"&gt;
        &lt;div class="caption" aria-label="Image caption"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
                Our body is an exquisite time-keeping machine. Every cell that has DNA has a molecular clock, but they don't keep perfect time on their own.
                &lt;b class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
                    
                    AzmanL/E+/Getty Images
                    
                &lt;/b&gt;
                &lt;b class="hide-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;hide caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
            &lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;


            &lt;b class="toggle-caption"&gt;&lt;b&gt;toggle caption&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/b&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

    &lt;span class="credit" aria-label="Image credit"&gt;
        
        AzmanL/E+/Getty Images
        
    &lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;/div&gt;
   &lt;p&gt;The return to "standard time" is better for our health according to sleep scientists, but the time change can be disruptive, and our bodies must also adjust to more hours of darkness as we head towards winter.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;The body is an exquisite time-keeping machine. And growing evidence shows that if you align your daily habits with&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2026/01/01/1261413416/how-to-optimize-your-circadian-rhythm" target="_blank"&gt; your circadian rhythms &lt;/a&gt;— including when you sleep, eat, and exercise — you can help fend off chronic disease and optimize good health.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Let's start with a quick primer: "Your body is filled with clocks, explains &lt;a href="https://inside.salk.edu/fall-2018/emily-manoogian/" target="_blank"&gt;Emily Manoogian&lt;/a&gt;, a researcher and chronobiologist at the Salk Institute for Biological Studies. In addition to the master clock in your brain, there are time-keeping mechanisms in every organ and in your cells.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;"Every cell in your body that has DNA has a molecular clock that keeps its own time," she says. They're all part of your body's circadian system helping you stay in sync with the 24-hour cycle.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But our bodies don't keep perfect time on their own. Every day, we stray a bit from the 24-hour cycle, and need a reset, explains Salk Institute researcher &lt;a href="https://www.salk.edu/scientist/satchidananda-panda/" target="_blank"&gt;Satchin Panda&lt;/a&gt;, author of &lt;em&gt;The Circadian Code: Lose Weight, Supercharge Your Energy, and Transform Your Health from Morning to Midnight. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;"The master clock in your brain coordinates all the other clocks through a series of different cues," Manoogian explains, including external cues — such as light, food, and movement. And that's why the timing of our habits can play a pivotal role in keeping our clocks in sync.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Light from the sun serves as the external cue to resynchronize the master clock. That's why it's helpful to open the blinds in the morning and spend time outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And, it turns out, our first bite of food each day also works as an external cue to sync the clocks in our digestive system and throughout our bodies.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Food is also a signal to reset the clocks, especially your gut," Manoogian says. "That's one of the reasons why making sure you're eating at the right time relative to light is important."&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;Eating is a cue to wake up your digestive and metabolic organs, which are primed to function best during the day. By nighttime, the metabolic system is ready for rest, too.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"When you're asleep, your body expects to fast. And so it shuts down the part of the system that captures glucose from the blood and stores it away," she explains.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;When people eat too close to bedtime or in the middle of the night, their metabolic organs aren't optimized to do their job. The misalignment can lead to poor blood sugar control. Her research shows that restricting the number of hours you eat during a day to about a 10 hour window, can lead to significant improvements in metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There's lots of evidence that eating out of sync with your circadian rhythms can increase the risk of metabolic diseases, including diabetes and obesity. Studies show that shift workers who work rotating, overnight&lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/363/bmj.k4641" target="_blank"&gt; shifts have a higher risk&lt;/a&gt; of developing these conditions due, in part, to the disruption of the natural rhythms.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;And when it comes to exercise, some people find they do best in the morning, others in the afternoon, says&lt;a href="https://www.feinberg.northwestern.edu/faculty-profiles/az/profile.html?xid=13785" target="_blank"&gt; Dr. Phyliss Zee&lt;/a&gt;, director of the Center for Sleep and Circadian Medicine at Northwestern University Feinberg School of Medicine. But the science shows exercising late at night, just before bed can disrupt sleep.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"There's a peak time for almost every physiological process," Zee says. "The timing of feeding, the time that you exercise, the physical activity, all of these help entrain the clocks in your body so that they're in sync," she says.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;If you eat dinner and go to bed around the same time most nights, your 'creature of habit' ways could pay off. "The science shows that regularity is very important for the circadian system and for health," Zee says.&lt;/p&gt;   
   

   &lt;p&gt;And while each person is unique she says,  a general rule of thumb is to begin limiting exposure to light, food and heavy exercise starting a few hours before bedtime.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But as scientists have learned more about the importance of keeping our biological clocks in sync, society has moved in the opposite direction. Manoogian points to advertisements for midnight food menus, and around the clock work and entertainment as examples of our 24/7 modern life.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;One way to push back is to track your daily habits. Michelle Pittsley, who lives in Vista, Calif., started using an app called &lt;a href="https://www.mycircadianclock.org/" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;myCircadianClock&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to log her eating and blood sugar. She says it helped her stick to a "time-restricted eating" window and helped her track her progress. The app was developed by Salk scientists as a research tool, and is used in Salk Institute studies. It's free to any adult who downloads it. The app provides guidance on when to sleep, eat, and exercise. (Note: if you sign up, you're sharing data with researchers.)&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;When we have "broken" circadian rhythms, the risk for chronic disease rises, including obesity, diabetes, heart disease, fatty liver disease, gut diseases and common cancers, say Panda and Manoogian. If you want to be more intentional about aligning your habits for better health, here are three strategies to try.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;1. Drop the late night snack, and limit the hours you eat.&lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;People who restrict their eating to a ten hour window can reduce their risk of Type 2 diabetes, Manoogian says. She and Panda co-authored a study of 108 adults, average age 59, who had symptoms of metabolic disease. They found those who followed time-restricted eating saw a significant &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/39348690/" target="_blank"&gt;reduction in their hemoglobin A1c&lt;/a&gt; (which is a person's average glucose level over a few months), compared to participants who did not restrict their eating window.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Participants were not asked to reduce calories, only to restrict the eating window for a period of three months.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"It was exciting to see that just the time restricted eating was able to reduce their risk for Type 2 diabetes by 60%," Manoogian says, because the reduction in blood sugar, if maintained, reduces the risk of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;Research also suggests that eating your biggest meal of the day in the afternoon, as opposed to later in the evening can be beneficial for those who want to lose weight. A study from Spain found &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/blogs/thesalt/2013/01/30/170591028/to-maximize-weight-loss-eat-early-in-the-day-not-late" target="_blank"&gt;early eaters lost 25 percent more weight&lt;/a&gt; than late eaters. Panda says when his mother gave up a late night snack that included tea with sugar and milk and an occasional snack, that one change led to a significant drop in her blood sugar levels.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;2. Go to bed about the same time most nights &lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"Keeping the same sleep schedule is optimal," Manoogian says. The consistency gives your body a chance to anticipate and keep internal clocks synchronized. During sleep, &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/shots-health-news/2024/06/26/g-s1-6177/brain-waste-removal-system-amyloid-alzheimer-toxins" target="_blank"&gt;waste is cleared out of our brains&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://medicine.yale.edu/news-article/sleeps-crucial-role-in-preserving-memory/" target="_blank"&gt;memories are consolidated&lt;/a&gt;, and there's a pile of evidence to show rest is critical for our health.&lt;/p&gt;   
   &lt;p&gt;But don't beat yourself up when you have a late night out. And of course, there will be disruptions due to travel, work deadlines or weekend celebrations. "Going off your circadian system is not like breaking an arm," Manoogian says. Think of the harms of erratic schedules akin to the way dripping water can erode stone. "Little hits, time after time, can wear down the system," she says. And the result is you can feel slower and older.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;There are&lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/2019/03/20/705224709/dont-count-sheep-better-bedtime-rituals" target="_blank"&gt; lots of bedtime rituals&lt;/a&gt; to foster a good night's sleep, including limiting light before bed and sleeping in darkness. Zee's research shows &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/health-shots/2022/04/01/1089997121/light-disrupts-sleep#:~:text=Unlike%20those%20who%20spent%20both,night%20could%20disturb%20our%20metabolism" target="_blank"&gt;even small amounts of light&lt;/a&gt; while sleeping  can have adverse effects on cardiovascular and metabolic health.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3 class="edTag"&gt;3. Time exercise to your 'sweet spot,' but not too late at night &lt;/h3&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Whether you're a morning lark or a night owl can influence the ideal time for you to exercise, so this will vary from person to person, Zee says. "The better time to exercise depends, in part, on what we call your chronotype," she says, which is a person's innate preference for timing of sleep or when they feel more alert and energetic. One way to estimate your tendency is with a &lt;a href="https://www.med.upenn.edu/cbti/assets/user-content/documents/Morningness-Eveningness%20Questionnaire.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;Morningness-Eveningness&lt;/a&gt; questionnaire.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;"If you're a morning person, then morning exercise can be beneficial," creating a consistent structure, Zee says, but people who grow more alert later in the day, may want to put it off until later. As people juggle competing obligations, exercise may be shoehorned into the time it fits on your calendar, even if it's not your body clock's preferred window. She says it's important to remember that exercise is beneficial, no matter what time you do it.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;But keep this in mind: "Exercise is a stimulatory cue to tell your body you should be awake," Manoogian says, so it's not a surprise that &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41467-025-58271-x" target="_blank"&gt;recent research&lt;/a&gt; shows that exercise just before sleep can &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-04-bed-linked-disrupted.html#google_vignette" target="_blank"&gt;disrupt sleep quality&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NPR</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxNT3M3cFBnaFE2UkhBVUhmNFROV0xZTEZRajVEbzl3T1NDeUNsVXVaby1kYXhxX0ZPM3VxeHl5eVkwbzFGVjEzM05LWjJTbUk4WXF6NzMzU2ZXRTA1RGFpbktIT2R1b2dnWFNYbVpMWDZjUEl1Q2h6bDZWUGYxYXU2ZzVXNmFJQkxxWW16UHRkbnA</guid></item><item><title>新药更有效地杀死癌症20,000倍，没有可检测到的副作用- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/new-drug-kills-cancer-20000x-more-effectively-with-no-detectable-side-effects/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipgFBVV95cUxQTjRaZkpKREI3YzFDVHhhTFpXeFFIY2x6ZFJ4eVRWNFlLZmllNXpHM1U1NWZtTDU1dFlabnJuZkNIc1BEQXVhMXVjYnc1UVdlRThRXzdFY1FUUFNKcW1ONzl1RnlrcFVwM3JMZjhORlhTX05iaXB0RVJQcHlLTUdQNHF4bk9QcEtlMGVILU1PNkhjTHRObjlGMFIzQW12d0QzekcwaVJB</guid></item><item><title>您不应忽视的癌症警告信号：持续的口腔溃疡、疲劳或出血可能很早-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/cancer-warning-signs-you-should-never-ignore-persistent-mouth-sores-fatigue-or-bleeding-could-be-early-red-flags-says-raipuroncologist/articleshow/125047353.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cancer often develops silently, with early signs so subtle that they are easily ignored or mistaken for minor health issues. According to Dr Jayesh Sharma, Consultant Surgical Oncologist at ITSA Hospitals in Raipur, paying attention to small but persistent changes in the body can be life-saving. He explains that early detection plays a crucial role in preventing cancer-related deaths, especially in India, where cancers such as oral, cervical, and breast cancer are highly prevalent. Dr Sharma urges people to take routine screenings seriously and not to dismiss recurring symptoms. Detecting cancer in its earliest stages greatly improves treatment outcomes, making awareness and timely medical consultation essential for safeguarding long-term health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="5"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;keyword id="29123405" type="General" weightage="20" keywordseo="early-cancer-symptoms" source="keywords"&gt;Early cancer symptoms&lt;/keyword&gt; are often silent, warns Raipur oncologist &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sharma explains that cancer rarely starts with pain or severe symptoms. It usually begins subtly, with small and seemingly harmless signs that gradually progress. Many people ignore these early indicators because they assume they are caused by stress, infection, or normal ageing. However, such delays often allow the disease to advance undetected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Cancer is curable if detected early: Signs to pay attention to&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He highlights that the key to survival lies in recognising these early changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Most cancers are curable if detected at an early stage,” says Dr Sharma. “Unfortunately, by the time people seek medical help, the disease has already progressed.” This is why awareness and regular check-ups are essential, especially for individuals with a family history of cancer or those exposed to known risk factors such as smoking, alcohol consumption, and poor diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Early signs of oral and cervical cancer for timely diagnosis&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most important symptoms to watch for, according to Dr Sharma, is any swelling, sore, or ulcer inside the mouth that does not heal even after several weeks. This is particularly relevant in India, where oral cancer is one of the most common forms of the disease. Tobacco use, both smoked and chewed, remains a major contributor. “If a mouth ulcer or sore persists beyond two weeks, it is not a simple infection. It needs medical attention,” he advises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He further points to abnormal bleeding as another crucial red flag. Bleeding without an obvious cause, such as coughing up blood, can sometimes indicate lung cancer. Similarly, bleeding between menstrual cycles or after menopause may suggest an underlying issue like cervical cancer. Dr Sharma urges people not to ignore these signs or self-diagnose. Instead, they should seek proper evaluation from a qualified healthcare professional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Common cancers among Indian women&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;For women, Dr Sharma highlights that cervical cancer continues to be the second most common cancer in India, followed closely by breast cancer. He explains that the earliest sign of cervical cancer is often unusual or persistent vaginal bleeding. “Women tend to normalise irregular bleeding, especially around menopause, but this can be dangerous,” he warns. “If the bleeding is inconsistent with your usual cycle or occurs after menopause, it requires immediate investigation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He stresses that the goal is not to create panic but to encourage awareness. “Not every irregular symptom means cancer,” he says. “The important thing is to notice when symptoms persist or recur. If your body repeatedly shows the same problem, it is sending a message that something may be wrong.” Regular screenings such as Pap smears, mammograms, and HPV vaccinations can help detect or even prevent certain cancers before they develop into severe conditions. Dr Sharma recommends that women over 30 should schedule regular check-ups and discuss preventive tests with their doctors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Recognising silent cancer symptoms before pain appears&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sharma emphasises that cancer does not begin with pain. Pain often appears in later stages, when the disease has already advanced. Instead, early symptoms can include persistent fatigue, unexplained weight loss, or changes in the skin and bodily functions. These small but recurring issues should never be brushed aside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="43"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He explains that the body often gives subtle clues long before serious symptoms arise. Paying attention to these signs and consulting a doctor early can lead to faster diagnosis and better treatment outcomes. “When something doesn’t feel right for a long time, don’t wait for it to worsen. Seek medical advice immediately,” he urges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Importance of regular check-ups and awareness&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sharma’s message serves as a reminder that cancer awareness and preventive healthcare are just as important as treatment itself. Routine medical check-ups, self-examinations, and an understanding of one’s own body can significantly reduce the risk of late-stage cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;He encourages people to avoid self-medication or ignoring recurring symptoms. Instead, they should schedule regular health screenings, especially if they belong to high-risk groups. “Awareness should lead to action,” he concludes. “When we take the initiative to understand and monitor our health, we can detect cancer at its earliest and most treatable stage.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Disclaimer: The information in this article is for general awareness and educational purposes only. It should not be considered a substitute for professional medical advice, diagnosis, or treatment. Always consult a qualified healthcare provider if you experience persistent or unusual symptoms, or before making any decisions about your health.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="56"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Also Read | &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/heart-health-alert-stem-cell-therapy-promises-to-reduce-heart-failure-risk-even-after-a-heart-attack/articleshow/124991461.cms" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;Heart health alert: Stem cell therapy promises to reduce heart failure risk even after a heart attack&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="60"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1AJBVV95cUxNRUZtUDIxemRZTTBNVHpaVXo5Nl81dV84ODc2cHZEbWJvRFlIczhGSC1JcHlSaXN0VDYyMUZqOVNMekVQZkZ1UG10bG15WVJnUVdzZDgtVzBqRlhrLTZNc2phUDNUcUxKLUlrS2doVDBveWloRTdvbTJPek56RGFfbHl3RUxvel9tbzBlYWZkVTgxZUlUUDFscVJIMG9ZUkNkSktMMTNnbXVYWFVhVzVhTWRxeUI4STh1Z3dsZzhvOWM0RUdLMHJFSEhjZ2dCcUp2RUdKbGxfdUFzbzJ6TTVRa0dMMG03TlJ5MGQyNTJBX241eVlGdXRrbUZhVnpDcDZZS2lpUzl4cjI3aEdBNENGTEJhTWJkUXZsNnZZQVVPUVlOcHF0ZzRHUXBfSGM5R1JxVTRoRDlSNlBSNkZoTWI2YmwtNDRWelRKS1NpR1gxZ3phZGxk0gHaAkFVX3lxTE15WDMtRWttYjd0b2VJOUZidWd0dUJCTHlZUmJZMkpIaFZ1ejRUYzlva1dhZkt4a2dPYWhRQUV1M2cxOFdoYVNuZEwxekxHMldyNld4WHlFQ0RISFJLRHRGTlBBajVXWTRBbEhJWEkwYjBIOFJCb0ZfcVM2eldEczJOZlNiNlRqa2JRWWdKZTBhYVhOR0VHU0MzYW5DTU1Yb2RnaWNyU3J4aW5VMFJRa2xJazVOLUNYb1c1cXJ5a0RXRGZOTlphOGRJZ3ViMC1nMnV4SFZWc1FlLUNJREtTb2NIa2xXNFIzb2tHam5xVTVNTmllM3JGa24yVnI4U3M4dFY2djZSOV9yZE5yVlNIR3RULWZzaU44al9TOUV3MnhZUGFVenJIVXI2WDVrMGhCWkU0TVJwa0JycXp1SW96WjZjSDhfMWNUZHhfM3BSYmRsUlVaLWNOS21zNUE</guid></item><item><title>5种被证明可降低胆固醇和支持心脏健康的草药茶-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/5-herbal-teas-proven-to-lower-cholesterol-and-support-heart-health/photostory/124990374.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;While chamomile is known to promote relaxation and sleep quality, it also indirectly supports heart health by reducing stress, a known risk factor for heart disease. With the presence of antioxidants such as apigenin it reduces inflammation, lowers blood pressure levels and improves cardiovascular health as well. A meta-analysis published in&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://journals.viamedica.pl/clinical_diabetology/article/download/DK.a2021.0034/64103"&gt;&lt;em&gt; Via Medica Journals, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;which reviewed several clinical trials to see how chamomile tea affects cholesterol and lipid profile, it showed that due to chamomile’s antioxidants (apigenin, luteolin, quercetin) and plant sterols, which help reduce oxidative stress, improve lipid metabolism, and limit cholesterol absorption.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 07:31:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi6AFBVV95cUxPdXNOUHRDdWhBZ3hkYVh1QzZSdHpkNy1ldWpscEp3RlE5ZVJhNjlyOU9NRENvLW16SFJxcWtTSUxPR21JbjZGSlpzQ2VDUHM2bEthNlpZc3ZxY0NfZHpwLVFVS1JpWm9YSnlQVFU1cHcyT3paXzBfT3RjRm1WaTA5WGdIRFJPZTAyZ1pmc3FtYTJ3Yk14SjFWUGhKc3RQWGhyS0dmUVpNaTkxM29ncmJsdE03WVQxRWQ2Tm1jc0FkX0FWb2lKbUUxYWxsV09DOElGZFhPc0F4V2hfaUZtMWZjd0ozaG1fcmVV0gHwAUFVX3lxTFBDUTVGUm8weGlUQlhjRVV5cEh3bkpuMFNxUDlRNmVNRDA4d0JBelpseUdKczFmUERhOV9ZSmFwZUY0MmJqclhUZWFUV1hLUTVTX3lSZ0hxQWJqdWZVZHNfdWxxYVZZUjJjcDU5b09NazJTTHVrdG5wRGFKZHhJOGw0X0o3R1FWYi1tWWVFSUFFQXh5YWVkLUlXcjhSTUVkc29rSi1vT1I1d2dlRFFzelpUVzh5SXBFeFY0RHBsUUIwOHJSblB4aFFpbkNfLTlHUG44ZzdqaExJNEgwVldvMFdFbTlCMnJTaE10Y2kya2RZaA</guid></item><item><title>研究人员在历史上最严重的爆发之一中分享了关于破坏性病毒的最新消息： “我知道的比我通常知道的要少” -雅虎</title><link>https://www.yahoo.com/news/articles/researchers-share-devastating-virus-amid-073000255.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Bird flu is in the midst of a resurgence in the United States, and researchers fear that while the risk to the general public remains low, many could be in the dark regarding its true impact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As The New York Times &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/22/health/h5n1-bird-flu.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reported;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt;, bird flu has once again reared its ugly head. According to data from the Animal and Plant Health Inspection Service, around 7 million farmed birds have died from the illness since the start of September. This includes the death of over 1 million turkeys from bird flu, causing supply concerns for the upcoming holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Outbreaks of bird flu typically flare up in the fall due to the seasonal migration of wild birds. This migration brings different bird populations together, increasing the virus' spread into new areas and into domestic flocks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why is an outbreak of bird flu this fall important?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the most popular bird to cook for Thanksgiving, turkeys are generally in very high demand throughout the month of November. The outbreak of bird flu this fall may increase turkey prices by reducing the supply of available healthy turkeys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Outbreaks during the fall migration can lead to the culling of large numbers of birds in an attempt to stop the spread. This can result in a shrinking overall flock size and higher prices due to tighter production and decreased supply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;With the recent government shutdown and revised policies of U.S. government agencies, an accurate representation of this season's bird flu outbreak may be unavailable to many. This could leave experts without the latest information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"Because of the government shutdown, I know less than I would normally know," &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/10/22/health/h5n1-bird-flu.html" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:said;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;said&lt;/a&gt; Dr. Amy Swinford, director of the Texas A&amp;amp;M Veterinary Medical Diagnostic Laboratory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's being done about bird flu?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Unlike previous outbreaks, the current bird flu outbreak has persisted for years and has been confirmed in every U.S. state at some point since 2022. According to a USDA &lt;a href="https://www.aphis.usda.gov/sites/default/files/hpai-2022-2023-summary-depop-analysis.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:report;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;, this outbreak has been declared the "longest and deadliest animal disease emergency in U.S. history."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Over the last three years, more than 168 million birds have been affected by bird flu, leading to millions of dollars in profit losses and a significant reduction in the country's food supply. The outbreak of bird flu was identified as the leading cause of a spike in egg prices across the country over the last few years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;To combat the spread of bird flu, animal science experts at Michigan State University offered several easy-to-follow &lt;a href="https://www.canr.msu.edu/news/fall-brings-bird-flu-risks-what-poultry-owners-need-to-know" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:recommendations;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;recommendations&lt;/a&gt; for farmers and breeders. These include everything from removing standing water sources that migratory birds may encounter to ensuring that "newly acquired animals" are quarantined for at least two weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?rec92BVPrKKRh5ou7" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 07:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilgFBVV95cUxNVnNKc05iQ3lJVWNoNFlOZ2o5MUx3MXlRTnU4VUpmSnRRMXl2cjk2LXZvMEpKQi1nbXMwb182bS1pRktLdXlaOEFUWERXdjdCU21EVjNZQ1VNYkthaUFwT29lVm9Qd1owWFhpc1hadUZmdHFpOW1HNXBaVkJabjJaeVh6ckpZNXFFZXl1OGY2Wm9wZG9ESHc</guid></item><item><title>阿尔茨海默氏症可能由破碎的睡眠-觉醒周期驱动- ScienceDaily</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2025/11/251102205012.htm</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p id="first" class="lead"&gt;Alzheimer's disease often throws a person's daily patterns into disarray. Difficulty sleeping through the night, restless tossing, and frequent daytime naps are common early warning signs. In later stages, patients often experience "sundowning," a period of increased confusion and agitation that tends to occur later in the day. These patterns hint at a close relationship between Alzheimer's progression and the circadian system -- the internal body clock that regulates sleep, wakefulness, and other daily biological cycles. Until recently, however, scientists did not fully understand how deeply this connection ran.&lt;/p&gt;

						&lt;div id="text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A team of researchers at Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis has now demonstrated, in mouse models, that Alzheimer's disease disrupts circadian rhythms within specific brain cells. This disturbance alters how and when hundreds of genes switch on and off, changing key processes that help the brain function properly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their findings, published October 23 in &lt;em&gt;Nature Neuroscience&lt;/em&gt;, suggest that restoring or stabilizing these internal rhythms could open up a new approach to treating Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"There are 82 genes that have been associated with Alzheimer's disease risk, and we found that the circadian rhythm is controlling the activity of about half of those," said Erik S. Musiek, MD, PhD, the Charlotte &amp;amp; Paul Hagemann Professor of Neurology at WashU Medicine, who led the study. In mice engineered to model the disease, these genes no longer followed their usual daily patterns. "Knowing that a lot of these Alzheimer's genes are being regulated by the circadian rhythm gives us the opportunity to find ways to identify therapeutic treatments to manipulate them and prevent the progression of the disease."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Burden of Sleep Disruption&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Musiek, who co-directs the Center on Biological Rhythms and Sleep (COBRAS) at WashU Medicine and specializes in aging and dementia, noted that disturbed sleep is one of the most frequent problems reported by caregivers of Alzheimer's patients. His earlier work showed that sleep changes begin years before memory loss becomes evident. Beyond exhaustion for both patients and caregivers, these disruptions create stress that may accelerate the disease's progression.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Breaking this cycle, he said, starts with identifying where it begins. The body's circadian system regulates roughly 20% of all genes in the human genome, orchestrating vital processes such as digestion, immune response, and sleep-wake cycles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_middle"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In earlier research, Musiek identified a protein called YKL-40 that naturally fluctuates throughout the day and helps control normal levels of amyloid in the brain. Too much YKL-40, which is linked to Alzheimer's risk in humans, can trigger the build-up of amyloid -- a sticky protein that forms plaques, one of the hallmarks of the disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Amyloid's Effect on the Brain's Timing Mechanisms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Because Alzheimer's symptoms follow a repeating daily pattern, the team suspected more circadian-regulated proteins and genes might be involved. In the new study, they examined gene activity in the brains of mice that developed amyloid build-up, as well as in healthy young mice and older mice without plaques. Samples were collected every two hours over a full 24-hour period to track how gene expression changed across the circadian cycle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The researchers found that amyloid deposits disrupted the normal rhythm of hundreds of genes in two key types of brain cells -- microglia and astrocytes. Microglia act as the brain's immune cells, clearing away waste and harmful materials, while astrocytes help neurons communicate and maintain healthy function. Many of the affected genes are normally responsible for microglia's ability to remove waste, including amyloid.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although these genes were not entirely switched off, their usual order and timing became chaotic, weakening the brain's coordinated system for removing toxins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Rhythms and Potential Therapies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study also revealed that amyloid plaques appeared to create new rhythmic patterns in genes that do not usually follow a daily cycle. Many of these genes are involved in inflammation or the brain's response to stress and imbalance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="insertion_bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to Musiek, these discoveries suggest that therapies aimed at adjusting circadian rhythms in microglia and astrocytes could support healthier brain activity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"We have a lot of things we still need to understand, but where the rubber meets the road is trying to manipulate the clock in some way, make it stronger, make it weaker or turn it off in certain cell types," he said. "Ultimately, we hope to learn how to optimize the circadian system to prevent amyloid accumulation and other aspects of Alzheimer's disease."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This research was supported by the National Institute on Aging (R01AG054517, T32AG058518), the National Institute of Neurological Disorders and Stroke (R01NS102272), and the National Institutes of Health (R00AG061231). The authors note that the content reflects their findings and does not necessarily represent the official view of the NIH.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

					&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceDaily</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 06:27:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTE83dHhSVjJiaUxNZW5DRDd4Z1VhZWl3ek9EWEhCX0xwVm5XM0RwLUV5aGliTElQLWVVanpjTUlCRG9PWWdMRVVtczNIcGhuTldkNFloT2F1aVkzR0FUYXA3ZkFGNlJZc3hOeGk5SXZzQQ</guid></item><item><title>一位普拉提教练说，随着年龄的增长，这是您应该重点加强身体的一个部位，并分享她建议的三个动作- Fit&amp;Well</title><link>https://www.fitandwell.com/exercise/pilates/a-pilates-instructor-says-this-is-the-one-area-of-the-body-you-should-focus-on-strengthening-as-you-get-older-and-shares-the-three-moves-she-recommends-to-target-it</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="article__body "&gt;
&lt;p id="fc2d88eb-1c65-49e1-949d-cf9430f5132e"&gt;At one point, you might have seen exercise mainly as a way to change how your body looks. But as you get older, you start to realize how transformative it can be for future-proofing your body, improving your everyday movement, and for reducing the risk of injury, aches and pains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to personal trainer and Pilates instructor &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.instagram.com/eloiseallexia/?hl=en" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.instagram.com/eloiseallexia/?hl=en" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Eloise Skinner&lt;/a&gt;, there’s one area you should pay some extra attention to if you’re training for longevity—your core.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="fc2d88eb-1c65-49e1-949d-cf9430f5132e-2"&gt;The core comprises all of the muscles around your stomach and lower back, including the abdominals, obliques and pelvis. “Core strength is really important as we get older, for both men and women,” Skinner tells &lt;em&gt;Fit&amp;amp;Well.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“When you train your body to activate those deep core muscles, it can be really protective,” says Skinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you slip or trip, your body can use the core to stabilize and protect you. If your body isn’t used to using core strength to take the force of a movement, it will usually place that force somewhere else, like your lower back or another joint,” Skinner says, adding this could easily lead to injury.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A stronger core also makes daily life easier. “Getting up from a chair, standing up from the floor, picking up your grandchildren—all those depend on the strength and alignment of your body, so the core is really, really important,” says Skinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are Skinner’s three go-to moves to build core strength and stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-i2uC9bBAviEptkYabt5J7W" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-i2uC9bBAviEptkYabt5J7W slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Start your week with achievable workout ideas, health tips and wellbeing advice in your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;a id="elk-1-roll-down" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-1-roll-down"&gt;&lt;span&gt;1. Roll-down&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="youtube-video youtube-facade" data-nosnippet id="VpQ9SPwNPvY"&gt;
&lt;div class="video-aspect-box"&gt;
&lt;div class="watch-on-iframe-VpQ9SPwNPvY" data-yt-video-token="VpQ9SPwNPvY" title="Pilates Spinal flexion Roll down - YouTube"&gt;
&lt;span class="youtube-video-title"&gt;Pilates Spinal flexion Roll down - YouTube&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/VpQ9SPwNPvY/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Pilates Spinal flexion Roll down - YouTube" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="play-button" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 234.67 165.33"&gt;&lt;path fill="red" d="M229.763 25.817c-2.699-10.162-10.65-18.165-20.748-20.881C190.716 0 117.333 0 117.333 0S43.951 0 25.651 4.936C15.553 7.652 7.6 15.655 4.903 25.817 0 44.236 0 82.667 0 82.667s0 38.429 4.903 56.85C7.6 149.68 15.553 157.681 25.65 160.4c18.3 4.934 91.682 4.934 91.682 4.934s73.383 0 91.682-4.934c10.098-2.718 18.049-10.72 20.748-20.882 4.904-18.421 4.904-56.85 4.904-56.85s0-38.431-4.904-56.85"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="m93.333 117.559 61.333-34.89-61.333-34.894z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;a class="watch-on-youtube-VpQ9SPwNPvY" href="https://youtu.be/VpQ9SPwNPvY" target="_blank" data-url="https://youtu.be/VpQ9SPwNPvY" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Watch On &lt;svg class="youtube-logo" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 507.9 113.39"&gt;&lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;path d="M64.792 80.99V32.396l42.082 24.297zm93.803-63.285a20.285 20.285 0 0 0-14.32-14.32C131.642 0 80.99 0 80.99 0S30.337 0 17.705 3.385a20.286 20.286 0 0 0-14.32 14.32C0 30.338 0 56.693 0 56.693S0 83.049 3.385 95.68A20.285 20.285 0 0 0 17.705 110c12.632 3.386 63.285 3.386 63.285 3.386s50.652 0 63.285-3.386a20.284 20.284 0 0 0 14.32-14.32c3.385-12.632 3.385-38.988 3.385-38.988s0-26.355-3.385-38.988m94.473 74.326c.887-2.314 1.332-6.098 1.332-11.35V58.556c0-5.097-.445-8.822-1.332-11.178-.888-2.355-2.452-3.533-4.69-3.533-2.163 0-3.69 1.178-4.577 3.533-.888 2.356-1.332 6.081-1.332 11.178V80.68c0 5.25.424 9.035 1.275 11.35.848 2.318 2.392 3.475 4.633 3.475 2.239 0 3.803-1.157 4.691-3.475zm-17.953 11.122c-3.207-2.16-5.486-5.52-6.835-10.079-1.352-4.554-2.027-10.617-2.027-18.185v-10.31c0-7.644.771-13.784 2.316-18.417 1.544-4.633 3.956-8.011 7.24-10.135 3.282-2.123 7.587-3.186 12.916-3.186 5.251 0 9.459 1.082 12.626 3.243 3.165 2.162 5.482 5.542 6.95 10.136 1.466 4.595 2.2 10.715 2.2 18.36v10.31c0 7.567-.714 13.65-2.142 18.243-1.43 4.595-3.747 7.955-6.951 10.077-3.205 2.124-7.548 3.186-13.03 3.186-5.64 0-10.06-1.082-13.263-3.243m248.053-57.981c-.81 1.005-1.352 2.646-1.621 4.923-.272 2.278-.404 5.734-.404 10.367v5.097h11.697V60.46c0-4.555-.155-8.011-.463-10.367-.309-2.355-.868-4.014-1.678-4.98-.812-.966-2.067-1.449-3.766-1.449-1.7 0-2.954.503-3.765 1.506zm-2.025 29.886v3.591c0 4.557.132 7.974.404 10.251.269 2.279.828 3.94 1.68 4.982.849 1.041 2.16 1.564 3.938 1.564 2.392 0 4.035-.927 4.923-2.781.887-1.853 1.37-4.942 1.447-9.268l13.785.812c.077.62.116 1.469.116 2.548 0 6.565-1.795 11.47-5.387 14.712-3.589 3.242-8.669 4.865-15.232 4.865-7.876 0-13.398-2.47-16.564-7.414-3.168-4.94-4.75-12.586-4.75-22.935V63.589c0-10.657 1.641-18.436 4.924-23.342 3.281-4.903 8.9-7.355 16.854-7.355 5.482 0 9.691 1.004 12.626 3.012 2.933 2.01 5 5.137 6.197 9.383 1.197 4.247 1.796 10.117 1.796 17.607v12.163h-26.757m-284.953-1.33-18.187-65.68h15.869l6.37 29.77c1.623 7.339 2.82 13.594 3.591 18.766h.464c.54-3.706 1.738-9.922 3.591-18.65l6.603-29.886h15.869l-18.417 65.68v31.51h-15.754v-31.51M322.115 34.23v71.007h-12.511l-1.39-8.688h-.347c-3.399 6.564-8.496 9.845-15.291 9.845-4.71 0-8.185-1.543-10.425-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.359-7.915-3.359-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.348 5.426 1.043 6.776.695 1.353 1.853 2.027 3.475 2.027 1.39 0 2.722-.423 3.996-1.275 1.274-.849 2.22-1.928 2.838-3.241V34.229h15.986m81.995.001v71.007h-12.511l-1.391-8.688h-.345c-3.402 6.564-8.498 9.845-15.292 9.845-4.711 0-8.186-1.543-10.426-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.358-7.915-3.358-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.347 5.426 1.041 6.776.696 1.353 1.855 2.027 3.476 2.027 1.391 0 2.723-.423 3.996-1.275 1.275-.849 2.22-1.928 2.839-3.241V34.229h15.985"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M365.552 20.908h-15.87v84.329h-15.637v-84.33h-15.869V8.05h47.376v12.858m76.811 53.636c0 5.174-.215 9.229-.639 12.162-.424 2.937-1.139 5.021-2.143 6.255-1.004 1.236-2.357 1.854-4.053 1.854a7.404 7.404 0 0 1-3.65-.927c-1.12-.618-2.026-1.544-2.722-2.78V50.796c.54-1.93 1.467-3.513 2.78-4.749 1.313-1.234 2.74-1.853 4.285-1.853 1.623 0 2.876.637 3.766 1.91.886 1.275 1.505 3.418 1.853 6.43.348 3.011.523 7.297.523 12.857zm14.652-28.964c-.967-4.478-2.531-7.721-4.692-9.73-2.163-2.007-5.136-3.011-8.919-3.011-2.935 0-5.676.83-8.224 2.49a16.926 16.926 0 0 0-5.908 6.545h-.117l.001-37.416h-15.405v100.777h13.204l1.622-6.717h.347c1.235 2.393 3.088 4.285 5.56 5.675 2.47 1.39 5.213 2.085 8.225 2.085 5.404 0 9.382-2.491 11.931-7.471 2.548-4.982 3.823-12.76 3.823-23.341V64.23c0-7.953-.484-14.17-1.448-18.65"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="91c42b6f-e729-49ae-8620-a142e655b1a6"&gt;This is a Pilates move that many people see as a stretch, but it’s also a fantastic way to switch on your core muscles. “It’s really good for mobility, flexibility, breath integration as well as core engagement, alignment and focus,” says Skinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 3&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="261a4ffb-5199-401a-b19d-6b7db06c27ab"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stand with your feet hip-distance apart.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tuck your ribcage in and squeeze your glutes slightly to &lt;a href="https://www.fitandwell.com/how-to/how-to-engage-your-core" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.fitandwell.com/how-to/how-to-engage-your-core"&gt;engage your core&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly tuck your chin toward your chest and lower your head, moving from the top of the spine down, vertebrae by vertebrae, with your arms hanging loosely by your body.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bend your knees as you get closer to the floor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Once your hands touch the floor, slowly roll back up to the start.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-2-bird-dog" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-2-bird-dog"&gt;&lt;span&gt;2. Bird dog&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class="youtube-video youtube-facade" data-nosnippet id="sznVxQViN-Q"&gt;
&lt;div class="video-aspect-box"&gt;
&lt;div class="watch-on-iframe-sznVxQViN-Q" data-yt-video-token="sznVxQViN-Q" title="Bird Dog for Seniors: Horizontal - YouTube"&gt;
&lt;span class="youtube-video-title"&gt;Bird Dog for Seniors: Horizontal - YouTube&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;img src="https://img.youtube.com/vi/sznVxQViN-Q/maxresdefault.jpg" alt="Bird Dog for Seniors: Horizontal - YouTube" data-aspect-ratio="16/9" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;svg class="play-button" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 234.67 165.33"&gt;&lt;path fill="red" d="M229.763 25.817c-2.699-10.162-10.65-18.165-20.748-20.881C190.716 0 117.333 0 117.333 0S43.951 0 25.651 4.936C15.553 7.652 7.6 15.655 4.903 25.817 0 44.236 0 82.667 0 82.667s0 38.429 4.903 56.85C7.6 149.68 15.553 157.681 25.65 160.4c18.3 4.934 91.682 4.934 91.682 4.934s73.383 0 91.682-4.934c10.098-2.718 18.049-10.72 20.748-20.882 4.904-18.421 4.904-56.85 4.904-56.85s0-38.431-4.904-56.85"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path fill="#fff" d="m93.333 117.559 61.333-34.89-61.333-34.894z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;a class="watch-on-youtube-sznVxQViN-Q" href="https://youtu.be/sznVxQViN-Q" target="_blank" data-url="https://youtu.be/sznVxQViN-Q" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;Watch On &lt;svg class="youtube-logo" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 507.9 113.39"&gt;&lt;g fill="#fff"&gt;&lt;path d="M64.792 80.99V32.396l42.082 24.297zm93.803-63.285a20.285 20.285 0 0 0-14.32-14.32C131.642 0 80.99 0 80.99 0S30.337 0 17.705 3.385a20.286 20.286 0 0 0-14.32 14.32C0 30.338 0 56.693 0 56.693S0 83.049 3.385 95.68A20.285 20.285 0 0 0 17.705 110c12.632 3.386 63.285 3.386 63.285 3.386s50.652 0 63.285-3.386a20.284 20.284 0 0 0 14.32-14.32c3.385-12.632 3.385-38.988 3.385-38.988s0-26.355-3.385-38.988m94.473 74.326c.887-2.314 1.332-6.098 1.332-11.35V58.556c0-5.097-.445-8.822-1.332-11.178-.888-2.355-2.452-3.533-4.69-3.533-2.163 0-3.69 1.178-4.577 3.533-.888 2.356-1.332 6.081-1.332 11.178V80.68c0 5.25.424 9.035 1.275 11.35.848 2.318 2.392 3.475 4.633 3.475 2.239 0 3.803-1.157 4.691-3.475zm-17.953 11.122c-3.207-2.16-5.486-5.52-6.835-10.079-1.352-4.554-2.027-10.617-2.027-18.185v-10.31c0-7.644.771-13.784 2.316-18.417 1.544-4.633 3.956-8.011 7.24-10.135 3.282-2.123 7.587-3.186 12.916-3.186 5.251 0 9.459 1.082 12.626 3.243 3.165 2.162 5.482 5.542 6.95 10.136 1.466 4.595 2.2 10.715 2.2 18.36v10.31c0 7.567-.714 13.65-2.142 18.243-1.43 4.595-3.747 7.955-6.951 10.077-3.205 2.124-7.548 3.186-13.03 3.186-5.64 0-10.06-1.082-13.263-3.243m248.053-57.981c-.81 1.005-1.352 2.646-1.621 4.923-.272 2.278-.404 5.734-.404 10.367v5.097h11.697V60.46c0-4.555-.155-8.011-.463-10.367-.309-2.355-.868-4.014-1.678-4.98-.812-.966-2.067-1.449-3.766-1.449-1.7 0-2.954.503-3.765 1.506zm-2.025 29.886v3.591c0 4.557.132 7.974.404 10.251.269 2.279.828 3.94 1.68 4.982.849 1.041 2.16 1.564 3.938 1.564 2.392 0 4.035-.927 4.923-2.781.887-1.853 1.37-4.942 1.447-9.268l13.785.812c.077.62.116 1.469.116 2.548 0 6.565-1.795 11.47-5.387 14.712-3.589 3.242-8.669 4.865-15.232 4.865-7.876 0-13.398-2.47-16.564-7.414-3.168-4.94-4.75-12.586-4.75-22.935V63.589c0-10.657 1.641-18.436 4.924-23.342 3.281-4.903 8.9-7.355 16.854-7.355 5.482 0 9.691 1.004 12.626 3.012 2.933 2.01 5 5.137 6.197 9.383 1.197 4.247 1.796 10.117 1.796 17.607v12.163h-26.757m-284.953-1.33-18.187-65.68h15.869l6.37 29.77c1.623 7.339 2.82 13.594 3.591 18.766h.464c.54-3.706 1.738-9.922 3.591-18.65l6.603-29.886h15.869l-18.417 65.68v31.51h-15.754v-31.51M322.115 34.23v71.007h-12.511l-1.39-8.688h-.347c-3.399 6.564-8.496 9.845-15.291 9.845-4.71 0-8.185-1.543-10.425-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.359-7.915-3.359-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.348 5.426 1.043 6.776.695 1.353 1.853 2.027 3.475 2.027 1.39 0 2.722-.423 3.996-1.275 1.274-.849 2.22-1.928 2.838-3.241V34.229h15.986m81.995.001v71.007h-12.511l-1.391-8.688h-.345c-3.402 6.564-8.498 9.845-15.292 9.845-4.711 0-8.186-1.543-10.426-4.633-2.24-3.087-3.358-7.915-3.358-14.48V34.23h15.985v52.126c0 3.168.347 5.426 1.041 6.776.696 1.353 1.855 2.027 3.476 2.027 1.391 0 2.723-.423 3.996-1.275 1.275-.849 2.22-1.928 2.839-3.241V34.229h15.985"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;path d="M365.552 20.908h-15.87v84.329h-15.637v-84.33h-15.869V8.05h47.376v12.858m76.811 53.636c0 5.174-.215 9.229-.639 12.162-.424 2.937-1.139 5.021-2.143 6.255-1.004 1.236-2.357 1.854-4.053 1.854a7.404 7.404 0 0 1-3.65-.927c-1.12-.618-2.026-1.544-2.722-2.78V50.796c.54-1.93 1.467-3.513 2.78-4.749 1.313-1.234 2.74-1.853 4.285-1.853 1.623 0 2.876.637 3.766 1.91.886 1.275 1.505 3.418 1.853 6.43.348 3.011.523 7.297.523 12.857zm14.652-28.964c-.967-4.478-2.531-7.721-4.692-9.73-2.163-2.007-5.136-3.011-8.919-3.011-2.935 0-5.676.83-8.224 2.49a16.926 16.926 0 0 0-5.908 6.545h-.117l.001-37.416h-15.405v100.777h13.204l1.622-6.717h.347c1.235 2.393 3.088 4.285 5.56 5.675 2.47 1.39 5.213 2.085 8.225 2.085 5.404 0 9.382-2.491 11.931-7.471 2.548-4.982 3.823-12.76 3.823-23.341V64.23c0-7.953-.484-14.17-1.448-18.65"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/g&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p id="518f0f5a-66cc-42c2-bb31-54b9435acefc"&gt;This is a popular, full-body Pilates move, but Skinner says it’s a great way to learn how to engage your core.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s really good for balance, proprioception [your sense of where your body is] and spatial awareness,” she says, explaining that these skills are particularly useful as we get older. “Having a good sense of how your body moves through space can help to avoid injuries.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reps:&lt;/strong&gt; 3-5 each side&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="4d1e3f43-4bc2-4298-bf22-6c3ba0c77b6b"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Start on your hands and knees, with your knees directly below your hips and your hands directly below your shoulders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tuck your pelvis in to engage your core.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Extend one arm forward to shoulder height and the opposite leg back.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pause for a second, keeping the rest of your body stable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Slowly bring your arm and leg under your torso, gently rounding your spine as you do.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Complete the repetitions on one side then repeat on the other.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;a id="elk-3-forearm-plank" href="" data-url="" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 class="article-body__section" id="section-3-forearm-plank"&gt;&lt;span&gt;3. Forearm plank&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="872cd79e-8723-43c5-90d3-2773a3fee22a"&gt;The plank is a fundamental core exercise—it recruits a variety of muscles and tests your stability. “It gets your back in good alignment, works the core, glutes and hamstrings, as well as muscles in your arms,” says Skinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She recommends a forearm plank over a full plank for beginners. “A forearm plank is a little bit more gentle on the wrists,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time:&lt;/strong&gt; 20sec&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul id="fa9b2ebd-cec3-4713-ab9b-6a8dc321dff8"&gt;&lt;li&gt;From kneeling, place your forearms on the floor, with your forearms and elbows underneath your shoulders, palms facing down.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tuck your toes, engage your core and lift your knees off the floor so your body is raised and in a straight line from head to heels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hold for 20 seconds to start, aiming to gradually increase how long you can hold it for as you get stronger.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fit&amp;Well</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 05:03:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgJBVV95cUxOYVM5d1AyU2lVWkJrcE1DS01nQXFBMVF2NF9Kb0FsdFB0S3VfTW1JTEtudDU1bU1rUWhOdGxaSEJMb3dsdUphOVk3cExYdGRhZ2hkb044TlRyclF1UEtJbm01eVRDOGNjb1ZpczM4MThMemE0aGtLZzRUZEVLUDFEcWxBLWowUDVHNU8tVFJuTTAyZzVYVFUzQnN5Z08yLW9Sck9HOFFEVzRTMEhvVjF6N09HSUVyY191dHZtQ1RweUJHX0x6RGZEUXpEa1c4TU5OYUtQQ2ZVRFNDZnV5SzcwbXppQVF2c194NVNEM19vVWpielRKZEpnTHFhZzZ1TWhQd1h3R1QxdmRjdm4xU3hvWE1Dc0RJOHAyb2tUMkh4cFlxQ1Q4WExQeklLeEk3NFI5ZkE</guid></item><item><title>拥有26年经验的神经外科医生警告说，您的高血压是一个无声的杀手： “您的血流量会减少......” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/neurosurgeon-with-26-years-of-experience-warns-your-high-blood-pressure-is-silent-killer-you-get-less-blood-flow-101762139496234.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/neurosurgeon-with-26-years-of-experience-warns-your-high-blood-pressure-is-silent-killer-you-get-less-blood-flow-101762139496234.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;As per &lt;a rel="nofollow" href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/hypertension" target="_blank" class="backlink" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="World Health Organisation"&gt;World Health Organisation&lt;/a&gt;, hypertension (high blood pressure) is a major cause of premature death worldwide, and an estimated 1.4 billion adults aged 30–79 years worldwide had hypertension in 2024; this represents 33 percent of the population in this age range, per WHO. &lt;strong&gt;Also read | &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-reveals-if-low-blood-pressure-can-trigger-heart-attack-shefali-jariwala-cause-of-death-speculation-101751355746236.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Cardiologist reveals if low blood pressure can trigger heart attack amid Shefali Jariwala’s cause of death speculation"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cardiologist reveals if low blood pressure can trigger heart attack amid Shefali Jariwala’s cause of death speculation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/03/550x309/shutterstock_2492441657_1744720954366_1762139936301.jpg" alt="Elevated blood pressure can damage blood vessel linings, leading to plaque buildup (atherosclerosis) and reduced blood flow to vital organs.(Shutterstock)" title="Elevated blood pressure can damage blood vessel linings, leading to plaque buildup (atherosclerosis) and reduced blood flow to vital organs.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/03/550x309/shutterstock_2492441657_1744720954366_1762139936301.jpg" alt="Elevated blood pressure can damage blood vessel linings, leading to plaque buildup (atherosclerosis) and reduced blood flow to vital organs.(Shutterstock)" title="Elevated blood pressure can damage blood vessel linings, leading to plaque buildup (atherosclerosis) and reduced blood flow to vital organs.(Shutterstock)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Elevated blood pressure can damage blood vessel linings, leading to plaque buildup (atherosclerosis) and reduced blood flow to vital organs.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What is hypertension?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/health-and-fitness/stop-self-medication-it-can-kill-patients-with-hypertension/story-yGk2ICZY6TECRlJub9Y7HI.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Hypertension"&gt;Hypertension &lt;/a&gt;occurs when the pressure in your blood vessels is too high (140/90 mmHg or higher) – it is common but can be serious if left untreated, as per WHO. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;On November 2, Dr Brian Hoeflinger – a neurosurgeon with 26 years of experience from Ohio in the US – took to Instagram to explain that high blood pressure is known as the 'silent killer' because it often doesn't show any symptoms, and people can go years without knowing they have the condition until a severe health issue arises.&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The dangers of untreated hypertension&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the video he posted, Dr Hoeflinger talked about how elevated blood pressure damages the blood vessel lining, leading to plaque buildup, known as atherosclerosis, which narrows vessels and reduces blood flow to vital organs. According to Dr Hoeflinger, this can cause fatal&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/cardiologist-shares-top-prevention-tips-for-people-in-20s-30s-40s-to-reduce-risk-of-heart-attacks-heart-disease-101755066069846.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="heart attacks"&gt; heart attacks&lt;/a&gt; or strokes, and almost 50 percent of individuals with high blood pressure don't experience symptoms, making regular monitoring crucial.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Do you know why high blood pressure is known as the silent killer? Because what happens when you have elevated blood pressure? That causes injury to the lining of your blood vessels in your body. And that injury results in a buildup of plaques known as atherosclerosis. And these plaques, as they build up, narrow the blood vessels. And once the blood vessels narrow, you get less blood flow to your body,” he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Hoeflinger added: “Particularly if you get less blood flow to the heart or brain, that can result in a heart attack or stroke, which can be fatal. Unfortunately, up to 50 percent of the people that have high blood pressure don't have symptoms from it and don't even know that they have it. And so that's why it's called the silent killer.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;How to lower your blood pressure naturally?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Want to know more about managing high blood pressure or reducing your risk factors? In a June 2025 &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/lower-your-blood-pressure-naturally-outsmart-hypertension-and-save-your-heart-with-lifestyle-changes-that-actually-work-101750833505700.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="interview"&gt;interview &lt;/a&gt;with HT Lifestyle, Dr Santosh Kumar Dora, consultant cardiologist at Mumbai's Asian Heart Institute, shared tips on how to lower your blood pressure naturally.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;He said, “Lifestyle modifications – such as adopting a healthy diet low in sodium, engaging in regular physical activity, maintaining a healthy weight, limiting alcohol consumption and managing stress, can significantly lower blood pressure and, in some cases, even eliminate the need for medication.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This report is based on user-generated content from social media. HT.com has not independently verified the claims and does not endorse them.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;   &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 03:30:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgJBVV95cUxNV3FNaGJwbFRXQ1NRcDh5RElEUmliMmRndU9HQjlWTTBvRWFYdVo1VXJkQXdXT3djTllvM1BGa1BJTVBKU2tINUJqVVFQY19qclg0dzJpZGZQdDNFLUNELWdQR1hvWnJfZGNUUTBVaFltMzUzMXhSNGVMQlRNQUlERkVab2RJOFBRY1FiZVlPdlc1U0FIcnhHS3lyTWdsa0RMNjV3MFBnakJkNVl2bW13LXQzWlY5blRvakp6VmZBelZsTGxCemxrMlNreHJzXzQyMWRjc0xiNjlsLUZpYzhNVmhaWFFmeGJ3YnAyTURVSzFneGhrWUpGV01ZY2VraUxsT2dmUEhfczdMYXJ0aEHSAZMCQVVfeXFMT0lPR19oRkZjOU41ZGRXWU5JUzJHWjZWZ2NqMFZONzlMOGJKZ3pzYTlBaVZOZ1hScTVobVI0Ml9EY0ZZSGMxLUZ3N3V2X2pOQWVNUmRyMUxLOVJwazlRRXdjVDNjVmV6ZjVMdkJNSmdRVjE4WG9VMDM4VVVVUjBzZEVlNlJfa2JrOFZNdElPVC13Q1gtaWdRdlUwUkxBRzBLaW1uYUV6NXRmT3NaZDFtREIxbXd1WmZZVHNkRWQyZVdoZDhvME9wVFZYcDI1UjhQVElZMWR0RW5CUVlWMnd1eHE4N09lQmZIenZQZEVyaE5QLS1GaWRZX2poRVBrS3I5MXpPRUpoaVY0RHhtbVlvRWFUcDg</guid></item><item><title>想在今年秋天领养一只成年犬？ 7天计划、5个代价高昂的错误和120 £的兽医线索- Sofeminine.co.uk</title><link>https://www.sofeminine.co.uk/thinking-of-adopting-an-adult-dog-this-autumn-7-day-plan-5-costly-mistakes-and-120-vet-clues/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content clear" itemprop="text"&gt;

		
		&lt;p&gt;Cold evenings, busy shelters and anxious owners raise the same question: how do you settle an adult dog with calm?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Across the UK, rescues expect a seasonal rise in adult adoptions as nights draw in. A clear first fortnight reduces stress, prevents bites and cuts the risk of returns. Here is a practical roadmap for people bringing home a grown dog, with costs, timings and simple steps that build trust quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874125"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Why autumn adoptions demand a plan&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Shorter days, wet pavements and fireworks can rattle even the steadiest rescue dog. Many arrive with an emotional history and unfamiliar routines. Homes feel noisy. Streets smell different. A plan narrows the world, adds predictability and stops misunderstandings from snowballing into anxiety or reactivity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Day one is about safety, not affection quotas. Reduce choices, give structure, and let the dog opt in.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Set up a safe base within one hour&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before the dog steps inside, prepare a quiet corner away from through-traffic and doorways. Choose a draft-free spot near warmth, but not next to a radiator that could overheat a resting body. Keep it stable for the first week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874126"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Room layout that lowers cortisol&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Heavy, non-slip bed or crate with the door open for choice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fresh water within two metres, changed twice daily.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Two tough chews to channel stress into licking and gnawing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baby gate to manage access without confrontation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Soft cloth with familiar scent if provided by the rescue.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Set feeding and walking at predictable times. Use the same tone of voice and the same short phrases. Predictability reduces uncertainty, which reduces adrenaline spikes and barking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The 7-day routine that calms adult dogs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Day(s)&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Focus&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th&gt;Practical measure&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;1–2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Decompression&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Short garden breaks, house tour on lead, one room base camp, gentle hand-feeding.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;3–4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Safe walks&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Two 15-minute walks on a Y-harness, quiet streets, allow sniffing, no greetings.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td&gt;5–7&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Light training&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td&gt;Three 3-minute sessions: name response, settle on mat, swap game for toys.&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anchor mealtimes 10–12 hours apart. Keep play brief and frequent. Sleep drives recovery; an adult rescue may need up to 16 hours of rest spread across the day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874128"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Five mistakes that cost you time, money and trust&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Too much freedom, too soon. Roaming leads to toilet slips and guarding. Use doors, pens and routines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Forcing introductions. Crowds, pubs and family parties overwhelm. Start with one person at a time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skipping the early vet check. Hidden pain fuels growls. Budget £120–£180 for a baseline consult and core vaccinations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using only a collar. A secure harness plus ID tag reduces escapes and injury; expect £25–£40.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Correcting fear with scolding. Fear punished becomes fear plus you. Pay calm, reward curiosity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Behaviour is often a pain story. Treat discomfort and half the “naughtiness” fades without a fight.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Health check in 48 hours: what to ask your vet&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Book an appointment within two days. Bring any rescue paperwork and note changes you observe at home. Ask targeted questions to build a health baseline.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vaccinations, microchip registration and parasite cover plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oral health: gum inflammation and worn teeth affect mood and food.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobility: screen for arthritis and cruciate issues; request a pain trial if murky.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weight: set a target range and feeding grams, not “cups”.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skin and ears: rule out allergies that drive rubbing and snapping.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Noise sensitivity ahead of fireworks: consider desensitisation and vet-approved aids.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Reading the small signals&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Adult dogs speak softly before they shout. Ears pinned, head turns, slow blinking and yawning show discomfort. Lip licking outside mealtimes can flag tension. A stiff tail says caution, not confidence. When you notice uneasy signals, reduce demands, add space and switch to calm, low-arousal tasks like scenting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When in doubt, lower the ask, raise the distance, and pay the calm you want to see again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874129"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Social introductions without the meltdown&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;People first, then pets&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One visitor at a time, seated, no looming over the dog.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Give the dog the choice to approach; no touching unless they request it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scatter a handful of treats away from feet to relieve social pressure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Walking beyond the postcode&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Double-clip the lead to harness and collar for backup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start at quiet times; add busier places for short intervals mid-walk.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Keep ID on at all times; update the microchip record the same day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;The calm contact method that builds trust&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Think “I am available, not insistent”. Sit on the floor with a turned shoulder and relaxed hands. Drop snacks next to you without eye contact. If the dog checks in, gently stroke chest or shoulder for two seconds, then stop and let them ask again. Short, predictable kindness beats marathon cuddles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Training that lowers stress fast&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Settle on a mat: reward any glance or paw on the mat. Build to 60 seconds of relaxed resting.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hand targeting: dog taps your palm, you pay. Handy for redirection away from triggers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Swap cue: present treat, say “swap”, take toy only after the dog releases. Prevents guarding rows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Keep sessions tiny. Three minutes, three times a day, in the quietest room. Progress comes from repetition, not heroics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What to do when setbacks appear&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many adult dogs follow the 3-3-3 pattern: three days to decompress, three weeks to learn the routine, three months to feel at home. Expect wobbles around week three as confidence grows. Regression is common after busy weekends. Dial back the schedule, rebuild the routine and practise the calm contact method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Extra help when history is unclear&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If behaviour feels sticky, book two sessions with a reward-based trainer accredited by a UK body. Bring video clips from daily life, a sleep log and a list of triggers. One well-timed change—like moving the bed or swapping the route—often releases the knot more than a dozen corrections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Added gains you can bank this month&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Budgeting protects the bond. Price your first-month essentials: £120–£180 vet baseline, £40 harness and lead, £25 tag and bowls, £30 bedding, £20 chews and food puzzles. Pet insurance reduces shocks; look at excess amounts and dental cover. Keep receipts; charities may offer discounts if you adopted from them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For enrichment, think nose, not speed. Scatter feeding in the garden, a rolled towel with kibble for unwrapping, cardboard “parcel” puzzles and short scent trails indoors drain stress without overexciting. Rotate toys every two days so novelty works for you. A calm brain learns. A predictable home heals. And a measured first week pays off for years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-type="_mgwidget" data-widget-id="1874130"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

		
		
			&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Sofeminine.co.uk</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 02:36:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivwFBVV95cUxNM3BXWHVrbmZhdkM0dmlWSDFpdFlqX0dJeWFJVjR5bkd5U1o0aGh2M3hkczNVQUF6amMwRjg2ejVPaEg2T3VvNVlvVDE5S2pna1VEbXNZYll4TlJDRm9jUUVRNmE3dzRXb3JFaEYyZ2RRQ2dSVWNZU1RieklEQk5UT201SHVWdW5BY2ZyUU1TMUVIdnpEMXhxaHV1dE93QWIxWGk0a1pTR2l5aklNY0hmYTBQNldoNWhrdVdDVHB3Zw</guid></item><item><title>年轻人中结直肠癌上升：洛杉矶顶级外科医生列出了应避免的五种食物和饮料-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/colorectal-cancer-rising-among-young-adults-top-la-surgeon-lists-five-foods-and-drinks-to-avoid/articleshow/125044455.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;p&gt;Colorectal cancer, which is also the most common type of gastrointestinal cancer, is increasing globally. Of late, there has been an alarming rise in the incidence of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/bjs/article-abstract/112/7/znaf102/8191209?redirectedFrom=fulltext" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;early-onset colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. A recent analysis by the Centers for Disease Control revealed an &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/united-states-cancer-statistics/publications/colorectal-cancer-stat-bite.html" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;185% increase in colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; among adults aged between 20 and 24, and a 333% increase in incidence among people aged between 15 and 19.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Karen Zaghiyan, a leading board-certified colorectal surgeon based in LA, highlights the alarming spike in colorectal cancer among young people in a video shared on Instagram. “We're seeing an alarming rise in young-onset colorectal cancer,” she said. The surgeon also listed some everyday foods and beverages that may be fuelling the disease. What are they? Let’s take a look.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Colorectal cancer is the third most common cancer in India and it’s fully treatable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Red meat&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="What is red meat?" msid="125044467" width="" title="Image credits: Getty Images" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-125044467/what-is-red-meat.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Image credits: Getty Images&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red meat has long been linked with an &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC4698595/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;increased risk of colorectal cancer&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. Dr Zaghiyan advises avoiding red meats, including beef, veal, lamb, and pork. “There's about an 18% increased risk of colorectal cancer in people who regularly consume red meat. We don't know of a safe amount, and if you're charring your meat, i.e. cooking it over a flame, that adds even more risk,” the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="21"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="22"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Processed meat&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second on the surgeon’s list is processed meats such as bacon, sausages, hot dogs, ham, salami, pepperoni, and deli meats. “Any of these are processed meats, and they increase your risk of colorectal cancer by 15 to 35% if you're eating one serving a day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The less you eat, the better. There is no defined safe amount,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sweetened beverages&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, sugary drinks are not just adding extra calories; they are also a red flag for your overall health. Store-bought juices, carbonated sodas, and fizzy drinks may taste sweet, but they are making your health bitter. “These beverages are artificially sugared with high-fructose corn syrup, sucrose, and fructose, and consumption of these has been associated with the development of colorectal cancer. A study found that two servings a day of sugared beverages doubled your risk of colorectal cancer versus those individuals who had it less than once a week,” the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="34"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Alcohol&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the best ways to reduce your risk of colorectal cancer? Quit, or at least limit, alcohol intake. Dr Zaghiyan emphasises that this includes beer and wine. “This is particularly magnified in individuals who consume alcohol daily. However, there is no safe amount that has been defined. Alcohol not only increases your risk of colorectal cancer, but it also increases your risk of multiple other cancers,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Ultra-processed foods&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultra-processed foods such as chips or ready-to-eat noodles are convenient, but they come at the hidden cost of your health. The colorectal cancer surgeon suggests avoiding anything that comes pre-packaged. “These include chips, packaged cereals, packaged baked goods, and a lot of store-bought breads. All fall into the category of ultra-processed foods,” she explained. The doctor adds that these foods are linked with an increased risk of various gut conditions and colorectal cancer. Why? “Due to the existence of emulsifiers, artificial sweeteners, and various additional additives like food dyes that come in these foods.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The doctor also suggests increasing the intake of whole foods, fruits, vegetables, and whole grains to minimise risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="52"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="54"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 01:27:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAJBVV95cUxQS0FaeHZROF9FN0xZYkhDNW1Pc2lQakNhMmpnTHJqU1B5ckxwMDRoUC1PZlBpVzZzMW1BV08ta2JIeElQaTdDdmkyWWhKT3lnTGhITjJjcm51TnNOOU1uZkZuY0VwZUxqNkQzQm9fQU82b2VYbndQQ3BwWnJhY054alctRmVnVHFGb2dXLUFWY1BMLTluajM1UmR6UzJYNXNUZEJDZUJjSmZKTzV2NGpKZUtrV3BvdkZaeHJhajVqc0lEUF85dGpZcjN3VURuc0pIVmRfTURPLTBCc1hnaHFrR01HOFhzNmx1QUtUU1VzeVBhZ1c4cVZIWWhhb3IxdlUyaEdXcHhHcW9rdFRfZGtMQ2hYcGQwSzEzNW1sUnQtUU8</guid></item><item><title>NHS医院将测试有助于诊断和治疗前列腺癌的人工智能工具-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/nov/03/nhs-hospitals-to-test-ai-tool-that-helps-diagnose-and-treat-prostate-cancer</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A tool that uses artificial intelligence to help diagnose men with prostate cancer and guide decisions about treatment is to be tested in &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/nhs" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;NHS&lt;/a&gt; hospitals, researchers have announced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The £1.9m Vanguard Path study, funded by Prostate &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/cancer" data-link-name="in body link" data-component="auto-linked-tag"&gt;Cancer&lt;/a&gt; UK and led by researchers at the University of Oxford, is expected to last three years and will test an AI tool called the ArteraAI Prostate Biopsy Assay. In total, biopsies from more than 4,000 men will be used.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The tool, which analyses digitised biopsy images to produce a personalised risk score, has already &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/may/30/new-ai-test-can-predict-which-men-will-benefit-from-prostate-cancer-drug" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;been shown in clinical trials&lt;/a&gt; to identify which men with high-risk prostate cancer would be most likely to benefit from the drug abiraterone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However, trials in the US have suggested it could also be used for less aggressive forms of prostate cancer to predict which men are most likely to benefit from having hormone therapy in addition to radiotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In addition, studies have suggested the tool can help identify which patients can be monitored without the need for immediate treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Dr Matthew Hobbs, director of research at Prostate Cancer UK, said: “If and when this gets implemented, you could use one tool irrespective of where you are on the aggressiveness scale, to make a very clinically and life-enhancingly important decision for each of those men.”. He added that the tool was already being widely used in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The new study will first use prostate biopsy samples from men who have already been diagnosed and treated for prostate cancer, and have suitable follow-up data, to explore whether the predictive prowess of the tool is seen when applied to UK patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The tool will then be tested at three sites – North Bristol NHS trust, Oxford University hospitals NHS foundation trust, and NHS Greater Glasgow and Clyde – as men undergo the normal pathway for prostate cancer diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Biopsies will be analysed, the treatment choices will be made, and the man will start treatment. But at the same time, the NHS clinicians will be given a readout from this tool and asked: ‘If you had this, would you have recommended the same treatment or not?’” said Hobbs, adding that part of the trial would also explore to what extent the tool affected the time between diagnosis and treatment choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Experts say the hope is that the tool will eventually help reduce under- and over-treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“A good outcome from this is that this tool is implemented in the NHS,” said Hobbs. However, for that to happen, he said, it had to be shown to be scientifically valid, cost-effective, and making a difference to treatment decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Prof Gerhardt Attard, from University College London, who was involved in the study around abiraterone use but is not part of the trial, said the research was important as approaches often worked well in clinical trials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“When you take that to the real NHS world, there are a number of challenges and differences that would inevitably arise and that’s what this study will address,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Ashley Dalton, the minister for public health and prevention, also welcomed the trial. “This groundbreaking research could be a huge step forward, demonstrating the power of technology to potentially transform lives and improve cancer outcomes,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This is exactly why we’re investing in a digital NHS. By harnessing AI and moving beyond outdated systems, we can transform cancer care – diagnosing earlier, treating more effectively, and improving patient experience.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 00:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxNVWY3RlFVcm1ZTXBTSGpCMjlKcnprNnNSMl9xS0ZFblhZaXZuRmRQdnJGUXNXN2FoMHdaTDFSaVF1RUlsRHpOZ2ZoTGM1RVJzdTBHVVZVUF9fUldwQjlfYWt6aUhpaGtDb0hXQXBlVkJ4bkhvODU3MklQM0k2T2ZvNmdTS1NDbkFDOGhxVl84c0xiQ2dpNTN5QzJLUFhHbnRUcWhmTzZpamxkV19rNEZQTEtYSENVSkFmWkdVcUN2UlI</guid></item><item><title>男性需要比女性锻炼更多才能降低心脏病。原因如下。- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/men-need-to-exercise-more-than-women-to-lower-heart-disease-heres-why</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Exercise is like medicine for the heart, and just like with medication, you need the right "dose" for it to be effective. But a recent study suggests that the dose might not be the same for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers found that men need roughly twice as much exercise as women to see the same reduction in their &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/topics/heart-disease-329"&gt;heart disease risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1038/s44161-025-00732-z"&gt;recent study&lt;/a&gt; asked over 85,000 UK adults aged 37-73 to wear an accelerometer (a device that measures body movement and activity levels) on their wrist for seven days. They then tracked each participant's health outcomes for just under eight years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-heartbeat-budget-could-help-keep-track-of-your-health-study-suggests"&gt;A 'Heartbeat Budget' Could Help Keep Track of Your Health, Study Suggests&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results are eye-opening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women who did roughly four hours of moderate-to-vigorous physical activity per week – activities, such as brisk walking, jogging, cycling or dancing, which raise your breathing and heart rate – had around a 30% lower risk of coronary heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men needed to do roughly nine hours of the same types of physical activity to see a similar reduction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_179856" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-179856" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/man_cycling_heart_642.jpg" alt="man riding a bike" class="wp-image-179856 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/man_cycling_heart_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/man_cycling_heart_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-179856" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Men need to do twice as much exercise as women to reduce heart disease risk by the same amount. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEI_kBvy3g/"&gt;ArtistGNDphotography/Getty Images Signature/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was also true for people already living with heart disease. The paper estimated that women diagnosed with coronary heart disease needed to do around 51 minutes of physical activity each week to reduce their risk of death from any cause by 30% – while men needed to do around 85 minutes of exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although these findings might sound shocking to the average person, they confirm something that exercise scientists have suspected for years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is also a clear biological reason that can partly help explain why women and men see such different results from physical activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Biological differences&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women typically have higher oestrogen levels than men. This hormone has important effects on how the body responds to exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oestrogen can help the body &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1210/jc.2004-1743"&gt;burn more fat for fuel&lt;/a&gt; during endurance exercise and helps keep the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s13293-017-0152-8"&gt;blood vessels&lt;/a&gt; healthy – partly by supporting their energy-producing mitochondria (the tiny powerhouses inside cells that generate energy for vital functions).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women also tend to have more &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/ca.24091"&gt;slow-twitch muscle fibres&lt;/a&gt;, which are efficient and fatigue-resistant. These muscles suit the kinds of steady, sustained physical activity most exercise guidelines recommend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/spark-into-space-comp"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg" alt="Win a $10,000 Space Coast Adventure Holiday" class="alignnone wp-image-177074 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-642x272.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/10/Mid-Article-Promo-Astro.jpg 844w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the gap in "minutes needed" for similar heart benefits between women and men isn't as shocking as the findings might suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the study used &lt;a href="https://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0169649"&gt;device-measured activity&lt;/a&gt;, instead of asking people to recall from memory the amount of activity they did, this means the data on physical activity was accurate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's also important to note the study still showed a graded benefit. More total weekly activity was linked to lower risk of coronary heart disease in both women and men. Everyone gains from moving more. The difference is just in how much activity buys the same reduction in risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study does not claim that women should do less exercise – nor that men can't reach similar benefits. It only shows that men may need more weekly activity to get there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_179859" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-179859" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/woman_outside_exercising_642.jpg" alt="woman exercising" class="wp-image-179859 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/woman_outside_exercising_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/woman_outside_exercising_642-600x327.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-179859" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Women still need to do the recommended amount of exercise each week to keep their hearts healthy. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAGxWNwr2I0/"&gt;Artem Varnitsin/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are limits to keep in mind. Activity was measured for only one week – then people were followed for about eight years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And, as it's an observational study, other factors that could have partly influenced the results were not taken into account – such as menopausal status (when oestrogen levels drop significantly) or whether a woman was using hormone replacement therapy (which can restore some oestrogen levels). These factors could influence how women's bodies responded to exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's also worth noting that the volunteers came from the UK Biobank study. These volunteers &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1093/aje/kwx246"&gt;tend to be healthier&lt;/a&gt; and less deprived than the general population – factors which can affect baseline heart health, access to safe places to exercise and time available for physical activity. This can affect how widely the results apply to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, these results make an important point about current exercise recommendations and whether they need to be revised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Exercise recommendations&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Current exercise guidelines from the &lt;a href="https://bjsm.bmj.com/content/54/24/1451"&gt;World Health Organization&lt;/a&gt;, the American Heart Association and the NHS are sex-neutral. But this new study challenges these recommendations – showing they might not apply equally to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, most exercise research was &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.17226/12908"&gt;done predominantly in men&lt;/a&gt; and results were often assumed to apply equally to women. As better device-based data arrives, we're learning that women and men may get different returns for the same number of active minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This matters because women and men &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1161/CIRCOUTCOMES.117.004437"&gt;experience heart disease differently&lt;/a&gt; – from symptoms to outcomes. If the amount of exercise needed to reach the same benefit also differs, our advice should reflect that while still keeping things simple and practical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This isn't about telling women to exercise less. The 150-minute baseline remains a useful target – &lt;a href="https://www.jacc.org/doi/10.1016/j.jacc.2023.12.019"&gt;and many people don't yet meet it&lt;/a&gt;. What these findings suggest is that women who meet current targets may see more heart health benefits per minute of exercise. That's encouraging news for anyone who struggles to find time for longer workouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For men, the message isn't "double your gym time". It's to keep building activity in ways that fit your week – with more total minutes bringing even greater heart health benefits. Whether different types or intensities of exercise might be more efficient for men remains a question for future research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both men and women clearly benefit from regular physical activity. That's not in question. But what does need to be recognised is the clear biological differences that influence the returns men and women see from the same types of exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1161/CIR.0000000000001289"&gt;Cardiac rehabilitation&lt;/a&gt; and exercise referral schemes often set identical targets for men and women. This new research suggests we may want to rethink schemes and tailor goals to each person's starting point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But until cardiac rehabilitation becomes more personalised, the core message for now is: move more, sit less. Aim for the baseline 150 minutes of exercise each week if you can. More helps if you're able to.&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/268624/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/jack-mcnamara-1352749"&gt;Jack McNamara&lt;/a&gt;, Senior Lecturer in Clinical Exercise Physiology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-east-london-924"&gt;University of East London&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/why-men-need-more-exercise-than-women-to-see-the-same-heart-benefits-268624"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 23:55:51 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQWllmOEdnbVphMV9LZWo5c3VqdjZuTWZVaTBJZWk1RHVNaTUyUzZoeFprT1EyeUZFd21Gb01iY0kyTXF6SjYyVTNJbnloYzVkcTlIR2k0UGhQVlN3cVM3amVXNEFkRjNCSG9vVDAxOU5qTDhVLXhFeU82RTFacnFpendIT1FsMGZfckZXYXk3SXlEcW1VbUhCbTZlUzR4VzA</guid></item><item><title>研究发现肠道和大脑节律之间存在令人惊讶的联系- Medical Xpress</title><link>https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-link-gut-brain-rhythms.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article-byline"&gt;
											by I. Edwards									&lt;/p&gt;
                                                                        &lt;div class="mt-4 article-main"&gt;
									    
&lt;p&gt;The human body is packed with natural rhythms, from your sleep-wake cycle to the steady pulsing of blood through the brain to heart rate and pulse.&lt;/p&gt;

                                        
                                        
                                          
                                         
										

                                                                                                                                    &lt;p&gt;Now, scientists say the gut may hold the key to understanding how this complex coordination happens in the &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/brain/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;brain&lt;/a&gt;'s blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers at the University of California San Diego have discovered that the gut's rhythmic muscle movements could help explain how blood vessels in the brain expand and contract together. Their findings were published recently in the journal &lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="https://journals.aps.org/prl/abstract/10.1103/8njd-qd14" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Physical Review Letters&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When neurons in the brain are stimulated, tiny blood vessels called arterioles expand to deliver more oxygen and nutrients.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These vessels pulse and are often in sync with one another. But for years, scientists have puzzled over how this synchronization occurs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The UC San Diego team turned to the digestive system for answers. They found that the intestines, which naturally contract in waves to move food through, rely on a pattern of synchronized oscillations that form a staircase effect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This same pattern, the researchers say, could also explain how brain &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/blood+vessels/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;blood vessels&lt;/a&gt; work together in harmony.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"Coupled oscillators talk to each other and each section of the intestine is an oscillator that talks to the other sections near it," Massimo Vergassola, professor of physics at UC San Diego, said in a news release.&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                        
    &lt;p class="w-100 mb-4 ads"&gt;
          
        
        &lt;ins class="adsbygoogle" data-ad-layout="in-article" data-ad-format="fluid" data-ad-client="ca-pub-0536483524803400" data-ad-slot="7099578867"&gt;&lt;/ins&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                                                                                                                                &lt;p&gt;"Normally, coupled oscillators are studied in a homogeneous setting, meaning all the oscillators are at more or less similar frequencies," he continued. "In our case, the oscillators were more varied, just as in the intestine and the brain."&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using mathematics, the researchers showed how nearby &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/oscillators/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;oscillators&lt;/a&gt;—whether in the gut or the brain—can lock onto each other's rhythm if their frequencies are similar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This creates step-like transitions, similar to the way food moves smoothly through the intestines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The mathematics had been solved in an approximate way before now, but not in a way that gave you these breaks and what happens at the breaks. That's a critical discovery," David Kleinfeld, professor of physics and neurobiology at UC San Diego, said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The new findings could eventually help scientists better understand not only brain function but also digestive issues affecting the movement of food, liquids and waste through the &lt;a href="https://medicalxpress.com/tags/gastrointestinal+tract/" rel="tag" class="textTag"&gt;gastrointestinal tract&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The brain is infinitely more complicated than the gut, but this is science at its best," Kleinfeld said. "You ask one question, it leads you somewhere else, you solve that problem, then return to your original question."&lt;/p&gt;

                                                                                                                                    
                                                                                
                                        											&lt;div class="article-main__more p-4"&gt;
												                                                    &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information:&lt;/strong&gt;
                                                    Marie Sellier-Prono et al, Defects, Parcellation, and Renormalized Negative Diffusivities in Nonhomogeneous Oscillatory Media, &lt;i&gt;Physical Review Letters&lt;/i&gt; (2025). &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1103/8njd-qd14" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.1103/8njd-qd14&lt;/a&gt;. On &lt;i&gt;arXiv&lt;/i&gt;: &lt;a data-doi="1" href="https://dx.doi.org/10.48550/arxiv.2502.09264" target="_blank"&gt;DOI: 10.48550/arxiv.2502.09264&lt;/a&gt;
																								
																								&lt;/p&gt;
																							&lt;/div&gt;
                                        											
										                                                                                    &lt;p class="article-main__note mt-4"&gt;
                                                Copyright © 2025 &lt;a href="https://consumer.healthday.com/" target="_blank"&gt;HealthDay&lt;/a&gt;. All rights reserved.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                                                                
                                        
                                        &lt;div class="d-none d-print-block"&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="mb-4"&gt;
                                                 &lt;strong&gt;Citation&lt;/strong&gt;:
                                                 Study finds surprising link between gut and brain rhythms (2025, November 2)
                                                 retrieved 3 November 2025
                                                 from https://medicalxpress.com/news/2025-11-link-gut-brain-rhythms.html
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                            &lt;p class="border text-muted p-3"&gt;
                                            This document is subject to copyright. Apart from any fair dealing for the purpose of private study or research, no
                                            part may be reproduced without the written permission. The content is provided for information purposes only.
                                            &lt;/p&gt;
                                        &lt;/div&gt;
                                        
									&lt;/div&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical Xpress</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 19:52:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidEFVX3lxTE9KQWpFUkZLdkczcDdOdTJiSUhLeFl6Z282VDBub09Gb3E0eEhSa2pldHZHRWhYMjk1b2RFZ1ZBWEhpUDRqaUk5ejNwcElkaFNZNmpJU0pQcUJSUlFnRmY5SEoxNzdMUVJnSDg3WlNGX2ZUOEta</guid></item><item><title>天生无手：创新手术消除了20年的疼痛- Ynetnews</title><link>https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/qs0uemi01</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-contents="true"&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="34q4g-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="34q4g-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="34q4g-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Yoav Rokach Penn (47) was born without hands and with short arms as a result of a rare defect. After undergoing surgeries in childhood to build fingers using orthopedic means, designed to help him with daily functioning, he began suffering from severe neuropathic (nerve) pain in his hands, for which no solution was found.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="5o927-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="5o927-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="5o927-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;After dozens of treatments he underwent in Canada, where he has lived with his family for over a decade, he found hope in Israel - in an innovative surgery recently performed at Sheba Medical Center in Tel Hashomer. "I feel excellent today, something I never believed I could say in the past," he told ynet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="fs4u0-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide firstImageInArticle firstImageInArticleBody"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.Sklh6m3SJ11l" id="image_ArticleImageData.Sklh6m3SJ11l"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.Sklh6m3SJ11l" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/11/02/B1HyboPNy11l/B1HyboPNy11l_0_0_1280_853_0_x-large.jpg" alt='יואב רוקח פן עבר ניתוח השתלת קוצבים עצביים שמסייעים בהפחתת כאב כרוני על ידי ד"ר רות גור במרכז הרפואי שיבא' title="Penn underwent a neural pacemaker implantation surgery performed by Dr. Ruth Gur at Sheba Medical Center (Photo: Yair Sagi) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.Sklh6m3SJ11l" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/11/02/B1HyboPNy11l/B1HyboPNy11l_0_0_1280_853_0_x-large.jpg" alt='יואב רוקח פן עבר ניתוח השתלת קוצבים עצביים שמסייעים בהפחתת כאב כרוני על ידי ד"ר רות גור במרכז הרפואי שיבא' title="Penn underwent a neural pacemaker implantation surgery performed by Dr. Ruth Gur at Sheba Medical Center (Photo: Yair Sagi) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Penn underwent a neural pacemaker implantation surgery performed by Dr. Ruth Gur at Sheba Medical Center&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Yair Sagi&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="d4g8a-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="d4g8a-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d4g8a-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;This is what the procedure he underwent looked like: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d4g8a-0-1"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Yoav says the pain began almost 20 years ago and has been getting worse since. "It's paralyzing pain. A person isn't supposed to feel all their organs, you don't feel your nose or ear, and I was constantly feeling my hands, at an annoying and terrible level."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="bht3h-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="bht3h-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="bht3h-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Over the past decade, he was treated at a pain clinic in Canada with both medications and invasive measures such as steroid injections, nerve freezing, and radiofrequency treatment, which according to him only helped for a certain period. "In recent years I went through almost every possible type of treatment, conventional or unconventional, and received medications in insane doses - morphine in quantities of between 5 to 10 mg each time. It turns you into a zombie, and it's terrible," he adds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="84oso-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="84oso-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="84oso-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Despite the disability he was born with, Yoav managed to maintain his independence throughout his life - "studies, degrees, great jobs, relocation, I did everything people dream about most," he says, noting that despite the disability he got a driver's license and was even the first disabled volunteer to go to officers' training course. However, about two years ago, the pain became unbearable, and he was forced to leave his job and invest most of his efforts in finding a solution. "It's a terrible feeling because it's as if all the independence you had suddenly disappears."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="cnl8v-0-0"&gt;&lt;div data-offset-key="cnl8v-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cnl8v-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;This past February, almost by chance, his mother came across an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a id="SkaSqcqWUJ11l" href="https://www.ynetnews.com/health_science/article/rkm1tsx9ye" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cnl8v-1-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;article published on ynet about nerve pacemaker implants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cnl8v-2-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt; that help reduce chronic pain by regulating electrical activity in the spinal cord. The article was written by Dr. Ruth Gur, director of the Center for Neurosurgical Pain Treatment at the Pain Institute at Sheba Medical Center and a specialist in neurosurgery and pain medicine. "What was written there ultimately wasn't suitable for me, but it was an initial opening to contact Dr. Gur, who eventually helped us find the solution," Yoav says.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="492bm-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="492bm-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="492bm-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Implanting electrodes on nerves to control pain is a known procedure that has been performed for decades on patients suffering from severe chronic pain whom previous treatments failed to help. Dr. Ruth Gur explains that in these cases, spinal pacemakers are used that are implanted inside the body - and their electrodes reach the spinal cord to control the electrical signal in the cord and disperse the pain signals. "The electrodes essentially create an electrical field at certain frequencies that mimics nerve activity and 'dresses' the painful nerves, and we transmit through the electrodes something that masks the natural conduction of pain, meaning we block it," she says.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="2gbt4-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.H1eHDN3SyWx" id="image_ArticleImageData.H1eHDN3SyWx"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.H1eHDN3SyWx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/11/02/H100wT641Wg/H100wT641Wg_0_0_2048_1366_0_x-large.jpg" alt='ד"ר אדריאן גרינפלד וד"ר רות גור בעת השתלת קוצב עצבי נגד כאב בבית החולים שיבא' title="Dr. Adrian Greenfeld and Dr. Ruth Gur during a neural pacemaker implantation procedure for pain relief at Sheba Medical Center.
 (Photo: Sheba Spokesperson) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.H1eHDN3SyWx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/11/02/H100wT641Wg/H100wT641Wg_0_0_2048_1366_0_x-large.jpg" alt='ד"ר אדריאן גרינפלד וד"ר רות גור בעת השתלת קוצב עצבי נגד כאב בבית החולים שיבא' title="Dr. Adrian Greenfeld and Dr. Ruth Gur during a neural pacemaker implantation procedure for pain relief at Sheba Medical Center.
 (Photo: Sheba Spokesperson) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Dr. Adrian Greenfeld and Dr. Ruth Gur during a neural pacemaker implantation procedure for pain relief at Sheba Medical Center.
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Sheba Spokesperson&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="36n8h-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="36n8h-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="36n8h-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;According to her, in recent years, thanks to technological development, it's possible to perform the implants also on peripheral nerves, meaning nerves outside the spinal column, such as in hands and legs. Dr. Gur explains that nerves usually have a long course, for example a leg nerve passes from the spinal cord to the tip of the foot. "Say someone was injured by shrapnel in the ankle, I can implant the pacemaker at knee or thigh level, far from that injury, and it will have an effect. But with Yoav, the anatomical damage and the surgeries he underwent over the years caused distortions along the entire nerve pathways. There's no person like him in the world with such an anatomical structure, and therefore even though the technology exists, we had to reinvent the wheel with the surgery." The one who operated with her is Dr. Adrian Greenfeld, a specialist in anesthesia and pain medicine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="eqag5-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="eqag5-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="eqag5-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;"Surgery that hasn't been done anywhere in the world"&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="b0jfo-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="b0jfo-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="b0jfo-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Despite the complexity, Dr. Gur didn't give up, and presented Yoav with the option of an exceptional surgery, with an approach to a central nerve junction that passes from the cervical spine near the collarbone area. During the surgery, the electrode is implanted on the nerve itself under live viewing of the electrode advancement by ultrasound according to a pattern designed based on an MRI performed in advance. Dr. Gur notes that the device is wireless, meaning the pacemaker is outside the body - and connected to it is an antenna that sits on the skin and transmits into a receiver located inside the electrode. From there the electrode transmits the electrical signals opposite to the electrical signals of the pain nerves - into the damaged nerve. "This specific surgery hasn't been done anywhere in the world," she says.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="95upb-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="95upb-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="95upb-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Dr. Gur explains that the main challenge in the surgery lies in its execution, in advance planning and in the sophistication required, as well as in the need for absolute precision in implanting the pacemaker on a specific nerve, given Yoav's complex anatomical structure. According to her, there was much deliberation before the surgery. "There were too many question marks. And yet, we took a calculated risk because it's definitely still within our capabilities," she says.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="d0u4t-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="d0u4t-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="d0u4t-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Yoav says that the doctor who accompanied him in Canada did offer him a surgical option, but according to him what brought him to come specifically to Israel was the high level of medicine in the country, as well as the long waiting times in Canada, which can reach even three years. "The clinic didn't even get around to making initial contact with me, and it was impossible to wait with this," he said. Later it turned out that the surgery offered to him in Canada wasn't at all suitable for his special anatomical case.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="6s9tp-0-0" contenteditable="false"&gt;&lt;div class="ArticleImageComponenta full_wide"&gt;&lt;a class="gelleryOpener" aria-label="open article gallery" data-image-id="ArticleImageData.rJgq2V2SJbx" id="image_ArticleImageData.rJgq2V2SJbx"&gt;&lt;p class="galleryCounterExpand"&gt;&lt;span class="numOfImg"&gt;3&lt;/span&gt; View gallery &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="expand" aria-hidden="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.rJgq2V2SJbx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/11/02/Skx111jv4y11x/Skx111jv4y11x_0_150_853_480_0_x-large.jpg" alt='יואב רוקח פן עבר ניתוח השתלת קוצבים עצביים שמסייעים בהפחתת כאב כרוני על ידי ד"ר רות גור במרכז הרפואי שיבא' title="Yoav Rokach Penn and Dr. Ruth Gur at Sheba Medical Center
 (Photo: Yair Snir) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span class="mobileView"&gt;&lt;img id="ReduxEditableImage_ArticleImageData.rJgq2V2SJbx" src="https://ynet-pic1.yit.co.il/cdn-cgi/image/format=auto/picserver6/crop_images/2025/11/02/Skx111jv4y11x/Skx111jv4y11x_0_150_853_480_0_x-large.jpg" alt='יואב רוקח פן עבר ניתוח השתלת קוצבים עצביים שמסייעים בהפחתת כאב כרוני על ידי ד"ר רות גור במרכז הרפואי שיבא' title="Yoav Rokach Penn and Dr. Ruth Gur at Sheba Medical Center
 (Photo: Yair Snir) " aria-hidden="false"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="ImageDetails"&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCaption"&gt;&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Yoav Rokach Penn and Dr. Ruth Gur at Sheba Medical Center
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="ImageCredit"&gt;(&lt;span disabled class="" contenteditable="false"&gt;Photo: Yair Snir&lt;/span&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="l07t-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="l07t-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="l07t-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;"It's flattering that he came specifically to us," Dr. Gur adds. "He was treated at a respectable pain clinic that didn't even think to offer him this. This proves the excellence and professional level of our unit."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="cgv94-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="cgv94-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="cgv94-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Yoav recently underwent the surgery at Sheba, at this stage only in his right hand, and already now he testifies to significant relief in the pain. "Suddenly there's light," he says. "Since the surgery I haven't taken any pain medication. If the pain was around 9 out of 10 before, today it's 1. I didn't believe it would work at this level, and certainly not so quickly, I was very skeptical. During the week or so that have passed since the surgery I kept convincing myself it wasn't working, that it was just post-surgery euphoria. There's also fear of disappointment after so many attempts, but after I was in a follow-up with Dr. Gur, she told me 'it's not placebo or euphoria, it's an implant that's working'."&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="6m24h-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="6m24h-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="6m24h-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;According to Dr. Gur, the success in Yoav's surgery is an opening for patients who until now received a negative answer. "It gives us an understanding that we can use this technology also in exceptional things that aren't by the book," she says.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text_editor_paragraph ltr" data-block="true" data-editor="d5jlf" data-offset-key="3oj23-0-0"&gt;&lt;p data-offset-key="3oj23-0-0" class="public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr"&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key="3oj23-0-0"&gt;&lt;span data-text="true"&gt;Pain of nerve origin can occur from a variety of causes - combat injury, car accidents, surgeries, and even nerve pain due to herniated disc or chronic inflammation. Dr. Gur explains that pain medicine, by any means, cannot cure the basic problem that caused the pain. "I can't restore a hand that was amputated or reverse a condition after spinal surgery. The goal of pain medicine is to improve the patient's quality of life as much as possible, but we can never predict with absolute certainty in advance if it will help, and if so, how much it will help. We define success as a reduction of 40%-50% of the pain."Retry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ynetnews</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 18:57:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiaEFVX3lxTFBSWEh3eGdOVXRmYTVRd05fTUYxTFRYbTctVUlMbjJHWURJU283T2FsWENzTXRmWWM5WG1ocjE4bFB3NTUtUjFsd0ZsZFBpM05KUGZrTHdWWmptd091T2Q2RzZKX3RtVmJm</guid></item><item><title>为什么这项临床试验给一些年轻的癌症患者带来了希望-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2025/11/01/children-cancer-clinical-trial-solid-tumors/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JWE7YLHN5FDZTERD72FTOVOQAM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Years of caring for children with solid tumors and looking into the eyes of parents starved for hope have led Catherine Bollard to what she calls the most important moment of her career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2VSXFKHFQRBIVJKFKFQS7DT2RE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Children’s National Hospital, where Bollard is senior vice president and chief research officer, is poised to start recruiting children with pediatric sarcomas and other solid tumors that have resisted chemotherapy and radiation for a clinical trial that will use an inventive new technique to combat one of the most persistent problems in cancer care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 17:00:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNOEFYb3RIRUZNbEx3Y0RHeGQ0eVJ6OWk5U3FkYkp0S2xibm16TWszazJWVUtUUUlMV2IwQ1Z5RllrODdiWjZmZVoxcTljSXVjZHZMeklUYXZDMVdEc3QtMENuYk9Cemh1ajlNWkx4UFpNMFNrNG5IM2Z4V1Rsd1RwbHNEUW4zcndWZk9LMGtjTUxkUXhTYmhGQVBB</guid></item><item><title>不仅仅是油炸食品！血管外科医生警告6种常见食物会增加心脏病发作的风险-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/not-just-fried-food-vascular-surgeon-warns-of-6-common-foods-that-raise-heart-attack-risk/articleshow/125032461.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to heart health, it is not always the obvious dangers that harm us; it is the everyday food items that we eat, without a second thought. The symptoms for heart-related problems are not dramatic as much; they are slow, silent, and gradually build up in our arteries that can lead to a life-changing event. Vascular surgeon, Dr. Sumit Kapadia, with 18 years of experience, cautions that even the foods that we find comforting might quietly be increasing the risk of heart attacks in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;But shockingly, it's not just fried rare treats or greasy food-seemingly harmless staples and trendy packaged foods open the gateway to arterial damage. The danger lies in how these six food groups, cherished and widely consumed, quietly raise blood pressure, blood sugar, and inflammation until your arteries cry out for help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="7"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Seven Daily Habits to Prevent Heart Attacks Revealed &amp;amp; Boost Heart Health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Processed Foods&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="11"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Processed items like seekh kebabs, sausages, salami, and mutton curries are full of saturated fat and sodium. With time, these foods harden the arteries and provoke inflammation, acting as a main reason for heart problems. High saturated fat levels gradually lead to a buildup of cholesterol in the arteries, while too much sodium increases blood pressure, both of which contribute to arterial hardening and inflammation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; What starts as an occasional indulgence can, over the years, turn into a major risk factor if not balanced with healthier choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Fried street food&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="17"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samosas, pakoras, bhajiyas, puris, and French fries aren’t just tempting; they’re risky when cooked in reused oils, which produce dangerous trans fats. These fats do more than just clog your arteries; they accelerate plaque buildup and amplify the risk of heart attacks, even in the young and healthy. Reused oils produce trans fat, a harmful type that clogs the arteries and also triggers inflammation and plaque buildup inside them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Refined carbs &amp;amp; maida-based food&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="26"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our favourite food options, like white bread, naan, pav, biscuits, pastries, and bakery puff, are prepared with refined flour-also known as maida or refined flour. These quickly raise blood sugar levels and initiate body-wide inflammation, promoting the development of cholesterol-rich plaques in the heart arteries. Over time, these constant fluctuations can lead to insulin resistance and chronic inflammation throughout the body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="33"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Sweetened drinks &amp;amp; packaged juices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sugar-loaded colas, energy drinks, canned fruit juices, and flavored lassis might sound refreshing, but they raise triglyceride levels and put additional pressure on your heart. Consuming these drinks daily has been related to the risk of sudden cardiac death as they interfere with heart rhythm and blood lipids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="39"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;High salt in pickles, namkee, and other foods&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="41"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indian meals are always full of pickles, 'papad', instant noodles, chips, and salty snacks, all loaded with sodium. High intake of salt retains water in your body and heightens blood pressure, inviting heart attacks and strokes. This is the risk which, for many, lies hidden in the taste of daily favorites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Ultra-processed foods&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="48"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, instant noodles, frozen parathas, ready-to-eat curries, chips, and packaged sauces come packed with hidden fats, sugar, and preservatives. Each serving of ultra-processed food can increase your heart risk by an alarming 7 percent—proof that convenience at the cost of health is rarely worth it in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A warning that can save lives&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The advice of Dr. Kapadia is the same, yet very powerful: avoid these six food groups and shut the entrance door to future heart attacks. Every meal we eat might be small, last a few minutes, but it requires us to make powerful choices that shape our heart's future. Let those choices be guided by awareness and balance. A little mindfulness goes a long way...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="57"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The choices you make at every meal quietly shape your cardiovascular fate, so let wisdom guide your plate. Even amidst cultural traditions and busy lifestyles, mindful eating can safeguard your heart and keep the silent dangers at bay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="59"&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAJBVV95cUxNTE9TWEE4QnNib001cW5nRE5qY2hSeWo3SGM1SWtpcDYyM0VpRnpXZWd5RklsVDRGU2JfbzBSNlJVdnVJYVY3UWpqQlNDMVRDRjZqMGtsTC1ZN05ucXRxSlRIQ0VJRUp4VGxKbGNoYm5QZlN4TUNMejBJU01hTTV4TmpDUDhuQmFtdm14Qk9vY2NFMnh5eXRRMVdFenRTWFJwUmtlck1PSFp3dnhHOTYycGdUZ3BlT2lpTzNpNFR2bFlRR096Y1hiTUZpUEhqdmg4eHdvV0czempoT2hDclZZbnZ3T2VhaUF0YV9uMlZrdzNGZ2FmM0lwNDBTMm42b1Z5STJCM25FQzc</guid></item><item><title>关于超加工食品和多巴胺的流行理论受到了重大打击- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/a-popular-theory-about-ultra-processed-foods-and-dopamine-just-took-a-major-hit/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A neuroimaging study of young, healthy adults showed that consuming a milkshake did not, on average, result in a significant release of dopamine in the striatum region of the brain. While dopamine levels did increase in some individuals, this variability was not associated with whether a person had a normal weight, was overweight, or had obesity. The research was published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cmet.2025.02.002" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Cell Metabolism&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultra-processed foods are industrially manufactured products made mostly from refined ingredients and additives, with little or no whole foods. They are often engineered to be highly palatable, so that consuming them engages the brain’s reward circuits more intensely than natural foods do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is usually achieved by ensuring that ultra-processed foods contain large quantities of easily digestible sugars and fats. Because humans have separate neural pathways connecting the gut to the brain’s reward areas that are triggered by fats and sugars, eating foods rich in both is often more rewarding than eating foods rich in fats or in sugars alone. This is particularly true if these sugars and fats are easier to digest than those found in natural foods, as is the case with many industrially added sugars and fats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This intense reward potential has led to a popular theory that ultra-processed foods may be addictive. The core of this theory is the idea that their consumption elicits an outsized dopamine response in the brain’s reward regions, a surge similar in nature to that caused by drugs of abuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to this model, this powerful initial reward reinforces consumption. Over time, repeated exposure is thought to cause the brain to adapt, leading to a down-regulation of dopamine receptors and a blunted response. This state, known as tolerance, could then compel an individual to consume even more of the food to achieve the same initial level of pleasure, creating a cycle of compulsive eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was this hypothesis that study author Valerie L. Darcey and her colleagues set out to test. They investigated whether humans exhibited an exaggerated dopamine release after drinking a milkshake, a food frequently used in studies as a proxy for an ultra-processed product because it is rich in both easily digestible fat and sugars and often contains flavor-enhancing additives. Dopamine is a key neurotransmitter in this process; it is a chemical messenger that helps signal reward and motivation in the brain, reinforcing behaviors that lead to pleasurable or satisfying experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Study participants were 50 young, healthy adults, 38 of whom were women. They were recruited to cover a full range of body mass index values, with roughly even numbers of participants with normal weight, overweight, and obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After joining the study, participants were supplied with meals designed to provide the exact number of calories needed to maintain their current body weight for a period of 3-5 days. All meals were prepared in the NIH Clinical Center Nutrition Department Metabolic Kitchen with all foods and beverages weighed on a gram scale. Participants were instructed to consume all the foods and beverages they were given. Any food and beverages not consumed were returned and weighed. This procedure aimed to stabilize their diets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After this period, participants were admitted to the center that carried out the study for several days, where they continued taking similar meals under observation. On the day of the experiment, participants first completed positron emission tomography (PET) scans of their brains in the morning, after having fasted overnight. After that, they rested for 75 minutes, at the end of which they received a glass of vanilla milkshake to consume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thirty minutes after drinking the milkshake, participants had their second PET scan. They also provided ratings of how pleasant the milkshake was, whether they wanted more, and how it compared to their expectations. Participants also completed several assessments of food-related behaviors, experiences, and depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results showed no significant average increase in dopamine after drinking a milkshake in the striatum region of the brain. The study’s authors focused on the striatum because it is a brain region central to the reward system that processes dopamine signals. They found pronounced differences between individuals in how their striatum reacted to the milkshake, but these differences were not associated with participants’ adiposity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, while the brains of some individuals reacted to the milkshake by releasing dopamine, the brains of others did not, and the presence or intensity of this reaction was not related to a participant’s body weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data indicated that dopamine responses might be related to how hungry participants felt and how enjoyable they found the milkshake to be. The dopamine response was also found to be weakly associated with the ad libitum (free) intake of ultra-processed cookies. This means that individuals whose brains reacted to the milkshake with a greater dopamine release tended to eat more cookies later when given the opportunity to eat as much as they wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Discussing the findings in the context of whether ultra-processed foods can be considered addictive, the study’s authors concluded that “post-ingestive striatal dopamine responses to an ultra-processed milkshake were likely substantially smaller than for many addictive drugs and below the limits of detection using standard PET methods.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study contributes to the scientific understanding of neural processes related to food intake. However, the authors note that the study did not include a control group. The design compared dopamine levels before and after drinking the milkshake. Therefore, the possibility remains that other factors could have influenced the changes in dopamine observed in some individuals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.cmet.2025.02.002" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Brain dopamine responses to ultra-processed milkshakes are highly variable and not significantly related to adiposity in humans&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Valerie L. Darcey, Juen Guo, Meible Chi, Stephanie T. Chung, Amber B. Courville, Isabelle Gallagher, Peter Herscovitch, Paule V. Joseph, Rebecca Howard, Melissa La Noire, Lauren Milley, Alex Schick, Michael Stagliano, Sara Turner, Nicholas Urbanski, Shanna Yang, Nan Zhai, Megan S. Zhou, and Kevin D. Hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:07:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxPMmdLcTdVRVRaLTk1MHBNX2EzNHAxdU1ZeTJmUnFOZW1CTFVuOFo4WW1CN0F0bi1scHBaYm5rdE9LT0gwdk1Qa3l6XzdDUVhiOHdNNGtvUEZwUndyLUF2U3pncFh2NW1SMS14X0JUVEhSdjE2QXU0WXZkWkowTDdTNTQ2bHdBWHB6aDMxRkZoUkJiYmcxZ0xXa1hxSWFadWtya1Y0QUg5bw</guid></item><item><title>我们与另一对已婚夫妇度过了一个狂野的夜晚。一个丈夫为错误的人参加了狂欢节。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/11/alcohol-husband-sex-drinking-group-wife-advice.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf99w7b000gbsksr78jaevl@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Stoya and Rich here.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9spfu003h3b78jnozr54x@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9ftt2001f3b787crws39m@published"&gt;Let’s say you’re in a couple play situation where there is lots of alcohol involved and one husband is feral for the other guy’s wife, to the exclusion of everything else. If his wife is upset by this, and there is almost zero chance the drinking will be less, it seems like continuing the play another time will just lead to more hurt. Is there a way through this? The husband is not interested in moving forward if his wife is hurt by his drunken behavior, but is it worth trying again if his intent is to be more conscious of how his wife is doing during play?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9ftw3001g3b78k20ozkzq@published"&gt;—Tunnel Vision&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9ftze001h3b78c9cv14jp@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Tunnel Vision,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="97" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9fu2o001i3b78o1i8xdlh@published"&gt;I think the most prudent thing to do here is to consider what the emotional fallout will be if the same thing were to happen again. You’ve written your letter in a hypothetical voice without identifying yourself, which is uncommon for this column, but I have a hunch that if you’re in this configuration, you’re the wife. If that is true, envision what a scenario will be like if your husband follows the same pattern. Will it be upsetting, devastating, relationship-upending? Something else? What exactly would you be risking if the worst-case scenario were to play out?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="115" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9fu5j001j3b78b9mcmkky@published"&gt;One positive here is that the husband no longer can claim plausible deniability should he zero in on a single target and others’ feelings catch strays in the process. He knows what happened last time. If alcohol clouded his judgement, he should take it upon himself to drink less—if getting loaded in the presence of available alcohol (and nonmonogamous sex) is an inevitability, that may signal an issue with substances or a general discomfort with this kind of play. Both should be interrogated. I know people love to get drunk and screw, but if they &lt;em&gt;have to&lt;/em&gt; get drunk to screw, they might want to think about why and consider other means of social lubrication.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="57" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9fu91001k3b78jzdthyr0@published"&gt;Another positive here is that he actively does not want to upset his wife again, which suggests he’s learning. Now is the time for the wife to voice her boundaries and for him to accept them. If these are successfully adhered to, you will both have grown from a negative situation, perhaps rendering it all worth it.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="148" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9fuc7001l3b783575zfk0@published"&gt;So, I say give him another chance unless you (I mean … the wife) are fairly sure that a repetition of the first time will cause irreparable damage. Obviously, he’s extremely into another woman there and part of the point of this kind of play is for people to have their fun. But it truly should not be to the exclusion of everything else, including consideration for one’s partner. If he truly cannot maintain that very meager standard, this kind of play should probably be taken off the table entirely. But you should also consider the fact that his interest for at least one other woman will likely endure whether you go forward and incorporate her into group sex or not. If the very fact of his attraction is bothersome or distracting, it may deserve a sober discussion and your own efforts to come to terms with it.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmhf9fyrx001o3b780w11r8as@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmhf9gecv001w3b78zm9fp7o1@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmhf9gnrj00203b78ong94jhk@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9lw9y002q3b781fn1dvgq@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="80" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76t002u3b784984qo2w@published"&gt;I’m a gay man and I don’t get any enjoyment from my penis during sex. I don’t enjoy anal, either. I love closeness and intimacy, including kissing and cuddling, and I am happy to give orally, but getting my dick sucked does nothing for me, nor does penetrating another guy and nor does bottoming. None of it is uncomfortable and I enjoy giving pleasure to others, but none of it is as satisfying as masturbation. Is there something wrong with me?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002v3b78nunm4n95@published"&gt;—(Not) My Pleasure&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002w3b78ztshofuu@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear (Not) My Pleasure,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="158" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002x3b78smjbc3oi@published"&gt;There’s a good chance there’s nothing “wrong” with you here. Maybe this is just how you are, and all the psychological searching you can muster (alone and/or with a therapist) won’t give you any answers. Maybe you just know what you like and what you don’t. Giving pleasure is a great thing, and there are guys who identify as cocksuckers who know this well. If masturbation is your primary vehicle for pleasure, maybe you’re a bator. Maybe you are somewhere on the asexuality spectrum (some deep thinking on the subject, by reading a book like Angela Chen’s &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Ace-Asexuality-Reveals-Identity-Meaning-ebook/dp/B07Y7H1WT9/ref=tmm_kin_swatch_0?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.kUEjXggB_7ggqNfz6k5l9CeMsuUoEMrPtAf932EMoLkRyJt6T1oNSaxDjzaUcPCOq_oYAMscOBxFhdZleUV1LR82ic00Rf3f9R6vBc4xHiqVBPMyR7Bmf7ZiSoYVFfRLif6TptxOirtny5lNPHmXyg.R-bIgGONNmYTuYiVCC65wBJvxqdmM7QGNVgmJnemEHA&amp;amp;qid=1761851333&amp;amp;sr=8-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ace&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; or browsing/participating in the discussion at &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/asexuality/"&gt;r/asexuality&lt;/a&gt; could be useful). Maybe none of these labels appeal to you. My sense is that you’re navigating your body’s responses to sex very well and still finding activities that are fun. If you can be at peace with where you are sexually, that’s more than can be said for a lot of people.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="195" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002y3b78bae8cffj@published"&gt;If, however, this is distressing and something you’d like to work on changing, definitely seek the services of a therapist (preferably a sex therapist, or even a sex coach) who can help you sort out whether these feelings might be a response to something that’s happened in your life or just a regular facet of your particular sexuality. There are no guarantees that you will be changed by the process—nor do I think you need to be—but the more you think about it and the more you attempt to work on it, the more likely such a change will occur. We can’t say for certain what’s going on from here, but if you’ve exhausted all potential reasons and this continues to bother you, you may want to look into whether what you’re experiencing is sexual anhedonia, a condition marked by an inability to feel sexual pleasure. It has many &lt;a href="https://www.menshealth.com/sex-women/a43455963/sexual-anhedonia/"&gt;potential causes&lt;/a&gt;, physical (like low testosterone, neurological issues, or medication) and psychological (depression, performance anxiety), alike. A visit to a doctor, hopefully one with whom you are comfortable discussing sex, may be illuminating. Let them know what’s going on, as they may want to run tests.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmhf9sybv003j3b78lwcegfxk@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmhf9t23i003l3b786nfh78c3@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Send Us Your Questions About the Workplace!

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="36" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9ta25003o3b78ui7802ea@published"&gt;The columnists behind our advice column, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/good-job"&gt;Good Job&lt;/a&gt;, want to help you navigate your social dynamics at work. Does your colleague constantly bug you after hours? Has an ill-advised work romance gone awry? &lt;a href="https://forms.gle/DEVPsiDdnLHQVX7h7"&gt;Ask us your question here&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmhf9tdwv003r3b78fqbaomic@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u002z3b78awv61oo9@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76u00303b78ccmagl2y@published"&gt;My boyfriend and I are both very ass-eating curious—especially him! He’s been begging to try this since early on in our relationship. I’ve always hesitated because it took me a while to open up to and get comfortable with being eaten out in the first place. With butt stuff, I’m especially nervous because of cleanliness issues even after a shower. What if it smells or he gets dirty or it’s gross! I don’t want to turn him off entirely! But I also admit I’m curious about it and think I could be into it. How do I get past my fears and give this a shot?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76v00313b78451oox46@published"&gt;—Backdoor Curious&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76v00323b78ydgzfw74@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Backdoor Curious,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="192" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76v00333b78udurhj85@published"&gt;A shower, in most cases, is sufficient prep for rimming. Things that may complicate this solution include stray hairs that poop can cling to (especially if you are less than thorough with your wash) and fecal incontinence. If you have no reason to suspect you experience the latter (and you’d know), you’re already ahead of the game. To keep things extra tidy, you can trim the hair around your hole (I personally trust the &lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B0CLWH333W/?_encoding=UTF8&amp;amp;pd_rd_plhdr=t&amp;amp;aaxitk=28a358c8be016b730e11e90c73409006&amp;amp;hsa_cr_id=0&amp;amp;qid=1761506763&amp;amp;sr=1-1-9e67e56a-6f64-441f-a281-df67fc737124&amp;amp;ref_=sbx_be_s_sparkle_dlcd_asin_0_title&amp;amp;pd_rd_w=VlfpI&amp;amp;content-id=amzn1.sym.9f2b2b9e-47e9-4764-a4dc-2be2f6fca36d:amzn1.sym.9f2b2b9e-47e9-4764-a4dc-2be2f6fca36d&amp;amp;pf_rd_p=9f2b2b9e-47e9-4764-a4dc-2be2f6fca36d&amp;amp;pf_rd_r=3HKJH7ES5X9X4QSPK0QM&amp;amp;pd_rd_wg=JCM99&amp;amp;pd_rd_r=70b7d3bc-1c66-4571-9284-87e350b0597b"&gt;Philips Norelco OneBlade Intimate&lt;/a&gt;, as it’s never nicked me unlike virtually every other shaver I’ve used, even ones marketed for “intimate” areas). I think some would douche in a situation like this, though it’s probably overkill in your case. Still, if you fear there’s any poop lingering around your rectum that may present itself during play, washing out a few times with water (filter it if you’re using tap and the water in your area isn’t suited for drinking) with a small bulb (&lt;a href="https://www.amazon.com/Pure-Men-Detachable-Reusable-Capacity/dp/B0C6B2B35B/ref=sr_1_8?dib=eyJ2IjoiMSJ9.c8CU8QHctZ3sGts0WvMHmvu6QH0tc5liZAZiOcWJEsd2So5iHTlt6ZDVvMduKgaAYjDVxOWW9RS-YTDOHHVzg38iNlfH07YWYroNtbvx6Td4vy8vE5a4QqG_aLGvKwcohX_8ROAG3oW3F8vvqXiro1KtF9Vuofmy1HC-edQC8j5Mw3cNzdHKTAIWeIQgQ7nsZgtc6Bvj_-e12VFNmedQ8fUx8zKym5164SI1gNL_xzEACqHIa8bWe6RnSKvDeFHvXW9GaBmGSvACEn1r2l3rr2uk6Os_9MeH_hkRX_payKM.oMYVURE242HER0a2ad8fv2qPX0MAs70fvCf-b5A6GF4&amp;amp;dib_tag=se&amp;amp;keywords=stay+ready+douche&amp;amp;qid=1761506961&amp;amp;sr=8-8"&gt;like this one&lt;/a&gt;) may help you feel hygienically secure. Regular fiber supplementation via psyllium husk could also help quell your fears. It helps bulk stool, often leaving little to none behind after a bowel movement.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="166" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9q76v00343b78l271ufas@published"&gt;If he is so excited about eating your ass, he likely realizes what may come with it. A mishap is unlikely to turn him off entirely. Or if it does, then you’d be no worse off than you are now—at least you will have tried this thing that you’re both curious about. So try to put those concerns out of your mind if you’re going to go forward with this. Probably the most effective thing you can do is just go through with it—take necessary steps to clean yourself as much as possible and let him have at it. You may gain a lot of confidence and security when the ass eating goes off without a hitch. It’ll show you that you can do this and make next time even easier to get into. Of course, if you do feel discomfort, unclean or any kind of vague negativity, you have every right to stop the session, but I would follow my curiosity if I were &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmhf9qh8600383b78oul729i1@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="100" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmhf9qtb5003b3b78kd0gik8k@published"&gt;This might sound odd, but I’m a 35-year-old woman, and I just found out that the female screaming orgasms you see in movies aren’t actually typical. That’s because I’m lucky enough to orgasm in that way. Occasionally, I’ll have an enjoyable orgasm that’s a little more restrained. But for the most part, I’m full-on Meg Ryan in the restaurant scene in &lt;em&gt;When Harry met Sally&lt;/em&gt;, except mine is real and not at all a performance. I realize this is the opposite of a problem. However, my question is: &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2022/10/loud-climax-sex-advice.html"&gt;Have most or even all of my partners assumed I’m probably faking it?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmhf99w7b000jbskssyf14xoi@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxQMVUtSEdPdUlaZGR1T0N6MHRyaGlDbDBJb2tCeFU5QnNlSU8xaUp2eExlWk9JN0RhRFZUUVZhc3VTZnYwOTZ4NXBSRGgxbjM5ZTE3ajZzOVRfTzRpMFpEdFpMaEVjbVRla1pxOTdXS0d4RkkzM3h0ek1UV0k0cmFlSmE2TU5NQVZCdUJMTQ</guid></item><item><title>维生素D3与K2 ：为什么同时服用这两种维生素很重要-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/vitamin-d3-with-k2-why-taking-the-two-vitamins-together-is-important/photostory/124998892.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the combination of vitamin D3 and K2 shows great promise, experts caution that more is not always better. The same NIH review warns that taking high doses of vitamin D3 or calcium supplements without adequate vitamin K may have unintended consequences.&lt;br&gt;When vitamin D levels rise, your body absorbs more calcium. But if you’re deficient in vitamin K2, the nutrient that directs calcium into bones, that extra calcium can start depositing in soft tissues, such as arteries, kidneys, or joints. Over time, this buildup may contribute to arterial stiffness and cardiovascular disease (CVD), especially in people already at higher risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 15:51:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi-wFBVV95cUxPM1pBbXpwc1doTlR4YjV0SE1HaHdHbnZQRFk0blR6X1c0NWRJQjFvUUR3cVZVbGJ6RHdQTDZZbWFCT3BJb2M1UWtTVlpRM0JIU3BoLU1KUW5pSFoxQW9Yd2F5NmhPeGtoMERGelo5eHhWTk9MUDFEeFIzdW80MzJHanZldENwR082VEllanV6NkZLcGplMFNldU5hemJkZXB2NEM5bWVISkpFb3hmcWZ5S0JTci1EYndoRGZQNTJ2OE01ZERodi1UeVpGWWhsSFhKV0pINi1ab1EzRl9sSndLVUNmdFpHM1ZFM05rNTV4cDJjQUtaTkhiRzFTVdIBgwJBVV95cUxQQmIwMmdKZWh5d09qRThyNmllR1o0UHFiWFBuVXJOVTEzNXJFc3RkelJMMkVxTHBTNE1rU001QkFzSkNqTVRXRkVZeGpsYU4xckpVS0ljcTN0ZlFiX05ibUVJTXZJUUJpLTlEZ0RyR1g5ckFPZmU3ZkczOUh5SlV6TWl2UDdmeWZ2SjVlaWVTRzlmQkJEOGItZ3RuTFhOLVNNTGVpY3FtalFidmZoRVM0ZHVMRkNtYmtrNUJZN2wwRE1RSlVxY0lNYkdDeUxER0ZPbkZPcHNHRnZvU1QyTWI2LThtdF9HY01wNmRUaTdocENDQnY1Q0pFM0hrNVdYQ0lPZGN3</guid></item><item><title>诺伊达心理学家分享了持续的屏幕时间如何导致青少年和年轻人的“爆米花脑综合症” |健康-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/noida-psychologist-shares-how-constant-screen-time-is-causing-popcorn-brain-syndrome-in-teenagers-and-young-adults-101762093785101.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/noida-psychologist-shares-how-constant-screen-time-is-causing-popcorn-brain-syndrome-in-teenagers-and-young-adults-101762093785101.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;With screen time at an all-time high, many youngsters are constantly switching between apps, videos, and games. This digital overload is affecting focus, memory, and &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/mental-health" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="mental health"&gt;mental health&lt;/a&gt;. In an interview with HT Lifestyle, Dr Jaya Sukul, Clinical Psychologist and Founder of Headspace Healing, Noida, sheds light on the emerging “popcorn brain” syndrome and how it impacts young minds.&lt;strong&gt; (Also read: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/psychiatrist-shares-how-late-night-scrolling-anxiety-and-stress-are-fueling-a-sleep-crisis-among-gen-z-101759762270680.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Psychiatrist shares how late-night scrolling, anxiety and stress are fueling a sleep crisis among Gen Z"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Psychiatrist shares how late-night scrolling, anxiety and stress are fueling a sleep crisis among Gen Z&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt; )&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/550x309/4333886_1762094833129_1762094847456.jpg" alt="Dr Jaya Sukul explains ‘Popcorn Brain Syndrome’ and how to reclaim focus in a screen-filled world. (Freepik)" title="Dr Jaya Sukul explains ‘Popcorn Brain Syndrome’ and how to reclaim focus in a screen-filled world. (Freepik)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/550x309/4333886_1762094833129_1762094847456.jpg" alt="Dr Jaya Sukul explains ‘Popcorn Brain Syndrome’ and how to reclaim focus in a screen-filled world. (Freepik)" title="Dr Jaya Sukul explains ‘Popcorn Brain Syndrome’ and how to reclaim focus in a screen-filled world. (Freepik)"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Jaya Sukul explains ‘Popcorn Brain Syndrome’ and how to reclaim focus in a screen-filled world. (Freepik)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;What is Popcorn Brain?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Popcorn Brain isn’t your brain literally popping,” says Dr Sukul. “It’s the sensation of your neural circuits being overstimulated by constant digital inputs. You may find yourself jumping quickly from one thing to the next, struggling to focus, and feeling restless offline because life seems slower than your online feed.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;She explains that modern lifestyles, &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/social-media" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="social media"&gt;social media&lt;/a&gt;, and continuous digital exposure have reshaped brain activity. “Your brain craves novelty, and devices exploit this craving, keeping you in a state of hyper-alertness. Over time, this can drain your energy, increase stress, reduce focus, and even affect sleep," Dr Sukul adds.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/original/vitaly-gariev-TTcTl02R9Ts-unsplash_1762094031595.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Dr Sukul highlights Popcorn Brain, a condition affecting focus and emotional well-being due to excessive screen time.(Unsplash)" title="Dr Sukul highlights Popcorn Brain, a condition affecting focus and emotional well-being due to excessive screen time.(Unsplash)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Dr Sukul highlights Popcorn Brain, a condition affecting focus and emotional well-being due to excessive screen time.(Unsplash)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Who is affected?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;While Popcorn Brain is most commonly seen in teenagers and young adults, Dr Sukul warns it is also affecting people aged 30-45. “It’s not the same as internet addiction,” she clarifies. “Internet &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/topic/addiction" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="addiction"&gt;addiction&lt;/a&gt; is a clinical syndrome that disrupts work, relationships, and daily life. Popcorn Brain affects your quality of life, attention, and emotional well-being, but it doesn’t necessarily ruin relationships or career performance.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Symptoms to watch for include:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Irritability and anxiety&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Trouble sleeping&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Difficulty focusing or paying attention&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Feeling hyper-vigilant or stressed&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Life offline feels dull or uninteresting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/11/02/original/Screenshot_2025-11-02_200817_1762094328846.png" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="To address 'popcorn brain', Dr Sukul advises creating screen-free zones, taking breaks from devices, practising mindfulness, and consuming media intentionally.(Google Gemini)" title="To address 'popcorn brain', Dr Sukul advises creating screen-free zones, taking breaks from devices, practising mindfulness, and consuming media intentionally.(Google Gemini)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;To address 'popcorn brain', Dr Sukul advises creating screen-free zones, taking breaks from devices, practising mindfulness, and consuming media intentionally.(Google Gemini)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to ease Popcorn Brain&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Sukul suggests several strategies to reclaim focus and peace of mind:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Create screen-free zones:&lt;/strong&gt; Designate areas in your home where phones and devices aren’t allowed.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Schedule device breaks:&lt;/strong&gt; Take intentional breaks from screens to reset your brain.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3. Practice mindfulness: &lt;/strong&gt;Meditation, yoga, and &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/feeling-stressed-and-out-of-focus-yoga-expert-shares-3-breathing-exercises-to-calm-your-mind-101761059032005.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="breathing exercises"&gt;breathing exercises&lt;/a&gt; can help improve focus and calm overstimulation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4. Work in focused bursts: &lt;/strong&gt;Short periods of concentration followed by breaks enhance productivity.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5. Be intentional with media consumption: &lt;/strong&gt;Ask yourself, “Who is in control, me or my phone?”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6. Avoid mindless scrolling: &lt;/strong&gt;Passive browsing actively overstimulates your brain and reinforces Popcorn Brain symptoms.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“By consciously managing digital consumption and including mindfulness practices, you can reclaim your attention, reduce stress, and improve overall well-being,” Dr Sukul concludes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 15:24:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxNcVpGdHhsbUJNN2JiTkZOclo4Q051SUdrd1VhS0h3R0U4QmphaWF1cS1NX1BPR0tMSUxkY2t3ZVBwaW5zTllBYi0yZkd5R0FROE5ka0ZiOTNxTExjalkyX1Y2aGI5dlBSMWJGZmpHNjdvbDFKdmhLMlRjd2tXak9XckFZZVRnZ05ma1JQWWdTNGlMTGdObTQxNE5OYnRBWlpGSFhUR1h2VnhzNTBIdXdYU3RycnhFS2dmc1lwNzE5RGpkcUJnMUZtQWFibFRaMUptN0Eyem5Uc0xrMUpCMjBGcHE5WnpQN09EMGRQWV9HUXo3WVh5NWNvbndRZWxvd1VRMV9LeEpWeEx0YkhOek8xNNIBlgJBVV95cUxOdDZtODRsWDV5cVllMHViTU12U05kcVZZZUtvbmJtMzByTmlWMnhyRlJTM3NqY1V3WHFtSE5DWjVoZHRia2hTblN4eXNETkxNODJmZjh1N19DWGVGMGpNdjN1SktiYnR3YzRzd2hFd0pERUhVQkJGcTYxZkNBV1BUODRROTZjMDNtTC0xLVVVdXZkZ1YxaExuZF91aFlHRDUxeTUxS3NZem5DUVVQSEh2ZHQyR3hkQllvZmlfcERpVVIxYjVGMzlrQk5iQXdpTElfdFRqTzgtUW42QmlwSzJlLWVHdjFGVS1kUzZyd2NoQmdGVmNRMXlyVENzX0lvQzYxNWNLak5Kek5oc3FGX1h6cV9CekNHZw</guid></item><item><title>为什么萨古鲁推荐这3种食物来提高免疫力-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/food-news/why-sadhguru-recommends-these-3-foods-to-boost-immunity/photostory/125036109.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadhguru also recommends drinking water stored in copper bottles. As per his post, water stored in copper vessels can play a significant role in cleansing our system of various toxins. “Because water has memory, we are very concerned with how we store it. If you keep water in a copper vessel, preferably overnight or at least for four hours, the water acquires a certain quality from the copper which is very good for your liver in particular and your health and energy in general,” he states. The post also reads that copper is an antimicrobial and it kills bacteria and viruses, sometimes within minutes. According to a study, published in the &lt;a href="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1419/0850/files/Copper_Water_Vessel_Study_1.pdf?11079965153100211770"&gt;Journal of Health&lt;/a&gt;, Population and Nutrition, scientists studied the effect of storing water in a copper container on microbially contaminated drinking water, including harmful bacteria such as E.coli. and salmonella. Water contaminated with this bacterium was stored in copper containers for 16 hours at room temperature. Incredibly, after the 16-hour storage period, the scientists were unable to recover the bacteria from the water. In addition, they found that the pH level of the water increased, which means that it became naturally more alkaline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Images Courtesy: istock&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: The information provided in this article is meant for general knowledge only and should not be taken as medical advice. Always talk to your doctor before starting any new routine.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 15:22:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0wFBVV95cUxOdnk0WE10LTJPMDc3amdZS243Yi1yQjNkQndVeEhMaVdxRk5pYmxvdU5FeE5lelpocUJQSzR4amdFdG93T2pobWlsY0lNX1VJTXV6NnNkSjdaYzMwUGpyUXFON01rM1loNTBCQnhVMi1sTUlLQzJZbEd2ZHNxNGRIQkFDRkpLYlFsUEtYQmtfcV9JT3B0aWNhTFhZNlQyQk8tNUVOcEpDU3A1UTZYSktScEIwVkpQanVjeFBUaTZYS2xBTHZ3R3F1VzdMUmFzVG5QVEhr0gHbAUFVX3lxTFAwSnd5Qnl6eUhpbU14LTUtSk9hS295V3o0WmdLQU1ZUnhGQjFUZGJiUW5hb1V5YnFkRDlMckRmblM4UlQtR1dneEEtQjE4eTJzcDZVTXM0RFc0YUVZNUsxMjVCdDNzWERPVVo0NFF2ekZBWjFzTFE4QmR3RkxRenpwdHlqMWc0eW1BUFN3bVVXeEkxcmZyRk84UTZveUYxUENpRkVJeElxQXdwbE55NVROTVpfamdpeTNDLUhVbUZXVW1QbzFqb1BPMGZEc21KNHlhS3dYaGcwbXFBaw</guid></item><item><title>运动引起的性高潮：科学家们正在深入研究这种不寻常的现象- PsyPost</title><link>https://www.psypost.org/exercise-induced-orgasms-scientists-are-diving-deep-into-the-unusual-phenomenon/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10508-025-03237-9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Archives of Sexual Behavior&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; provides the most detailed account to date of women’s experiences with orgasms that occur during physical exercise. Through in-depth interviews, researchers found that these experiences often begin in childhood, are felt as a deep, internal sensation, and can be integrated into a person’s sexual life. This work builds on more than a decade of research that challenges the common understanding of orgasm as a strictly sexual event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research was conducted by a team at The Center for Sexual Health Promotion at Indiana University, led by Debby Herbenick, a prominent sexuality researcher. The scientific rationale for these studies stems from a desire to understand the full spectrum of human orgasmic response. Before this work began, the phenomenon was mostly a subject of popular curiosity, often called a “coregasm” in magazines and online forums because of its frequent association with abdominal workouts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While orgasm is almost exclusively discussed in sexual contexts, historical medical literature and early sexuality research, like the Kinsey reports, had occasionally noted orgasms occurring during non-sexual activities. However, these observations were limited, and a scientific gap remained between the popular buzz and empirical evidence. By systematically investigating this phenomenon, the researchers hoped to gain a clearer picture of the physiological and psychological processes of orgasm, independent of sexual fantasy or direct genital stimulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This line of inquiry began with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/14681994.2011.647902" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a foundational study&lt;/a&gt; in 2011. The researchers conducted an anonymous, internet-based survey of 530 women who had experienced either orgasm or sexual pleasure during exercise. The goal was to systematically describe a phenomenon that had, until then, been confined to popular media articles and scattered case reports. This initial study was exploratory, aiming to identify which exercises were most commonly associated with these experiences and what the experiences felt like for the women involved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The findings from that first survey established a baseline understanding. Among women who reported exercise-induced orgasms, the most common activities were abdominal exercises, climbing poles or ropes, and lifting weights. A large portion of these women reported feeling self-conscious about their experience, particularly when exercising in public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The data also showed that sexual thoughts or fantasies were rarely associated with these orgasms, suggesting the experience was primarily physiological rather than psychological in origin. For women who experienced sexual pleasure without orgasm, biking or spinning was frequently identified, along with abdominal exercises and weight lifting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeking to understand the prevalence of this phenomenon in the general population, the research team conducted &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10508-021-01996-9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;a follow-up study&lt;/a&gt; using data from the 2014 National Survey of Sexual Health and Behavior. This survey involved a nationally representative probability sample of over 2,000 U.S. adolescents and adults, allowing for a much broader and more generalizable analysis. This study was the first to provide population-level estimates for exercise-induced orgasm and included men in its analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2021 study revealed that approximately 9% of the survey respondents reported having experienced an orgasm during exercise at least once in their lifetime. There was no statistically significant difference in the prevalence between men and women. The researchers did find a gender difference in the age of first experience, with women reporting a mean age of about 23, while men reported a mean age of about 17.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The types of exercises associated with the first experience were consistent with the 2011 findings and included abdominal exercises, climbing, and weight lifting for both genders. The analysis also identified an association between having an exercise-induced orgasm and having an orgasm during sleep, but not with having an orgasm during a recent partnered sexual event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most recent study, published in 2025, moved from quantitative surveys to qualitative interviews to capture the rich, lived experiences of women. The research team conducted in-depth, semi-structured interviews with 21 women, ranging in age from 19 to 68, who had a history of exercise-induced orgasms. The interviews took place in a setting equipped with exercise mats and a Roman chair, allowing participants to demonstrate, if they felt comfortable, the specific movements that led to their experiences. This method allowed for a detailed exploration of their personal histories, physical sensations, and emotional responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key finding from these interviews was that the first experience with exercise-induced arousal or orgasm often occurred during childhood or early adolescence. Many women recalled feeling these sensations as young as five or six years old while climbing poles on a playground, doing gymnastics, or performing sit-ups in physical education class.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time, they were often confused by the sensations, with several participants describing the initial feeling as a sense that they needed to urinate. They lacked a framework for understanding what was happening to their bodies, but they recognized the feeling was pleasurable and, in some cases, sought to reproduce it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The participants often described an “aha” moment, which typically occurred later in adolescence or adulthood, when they gained more sexual knowledge from peers, media, or their own sexual experiences. It was at this point they connected their childhood sensations with the concept of arousal and orgasm. One woman recounted how making out with someone for the first time made her realize, “This is the same feeling, how strange.” This moment of recognition helped them make sense of a long-standing, and sometimes bewildering, bodily experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The interviews provided detailed descriptions of how an exercise-induced orgasm feels physically. Many women characterized it as a deep, internal sensation, originating in the lower abdomen between the belly button and the pelvis. They often contrasted this with orgasms from direct clitoral stimulation, which they described as more external.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some participants noted a progression of sensations, starting with a warmth or tingling in their core that would build and radiate downward. The experience was often predictable, with women learning that orgasm would occur after a certain number of repetitions of an exercise, such as after 50 leg lifts or during the third set of pull-ups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The emotional responses to these experiences were complex and often evolved over time. Embarrassment and shame were common, especially when the orgasms occurred in public spaces like a gym or during a group fitness class. Participants worried that others might notice their facial expressions or hear them make sounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some developed strategies to mask the experience, like keeping a serious facial expression, or to avoid it altogether by choosing different exercises. These feelings were sometimes rooted in cultural or familial taboos around sexuality, which made experiencing an orgasm in a non-sexual, public setting feel inappropriate or wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these negative feelings, many women came to accept and even enjoy their ability to have orgasms through exercise. Some viewed it as a motivator to work out, an “added perk at the end of the 100 reps.” Others described it as an empowering experience that gave them a sense of control over their own pleasure, independent of a partner. One woman explained that if she was not getting the attention she needed from her husband, exercise was another way to achieve the stress release of an orgasm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A significant finding was how some women integrated their knowledge of exercise-induced orgasms into their sexual lives. After learning which muscle contractions produced pleasure during exercise, they were able to apply similar movements during partnered sex. One participant explained that she could tense her core muscles to achieve a stronger or faster orgasm, sometimes allowing her to climax at the same time as her partner. For some, exercise became a form of masturbation or foreplay, and for one woman, it was the only way she had been able to experience orgasm until recently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These studies have some limitations. The initial survey used a convenience sample, which cannot be used to determine prevalence. The new qualitative study involved a small number of participants who were mostly young, white, and living in the United States, so their experiences may not reflect those of a more diverse population. Future research is needed to explore these experiences among men, gender-diverse individuals, people from different cultural backgrounds, and older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A major direction for future research is to understand the physiological mechanism behind exercise-induced orgasms. It is still not known precisely how muscle contractions during certain exercises trigger an orgasmic response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Subsequent studies could involve biomechanical analysis, neuro-imaging, or other physiological measures to investigate the roles of muscle tension, nerve pathways, and the sympathetic nervous system. A better understanding of the mechanism could have practical applications for physical therapists, personal trainers, and even military personnel who must pass rigorous fitness tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1080/14681994.2011.647902" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Exercise-induced orgasm and pleasure among women&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Debby Herbenick and J. Dennis Fortenberry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s10508-021-01996-9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Exercise-Induced Orgasm and Its Association with Sleep Orgasms and Orgasms During Partnered Sex: Findings From a U.S. Probability Survey&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Debby Herbenick, Tsung-chieh Fu, Callie Patterson, and J. Dennis Fortenberry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s10508-025-03237-9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Women’s Experiences with Exercise-Induced Orgasm: Findings from Qualitative Interviews&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Debby Herbenick, Callie Patterson Perry, J. Dennis Fortenberry, Ruhun Wasata, Jodi Wilson, Owen Miller, Kayla Willens, Alyssa Williams, and Georgia Frey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 15:07:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMipwFBVV95cUxQNUpXZFI3dkt2WnJqeUlybHllSmpBMjdUOTVKMUh0MXU4Y1I3U3E2YURTODI1bEVERURhZ1BJdzBkQktjQnJjQU12NVd5MXNjYmZOOXdGclNyelBpVFI2ZTZMVUVIVF9zcG5WNmp3MDllVjgtUjV3bzBGTHppcVJuZTFURVNqVTZJWE9DaDZJeTNYMjI0T3lITXlSTTBPY2dxZjVCNmNBNA</guid></item><item><title>如何在没有药物的情况下降低血压-每日邮报</title><link>https://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-15248749/high-blood-pressure-medication.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When Pauline Richardson was told during a routine GP appointment that her blood pressure was high, in the aftermath of losing her husband it was the least of her worries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Aged just 46, the nurse from Hampshire was left raising two small children by herself, as well as caring for her terminally ill mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I had put on a bit of weight at the time,' she says. 'But while the stress reduced eventually, the weight didn't.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Pauline knew her blood pressure was putting her at higher risk of stroke, heart attack and dementia. But it wasn't until decades later, after watching an episode of a healthy-eating series presented by Dr Michael Mosley, The Mail on Sunday columnist who passed away last year, that Pauline found the key to losing the extra pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Seeing him explain his high-protein, low-carb diet made me think that I could follow it,' says Pauline. 'And, alongside more regular exercise, the weight fell off.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Three years in, Pauline, now 72, has lost 4st 8lb (30kg), does 140 squats a day, and has got her blood pressure in a normal range – all without medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It seems miraculous, but experts speaking to The Mail on Sunday say that anyone can – and should – fix their high blood pressure through simple lifestyle changes like Pauline's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;High blood pressure is the leading cause of heart attack and stroke in the UK – impacting nearly 14 million adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;High blood pressure is the leading cause of heart attack and stroke in the UK – impacting nearly 14 million adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Professor David Webb, a clinical pharmacologist at the University of Edinburgh, says losing some weight is an effective way to lower your blood pressure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The condition is rising among young people as well – with nearly 170,000 16-24-year-olds estimated to be living undiagnosed. Also known as hypertension, the condition occurs when the pressure of blood pushing against the heart walls is consistently too high, damaging the arteries and restricting blood flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;People of African and Caribbean descent, as well as those with a family history of the condition, are more likely to develop hypertension. But being overweight, smoking, not doing enough exercise and eating a diet high in salt can all also contribute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If left untreated, high blood pressure can be fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But surprisingly, experts say the best way to tackle high blood pressure is not medical treatment but lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Last week, The Mail on Sunday's GP columnist Dr Ellie Cannon wrote that high blood pressure is the long-term health condition where she feels patients can make the most difference themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And she asked readers to write in about their own attempts to lower their blood pressure at home – and was flooded with messages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One 63-year-old man said that eating a daily dose of 85 per cent dark chocolate, as well as more fruit, reduced his blood pressure without him needing to take any medication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Another 56-year-old woman wrote that swapping to decaffeinated coffee brought her blood pressure down to normal levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And a 72-year-old woman said that buying a mini trampoline was her key to reducing her blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'All I need to do is five minutes of exercise in the morning and five in the evening,' she explained. 'This can be either bouncing or jogging on the spot, but it has to be fairly energetic. I make sure I'm slightly out of breath before I finish. I was previously prescribed medication, but now I no longer need to take it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;So here are the eight simple steps that experts say are scientifically proven to reverse your high blood pressure without drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;One teaspoon of salt a day... and no more&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Cutting out salt from your diet is the single most important thing you can do to lower your blood pressure, says Professor Francesco Cappuccio, a cardiology expert at the University of Warwick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Salt is made up of chloride and sodium – the latter of which we know impacts blood pressure,' he says. 'If you reduce your sodium intake, you reduce your blood pressure significantly.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Too much sodium raises blood pressure by causing the body to retain excess water, which increases the blood's volume and puts pressure on artery walls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Most adults in the UK eat about 8g to 9g of salt a day – but the recommended limit is no more than 6g, or about one teaspoon in total.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Too much sodium raises blood pressure by causing the body to retain excess water, which increases the blood's volume and puts pressure on artery walls&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Reducing this amount can lower your blood pressure within just a few weeks, studies have shown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts say the best way to lower intake is to stick to home-cooked food. This is because processed, ready-made foods, such as bread, sauces, soups and ready meals are the main source of added salt in our diets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But while it's good to limit your intake of processed foods, you don't have to go cold turkey, says Professor David Webb, a clinical pharmacologist at the University of Edinburgh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'You can retrain yourself by reducing the amount you add when cooking – though food might taste a little bland at first,' he adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'And don't add salt at the table, if you can avoid it.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;Shedding a few pounds makes a huge difference&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As was the case for Pauline, losing weight can be another key way to bring down blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Being overweight or obese causes hypertension due to excess fat, forcing the heart to pump harder in order to supply blood to the body. That strains the heart and increases resistance in the blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Likewise, says Prof Webb, sleep apnoea – a disorder often triggered by obesity in which breathing stops and starts repeatedly while in bed – can raise blood pressure significantly at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research shows that losing even 5 to 10 per cent of body weight can lower blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But waist size is key: for men, their waist circumference should measure less than 37in (94cm), while for women, waist size should not exceed 31.5in (80cm).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prof Webb said: 'If you can lose even a little weight, this can help lower blood pressure.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;Skip the lift and take the stairs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As well as helping you lose weight, research suggests that regular aerobic exercise – physical activity that increases your heart and breathing rates – can have a direct effect on blood pressure. NHS guidelines advise patients with high blood pressure to aim for at least 150 minutes of moderate exercise a week – which includes anything from brisk walking to trampolining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But one of the most effective ways to get some cardio into your day could just be taking the stairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;NHS guidelines advise patients with high blood pressure to aim for at least 150 minutes of moderate exercise a week - and taking the stairs can help achieve that&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2023 study from researchers in China found that climbing five flights of stairs a day reduced the risk of heart attack, stroke and blood clots by 20 per cent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Climbing up stairs is brilliant for blood pressure,' says Prof Webb. 'The more breathless and sweaty you get, the better.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While aerobic exercise raises your blood pressure in the short term, it has long-term benefits for your heart. 'It controls the heart rate, keeps muscles healthy and is generally a very good thing to do for your health,' says Professor Cappuccio. 'And it's a good preventative strategy to delay the rise in blood pressure that happens naturally with age, even if you don't yet have hypertension.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;Daily squats could be the answe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Strength training is just as crucial as aerobic exercise in lowering hypertension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This could involve lifting weights or using resistance bands, or doing bodyweight exercises such as push-ups or wall-sits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And while Pauline likes squats, others may prefer to plank – an abdominal exercise that involves holding a position similar to a push-up without bending the arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;As well as helping to tone your glutes, regular squats can lower hypertension and thus lower blood pressure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For 80-something Tony Gregory, it was a 30-second plank every morning that brought down his blood pressure. 'I had read about over 100 clinical trials that involved about 100,000 participants that showed doing the plank was especially effective in helping to control blood pressure – and this certainly appears to be working for me!' he wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prof Webb adds: 'It's not exactly clear why any of these exercises are so good for blood pressure, but we think it's likely because they improve cardiac efficiency and reduce resistance in blood vessels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'They can change the way the heart and blood vessels work.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;For those looking to lower their blood pressure, Prof Webb advises weight training three times a week (even if only for 10-15 minutes) alongside aerobic exercise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;Eat more bananas and lentils&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eating more bananas may also help lower blood pressure. The fruit is packed with potassium, a mineral which helps the body balance sodium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other great sources of potassium include kiwi fruit, potatoes, beans, lentils, leafy greens, yogurt, avocado and salmon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'We don't eat enough potassium in our diets – particularly as there's hardly any of the nutrient in processed foods,' says Prof Cappuccio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, experts warn patients to be wary of over-supplementing the nutrient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Adults aged 19 to 64 only need about 3,500mg of potassium a day – though the American Heart Foundation recommends up to 5,000mg a day for managing high blood pressure. Regularly exceeding this amount can damage the kidneys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;Swap a glass of orange for... beet juice&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A glass of bright red beet juice may seem an odd cure for hypertension. But recent studies show beets – or their juice – can help lower blood pressure due to their high content of inorganic nitrate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When consumed, whether eating or drinking it, this nitrate is converted into nitric oxide, a compound shown to relax blood vessels and improve blood flow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Research from scientists at the University of Exeter found that a glass of beetroot juice twice a day significantly lowered blood pressure in adults aged 67 to 79.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Beet juice contains nitrates and antioxidants that can lower blood pressure&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Derek Peel, 75, told us: 'I suffered on and off with high blood pressure until I discovered beetroot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I take a large glass of warm water with a squeeze of lemon juice and a teaspoon of beetroot powder mixed in every morning. Some days I might take a beetroot tablet as well – it really does work and I don't take any medication.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Prof Webb says: 'There's definitely evidence that beetroot does lower blood pressure, but we need more research into it. It's certainly not an alternative to exercise or cutting down on salt, but might be something to take alongside.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;Ditch booze - one pint could put you at risk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol has been proven to raise blood pressure – even in moderate amounts, says Prof Cappuccio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Studies have shown that the morning after binge drinking, there's an increase in stroke rates as the body's blood pressure is surging,' he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'But even regular light to moderate drinking will have a sustained effect in terms of lifetime risk.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Alcohol raises blood pressure, in the short and long-term, by stimulating the nervous system, which raises heart rate and narrows blood vessels. Regularly drinking more than the recommended limits can also cause lasting high blood pressure by limiting the brain's ability to regulate blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This sustained high pressure can strain the heart muscle and damage blood vessel walls, increasing the risk of heart attack and stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One 2023 study, spanning several decades and including 20,000 people, suggests that blood pressure increases in line with alcohol consumption, starting from as little as one glass of wine per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To limit damage, don't drink more than 14 units – not drinks – of alcohol a week, and spread this over several days, to give the body a chance to recover, NHS guidelines say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;Try to get six to eight hours' sleep each night &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Sleep is crucial to health – and blood pressure is no exception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'It's an environmental factor that has been neglected for many years, but lots of studies in recent years have shown the importance of good sleep for blood pressure,' says Prof Cappuccio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'The chance of developing high blood pressure is two to three times higher for sleep-deprived people. Whereas if you sleep for longer, research shows that your blood pressure will go down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Sleep also has a massive effect on weight gain, which in turn affects blood pressure. We should really all be making an effort to sleep for at least six to eight hours a night.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To do this, he says: 'Make sure your bedroom is a place to sleep – not live. Dim the lights, get rid of any screens, keep it at a cosy temperature and read a nice book.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="mol-para-with-font mol-style-subhead"&gt;&lt;span class="health-ccox"&gt;I ran back to health in memory of my mum&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bradley Pike had never been particularly healthy. But after his mum died from a heart condition in 2023, the dad-of-three began to slip into even worse habits than before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'I started drinking and smoking loads, as a way to deal with the grief,' the 31-year-old, pictured left, says. 'I felt ill all the time and was having dizzy spells a lot.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Bradley went to his GP, who ran tests that revealed he was prediabetic and had worryingly high blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Bradley Pike lowered his blood pressure through running and lost 2.5st in the process&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'They were reluctant to put me on drugs, because I'd need to be on them for life and I was so young,' he explains. 'But they told me I needed to change my lifestyle.' Luckily for Bradley, the route back to health dropped into his lap a few weeks later. He was offered a place in the London Marathon by the British Heart Foundation in memory of his mother.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At first, training was incredibly difficult, due to his weight and blood pressure. But he stuck with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In three months, he lost 2.5st (15kg) and brought his blood pressure down to normal levels. He has since run two more marathons and completed a 62-mile (100km) ultramarathon across the Gower Peninsula. 'I look back at my life before and barely recognise myself,' he says. 'There's so much you can do to turn your health around. All you have to do is start.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 14:54:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAFBVV95cUxQb1VTTGFQVFk4MkhBb0IxVEU5LU4zRUpNcXQzWVVEWEZCZFhOYWY2dTZoTE5CM21zZ3hSQnNRMDdiYTREMzhIcVpxckdONGV5b0FtNS0tN3F1VEl2NEdRcWpYYlBkb1VRUDJNMktFbDc3S3NDeDI5U0YyQ0hkVGktNXRKenpQMlRMb3E0WEozLWQ</guid></item><item><title>世卫组织警告全球“分支Ib” Mpox病例上升：我们应该注意的5种症状-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/who-warns-of-rising-clade-ib-mpox-cases-worldwide-5-symptoms-we-should-watch-out-for/photostory/125035635.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Early recognition helps stop the spread. The following signs should prompt medical attention:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Fever and chills: Usually the first warning, lasting two to three days.&lt;br&gt;Painful rashes or lesions: Start as red spots, then form blisters and scabs, commonly on the face, palms, genitals, or mouth.&lt;br&gt;Swollen lymph nodes: A telltale sign that differentiates Mpox from other rashes like chickenpox.&lt;br&gt;Muscle pain and fatigue: The body’s immune system fights hard, causing exhaustion.&lt;br&gt;Sore throat or headache: May appear before rashes, often misread as flu symptoms.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 14:46:50 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikAJBVV95cUxOR0h0aDRYLXN4aHZhS0R6S0FrTkl4dVJaNTgwUWtnODl3em5BZTNSeTNBR1J4S2dEeTh5RFRzQmlpdjBZTWlaMURhZjMtTDFGUUNGOFVQZ2VXQXB3M0FyMWVLWXZSSmFTMkxQbDBjV1Y3NjBxZmhMdjRwc2d4QUxuTVlia2JtRHdsc0xHRVFnSmo0YmE1VUlGZ3pXY1Blc0pjemliUUlYOFdubGVBYXR0TmpOMmtGVkhZQ1ZsSkVHMzZBek5LSDhnbWc5M1UyQVc0UEVVaWFuWGVtZFdQZDBnQlVacmFlNE44emJrUDRhVzUwcVhtZ1BaRVlMMnIyQ21WYXN6T0Y1alBYQktzdWI2dNIBmAJBVV95cUxOWWlDUmZwMEdmVkNQUENqRVlyc1pnNVRTbXdzSXp5RnkyRnBsSVR4V0FDUWpaSlJSMnl2Mklyajc0SWN2ZU81SjZhZG1LM1EzdGtOV3hZTk52SElELVdGSDhJTTZMdTFJSmhncGVfS0k2RGlKZTVxMmFMWUJ6aTY4dDZ0VVV4SjZTZ29LX21iRHlQSzRFckEtRUhyU0Z1NExoRjlveXdDMm1sVlFkUU9ob3ZhamRBeDhJblVncTFfaV9hSmZ6S3FWSGNOTHZPQUQwN0xjNXRzN3puZWw0QUVkZjk5MGRockpuaG1sT2dZSl9CeE00R1JRTjVNNm4td0Y1aXp4c0d0RllGd1E3Z21wV1lvblpBMUVJ</guid></item></channel></rss>