<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>进行尸体解剖的人正在分享他们在检查尸体时发现的令人震惊的事情- BuzzFeed</title><link>https://www.buzzfeed.com/abbyzinman/doctors-share-autopsy-stories</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-23
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="fast fashion" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="139869546" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title  "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;12.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"When I was in my emergency medical services (EMS) class, my teacher brought in a death investigator and former autopsy examiner to speak to our class. She told us that while she worked as an autopsy examiner, she got this women who at the time mysteriously suffocated after a car accident. Apparently this women was driving, and while she was driving, she grabbed her lighter from her purse and was holding it in her mouth while she fumbled through her bag for her cigarettes. While doing this, she got T-boned. The airbag went off, and on the way to hospital, they kept trying to put tubes down her throat to open her airway, because she was having trouble breathing. But no luck. When they cut open her throat during the autopsy, they found her lighter jammed down there. Apparently when the airbag went off it got jammed down her throat and no one knew."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;–&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/I_Feel_Dizzzy/" target="_blank"&gt;I_Feel_Dizzzy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I often think of this type of airbag problem when I see folks wearing pointed things from their necklace chains and earrings. Pointed objects near the ears, neck, and chest just seem like welcoming signs inviting accidental death. Random? I know. But you can't unsee it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;–&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/user/Wendy28J/" target="_blank"&gt;Wendy28J&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BuzzFeed</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 19:01:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE1EX2QxVjdDV3h3OHhPUWw0UkVuYlotb0k3SXJpQU1Za1ZULXlUcjBtd2tuQTBmNk1xUmMzYTlUM0VpajdtdGhob1JqUldTUk5NcXpTLVhaY3Rsa3lBamJ5UFNLZE1xazl0NkRrTnpXWk9sMkE</guid></item><item><title>两名威斯康星州儿童死于呼吸道疾病，国土安全部证实- 3000频道</title><link>https://www.channel3000.com/news/two-wisconsin-children-die-from-respiratory-illnesses-dhs-confirms/article_6e2f4061-fd53-49e2-a100-53b5cebae7ed.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;MADISON, Wis. -- Two Wisconsin children died from respiratory illnesses, the Department of Health Services confirmed Thursday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One child died from COVID-19 and the other died from influenza. They are the first children to die of a respiratory illness during the current respiratory virus season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is a reminder about how serious these viruses can be, but it's not too late to protect yourself and your family by getting vaccinated," DHS Respiratory Disease Epidemiologist Tom Haupt said. "Respiratory vaccines are safe, effective, and the best tool we have to prevent doctor visits, hospitalization, and death for Wisconsinites."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can schedule a vaccine through your primary care provider, local health department, pharmacy or community clinic. The &lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/immunization/vfc-parent.htm"&gt;Vaccines for Children program&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dhs.wisconsin.gov/immunization/vfa.htm"&gt;Vaccines for Adults program&lt;/a&gt; have also been set up to help those without insurance cover the costs of vaccination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's also important to take steps to stop the spread of germs during the times of year when respiratory viruses are more prevalent. The DHS recommends Wisconsinites:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wash hands often with soap and water for 20 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid touching their nose, eyes, and mouth.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay home and away from others if feeling sick.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Avoid being around others who are sick or have flu symptoms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cover their nose and mouth when coughing or sneezing and encourage children to do the same.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wear a high-quality mask around others to prevent the spread of respiratory illness.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;​COPYRIGHT 2025 BY CHANNEL 3000. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. THIS MATERIAL MAY NOT BE PUBLISHED, BROADCAST, REWRITTEN OR REDISTRIBUTED.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Channel 3000</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:24:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi4wFBVV95cUxPLUs2TEg3M0pWZ1EwZFlYaHlMNzlIcGcxTXBpSkxXd1Q4aExIS0FRRURQM0xFUDR3TS1uVHhQUzg1emJWMG1IX3BJNjJUYjlVNjFxUXVVSXdsaXhRV0JTSXZQdUlzRTJtbjZfYnpjNWZTOGNJbUFQdjllWjBneDBCaEFlOWxCZktiMWFTTHM1MG9SRUowQTNHanBVVUNvMHFwMVRJQkpRbWZuS0VIUmZLdy05bUNBcm1UX0U3d1BTVktxNUlZVEZFS1lBYmVMM1AtTTdCUnEwb3JmUmo2V3dKeGIxOA</guid></item><item><title>我怀疑我知道为什么我的妻子有些不对劲……就在下面。她还没有准备好听。-石板</title><link>https://slate.com/advice/2025/12/sex-advice-wife-vagina-something-off.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="18" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmknsl0043uum2ha658npx@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Do It is Slate’s sex advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a question? &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Send it to Jessica and Rich here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt; It’s anonymous!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="5" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbn4z9a005m3b795eoi3gjh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear How to Do It,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="114" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbn4ue1005e3b79d722fxj9@published"&gt;I am a 54-year-old man who has been married for 20-plus years to a 50-year-old woman. I had a pretty active sex life before we met, and she had some experience, but mostly just a few hook-ups, that, by her recollection, were mostly her opening her legs and letting the guy finish hurriedly. She claims that her first non-solo climax was with me and that was one reason she continued seeing me, leading to a very deep bond. Similarly, while she wasn’t particularly sexually adventurous, she was open to various positions and, honestly, after experiencing a pretty good sample size, I found her vulva and vagina to feel, taste, and look better than others.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="20" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmlizd00123b79cr861v17@published"&gt;While our frequency has declined over the years, our weekly (sometimes semi-weekly!) sex is generally fine, except for one thing.&lt;/p&gt;

    


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="61" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbni75c006q3b79ga05q5to@published"&gt;Her vagina is too loose now, and I have trouble getting enough friction to cum. This is new to me, because while I am not much longer than average, I had always been told that my erections are much thicker than other guys’ and had always found every partner to be “tight.” Would 25 years of active sex “stretch” her out?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="123" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmlj1200133b79dypujxy3@published"&gt;This has been building for a few years, and yes, now that I am older, it takes a little bit more “action” for me to finish. We’ve tried various positions and some work better than others, but in general, it just gets tiresome thrusting away as she visibly loses interest a few minutes after her orgasm (which happens in all but our most hurried sessions). While she will give some half-hearted licks, she doesn’t like giving oral—especially after penetration—and we tried anal a couple of times, but neither of us is really into that. So most of our sessions end with me jacking off next to her, while she is obviously content and thinking about other things, which sometimes kills the vibe completely.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="115" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmlj3700143b79ofpz18zt@published"&gt;I’ve mentioned to her a few times to “try to squeeze it,” but she just sort of laughs it off, which also tracks with her generally viewing sex as something that the man puts most of the effort into. Plus, while I enjoy taking the lead in bed, I don’t like telling her what to do sexually or otherwise. I don’t want to hurt her feelings, and this isn’t the most important thing, but I’ve had trouble getting the point across that now that we are older, I need her to put a little more effort into it, whether that be Kegels, something to tighten up, or more active participation in our sessions. Any advice?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbn4dwq004k3b793f4plr9z@published"&gt;—Worn Out&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjbn4gdk004r3b79i3rr4aco@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSdx34-uOijrCIKqMdw5hnyYahSJBKa4AaSzDCu1nfcpmd3IjA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmjbn4nvh00553b79wpety3l7@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmjbn4ihw004y3b79x9gqemwd@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="48" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmlj5700153b79df7ue3v9@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica Stoya: &lt;/strong&gt;Oh, boy. His sentence, “And this isn’t the most important thing,” is perfunctory and performative. I feel like the writer had a sense that people might judge the language used and the issue at hand, and felt like he had to say it’s not that important.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="21" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmug2t001b3b792ubt1q29@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich Juzwiak: &lt;/strong&gt;Right. It’s important for our purposes: It’s the focus of the letter, and that’s what we’re here to address.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuhu1001h3b792ulsb8wk@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica:&lt;/strong&gt; It’s also clearly pretty important for him. Would 25 years of sex stretch her out? That’s not how things work. Also, our writer likely had very little opportunity to learn in his lifetime whether that is or is not how things work. But both sexes tend to lose pelvic floor tone as they age, regardless of how much sex they’ve had, how big any penises might have been, whether pregnancy has happened and a woman has given birth, fisting, orgasming, etc. It’s just age. Often, women who have given birth are given access to the tools to maintain pelvic floor function as part of the recovery process.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="94" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuk4f001n3b79u8e59tl9@published"&gt;My biggest concern at the moment is how to get the wife into the kind of doctor who can evaluate whether some pelvic floor therapy needs to happen, regardless of how the sex is going to feel for this guy. When you get into your 60s and 70s, if you don’t have a strong pelvic floor, stuff can start to prolapse, you can have urinary and bowel leakage, it’s not a good scene, and it’s a lot easier to intervene earlier than to be like, “I’m 70, and I can’t control my pelvic floor.”&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="83" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmumhg001t3b798xajsuu2@published"&gt;In order to achieve that, I’m pretty sure he’s going to have to put sexual satisfaction on a shelf and just focus on saying, “I think this is something you should mention to your doctor.” He can do that with the knowledge that it’s likely to help her pelvis tighten back up. But often, in these kinds of discussions, if you portray it as just kind of a sex thing, the person who’s not particularly invested in sex is going to dismiss it.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="103" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuq8m001z3b79zahotwr2@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;Yeah, it’ll just seem selfish and insulting. But that’s why I think the letter writer has to position himself as an expert. There’s nobody who knows the feel of her vagina as he does; they’re monogamous. Also, hormonal changes can create a different kind of effect. What he is feeling in terms of looseness is an estimate; it’s his assessment. He’s not the expert on what’s going on; he’s just the expert in the fact that &lt;em&gt;something&lt;/em&gt; is going on. He can tell her that he’s noticed something’s a little bit different, and so she might want to get that looked at.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="33" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmus6h00253b79skjfgg39@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica: &lt;/strong&gt;Also, sometimes penises get smaller or less hard on average as time goes on, so it could be that a portion of the difference in friction is because he’s shrinking a bit.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="137" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmutzn002b3b79codyhevs@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;Exactly. Obviously, a PDE5 inhibitor would be useful in keeping you at full mast. You will shrink sometimes because there’s just not as much blood going into your dick, so if you can get that going using some medication, then you may retain your previous max size, and maybe that would actually give you a change in sensation as well. In a long session like that, especially with a partner who’s kind of just going along for the ride, there can be a distracting element of, “Well, this isn’t ideal in terms of the titillation I’m feeling, so is my erection going to go away?” Then that gets into your head, and it affects the sex. So that’s why the ED drugs are useful beyond the blood flow; they help with the psychology of it sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="127" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuvrj002h3b79zzcbun5h@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica:&lt;/strong&gt; It’s really great that our writer was able to be, it turns out, permanently the person who can help his wife have an orgasm. And I always prefer when men who enjoy sex with women err on the side of prioritizing the woman’s orgasm. That said, in the same way that when I’m having sex with a man, I know once they have an orgasm, my fun is finished, so I kind of factor for that, he might consider trying to aim for sex where she doesn’t orgasm until right before he’s about to, and that’s probably going to result in her staying engaged throughout. Lots of women do have one orgasm and go, “Yeah, I’m done now.” I would roll over and go to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="151" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuxk1002n3b799ux9p3va@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;Right. And I understand that these issues are important for the writer, but look, you’re having regular sex decades into your relationship, and she’s coming. What he describes in terms of her coming and then he’s jacking himself off is a really common thing that happens. I see it a lot myself in my own experiences. In terms of gay male sex, bottoms, if they come, a lot of the time, they can’t keep taking the dick; it’s just too much, and so then the top finishes himself off. Of course, you want people to be engaged and to enjoy that along with you until the end, but there are worse things. The way that they’ve sorted it out is what I would recommend. So yes, this isn’t optimal. I understand you want it to be even better, but a little perspective is called for. It’s still pretty damn good.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="38" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmuzby002t3b797t7kz219@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica:&lt;/strong&gt; From the context of a very heteronormative relationship that I’m in now, it’s often a similar experience in those contexts. It’s rare for both people to have the Bridgerton-style, coming at the same time kind of moment.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="102" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv1d6002z3b79al3gdm8w@published"&gt;We can often get these scripts in our heads of how sex is supposed to play out. In the context of a long-term relationship, you can develop a very specific and almost rigid routine. So keep in mind you don’t have to adhere to a routine that isn’t working. You also don’t have to switch to one other routine. Sometimes she finishes, and you’re there jacking off. Sometimes you aim for her to orgasm just before you do. Maybe every once in a while it doesn’t happen for her, that’s probably going to be OK, and sometimes you can do other things.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="101" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv3f200353b7997tuksg9@published"&gt;Then, just to address his thing about positions: My instinct is that positions where her lower back is quite arched in one direction or another, or her legs are pressed together, even crossed, are going to be the positions where there’s more of a sensation of tightness. As much as I really love and support open dialogue, if that’s not going to function or if he needs to not mention sex at all to tell her that it would be a good idea to mention the pelvic floor changes to a doctor, he can  just casually go for positions that feel tighter.&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="23" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv55x003b3b7950hqhr4p@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;Yes. But obviously, ideally, talking about this as gently as possible, and not using words like loose, is the way to go.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="14" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv6hg003h3b79ubv9iqkt@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica: &lt;/strong&gt;Do not say anything about sample sizes or better or worse than others.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="69" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv89g003n3b79kqn1i41i@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rich: &lt;/strong&gt;It’s funny, because a lot of the time, my advice is to use the letter sent in as a template for how to talk about it with your partner. This is one of those letters that’s not the template. You don’t want to go into a lot of this stuff just for the sake of being heard; you don’t want to hurt her feelings and shut her down.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="106" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbmv9sk003t3b79v9ee21r9@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jessica: &lt;/strong&gt;I would prioritize saying, “It seems like there are some physical changes. I would really love it if you’d mention that to your primary care or gynecologist next time you see them.” Then, when addressing the sex, do your best to make it a neutral issue. Err on the side of it being your own issue. If it’s true that his erections are not as firm as five, 10 years ago, use that, just because this kind of stuff is not easy to hear, especially for women who are aging and don’t really have that much of an investment in sexual pleasure to begin &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;with.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmjbn443e00463b793dgukvn1@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="82" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmjbn41pg003z3b79feyftsrj@published"&gt;I’m 64 and my husband is 65. We’ve been together for nearly 40 years. He is still crazy about me, thinks I’m beautiful and sensual, and has always had a much higher sex drive than I have. In fact, since my breast cancer surgery seven years ago and the estrogen-blocking medicines I’ve been on, my sex drive is pretty much zero. But he’s loyal and honorable so he’d never have an affair or pay for sex, &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/03/husband-fantasy-cheating-sex-advice.html"&gt;so he’s devised a different routine…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmjbmknsl0046uum25c3v2zfb@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Slate Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the latest from Prudie and our columnists in your inbox each weekday, plus special bonus letters on Saturdays.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE9HWFp2bHBJV0N6TXFDR2M0RUF1MUhfcVQ5Uk5iTHNpQ01IUXpjRTV0YlY1ZDRpVnp0RXVtSDNyN3pjMGxlLURfNWQ5QzBRUXkyb2dHZFBTOVNmX2tabzZxNnB0cGJFazRYdTZBZVp4M1A4Qll1MllTQ1pIME5zMGM</guid></item><item><title>根据专家的说法，所有降低胆固醇的食物- GQ</title><link>https://www.gq.com/story/all-the-foods-that-lower-cholesterol-according-to-experts</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. has a &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/what-is-ldl-cholesterol-and-how-do-you-lower-it"&gt;cholesterol&lt;/a&gt; problem. Roughly &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.americashealthrankings.org/explore/measures/High_Chol" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.americashealthrankings.org/explore/measures/High_Chol"}' href="https://www.americashealthrankings.org/explore/measures/High_Chol" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;37% of Americans&lt;/a&gt; have high cholesterol, a statistic that’s likely underreported, considering that, according to &lt;a href="http://google.com/url?q=https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamacardiology/fullarticle/2811350&amp;amp;sa=D&amp;amp;source=docs&amp;amp;ust=1765993289197644&amp;amp;usg=AOvVaw2FElvu2xrMvjt8dRON0ocN"&gt;a 2023 study&lt;/a&gt;, many people with high cholesterol don’t know they have it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem specifically is low-density lipoprotein, or &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/what-is-ldl-cholesterol-and-how-do-you-lower-it"&gt;LDL cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;, which clogs arteries when there’s too much of it. This is different from high-density lipoprotein (HDL), which transports cholesterol to the liver, where it’s broken down and excreted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-offer-url="https://findcare.nuvancehealth.org/provider/sunny-s-intwala/1746052" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://findcare.nuvancehealth.org/provider/sunny-s-intwala/1746052"}' href="https://findcare.nuvancehealth.org/provider/sunny-s-intwala/1746052" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Sunny S. Intwala, MD,&lt;/a&gt; a preventive cardiologist with Nuvance Health in New York, says that high cholesterol often flies under the radar. Even if you’re young and in good shape, if your diet and lifestyle habits don’t support healthy cholesterol levels, it will catch up with you. “You can be lean, fit, and young, and still silently be accumulating plaque in your arteries,” Dr. Intwala says. “Your arteries don’t care how good your &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/vo2-max-2"&gt;VO2max&lt;/a&gt; is. Supporting healthy cholesterol levels is about protecting your future health.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK279318/"&gt;High cholesterol is literally life-threatening&lt;/a&gt;. It increases the risk of heart attack and cardiovascular disease, which is the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/fastats/leading-causes-of-death.htm"&gt;number one cause of death in the U.S&lt;/a&gt;. Here’s the good news: It’s completely controllable, and the sooner you have cholesterol-supporting habits in place, the better. A major part of that has to do with what you’re eating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to lower cholesterol through diet and lifestyle&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.columbiacardiology.org/profile/corey-k-bradley-md" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.columbiacardiology.org/profile/corey-k-bradley-md"}' href="https://www.columbiacardiology.org/profile/corey-k-bradley-md" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Corey K. Bradley, MD, FACC&lt;/a&gt;, a preventive cardiologist at Columbia University Irving Medical Center, roughly 20 to 30% of high cholesterol is controllable through diet and lifestyle habits. The rest, she says, comes down to whether you are genetically predisposed to have high cholesterol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Bradley says that roughly one in 250 people has a genetic disorder called &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/cholesterol/genetic-conditions/familial-hypercholesterolemia-fh"&gt;familial hypercholesterolemia (FH)&lt;/a&gt;, an inherited disorder leading to extremely high LDL cholesterol and must be treated with medication, along with diet and lifestyle interventions. “You can be the picture of health on the outside, but still have really dangerous levels of LDL cholesterol,” she says, emphasizing that this is why it’s important for everyone to have their cholesterol levels checked at least every couple of years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/how-to-lower-your-cholesterol"&gt;the 20% and 30% that is in your control&lt;/a&gt;, all three cardiologists we spoke to advise a combination of not smoking, &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/how-many-days-a-week-should-you-work-out-2#:~:text=In%20real%20life%2C%20GQ's%20fitness,and%20abilities%2C%E2%80%9D%20he%20says."&gt;exercising regularly&lt;/a&gt;, and following a heart-healthy diet. Dr. Bradley is a big advocate of following the &lt;a href="https://www.gq.com/story/what-is-mediterranean-diet-3"&gt;Mediterranean diet&lt;/a&gt;, which has been repeatedly scientifically shown to keep LDL cholesterol low. This way of eating prioritizes seafood, lean proteins, vegetables, fruit, and whole grains, while minimizing ultra-processed foods and fatty meats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>GQ</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:23:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOT0IxSzRPSThUejN6QURtendVZTM5R1lINzh3YjlsaEJZRGc3ZktJQVhUSEtiS25ZcnRwdW9Wc2tlLUJUWHdiZG1qcmFPUmZIYkxfaGtWNW8zM3o5RXhXX1RzM1ZPMEZObXE2ZmJCeU4tWFZwNGJIZl9VbWRLNWhwZDFXUGd0X2o5cEE</guid></item><item><title>以色列研究：未治疗的妊娠期慢性甲状腺疾病增加儿童自闭症风险-以色列时报</title><link>https://www.timesofisrael.com/israeli-study-untreated-chronic-thyroid-condition-in-pregnancy-ups-autism-risk-in-children/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="the-content"&gt;
					&lt;p&gt;Israeli scientists say that women with persistent thyroid hormone imbalance during their pregnancy may be at an increased risk of having children with autism spectrum disorder (ASD).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Their new peer-reviewed study tracked thyroid levels in more than 51,000 pregnant women. The study found that children of women with long-lasting, untreated thyroid hormone imbalance during pregnancy had about two to three cases of autism per 100 children, compared with about one case per 100 in the general population.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Women who had a chronic thyroid condition that went untreated and got worse during pregnancy had a greater risk of having children with autism than pregnant women who were adequately treated,” Prof. Idan Menashe of Ben-Gurion University of the Negev, the study’s lead author, said in a phone call.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p id="gpt-passback"&gt;
        
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    
    
    
&lt;p&gt;However, the scientists found that when a pregnant woman’s chronic thyroid dysfunction was “adequately treated,” there was no association with increased autism risk in her offspring, said Menashe, who is head of Ben-Gurion’s Department of Epidemiology, Biostatistics and Community Health Sciences, and the scientific director of the Azrieli National Center for Autism and Neurodevelopment Research.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ben-Gurion researcher Leena Elbedour, May Weinberg of the Meir Medical Center and Tel Aviv University, Analya Michaelovski of Soroka University Medical Center, and Prof. Gal Meiri, also of Soroka University and Ben-Gurion University, collaborated on the study, which recently appeared in &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jcem/advance-article/doi/10.1210/clinem/dgaf596/8339900"&gt;The Journal of Clinical Endocrinology &amp;amp; Metabolism&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter newsletter-article" data-website="timesofisrael" data-from="Israeli study: Untreated chronic thyroid condition in pregnancy ups autism risk in children"&gt;
	&lt;div class="newsletter-article-inner"&gt;
		&lt;p class="newsletter-article-text newsletter-article-part"&gt;
			&lt;span&gt;Get The Times of Israel's Daily Edition&lt;/span&gt;
			&lt;span&gt;by email and never miss our top stories&lt;/span&gt;
		&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="newsletter-article-form-wrapper newsletter-article-part"&gt;
			
			&lt;div class="newsletter-article-terms"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
				By signing up, you agree to the &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="/terms"&gt;terms&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;p class="newsletter-error newsletter-article-error"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
		
&lt;h3&gt;Thyroid hormones contribute to brain development.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The thyroid is a small, butterfly-shaped gland at the front of the neck.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thyroid hormones regulate the body’s metabolism, which is how the body uses and manages energy. These hormones also play a crucial role in essential processes such as heart rate regulation and the body’s muscle control.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3704008" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/idanMenashe-copy.jpg"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-3704008" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/idanMenashe-copy-640x400.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Prof. Idan Menashe, head of the Epidemiology, Biostatistics and Community Health Sciences Department and the Scientific Director of the Azrieli National Center for Autism and Neurodevelopment Research at Ben-Gurion University of the Negev. (Courtesy)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thyroid hormones also support the production of myelin, an insulating, fatty coating around nerve fibers. These allow electrical signals to travel between the brain and body more quickly.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;During pregnancy, a woman’s thyroid hormone is essential for the neurodevelopment of the fetus. Studies have shown the association of a woman’s thyroid imbalance with atypical neurodevelopment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When the thyroid produces the right amount of hormone, it is considered to be within the normal range, or balanced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If a pregnant woman’s thyroid hormone levels are too low, doctors usually prescribe an artificial hormone that safely replaces the missing hormone.&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_2905684" class="wp-caption  alignnone"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1401898908.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-2905684" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2022/12/iStock-1401898908-640x400.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustrative: a doctor carrying out checks for an autoimmune thyroid disease. (swpispix; iStock by Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Children with autism may have delayed or absent speech, difficulties with social interaction, motor impairment, and repetitive behavior, with a spectrum of severity.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Around the world, autism spectrum disorder diagnoses have increased, including in Israel. A recent Israeli &lt;a href="https://www.bgu.ac.il/en/news-and-articles/dinstein-autism-prevalence/"&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; found the number of ASD cases had quadrupled from 2017 to 2021 in two- and three-year-old children, and doubled in older ages.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Thyroid imbalance during pregnancy&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Scientists have studied the connection between a woman’s thyroid levels during pregnancy and her child’s development. However, most earlier studies checked the thyroid hormone once, usually early in pregnancy, and not throughout the pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;Menashe’s research, done at Soroka Medical Center, followed more than 51,000 births between January 2011 and December 2017 in a retrospective cohort study, with a follow-up through January 2021.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Using blood-test data and the women’s medical records, the team divided the mothers into four groups: those with no thyroid problems, those with a chronic thyroid condition whose hormones were balanced in pregnancy, those with thyroid imbalance only during pregnancy, and those who had both a chronic thyroid condition and imbalance during pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This gave researchers the data to compare the women’s thyroid levels during pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“What surprised me is that only the last group, those who had both a chronic thyroid condition and were imbalanced during pregnancy, were at risk of having a child with autism,” Menashe said.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scientists also observed that the longer the duration of thyroid dysfunction across trimesters, the higher the risk.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“We don’t really know the cause,” Menashe said. “But we know there is a link between them.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When asked if he could calculate the specific percentage of risk, the scientist replied, “Not exactly, because this is not the exact way to assess risk. All we can say is that we see an increased risk, or more exactly, untreated thyroid problems are associated with an increased risk of autism.”&lt;/p&gt;

	&lt;figure id="attachment_3708009" class="wp-caption  alignright"&gt;&lt;a href="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/8597643e-4c7b-491e-a8ad-9de121448a75.jpg"&gt;&lt;img loading="lazy" decoding="async" class="size-vertical wp-image-3708009" src="https://static-cdn.toi-media.com/www/uploads/2025/12/8597643e-4c7b-491e-a8ad-9de121448a75-300x480.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
		&lt;figcaption class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Dr. Dorit Shmueli, a specialist in neurology and child development and child development coordinator at Clalit Health Services. (Courtesy/Hagai Shmueli)&lt;/figcaption&gt;
	&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Dorit Shmueli, a specialist in neurology and child development and the Child Development Coordinator in Clalit Health Services, told The Times of Israel that research on the safety and importance of balancing hypothyroidism in pregnancy is “essential.”&lt;/p&gt;
               
           
           
        
&lt;p&gt;“Optimal maternal thyroid function plays a key role in supporting healthy fetal brain development, and understanding how best to manage it can directly influence the developmental outcomes we see in children, especially autism spectrum disorder,” said Shmueli, who was not involved in the study. “Evidence-based insights from Prof. Idan Menashe’s research are crucial for informing clinical guidance and improving long-term well-being in the populations we serve.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Researchers believe there is “some mechanism where the imbalance in the maternal thyroid hormone affects the neurodevelopment of the fetus,” Menashe said. “Eventually, this abnormal neurodevelopment is translated into autism in the child.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Israeli Medical Association, following international guidelines, recommends that thyroid levels be monitored in pregnant women who are already being treated for thyroid imbalance. However, it does not recommend universal screening because treating mild thyroid problems has not been shown to clearly improve pregnancy or neurodevelopmental outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When asked whether there has been a change in the Health Ministry’s policy about routine thyroid screening, Menashe said, “I don’t think doctors change the protocols based on one study.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Health Ministry did not respond to a query about this issue.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Menashe said that more research is needed to “really study these mechanisms in animal models on a molecular level, and to specifically test these hypotheses.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Until then, he said, the findings “underscore the need for routine monitoring and timely adjustment of therapy to maintain normal thyroid hormone levels throughout pregnancy.”&lt;/p&gt;

				&lt;/div&gt;

				
				

					
			&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Times of Israel</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 16:06:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxOSDU4UEY1Wk5aMWRxdXBOall2UXVpZzFUSEw2MmY1WWJhdm52WkY1RklVdEFLdW9IMjAyMTZXSkZVN2lOMktsWk1PRzdKM0E5QVRKXzhDUWFpbWxiQVJySkwzSWF1LVpKUXdEWHRYMGZQd1VGUkhJbEt3ZFZ1OU02R0dPU2NRZ0xXWndPLW5VN190SmxJWC0wa1ZoTklmeHFZSEZZRlZ5OHdORTZIVWxLRWpGY055Um0tUHI3U1F30gHDAUFVX3lxTE1Hdk1tWHNJLS1udnhqd0N0emxlaWxoaEU4Z0lnLUhjYVByU1FUb3k3MnQ3NWt6MTU5Uy1wSnk4TkRrcUhlODBsN3lld3d2anZzekFnRTNnOVJVZ0J4di1mVFAxNnRuRjRJNDVEYjJxMWF0YUtqZG9KQ2QzZjVaamlzbmVIUF9XcF9tanJDX0Zad1lNYXN1dUw4Yzk0alh3dGkwZjdTb0RvX2EtTm9ZYnhjcmhSSFM1SDJTbVI1b0wweU40WQ</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心为有争议的丹麦研究人员开展的乙型肝炎疫苗研究提供160万$ - CIDRAP</title><link>https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/cdc-awards-16-million-hepatitis-b-vaccine-study-controversial-danish-researchers</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-field-body field--type-text-long field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) &lt;a href="https://public-inspection.federalregister.gov/2025-23245.pdf"&gt;has awarded an unsolicited $1.6 million grant&lt;/a&gt; for vaccine research to Danish researchers whose studies &lt;a href="https://health.au.dk/en/display/artikel/randomized-trials-show-no-evidence-of-non-specific-vaccine-effects"&gt;have been challenged&lt;/a&gt; by mainstream scientists but &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/news/the-impact-of-vaccines-on-mortality-decline-since-1900-according-to-published-science/"&gt;championed by anti-vaccine activists,&lt;/a&gt; including Health and Human Services (HHS) Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a notice in the &lt;em&gt;Federal Register&lt;/em&gt; posted yesterday, the CDC is paying the University of Southern Denmark to conduct a single-blind clinical trial of the hepatitis B vaccine in newborns in Guinea-Bissau, a small country in West Africa with exceptionally high rates of maternal and infant mortality, where nearly one in five people &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/31746078/#:~:text=Results:%20A%20total%20of%202715,enqu%C3%AAtes%20dans%20la%20population%20g%C3%A9n%C3%A9rale."&gt;are infected with the hepatitis B virus.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CDC is an agency within HHS. The study aims to assess the optimal timing and delivery of hepatitis B vaccinations, according to the notice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;‘Appearance of blatant cronyism’&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new study was awarded without any competition from any other scientists, giving it “the appearance of blatant cronyism,” said Angela Rasmussen, PhD, a virologist and professor at the University of Saskatchewan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the federal announcement did not include the names of the researchers, the Danish university’s Bandim Health Project, which has conducted vaccine research in the developing African country for decades, &lt;a href="https://Although%20the%20federal%20announcement%20did%20not%20include%20the%20names%20of%20the%20researchers,%20the%20Danish%20university%E2%80%99s%20Bandim%20Health%20Project,%20which%20has%20conducted%20vaccine%20research%20in%20the%20developing%20African%20country%20for%20decades,%20has%20acknowledged%20being%20awarded%20the%20CDC%20grant."&gt;has acknowledged being awarded&lt;/a&gt; the CDC grant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Bandim project leaders &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/vaccines-have-health-effects-beyond-protecting-against-target-diseases-106383"&gt;have claimed to find “non-specific effects”&lt;/a&gt; from vaccines—some good and some bad—that they say &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10116894/pdf/40264_2023_Article_1295.pdf"&gt;should change how vaccine safety studies&lt;/a&gt; are conducted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their message has &lt;a href="https://www.weekendavisen.dk/samfund/et-daarligt-immunforsvar"&gt;resonated with Kennedy,&lt;/a&gt; a long-time anti-vaccine activist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In June, Kennedy &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/kennedy-pulls-us-support-gavis-vaccine-efforts"&gt;used a single study&lt;/a&gt; by the Bandim group &lt;a href="https://www.npr.org/sections/goats-and-soda/2025/07/01/g-s1-74752/rfk-jr-vaccines-safety-gavi"&gt;to justify canceling&lt;/a&gt; more than $1 billion in funding for childhood vaccinations in developing countries. The observational study found an increased risk of death in children who received a combined vaccine for diphtheria, tetanus and pertussis (DPT) that hasn’t been used in the United States in three decades. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists say people shouldn’t put too much faith in that study, which is an outlier and conflicts with hundreds of studies showing that vaccines are safe and save lives. Researchers and policy makers normally consider the totality of scientific evidence on vaccines, rather than a single study, which may be flawed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, observational studies, in which scientists merely follow patients but do not randomly assign them to undergo different medical interventions, are not able to prove cause and effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet Children’s Health Defense, the anti-vaccine organization Kennedy founded, &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/research_category/dtap-tdap/#:~:text=Blok%20BA%2C%20de%20Bree%20LCJ%2C%20Diavatopoulos%20DA%2C,van%20Crevel%20R%2C%20Benn%20CS%2C%20Netea%20MG."&gt;cites the Danish group’s research&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/research_tags/diphtheria-tetanus-pertusis-dtp/"&gt;multiple pages&lt;/a&gt; of its website. One article &lt;a href="https://childrenshealthdefense.org/news/the-impact-of-vaccines-on-mortality-decline-since-1900-according-to-published-science/"&gt;praises the Bandim Health’s founder,&lt;/a&gt; Danish anthropologist Peter Aaby, casting him as a martyr who lost his funding when he suggested vaccines cause more harm than good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple scientists have criticized the Bandim group’s methodology and conclusions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A review &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0264410X25012344"&gt;published in &lt;em&gt;Vaccine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; last month found that Bandim Health researchers “have systematically over-interpreted the findings from their randomized trials” for 25 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 23 out of 25 articles, the researchers highlighted secondary findings as support for their theories, but in 22 of these cases the evidence disappeared after proper statistical handling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group “systematically selected and highlighted results that supported their theories, while downplaying the fact that they did not confirm the primary hypothesis the trials were actually designed to test,” said Henrik Stovring, PhD, a professor of biomedicine at Denmark’s Aarhus University who led the new review, &lt;a href="https://health.au.dk/en/display/artikel/randomized-trials-show-no-evidence-of-non-specific-vaccine-effects"&gt;in a press release&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In 23 out of 25 articles, the researchers highlighted secondary findings as support for their theories, but in 22 of these cases the evidence disappeared after proper statistical handling,” said Stovring said, who is &lt;span&gt;also a professor at the Steno Diabetes Center Aarhus&lt;/span&gt;. “When you look at the overall picture, there are almost no real findings left.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two reviews commissioned by the World Health Organization &lt;a href="https://www.bmj.com/content/355/bmj.i5434#:~:text=Taken%20together%2C%20the%20two%20systematic,countries%20is%20the%20only%20alternative."&gt;concluded that the evidence for non-specific effects&lt;/a&gt; “remains weak and vulnerable to biases.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Danish media also &lt;a href="https://www.weekendavisen.dk/samfund/et-daarligt-immunforsvar"&gt;have criticized&lt;/a&gt; Aaby and Christine Stabell Benn, MD, PhD, his wife and research partner, for &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/05/19/tracy-beth-hoeg-fda-advisor-marty-makary-vinay-prasad-vaccine-policy/#:~:text=Stabell%20Benn%20and%20her%20husband,results%20of%20the%20observational%20study."&gt;touting the findings of their observational study&lt;/a&gt; while &lt;a href="https://www.sensible-med.com/p/the-false-narrative-of-nonspecific"&gt;failing to publish the results&lt;/a&gt; of a randomized controlled trial—considered the gold standard of medical evidence—on the DPT vaccine, conducted 14 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By commissioning the new vaccine study, the Trump administration’s is trying “to do anything they can to discredit all vaccines,” said Peter Hotez, MD, PhD, endowed chair of tropical pediatrics at Texas Children’s Hospital and co-director of its Center for Vaccine Development. “This is so self-defeating for the country.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Danish researchers have influenced US vaccine policy&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet Aaby and Stabell Benn have found an audience in an influential federal advisory group whose members were handpicked by Kennedy, who fired all of the previous members. The Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, which advises the CDC, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-09-18-19/effects-hep-b-vax-summary-508.pdf"&gt;cited the Guinea-Bissau research multiple times&lt;/a&gt; in a presentation at its September meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stabell Benn has &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-09-18-19/01-levi-covid-508.pdf"&gt;served as an expert source&lt;/a&gt; for ACIP and &lt;a href="https://podcasts.apple.com/us/podcast/how-the-next-four-years-can-improve-our-evidence-base/id1629371129?i=1000680049921"&gt;has collaborated&lt;/a&gt; on a Substack post and a series of podcasts with a senior leader at the Food and Drug Administration (FDA), Tracy Beth Hoeg, MD, PhD, who attends the committee’s meetings on behalf of agency. Hoeg previously &lt;a href="https://www.fda.gov/about-fda/fda-organization/tracy-hoeg"&gt;worked as an adjunct associate&lt;/a&gt; professor at the University of Southern Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role="group" class="caption caption-img align-left"&gt;
&lt;img alt="Vaccine needle and vial" src="/sites/default/files/Vax%20needle%20entering%20vial.jpg" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;figcaption&gt;Peter Hansen / iStock&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At an ACIP meeting this month, Hoeg &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/acip/downloads/slides-2025-12-04-05/01-Hoeg-Danish-vax-schedule-508.pdf"&gt;presented slides&lt;/a&gt; about vaccination practices in&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Denmark, suggesting that the United States follow that country’s approach. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within hours, President Donald Trump &lt;a href="https://www.whitehouse.gov/fact-sheets/2025/12/fact-sheet-president-donald-j-trump-begins-process-to-align-u-s-core-childhood-vaccine-recommendations-with-best-practices-from-peer-developed-countries/"&gt;called for the US to align&lt;/a&gt; its childhood vaccination schedule with those of countries such as Denmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither Stabell Benn nor Aaby responded to a request for an interview by deadline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An HHS spokesman said the study in Guinea-Bissau will fill a vital need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This award supports an independent study designed to answer important questions about the broader health effects of the hepatitis B birth dose,” said Andrew Nixon. “This research aims to fill existing evidence gaps to help inform global hepatitis B vaccine policy and we will ensure the highest scientific and ethical standards are met.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In spite of strenuous objections from three physicians on the committee, ACIP earlier this month &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/anti-science/cdc-advisers-drop-decades-old-universal-hepatitis-b-birth-dose-recommendation-suggest"&gt;voted to abandon&lt;/a&gt; a 34-year-old recommendation to vaccinate all newborns for hepatitis B, a practice that has reduced infections in children and adolescents by 99%. Since 1991, the universal HBV birth dose &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/vaccinating-newborns-against-hepatitis-b-saves-lives-why-might-cdc-panel-stop"&gt;has prevented an estimated&lt;/a&gt; 90,100 childhood deaths. Its safety &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/sites/default/files/searchable-download/Universal%20Hepatitis%20B%20Vaccination%20at%20Birth%202Dec2025.pdf"&gt;has been demonstrated in hundreds&lt;/a&gt; of studies over the past four decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The acting CDC director this week &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/hepatitis/cdc-accepts-acip-s-hepatitis-b-vaccine-recommendations-babies"&gt;followed ACIP advice&lt;/a&gt;, recommending a birth dose of hepatitis B vaccine only for babies who mothers are infected with the virus or whose infection status is unknown. The change &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/childhood-vaccines/cidrap-op-ed-heres-what-removal-hepatitis-b-birth-dose-will-look"&gt;will lead more babies to develop hepatitis B&lt;/a&gt;, which can lead to liver cancer, liver failure and death, wrote Jake Scott, MD, a clinical associate professor of infectious disease and geographic medicine at Stanford University School of Medicine, in an editorial for CIDRAP News.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Cherry-picking studies and researchers&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple researchers who spoke to CIDRAP News questioned the need for another study of hepatitis B vaccines, which &lt;a href="https://www.cidrap.umn.edu/sites/default/files/searchable-download/Universal%20Hepatitis%20B%20Vaccination%20at%20Birth%202Dec2025.pdf"&gt;have been proven safe and effective&lt;/a&gt; in more than 400 studies over 40 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The data that supports the safety advocacy of the current hepatitis B vaccines is very robust,” said Amesh A. Adalja, MD, a senior scholar at the Johns Hopkins Center for Health Security. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Given the stance of the CDC under RFK Jr’s control, one can assume that the results of this study will be preordained to be against the hepatitis B vaccines,” Adalja said. “Continuing to do studies on a question that is already been answered sufficiently is a waste of resources that could better be used answering new questions.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some researchers question where the Trump administration found $1.6 million for the study, given that it &lt;a href="https://www.americanprogress.org/article/mapping-federal-funding-cuts-to-us-colleges-and-universities/#:~:text=According%20to%20the%20Trump%20administration,claiming%20as%20victories%20thus%20far."&gt;has cut billions of dollars&lt;/a&gt; in federal support for science.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“NIH is in crisis, grants are being terminated, labs are closing, researchers are being laid off,” Scott told CIDRAP News. “But they found $1.6 million for an unsolicited proposal to study whether we should delay a vaccine we’ve been safely giving for 40 years, in a country where infants are at high risk of infection. The money exists. It’s the priorities that have changed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists said the new study raises ethical concerns on several fronts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Awarding money to an organization without allowing other scientists to compete for the grant is very unusual, Rasmussen said. When this happens, the study protocol typically undergoes rigorous review.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HHS has not released details of the study, noting only that the research will involve a “comparable study of the optimal timing and delivery of … hepatitis vaccinations on newborns in Guinea-Bissau. Activities will include conducting a randomized controlled trial to assess the effects of neonatal hepatitis B vaccination on early-life mortality, morbidity, and long-term developmental outcomes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rasmussen notes that it would not be ethical to provide a birth dose of the hepatitis B vaccine to some babies but not others, given that doctors know the immunization saves lives, both in the early newborn period and decades later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exposing thousands of babies to “a significant risk” of hepatitis B “in a low-income country with limited health care resources” would be “wildly unethical and a disgraceful use of American taxpayer money,” Rasmussen said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers note that Guinea-Bissau, &lt;a href="https://www.afdb.org/en/countries/west-africa/guinea-bissau/guinea-bissau-economic-outlook#:~:text=According%20to%20World%20Bank%20data,an%20estimated%203.9%25%20in%202023."&gt;has a poverty rate of 60%&lt;/a&gt; and a population of 2.2 million, about 150 times smaller than the United States.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you commission research after making a decision, you're not looking for answers—you're looking for validation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Guinea-Bissau study’s findings are unlikely to be relevant to US vaccine policy, given the nation “has very different population demographics from the US and has a health system which is very different from the US,” said Robert H. Hopkins Jr., MD, medical director of the National Foundation for Infectious Diseases (NFID). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott said the study’s announcement suggests that the CDC isn’t truly looking for answers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In evidence-based policy, you gather data and then make a decision,” Scott said. “This is the reverse. CDC made the policy decision and then funded research to back it up. When you commission research after making a decision, you're not looking for answers—you're looking for validation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Note:&lt;/strong&gt; This story and headline were updated shortly after the story was published after the Bandim group confirmed that they are the recipients of the CDC funding.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CIDRAP</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:59:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxPWWJCbk8zR2NVbmFydnpQMXg0dGpfbm1FWWVpd1ROTW5EMm13UU1jaDdXZExfOWdfRVVoVy1Leko4RjJSS1h0NERDX0xxazlERkY0QmJLN1NoanZHM0dRWjFqRmxFTGdIX3NHdkxzd2Z1NjlZdG5QeU1OTGN2M2R3SmhHT255MmozVDhtSXNNU1BSTVViNHZZek9RY0VJdWh6ZXhXQnJnYXhwUzdDZWVMa2d2OGpmTFhoak5EbWoyUlhpZThl</guid></item><item><title>咒骂会让你更强壮吗？科学说是。- Ars Technica</title><link>https://arstechnica.com/science/2025/12/does-swearing-make-you-stronger-science-says-yes/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content post-content-double"&gt;
          
          
&lt;p&gt;The result: Only the F-word had any effect on pain outcomes. The team also measured the subjects’ pain threshold, asking them to indicate when the ice water began to feel painful. Those who chanted the F-word waited longer before indicating they felt pain—in other words, the swearing increased their threshold for pain. Chanting “fouch” or “twizpipe” had no effect on either measure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;F@%*-ing go for it&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For this latest study, Stephens was interested in investigating potential mechanisms for swearing as a possible form of disinhibition (usually viewed negatively), building on his team’s &lt;a href="https://psycnet.apa.org/record/2018-06780-014"&gt;2018&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35135411/"&gt;2022&lt;/a&gt; papers showing that swearing can improve strength in a chair push-up task. “In many situations, people hold themselves back—consciously or unconsciously—from using their full strength,” &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1110041?"&gt;said Stephens&lt;/a&gt;. “By swearing, we throw off social constraint and allow ourselves to push harder in different situations. Swearing is an easily available way to help yourself feel focused, confident and less distracted, and ‘go for it’ a little more.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In two separate experiments, participants were asked to select a swear word they’d normally use after, say, bumping their head, and a more neutral word to describe an inanimate object like a table. They then performed the aforementioned chair push-up task: sitting on a sturdy chair and placing their hands under their thighs with the fingers pointed inwards. Then they lifted their feet off the floor and straightened their arms to support their body weight for as long as possible, chanting either the swear word or the neutral word every two seconds. Afterward, subjects competed a questionnaire to assess various aspects of their mental state during the task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results: Subjects who swore during the task could support their body weight much longer than those who merely repeated the neutral word. This confirms the reported results of similar studies in the past. Furthermore, subjects reported increases in their sense of psychological “flow,” distraction, and self-confidence, all indicators of increased disinhibition.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“These findings help explain why swearing is so commonplace,” &lt;a href="https://www.eurekalert.org/news-releases/1110041?"&gt;said Stephens&lt;/a&gt;. “Swearing is literally a calorie-neutral, drug-free, low-cost, readily available tool at our disposal for when we need a boost in performance.” The team next plans to explore the influence of swearing on public speaking and romantic behaviors, since these are situations where most people are more hesitant and less confident in themselves, and hence more likely to hold back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DOI: American Psychologist, 2025. &lt;a href="http://dx.doi.org/10.1037/amp0001650"&gt;10.1037/amp0001650&lt;/a&gt;  (&lt;a href="http://arstechnica.com/science/news/2010/03/dois-and-their-discontents-1.ars"&gt;About DOIs&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;


          
                  &lt;/div&gt;

                  
          &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Ars Technica</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:46:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxNc3hmZDJieEtZcWs4aDNFVnFxMFZRaVowZjV6X3Jid0xiVklSNWZFWlBMYi1FZUV6aE0tX0FLdEdwelhsQ2RfZkh4Y3N5VDE0Q2h1ZW1nS2tGVHJXenh5ek1BTDdfSy1xWUZtbU03UlFhUElVemJMRGx5dnIxUDVrOUU1WjNlWUQyT05mX21aSE9sSU0</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，不要犹豫，咒骂可以通过降低抑制来提高表现-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/science/2025/dec/18/swearing-can-boost-performance-lowering-inhibitions-study</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;It may not be in keeping with the festive spirit, but if you find yourself dropping the F-word while wrestling a Christmas tree up a flight of stairs, scientists say you could be on to something. A study has found that swearing can enhance physical performance by lowering inhibitions and pushing the brain into a “flow state”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“In many situations, people hold themselves back – consciously or unconsciously – from using their full strength,” said Dr Richard Stephens, a psychologist at Keele University who led the research. “Swearing is an easily available way to help yourself feel focused, confident and less distracted, and go for it a little more.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Previous research found that swearing could increase strength and pain tolerance in tests where participants repeated swearwords while pushing themselves to the limit, such as cycling at maximum effort or holding a hand in icy water. Researchers initially hypothesised that swearing triggered a “fight or flight” response but found no supporting evidence, such as an increased heart rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Instead, the latest research suggests swearing triggers a state of disinhibition. “By swearing, we throw off social constraint and allow ourselves to push harder,” said Stephens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;To test this, the researchers ran two experiments involving 192 people. In each, participants were asked to repeat either an expletive of their choice or a neutral word every two seconds while performing chair pushups. After completing the exercise, they answered questions about their mental state during the task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Their answers suggested that swearing boosted self-confidence, improved psychological “flow” and distracted them from the task – important aspects of disinhibition. Confirming earlier findings, the researchers found that swearing increased the length of time people could maintain a chair pushup by 11%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“These findings help explain why swearing is so commonplace,” said Stephens. “Swearing is literally a calorie-neutral, drug-free, low-cost, readily available tool at our disposal for when we need a boost in performance.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Stephens said the power of swearwords was likely to lie in their taboo nature. His team is investigating whether more offensive language produces greater physical gains, in a “dose-response” trial that will test how long participants can tolerate holding their hand in icy water while repeating either mild or strong swearwords.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The team is also exploring whether the confidence boost associated with swearing could help in other contexts, such as public speaking or making a romantic approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There are lots of situations where hesitancy might be to our detriment,” said Stephens. “You could go into a quiet room, go for it swearing for a minute and then go out and give your talk. I bet people do it already.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;However, he cautioned that swearing was not an entirely risk-free strategy. “You’re never quite sure when you use a swearword how it’s going to land,” he said. “You have to know your audience and who is around. You could land yourself in hot water if you swear inappropriately.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The findings are published in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/amp-amp0001650.pdf" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;American Psychologist&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqAFBVV95cUxOZExSNzdzVlFTZWNvLUN1enRoUzJHc3ZUNTgycGZCdW1qdWhwTVl0Ql9ZTzVYcWZBZ1lubndqWWR6amRDMTVQNEJTMjA4ZXlxT3ZxUkUya0preERwdUxSTy1FU19qUmJ1MGY2TEt2blJtenMyN1g3NWJGeUNwWl9jbHFwdUljXzBSVkgxaDhzdjNBUzRaUHhGaVhWc2RlWHhCV0ZzUHhHakQ</guid></item><item><title>避免在飞机上生病的最佳座位-福克斯新闻</title><link>https://www.foxnews.com/lifestyle/best-seat-avoid-getting-sick-plane</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Fox News</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:18:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMid0FVX3lxTE5fdUZhTWJPdVFPY3IwdVZHbW1jZUVyMnFKejlFcTlFTXR0enVuaGprREhyUko4aVByZWlzRE90ekdIRi16VTVoWXdoVVYwOXdxMnRDRXFFS3FIbFpYSi01SG5iYThMLTE0TG5VNHc0ZVVDTVdqWWxz</guid></item><item><title>为什么女性要支付超过2000 $来逆转“Ozempic阴道” ，因为它变得越来越普遍- UNILAD</title><link>https://www.unilad.com/news/health/ozempic-vagina-explained-labia-puffing-380308-20251217</link><description>&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p class="loading-bar_loader__2fNms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;main class="article_main__eth__ "&gt;&lt;template id="B:0"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;p class="article-page-skeleton_background__h2J4n"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/main&gt;&lt;p hidden id="S:0"&gt;&lt;template id="P:1"&gt;&lt;/template&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;</description><author>UNILAD</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:18:17 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwFBVV95cUxPZGVuVzZ1N1BOYlZBRUl3LUxfa0g2SHBJMnpydXBJV2NPSG40MUZMYkp5UmJWWjJxWXlpZUpLVGlwb1JHTkY0SDVJRWFRQjdNVDFZV3JXLU5vT3M5eWYxOEdqdXRRWWthWXRYMGNRUFc0YUtvWlZwQ3FWYU84dGRxakN5WjdZdjg2VG9mazIxUWpHMnc</guid></item><item><title>哪些血液测试可以检测出阿尔茨海默氏症的生物标志物，哪些不能告诉您-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/12/18/alzheimers-detection-blood-tests/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SABCJW3FRFH7ROGV42QTW5UAXI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;As scientists race to develop simple blood tests that could one day act as an early warning system for Alzheimer’s disease by sounding the alarm before memory problems appear, new research shows tracking shifts in certain protein biomarkers over time is more accurate than relying on a single test result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 13:01:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxOZEVYaXBwenMtT0h0cWJPcFZwNTQ0emJERF95R2JJZU1rNnBEcndteExJOGZESDEwSGRGMnZTWFhlRWhnNzRKbWZER2tlclVvQTVROXc4MGtjTWZYbXJnSmNzOXpxQmFCWDhyRnJabmJwclVpTlJhX0ItMlVQcXI0aGtIMW5DbTdUZWc</guid></item><item><title>流感疫情：您所在地区的医院如何受到影响？ - BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cvgqkvll1yvo</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Hospitals across the UK are seeing high levels of flu cases this winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The NHS in England has said it is on "on high alert" after seeing the highest ever number of flu cases in hospital for this time of year, in the week ending 14 December.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;You can use our tool below to find out how many flu patients there are in hospitals near you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Figures relating to flu cases in hospitals are collected in different ways in each UK nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In England it is the weekly number of beds occupied by patients with a laboratory confirmed flu case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This data is provided at NHS Trust level. Trusts are organisations which include hospitals, community services and providers of other forms of patient care. You can find which trust your local hospital belongs to on the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhs.uk/nhs-services" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;NHS England&lt;/a&gt; website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In Scotland the figures relate to the number of patients admitted to hospital with a laboratory confirmed flu case taken between 14 days before the admission date and 48 hours after the admission date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In Wales it is the weekly number of patients in hospital with a laboratory confirmed flu case taken from 28 days before the admission date if tested outside of hospital, or within two days after admission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Figures for Scotland and Wales are provided at NHS Health Board level. Health boards are responsible for all frontline healthcare services. You can find which Health Board your local services belong to on the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nhsinform.scot/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;NHS Scotland&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.wales.nhs.uk/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;NHS Wales&lt;/a&gt; websites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In Northern Ireland the figures show the number of new flu cases admitted to hospital that were acquired outside of hospital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This data is provided at Health and Social Care Trust level. Trusts are responsible for providing local and regional health services. You can find which trust your local hospital belongs to on the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.nidirect.gov.uk/information-and-services/health-and-wellbeing/health-services" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;NI direct&lt;/a&gt; website.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:37:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE91WGdoVG5XcXplSkZobkRGM2oyLXV0aXN4QmhvMWQzWDNGTDVfNllOT2UzZGJTQU9feGhqX3pyblJIMG1lbEdCZjFsMGxFTnU4cDlvTGd0M1JtQdIBX0FVX3lxTE5FeXZkT1VmRUpNQmpQX2puQUt4dG5naFJpemZhY3c0VFFPOFJuMEVVZm5FbU1WZHE4VEIyWU00TlRMOXloUHh0LTRKazZNVWRSemMwOFlYel9jbmJrVFdn</guid></item><item><title>新的“超级抗生素”在不破坏微生物组的情况下杀死致命的肠道感染- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/new-super-antibiotic-kills-deadly-gut-infection-without-destroying-the-microbiome/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:35:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxQNjYzOUw4bjZwSnRNZFpnaUtsQWhkUkRtcnVWMHF2dXlzNC1yOE81WFlXZFE2WHBubEVFOEhaRWtfaVhqeHRLLUNjVks1X0o4UnYwaE1DaGlZY05FbllqQXVaU05yQlVxMWtLS0dqQmxjY0lubXVEdFNqY1VVVFo0STI2LUFDUmNES0dqTlpwTldTanR4WWY3UERQV19xM1liQWw2cWJuLTRKaTA</guid></item><item><title>在为期25年的研究中，奶酪与降低痴呆风险有关- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/cheese-linked-to-lower-dementia-risk-in-25-year-study</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;One of the finest foods available to humanity may carry an unexpected benefit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study has found that eating 50 grams (1.76 ounces) or more of high-fat cheese a day correlates with a lower risk of developing dementia. That means all cheeses with more than 20 percent fat content, &lt;a href="https://bcpa.eu/factsheets/FatContentOfCheeses.htm"&gt;including&lt;/a&gt; brie, gouda, cheddar, parmesan, gruyere, and mozzarella.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extensive, long-term study followed 27,670 adults in Sweden for around 25 years. The findings establish an association between daily consumption of high-fat cheese and lower dementia risk that is statistically detectable – although more research needs to be done to figure out the potential mechanism behind it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Related: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-common-sleeping-pill-could-reduce-buildup-of-alzheimers-proteins-study-finds"&gt;&lt;b&gt;A Common Sleeping Pill Could Reduce Buildup of Alzheimer's Proteins, Study Finds&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"For decades, the debate over high-fat versus low-fat diets has shaped health advice, sometimes even categorizing cheese as an unhealthy food to limit," &lt;a href="https://www.aan.com/PressRoom/home/PressRelease/5304"&gt;says nutrition epidemiologist Emily Sonestedt&lt;/a&gt; of Lund University in Sweden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our study found that some high-fat dairy products may actually lower the risk of dementia, challenging some long-held assumptions about fat and brain health."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dementia is an umbrella term for &lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/what-is-dementia/types-of-dementia"&gt;several conditions&lt;/a&gt; that impair cognitive function, such as  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="186017" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease (the most common form), vascular dementia, and dementia that can develop in disorders like &lt;a href="https://www.alz.org/alzheimers-dementia/what-is-dementia/types-of-dementia/parkinson-s-disease-dementia"&gt;Parkinson's disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An estimated &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/dementia"&gt;57 million people&lt;/a&gt; were living with dementia in 2021, and an estimated 10 million new cases are diagnosed every year. A 2019 Global Burden of Disease analysis projected that, by 2050, the number of cases could rise &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/s2468-2667(21)00249-8"&gt;as high as 153 million&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since there's a dearth of effective treatments for dementia, some researchers are focusing their efforts on ways of reducing the chances of developing dementia, with &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/major-study-links-4-healthy-diets-with-up-to-28-lower-dementia-risk"&gt;diet playing a major role&lt;/a&gt; in these &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-diet-helps-lower-dementia-risk-and-we-may-finally-know-why"&gt;risk mitigation strategies&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The so-called MIND diet – a variation of the Mediterranean diet – has &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/sticking-to-the-mind-diet-could-reduce-your-risk-of-developing-dementia"&gt;been touted as promising&lt;/a&gt;; however, &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1186/s13195-022-00957-1"&gt;findings&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1001/jamapsychiatry.2023.0800"&gt;different studies&lt;/a&gt; are &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/nu15010032"&gt;inconsistent&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dairy is one particular food group whose association with dementia has been difficult to establish. Studies from &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s00394-022-02834-x"&gt;Finland&lt;/a&gt;, the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1007/s11357-022-00615-2"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-taste-for-cheese-may-reveal-your-future-risk-of-dementia"&gt;Japan&lt;/a&gt;, for example, have looked at different amounts of cheese consumption and found varying results in dementia links.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the new paper, led by nutrition epidemiologist Yufeng Du of Lund University, researchers set out to clarify these inconsistent findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They based their analysis on the &lt;a href="https://www.malmo-kohorter.lu.se/malmo-diet-cancer-mdc"&gt;Malmö Diet and Cancer cohort&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;span&gt;a long-running observational study surveying Swedish residents about their diet and tracking health outcomes&lt;/span&gt;. &lt;span&gt;Of the 27,670 participants, 3,208 developed dementia over the course of about 25 years.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants recorded their diet at baseline using a 7-day food diary, a food-frequency questionnaire, and a detailed interview about food preparation and eating habits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="docos-replyview-body docos-anchoredreplyview-body docos-replyview-body-emoji-reactable docos-replyview-body-emoji-reactable-background" dir="ltr"&gt;The researchers compared people's dementia risk based on their cheese intake. Around 10 percent of those who ate 50 grams or more of high-fat cheese per day developed dementia, compared to about 13 percent of people who ate less than 15 grams a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After adjusting for age, sex, education, and overall diet, people who ate more than 50 grams of high-fat cheese per day had a 13 percent lower all-cause dementia risk compared to people who ate less than 15 grams per day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No such association appeared for low-fat cheese or cream, any kind of milk, or fermented milk products such as yogurt and kefir. Butter showed mixed results, including a possible increased Alzheimer's risk at high intake compared to people eating no butter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But before you chow down on cheese with abandon, other researchers point out important issues with the research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;"One of the biggest limitations of this study is the cheese consumption as recorded from a food diary and interview at one time point 25 years before the analysis of dementia diagnosis. It is highly likely that diet and other lifestyle factors changed in those 25 years," &lt;a href="https://www.sciencemediacentre.org/expert-reaction-to-study-looking-at-the-association-between-eating-high-fat-cheese-and-cream-and-dementia-risk/"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Tara Spires-Jones, Division Lead in the UK Dementia Research Institute, who was not involved in the study.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As nice as it would be, it may not be wise to pin your hopes on any one food to protect yourself against dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1212/WNL.0000000000214343"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Neurology&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:02:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiigFBVV95cUxQdlczWVRkSXQyVlA3NDV6enQ2aDdHTmhpZWNYS2FtNGczZGhvRXVndVpMVnkzaXVPTG91Zmx3U016V3dhR2JpVktUU3ZlSjRORnp6d0lmbnJ4LWduOGt1VDBhVWlmV2xRVWtPbjRYNGlpc2NaMWVpNUJNZmpMOFhXVTRkNmNJNW9aWWc</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心官员敦促美国在去年创纪录的儿童死亡后接种流感疫苗-卫报</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/dec/18/cdc-flu-vaccination</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Officials are urging doctors to vaccinate their patients and provide flu antivirals after deaths among children reached record highs and as a concerning mutation of the virus circulates in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Influenza activity is increasing in the US. The time to get vaccinated for this season is now,” Timothy Uyeki, the chief medical officer of the influenza division at the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), said in a call with clinicians last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The message comes amid diminishing access to and flourishing rumors about vaccines under Robert F Kennedy Jr, the secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services, who has made &lt;a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2025/01/28/health/rfk-jr-vaccines-autism-video.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;false claims&lt;/a&gt; about the ineffectiveness of flu vaccines and &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/dec/06/vaccine-panel-hepatitis-b-change" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;overseen limitations&lt;/a&gt; on routine vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;After a year of dramatic cuts to staff and programs at health agencies, CDC officials highlighted the need to continue monitoring variants such as the H3N2 virus subclade K – currently the top strain in the US – as flu season unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s hard to say what will happen throughout the season, and that’s why we need surveillance to really track this,” Uyeki said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;A child died of the flu in the week ending 22 November, marking the first known pediatric death this season, the CDC &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/fluview/surveillance/2025-week-49.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; earlier this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The CDC also reported another child death from flu during last year’s season, bringing the total to 288 – the deadliest pediatric flu season on record outside of a pandemic. Last year, there were an estimated 610,000 to 1.3 million hospitalizations from influenza in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Last season, by all indicators, was a high severity season and one of the highest we have experienced in the US,” Uyeki said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Officials at the CDC on last week’s call highlighted changes in vaccine policy – including a new recommendation against thimerosal, a preservative also known as thiomersal, previously used in a small percentage of flu vaccines. The CDC’s vaccine advisers voted to recommend only flu vaccines without the preservative in a June meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The top regulators of vaccines and drugs at the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) also recently announced changes to how flu vaccines will be approved, which may include &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/dec/11/fda-vaccine-regulations-unconfirmed-covid-deaths" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;extensive trials&lt;/a&gt; each year for children and pregnant people that would put annual vaccination &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/dec/04/us-vaccines-vinay-prasad-memo" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;out of reach&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Children, pregnant people, immune-compromised people, and the elderly are among those at highest risk of illness and death. Vaccines protect against severe complications like pneumonia, cardiac complications, neurological issues, and encephalopathy, or brain dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;There were 109 cases of encephalopathy among children last year, with 74% needing intensive care and 54% needing mechanical ventilators. Most (55%) of the children with encephalopathy had no underlying conditions – except for not being vaccinated. Only 16% of the children who were eligible had gotten vaccinated. Nearly one in five (19%) of the children with encephalopathy died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The majority of these are preventable, and this is really, really tragic,” said Uyeki.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“This is the highest number of deaths for a seasonal influenza epidemic since we’ve been keeping track, and clearly highlights the fact that we need to do a much better job of preventing influenza and preventing influenza-associated death in children in the United States.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Last year, the vaccine was 63% to 78% &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/74/wr/mm7406a2.htm" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;effective&lt;/a&gt; at preventing hospitalization among children and 41% to 55% effective against hospitalization among adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In August, the CDC identified the new variant (H3N2 virus subclade K), which mutated from the version of H3N2 included in the vaccine – raising concerns that the flu vaccine might be less effective this season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="EmailSignUpWrapper" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props="{&amp;quot;index&amp;quot;:16,&amp;quot;listId&amp;quot;:4152,&amp;quot;identityName&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;today-us&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;description&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Get the most important US headlines and highlights emailed direct to you every morning&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;name&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Headlines US&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;frequency&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Every day&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;successDescription&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;We'll send you The Guardian Headlines US every day&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;theme&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;news&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;idApiUrl&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;https://idapi.theguardian.com&amp;quot;}"&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;As the flu season in the US is only beginning now, there is too little data so far to calculate how effective the vaccine is against it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It’s too early to know what impact exactly this new subclade will have on the influenza vaccine effectiveness for this season,” said Lisa Grohskopf, also a medical officer in the CDC’s influenza division.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It takes a little while before accumulating enough activity and specimens to be able to calculate [vaccine effectiveness].”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Based on early numbers from the United Kingdom, which had an early start to the flu season, vaccine effectiveness is about 70 to 75% for children and 30 to 40% for adults – similar to prior vaccine efficacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The evidence indicates that “influenza vaccination remains an effective tool in preventing influenza-associated hospitalizations for the season”, Grohskopf said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The flu vaccine is recommended for everyone six months and up, she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Providers have been &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/nov/11/pediatricians-vaccines-flu-season" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;recommending FluMist more&lt;/a&gt; to patients who are eligible. It’s not a shot, which may assuage vaccine hesitancy. And it may now be given at home by a caregiver or the patient after a major change from the FDA in September 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;​​Antivirals are also a safe and effective way to treat and prevent severe illness, including in pregnancy, and they work best the sooner they can be started.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In recent years, flu antiviral prescriptions have dropped, Uyeki said. Only 35% of children at high risk are prescribed antivirals, and only 32% of children who visited emergency departments because of flu were prescribed antivirals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE5XYjFjM1J0WUxCVWZZcXI3d05pbGRXVzZIUU1wakNYd3pzOWNrNVBoaFFXLWZLdkRXdk9FUjJudG4tMXJ4cHJEQTNDY1VlM3JUbnVsVkdUQm9RVERzak9Hc2Q2TzZKUzJIOUFHVV9mWjJkWl91NkE</guid></item><item><title>尝试治疗喉咙痛的7种家庭疗法-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/12/18/sore-throat-home-remedies/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="N52IDJ4S7RDVJOHY2YI3DAAQGU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Woke up to a sore, scratchy throat? You may want to blame it on dry air, but it’s usually a sign your body is fighting a viral infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text subtype-from-the-source" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SXLK7G6S35H2TC4RAG44PZEQEY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“The top five causes of a sore throat are a virus, a virus, a virus, a virus and a virus,” said Elisabeth Fowlie Mock, a family physician and director at the American Academy of Family Physicians. The culprits that can trigger a sore throat include rhinoviruses (the most common cause of colds), influenza, coronavirus and respiratory syncytial virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:57:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMigwFBVV95cUxOcWtzYkFrc1V0RHdPVFpEaGo0ZlFKNTZFSHpkbGRCaXVwZl9XVTdJcHlBX0VCaGtncDVSUEw3TllUcVBxY0Z4Um5SOXZkbDNqUEpDYm5QTXR6eFg0NS1jZ0ZOb054YlNJSWk0QzF2SmdEbjdIbkpINFAzenk1YmRIOWdpMA</guid></item><item><title>新药片终于可以在没有口罩的情况下治疗睡眠呼吸暂停- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/new-pill-could-finally-treat-sleep-apnea-without-a-mask/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:25:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxObzdKdzRNTTJXdFdXNU5Mal9VMW9Bd3B2VlVjRnBaNDd6NU1CQ2ZqX1lrTmluS0xjSE0taEpXNm54dTA2aHB4dGZmS19feXVTNWhKUmt2YjhpMklmaHEwdUVfN2I5ZjVuc2xQb19ObzJRbmlyLXdJQUxVWmpFVzhLb0FmX1FDX0Vv</guid></item><item><title>科学家确定了预测痴呆风险的6个关键抑郁症状- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-identify-6-key-depression-symptoms-that-predict-dementia-risk</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Symptoms of  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/depression" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73097" data-postid="185948" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;depression&lt;/a&gt; in middle age could point towards &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/dementia-risk-declining-with-each-generation-says-promising-new-study"&gt;the likelihood of dementia&lt;/a&gt; later in life, a new study shows, which could perhaps enable &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/6-things-gen-z-should-be-doing-right-now-to-stave-off-dementia-later"&gt;precautions&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/an-existing-vaccine-could-slow-dementia-and-cut-death-risk-by-30"&gt;treatments&lt;/a&gt; to be put in place earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Depression and dementia have been &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/alzheimers-is-linked-to-stress-and-depression-and-we-may-know-why"&gt;linked before&lt;/a&gt;, which is part of the reason for the new research, led by a team from University College London (UCL). In this study though, the researchers identified six specific symptoms that may act as warning flags.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Our findings show that dementia risk is linked to a handful of depressive symptoms rather than depression as a whole," &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/news/2025/dec/specific-depressive-symptoms-midlife-linked-increased-dementia-risk"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; epidemiological psychologist Philipp Frank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This symptom-level approach gives us a much clearer picture of who may be more vulnerable decades before dementia develops."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/laughing-gas-can-offer-immediate-relief-from-depression-study-finds"&gt;Laughing Gas Can Offer Immediate Relief From Depression, Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers analyzed data for 5,811 individuals taking part in a longitudinal study in the UK. Information on patients' mental health was collected between 1997 and 1999, when the participants were aged between 45 and 69 and all dementia free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The health of these volunteers was then tracked for around two decades afterwards, on average. Dementia diagnoses &lt;span&gt;recorded in UK health records and registries &lt;/span&gt;up to 2023 were used in the final results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over that time, 10.1 percent of the participants developed dementia – and those who reported five or more symptoms of depression in middle age were found to have a 27 percent &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/the-roots-of-dementia-trace-back-all-the-way-to-childhood-experts-find"&gt;higher risk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, this risk increase was driven by six specific depressive symptoms, out of 30 assessed in total. Those six were losing confidence, difficulty coping with problems, not feeling affection for others, being &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-trial-compares-yoga-and-therapy-as-a-treatment-for-anxiety"&gt;nervous all the time&lt;/a&gt;, having difficulty &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/switching-off-for-a-moment-lets-your-brain-do-something-wonderful"&gt;concentrating&lt;/a&gt;, and not being satisfied with the way tasks are carried out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_185951" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-185951" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/DepressionChart.jpg" alt="Depression chart" class="wp-image-185951 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/DepressionChart.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/12/DepressionChart-600x571.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-185951" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;The researchers linked six symptoms of depression with dementia risk. (Frank et al., &lt;em&gt;Lancet Psychiat.&lt;/em&gt;, 2025)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The loss of self-confidence and not being able to deal with problems were particularly significant, with each increasing dementia risk by around 50 percent. Some symptoms, such as &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/poor-sleep-can-trigger-a-vicious-cycle-your-brain-cant-break-experts-warn"&gt;sleep problems&lt;/a&gt; and suicidal ideation, showed no long-term correlation with dementia diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the structure of the study doesn't show direct cause and effect, it suggests that certain elements of depression are associated with a higher chance of developing dementia – which may in turn inform research into &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/massive-study-links-15-factors-to-early-dementia-risk"&gt;why dementia takes hold&lt;/a&gt; of some brains but not others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everyday symptoms that many people experience in midlife appear to carry important information about long-term brain health," &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/news/2025/dec/specific-depressive-symptoms-midlife-linked-increased-dementia-risk"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Frank. "Paying attention to these patterns could open new opportunities for early prevention."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We know that both &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/some-antidepressants-could-speed-decline-in-dementia-patients"&gt;depression and dementia&lt;/a&gt; are complex and multi-faceted, and different between individuals. That makes trying to establish &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/dad2.70036"&gt;connections&lt;/a&gt; between them challenging – but &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1002/gps.5711"&gt;not impossible&lt;/a&gt;, as this study shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, there's no guarantee that these results apply universally. The team acknowledges that the research was conducted only in the UK, using relatively healthy civil servants. Dementia was found to be less common in participants in the longitudinal study, compared to the general UK population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More research is needed in more diverse cohorts, especially with &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2468-2667(21)00249-8"&gt;dementia expected&lt;/a&gt; to become more prevalent as the growing global population gets older. But it could give scientists a place to start at least, and if a proportion of those cases can be prevented, it could make a huge difference.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Depression doesn't have a single shape – symptoms vary widely and often overlap with anxiety," &lt;a href="https://www.ucl.ac.uk/news/2025/dec/specific-depressive-symptoms-midlife-linked-increased-dementia-risk"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; epidemiologist Mika Kivimäki. "We found that these nuanced patterns can reveal who is at &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-identify-4-key-factors-that-may-predict-cognitive-decline"&gt;higher risk&lt;/a&gt; of developing neurological disorders."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This brings us closer to more personalized and effective mental health treatments."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/S2215-0366(25)00331-1"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Lancet Psychiatry&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:02:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiowFBVV95cUxPb3h6Tk9Cekl4cy00UDdEUm9velRBUGRMa3ctN0NoNW93Q1oxV1U2Q3Z1YkVBbE11WkR3V0FqcHNwZzVhOXdjYmV3NjV5YWxWNTlFTGFVX1U3QzJzcWhSQTB4RDFsMGN4NzFVd3JCWjA4YTJUc1RyWENkQXkxd3ZTTVZUcGY1Nm1IZFM0ckxYbWdpU0FlZkJsQVo2SXN1V1pVc1M0</guid></item><item><title>佛罗里达州计划不再需要的四种疫苗是什么？ -坦帕湾时报</title><link>https://www.tampabay.com/news/florida-politics/2025/12/18/florida-vaccine-mandate-explained-ladapo-chickenpox-hepatitis-hib/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="author-bio article"&gt;&lt;a class="author-bio__image--wrapper" href="/author/romy-ellenbogen"&gt;&lt;figure class="author-bio__image" itemscope="" itemtype="https://schema.org/ImageObject"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="author-bio__content--role"&gt;Romy Ellenbogen is a Tallahassee correspondent, covering state government with a focus on criminal justice and health. Reach her at rellenbogen@tampabay.com. 
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tampa Bay Times</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:01:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxOaTdHelF2enR2RUl3X0xqdzB5TkYxamg4eFdZa2JlLTRDZ2tRRG0yZTVleFFtRFZkdV9TRjE3dHMyZGd2bUhfaWVtX1pld2FKOFd6VFlIYnJwSVBlb2pUNUdKdmRuak1sNjZZclRlVTlLQjhzX2NmYzRDeld1dUI5dzJFaTdrZ2JSNVk5TXFWTlhIWTh4THFVSmdkLVhkM094Tno0em9ncWRxSV9tc0F3OFptWnFsM2ZtS0wtV01FbGFNUQ</guid></item><item><title>人格障碍患者经常以不同的方式使用语言–我们的研究揭示了如何- The Conversation</title><link>https://theconversation.com/people-with-personality-disorders-often-use-language-differently-our-research-reveals-how-271109</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="grid-ten large-grid-nine grid-last content-body content entry-content instapaper_body inline-promos" itemprop="articleBody"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Is it possible to spot personality dysfunction from someone’s everyday word use?  My colleagues and I have conducted research that suggests you can, and often sooner than you might expect. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether in a quick text message, a long email, a casual chat with a friend, or a comment online, the words people choose quietly reveal deeper patterns in how they think, feel, and relate to others.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone has personality traits – habitual ways of thinking, feeling and behaving. When these patterns become rigid, intense or disruptive, they can cause ongoing problems with emotions, sense of self and relationships. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the more severe end are personality disorders, where these patterns create significant distress and impairment. Common &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/people-with-personality-disorders-are-more-likely-to-sign-up-for-psychology-studies-heres-why-thats-a-problem-201237"&gt;personality disorders&lt;/a&gt; include narcissistic, antisocial, and borderline personality disorder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But not everybody has a full-blown disorder. Personality functioning actually exists on a spectrum. &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/why-are-we-becoming-so-narcissistic-heres-the-science-55773"&gt;We’re all a little narcissistic&lt;/a&gt;, after all. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many people you meet – at work, when dating, or online – may show milder difficulties, such as mood fluctuations, negativity, rigid thinking or darker traits like manipulation and callousness. These patterns often &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1146/annurev.psych.54.101601.145041"&gt;slip into how people speak&lt;/a&gt; or write long before they show up in more explicit behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are some extreme examples. Linguists &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3390/forensicsci3010006"&gt;analysing the personal letters of Austrian serial killer Jack Unterweger&lt;/a&gt; – widely viewed as a classic case of malignant narcissism – found unusually high levels of self-focused language, such as “I” and “me”. He also had a notably flat emotional tone. Likewise, letters from Dennis Rader, the BTK killer (bind, torture, kill) displayed strikingly &lt;a href="https://press.uchicago.edu/ucp/books/book/distributed/C/bo44312033.html"&gt;grandiose, detached and dominance-focused wording.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Psychologists have long known that certain linguistic habits reveal how people are functioning internally. For example, people experiencing distress consistently use more &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jrp.2017.02.005"&gt;self-focused language&lt;/a&gt; and more &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.chb.2018.05.035"&gt;negative emotion words&lt;/a&gt;. That’s because they internalise a lot and experience negative affect. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those with darker personality traits often use more &lt;a href="https://dl.acm.org/doi/10.1145/2983323.2983822"&gt;hostile, negative and disconnected language&lt;/a&gt;, including more swear words and anger words, such as “hate” or “mad”. At the same time, they use fewer socially connected terms like “we”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vitally, these patterns aren’t usually deliberate. They emerge naturally because &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1177/0261927X09351676"&gt;language tracks attention, emotion and thought&lt;/a&gt;. With computational text analysis, researchers can now analyse these subtle cues at scale, and rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Our research findings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Across four studies using computational text analysis – three of which formed my &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.17635/lancaster/thesis/2215"&gt;PhD research&lt;/a&gt; – my colleagues and I found clear evidence that personality dysfunction leaves a detectable trace in everyday communication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In one study of 530 people, published in the &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1521/pedi.2023.37.4.444"&gt;Journal of Personality Disorders&lt;/a&gt;, we analysed written essays about peoples’ close relationships. We also collected data on their levels of personality dysfunction. Those with greater personality dysfunction used language that carried a sense of urgency and self-focus – “I need…”, “I have to…”, “I am…”. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was expressed alongside ruminative, past-tense wording. They also had more negative, particularly angry, emotion terms, such as “furious” and “annoyed”. At the same time, they used noticeably less intimate or affiliative language such as “we”, “love” and “family”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a second project, published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1016/j.jadr.2023.100647"&gt;Journal of Affective Disorders Reports&lt;/a&gt;, we again analysed written essays (530 people), as well as transcribed conversations from 64 romantic couples which included women with diagnosed personality disorders.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Across both written and spoken communication, those with more dysfunctional or disordered personalities used more negative emotion words – and a wider variety of them. Even during mundane conversations, their language carried heavier negative affect, indicating a preoccupation with negative feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Turning to online communication, in a study recently published in &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s44184-025-00142-w"&gt;npj Mental Health Research&lt;/a&gt;, we analysed nearly 67,000 Reddit posts from 992 people who self-identified as having a personality disorder. Those who frequently engaged in self-harm used language that was markedly more negative and constricted. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their posts contained more self-focused language and more negations – such as “can’t”. They also used more sadness and anger terms, and more swearing, while referencing other people less. Their wording was also more absolutist, reflecting all-or-nothing thinking, favouring words like “always”, “never”, or “completely”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class="align-center zoomable"&gt;
            &lt;a href="https://images.theconversation.com/files/707834/original/file-20251210-64-6jtq4l.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;q=45&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=1000&amp;amp;fit=clip"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
            &lt;figcaption&gt;
              &lt;span class="caption"&gt;Look out for anger and swearing.&lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;span class="attribution"&gt;&lt;a class="source" href="https://www.shutterstock.com/image-photo/angry-furious-businesswoman-working-on-computer-325331660?trackingId=%7B%22app%22%3A%7B%22module%22%3A%22image-search-results%22%2C%22name%22%3A%22next-web%22%2C%22page%22%3A%22ecomm%22%7D%2C%22providers%22%3A%5B%7B%7D%5D%2C%22svc%22%3A%22recommendation-api%22%2C%22strategy%22%3A%7B%22name%22%3A%22INTENT%22%2C%22version%22%3A%221.0%22%7D%2C%22uuid%22%3A%22571603c8-1ddf-405c-aa49-422d54d50e20%22%7D"&gt;pathdoc/Shutterstock&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
            &lt;/figcaption&gt;
          &lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Together, these features created a linguistic picture of emotional overwhelm, negativity, withdrawal and rigid thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, in an ongoing project analysing more than 830,000 posts from the same 992 individuals with personality disorder, plus 1.3 million posts from a general-population comparison group of 945 people, we examined how people express their self-beliefs (“I am …”, “I feel …”, “My …”). Using an &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.18653/v1/2025.acl-long.69"&gt;advanced self-belief classification tool&lt;/a&gt;, we found that people with personality disorders shared self-beliefs on online discussion forums far more often, and their wording differed profoundly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Their self-beliefs were more negative, extreme, and disorder-focused, including phrases like “my mental health”, “symptoms”, “diagnosis” and “medication”. They also used more emotional descriptors such as “depressive”, “suicidal” and “panic”. Many self-belief statements centred on pain and trauma – “abusive”, “abandonment”, “hurt”, “suffer”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They also frequently referenced childhood or significant relationships (“mother”, “partner”, “relationship”). These patterns arose across a wide range of discussion contexts, suggesting that deeper struggles with identity may surface in language universally.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Why this matters&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understanding these linguistic patterns isn’t about diagnosing people from their texts. It is about noticing shifts in language that can provide gentle clues. If someone’s messages suddenly become unusually urgent or extreme, emotionally negative, absolutist, inward-focused and socially detached, it may be a sign they’re struggling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And in everyday situations – dating, befriending, online interactions – recognising patterns of hostility, extreme negativity, and emotional and cognitive rigidity can help people spot early red flags. This is particularly for dark personality styles, such as psychopathy or narcissism. For instance, noticeably high use of self-references (“I”, “me”), anger words (“hate”, “angry”), and swear words, combined with a lack of terminology indicative of social connection (“we”, “us”, “our”), may be important language patterns to look out for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But no single word or phrase reveals someone’s personality. People vent, joke, and use sarcasm. What really matters is the pattern over time; the emotional tone, themes and recurring linguistic habits. Subtle linguistic traces can offer a window into someone’s emotional world, identity, thinking patterns and relationships long before they speak openly about their difficulties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Noticing these patterns can help us learn about and understand others, support those who may be struggling, and navigate our social lives safely – online and offline – with greater awareness.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;

        

        
    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Conversation</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 11:01:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwgFBVV95cUxNVkdlbGZPTjVSQUEyU1V2THN1ZndKbUxfX29RRFd4SDFJYkhkRk9uYnhteWVMaHFFeFJuSm9UZUpNT3lHc0JPLXJrUGtWeXNEdDBYOVZKeHZ2bDhxbEg0b0pYZk52bzR0QVgyV3FwbHo1QmcyS2tpMUp0d0VvempqMjNnZndUZWowOFZkb2JaM0laak9zTS1nZDR4TEVhYXFwYUNpMVJ1UlI2bk8tMlBmRW1BWWs5bjczN1ZiTXhjN2lGUQ</guid></item><item><title>新的病毒“开关”可能有助于对抗抗生素耐药性-耶路撒冷邮报</title><link>https://www.jpost.com/science/article-880658</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Jerusalem Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 10:29:31 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiV0FVX3lxTE82ZXRNdHBxY2lLc0VLbG11bmwyRmhrcHRsdVNmZUhpUVFGWUMwM2dsZndkOXJPSjQtV2VlMG9saXZpLVVvMEhkNTRwdWFNZlJkRk52SDRTQQ</guid></item><item><title>南泽西小学的胃肠道疾病爆发使孩子们生病- WHYY</title><link>https://whyy.org/articles/central-elementary-school-haddonfield-new-jersey-norovirus/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="flexible-content-container wysiwyg-styles"&gt;
                                                                                                                                                                                                                        &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From Philly and the Pa. suburbs to South Jersey and Delaware, what would you like WHYY News to cover? &lt;a href="#Section1"&gt;Let us know!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent outbreak of gastrointestinal illness at a South Jersey school has public health experts urging people to take precautions this winter and ahead of the holidays to avoid additional infections.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Camden County officials did not confirm the name of the school, but the outbreak is taking place at Central Elementary School in Haddonfield, according to a CBS &lt;a href="https://central.haddonfieldschools.org/"&gt;report&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exact number of affected students is unknown, but county officials say the school has reported an “unusual increase” in children with nausea, vomiting and other symptoms since Dec. 10.
  &lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;The scope of the outbreak grew Friday when the school reported an uptick in illnesses to the county’s Department of Health and Human Services.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Gastrointestinal illnesses can be highly contagious, so it is essential that families are aware of the signs and symptoms,” Virginia Betteridge, the department’s commissioner liaison, said in a statement.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Symptoms of &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/7040-gastrointestinal-diseases"&gt;gastrointestinal illness&lt;/a&gt; can also include diarrhea, stomach cramps, fever and fatigue. While most people can manage it and recover at home, others including young children, seniors and those with weakened immune symptoms are at risk of dehydration and other complications.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gastrointestinal illnesses are typically caused by bacteria, parasites or viruses like &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/17703-norovirus"&gt;norovirus&lt;/a&gt;, which can survive on high-touch surfaces like doorhandles, keyboards, phones and countertops for days or &lt;a href="https://health.clevelandclinic.org/how-long-do-norovirus-germs-live-on-household-and-office-surfaces"&gt;even weeks&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The risk of outbreaks in the winter and during holidays&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cases and outbreaks are more common in the winter as people spend more time indoors and in settings like schools, long-term care facilities and daycares, said Caryelle Lasher, director of the county’s Department of Health and Human Services.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Infections caused by norovirus usually spread when people come into contact with fecal matter and then ingest microscopic particles on their hands, on cups or utensils, or in food.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“And that can happen from people not washing their hands well or it can be spread through things contaminated by vomit,” she said. “That’s where we see these really quick spreading, intense outbreaks because it takes so little to make people sick.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Schools are especially susceptible for outbreaks, Lasher said, “with young children who may not know to do a really thorough frequent hand washing after the use of the bathroom or before eating or preparing food.”
        &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WHYY</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 10:18:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOcEtwYnBvc3RRN2pDY1JmYUVFTnlqLTFrMVlqS0hSMnR2aGVhQVEyRFJVNUJ6Uzc0dndsbkd2U28xOHFDMXNxR0phYk5lalRlYzRsTWNncFdFVkVvQ1g4Ty1tUERoc3RTVzlVRk00cWJyMndjb3YxRllQR2oxVk9rYWY2RW8wcG9hYW83ZGVR</guid></item><item><title>在非洲丛林中与致命疾病作斗争的摩托车手- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/future/article/20251217-the-motorcyclist-fighting-the-worlds-second-deadliest-parasite-in-the-african-bush</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="sc-85f9acf9-0 kfxpiP"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Now, she worries about her own children's health. She is in her twenties but unsure of her exact age. People in this part of the world tend to mark the passage of time by rains, rather than calendar years. Either way, she looks older than she really is. In Pokot culture, women bear all the essential burdens of life, from birthing children and fetching water to building houses and cooking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="sc-bc40c3a0-0 kXcvpr"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 jJmNMc"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/160xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 160w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/240xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 240w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/320xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 320w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 480w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/640xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 640w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/800xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 800w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1024xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 1024w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1376xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 1376w, https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/1920xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp 1920w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/images/ic/480xn/p0mp4f4c.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Kang-Chun Cheng Ochieng uses a rapid antigen test to help him diagnose people with visceral leishmanaisis (Credit: Kang-Chun Cheng)" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Kang-Chun Cheng&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Ochieng uses a rapid antigen test to help him diagnose people with visceral leishmanaisis (Credit: Kang-Chun Cheng)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Ochieng finds that, thankfully, her four young children all appear to be free of the disease. But the risk of visceral leishmaniasis, and poor health exacerbated by poverty, is constant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Selina's family eats just once a day, in the morning: tea, &lt;i id="ugali" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;ugali&lt;/i&gt; (boiled maize meal), and sokoria leaves, which she plucks from a tree. Selina boils them, pounds into a mash and then fries the mixture. "What we can find is what we eat," she says, her toddler clinging to her side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She still remembers the painful injections she received all those years ago. But, to her, that made them more effective than any other kind of medication. It is a common belief here, according to Sagaki – that pain is the best way to deal with disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixAFBVV95cUxOQndlSDJTVGNDckNnS3FkdVpiWWlTc0NYbWNRcHA3ZXI4S3BqNG94U2NJdmtfZWVxeUY0X1FtUGhIaGlVNFlXWWRuSHllcXY1UDRPWUl3bFRnU3dfc0xCY2hGR1hqOU1lNFFOYmUtZkVFUXV4M2p5dWx3UXZ3allrVnlQcXkyTUxpT3pxLU1aczJNaDNjV0lyTkUwMjI0cG42QXhVNkJkTUlwNTBQZ2JqTFVyZng3T20xbk9GMVlLeXZhbmY2</guid></item><item><title>Tracy Leigh Mitchell ， 60岁- Coeur d 'Alene Press</title><link>https://cdapress.com/news/2025/dec/18/tracy-leigh-mitchell-50/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-body font-weight-normal fr-view" id="storycontent"&gt;
	
		
		

			

			
	                        &lt;p&gt;Tracy Leigh Scott Mitchell, a devoted mother, grandmother, sister and friend, passed away Dec. 8, 2025. She will be deeply missed by her loving family and all who knew her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tracy is survived by her children, Shantel Mitchell and Misty Howard; her siblings, Crystal Hill, Janette Jerauld, Denice Duncan and Sheldon Scott; and her beloved grandchildren.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tracy was a kind and caring person who loved her family with all her heart. She will be especially remembered for her warmth, generosity and unwavering support. Her children and grandchildren were the light of her life, and her absence will be deeply felt by all who knew and loved her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tracy is preceded in death by her mother, Annabelle Scott, and her sister, Lenice Kuykendall, with whom she will now rest in eternal peace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A memorial service will be held at a later date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In lieu of flowers, donations may be made to help her children with cremation expenses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Family and friends are invited to sign Tracy’s online guest book at www.coffeltfuneral.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arrangements are entrusted to Coffelt Funeral Services of Sandpoint, Idaho.&lt;/p&gt;
			        	
				
			
		
	

&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Coeur d'Alene Press</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 09:04:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMib0FVX3lxTFAwOWlSLUdiTXRCSU8zNmhYR1ZhV1plWXNQaGI2RmNWcktpQ3B3ZjdjN1JHY0toRl9JTzdIUG54NllBUmN0LUxFZGNuMVZpYnRlWjc2VzlYejlKWUdCY3YzMFA3Rm52ejBQUmJaZGNMcw</guid></item><item><title>大麻化合物有望抵御最致命的癌症之一--SciTechDaily</title><link>https://scitechdaily.com/cannabis-compounds-show-promise-against-one-of-the-deadliest-cancers/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 04:03:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxPbHNGeVZyd2VldGxkX09mREJkYkJnZGZhRWY1RkNtUTNwVFduazVwbVh1TzliazdOb3VpME51aTdTLUtFT0x3S09ldFlGZXZNT0c0YzRtTWFMbHB6NVd3N0dfTUowQnBfX1VFQ0hZSDBzTzdUdkRHbjAyZXBjNXZ0Z21yVlZqMHh0YnNOcnNtUXZWZUNRY082NENR</guid></item><item><title>布朗大学卫生部在呼吸道病毒上升的情况下颁布口罩要求- WJAR</title><link>https://turnto10.com/news/local/brown-university-health-enacts-mask-mandate-rise-respiratory-viruses-transmission-patient-care-visitors-december-17-2025</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="TeaserLink_teaserText__g1DQc"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expert: Sharing unofficial AI-generated images could confuse, hinder Brown investigation&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="TeaserLink_galleryIcon__W3OjR"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="TeaserLink_videoIcon__vD91T"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="TeaserLink_teaserSummary__nulFo"&gt;Experts say creating and sharing photos that are generated by AI is an incredibly dangerous game to play and not helpful to the investigation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WJAR</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 03:25:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi5wFBVV95cUxNMURBbGt5Vk5WaXpZRzlER0ZEWjJzUV9fam1MaVY5a3EyeXJvYVJJdldBR2pCMVhueFlPYTJ2eldYd0NDVGZPTzNHaDNPdXpsTE5hQThXSnlaY0J1YkxuZnR0REFOUDJ3SkZsTExubWV6TEhyMllUdEFBczhiUkhrRDhHVEozLTJxRVM1ZXo0WDdKZ2ZFZUpnOGpJM0o3REQ5QXRqMmV6M3J2akg1eXpTSHpZT1RpY0VmWkRJRGkxTW44NzJQMzduUkNTZ2FJZ1haOURDeDFFNXZtV1p6c3ZMRjJldVFhRm8</guid></item><item><title>官员说，一名麻疹患者在弗吉尼亚州和北卡罗来纳州旅行-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/dc-md-va/2025/12/17/measles-virginia-north-carolina-exposure/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OGZXH3UO65GT7LPFB4A4SGQTLY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A person with measles recently traveled through a North Carolina airport and to south and central Virginia in early December while they were contagious, public health officials said Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YURLOBFNTZCBPBXRX3URBHQIB4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The person visited a Home Depot in South Hill, Virginia, on Dec. 5, a cafe in Kenbridge on Dec. 6 as well as the Lynchburg Livestock Market and a nearby McDonald’s in Rustburg on Dec. 8, according to the Virginia health department, which is warning people of potential exposures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 02:09:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNMkJsZVNIQTd3X21qLXNXWjlyRmtXbzJjcnN3LXFhS0Ixa0dxRXdlanNfay1RWkJIUEZ3Vjg2cWlKdFhBd3d1blByT2p5eWxoRGtxZ2J1MVJfOFJobGZRa0Y2T09jWTNJNEdpQ2tsYnRaelZ0d1p0ZzhFUzhfZlFMQXVlRWQ2WjV2R2lBMFoxWE5MOVAwVjdZ</guid></item><item><title>果汁净化，禁食不起作用：专家揭示了实际上排毒肝脏和肠道的5个习惯-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/juice-cleanses-fasting-dont-work-expert-reveals-5-habits-that-actually-detox-your-liver-and-gut/articleshow/126048474.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;In today’s wellness landscape, buzzwords like “detox”, “cleanse” and “liver flush” are everywhere but often divorced from biological reality. Health experts assert that true detoxification is not about gimmicks or extreme cleanses, it is about lifestyle habits that support the body’s innate cleansing systems, particularly the liver and gut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="2"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While pop health culture oversimplifies detox, decades of medical research show that specific lifestyle factors like diet composition, physical activity, microbiome balance, control of metabolic disease and personalised genomic insights play crucial roles in maintaining healthy liver and gut function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="lOvcW vdo_embedd"&gt;&lt;div class="k7lcu"&gt;&lt;p class="efT4r"&gt;Five Effective Ways to Detoxify Your Gut Health&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="6"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an interview with the Times of India, Dr Sajeev Nair, Founder and Chairman of Vieroots, shared, “Detox and detox diets have become widely misused terms in pop health circles. In this context, it would be enlightening to look at how real detox with regard to liver and gut, that are research-validated, like elimination of ‘toxins’ and adoption of healthy lifestyles through genomic lifestyle management, can help.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are 5 such most important means to pursue real detox of these vital organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="15"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Dietary detox: Reining in harmful exposures&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="16"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While food is not a “toxin” in the strict chemical sense, diet can act as a major source of metabolic stress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excess sugars, refined carbohydrates and saturated fats, as well as alcohol, challenge liver function and disrupt gut health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="20"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Nair warned, “The primary ‘toxic’ substances for your gut and liver are macronutrients like carbs and fats that are taken in excess. The only exception here is alcohol, which is toxic by its very nature. Among excessive carbs and fats, two require special mention - sugars and foods that raise triglycerides like meat, butter, fries, refined carbs etc. These raise the risks for liver diseases like fatty liver and gut issues like dysbiosis and pancreatitis. Avoiding such foods is the most essential gut and liver detox.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Think Detox Means Cleanses? Expert Says This Is What Real Liver Detox Looks Like​" msid="126048662" width="" title="Think Detox Means Cleanses? Expert Says This Is What Real Liver Detox Looks Like" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-126048662/think-detox-means-cleanses-expert-says-this-is-what-real-liver-detox-looks-like.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Think Detox Means Cleanses? Expert Says This Is What Real Liver Detox Looks Like&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="28"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.journal-of-hepatology.eu/article/S0168-8278(20)30119-6/fulltext" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2020 study published in Journal of Hepatology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, researchers found that diets high in added sugars and saturated fats are strongly associated with the development of non-alcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD), a condition in which excess fat accumulates in the liver and impairs its ability to detoxify and metabolise. Sugary beverages, processed meats and refined grains are all common in modern Western eating patterns and exacerbate fat deposition and inflammation in the liver. Avoiding these foods is not a fad, it is metabolic self-defence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="36"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Fitness detox: Moving beyond the gym session&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="37"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exercise is not just about building muscle or hitting a step count. Physical activity, particularly habitual movement throughout the day, reduces metabolic stress on both the gut and liver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Nair suggested, “Next only to dietary factors, the most essential gut and liver detox is physical fitness. By this I don’t just mean once-daily exercise sessions, muscle building or metrics like VO2 Max but following an active lifestyle throughout your waking hours. This is because a sedentary lifestyle is toxic to the gut, causing issues like slower digestion, constipation, bloating, gas, IBS, ulcers etc. and to the liver, by causing non alcoholic fatty liver disease (NAFLD), cirrhosis, metabolic dysfunction etc.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="44"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/30809066/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2019 meta-analysis in Journal of Gastroenterology and Hepatology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; reviewed multiple cohorts and found that regular physical activity, even modest increases in daily movement, was associated with lower odds of NAFLD, independent of weight loss. The authors noted, “Greater physical activity was significantly associated with reduced odds of non-alcoholic fatty liver disease, regardless of body mass index.” Movement stimulates blood flow, enhances insulin sensitivity and reduces visceral fat, which are key drivers of both liver and gut dysfunction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="50"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Microbiome detox: Balancing gut bacteria for systemic benefits&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="51"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gut microbiome or the trillions of bacteria living in your digestive tract plays a central role in digestion, immune modulation and even the “gut-liver axis”, a two-way communication network between gut microbes and liver cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="53"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Nair said, “Many of you might have heard about the gut microbiome - the beneficial, benign and harmful mix of microbes in our gut and how it contributes to not only gut health but overall health including psychological health. Prebiotics and probiotics optimise the microbiome and its metabolites like SCFAs, helping the liver through the Gut Liver Axis, protecting against common liver diseases like alcoholic and non-alcoholic fatty liver and by helping in liver repair and regeneration.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="58"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="From Diet to DNA: The Surprising Science Behind ‘Real Detox’ Doctors Want You to Know" msid="126048674" width="" title="From Diet to DNA: The Surprising Science Behind ‘Real Detox’ Doctors Want You to Know " placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-126048674/from-diet-to-dna-the-surprising-science-behind-real-detox-doctors-want-you-to-know.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;From Diet to DNA: The Surprising Science Behind ‘Real Detox’ Doctors Want You to Know &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell-metabolism/fulltext/S1550-4131(21)00287-X" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2021 Cell Metabolism review article&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, researchers explained how microbial metabolites such as short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs) help reduce inflammation and support liver health, while gut dysbiosis (imbalance of bacteria) can promote liver disease. They established, “Microbiota-derived metabolites have profound effects on host metabolic pathways, immune function, and liver homeostasis, implicating gut dysbiosis in the pathogenesis of liver disease.” Prebiotics (fibre that feeds good bacteria) and probiotics (beneficial bacterial strains) can help restore balance and promote metabolites that protect both gut and liver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="68"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Disease detox: Addressing the underlying drivers &lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="70"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gut and liver dysfunction rarely occur in isolation. Conditions like obesity, diabetes, hypertension, hyperlipidaemia and metabolic syndrome all share common inflammatory and metabolic roots with liver and gut disease. Controlling these conditions is a form of real detox by reducing systemic stressors that otherwise overwhelm the body’s organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="74"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Nair said, “This is one of the most commonly overlooked detoxes required by both your gut and your liver. Common gut and liver issues don’t occur in isolation but are often found along with lifestyle diseases like diabetes, obesity, hypertension, hyperlipidaemia, metabolic syndrome etc. Examples are diabetes linked fatty liver, gastroparesis, acid reflux, constipation, diarrhoea etc. Hence, it is essential to ideally prevent or at least control such lifestyle diseases.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="79"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4812181/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2016 comprehensive review in World Journal of Gastroenterology &lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;confirmed that features of metabolic syndrome including high blood sugar, increased waist circumference and abnormal lipid profiles are consistently linked with fatty liver and gut impairment. The study found, “Metabolic syndrome significantly increases the risk of non-alcoholic fatty liver disease and related complications.” Effective management of blood glucose, lipids and weight is therefore a cornerstone of preventing liver and gut diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="85"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="86"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Genomic lifestyle detox: Personalised risk management&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="87"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emerging research reveals that genetic predisposition plays a meaningful role in many gut and liver disorders. For instance, conditions like Irritable Bowel Syndrome (IBS) and NAFLD have heritable components, meaning why one person gets sick and another doesn’t may partly stem from genetic susceptibility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="90"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;div data-pos="0" class="id-r-component QbQNS undefined  
        "&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;img alt="Detox Is a Lie? Doctors Explain How Your Liver and Gut Really Eliminate Toxins" msid="126048687" width="" title="Detox Is a Lie? Doctors Explain How Your Liver and Gut Really Eliminate Toxins" placeholdersrc="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" imgsize="23456" resizemode="4" offsetvertical="0" placeholdermsid="" type="thumb" src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/83033472.cms" class="" data-src="https://static.toiimg.com/photo/imgsize-23456,msid-126048687/detox-is-a-lie-doctors-explain-how-your-liver-and-gut-really-eliminate-toxins.jpg" data-api-prerender="true"&gt;&lt;p class="q3gJl"&gt;Detox Is a Lie? Doctors Explain How Your Liver and Gut Really Eliminate Toxins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="93"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;While genomic lifestyles have yet to enter mainstream clinical practice, early evidence suggests that identifying genetic risks and tailoring lifestyle changes accordingly can provide a proactive strategy for prevention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="95"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Nair said, “Until now, I have discussed the various lifestyle related factors that can act like toxins on your gut and liver. An even deeper and significant ‘toxin’ is your genetic susceptibility for developing gut and liver issues. For instance a common gut issue like IBS and a common liver issue like NAFLD both have nearly 60% genetic components. A genomic lifestyle management solution like Eplimo can detect risks for these gut and liver issues years or decades before they actually develop and help prevent them by personalised lifestyle changes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="100"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://aasldpubs.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/hep.29367" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="_blank" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;2018 study published in Hepatology journal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, one of the strongest genetic associations with NAFLD involves variants in the PNPLA3 gene, which influences fat storage in liver cells. Individuals with certain variants are more likely to accumulate liver fat even with modest risk exposure. It revealed, “Variations in the PNPLA3 gene are strongly associated with susceptibility to non-alcoholic fatty liver disease and its severity.” Identifying such genetic risk factors allows for earlier lifestyle intervention, which is a true form of precision detox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="106"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="107"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Bottom line&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="108"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many commercial detox diets promise to “clear toxins” in a matter of days, often through extreme restriction or supplementation but the evidence shows that the liver and gut already have powerful physiological detox systems:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="110"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="111"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The liver metabolises and eliminates endogenous and exogenous compounds through phases of biochemical transformation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The gut prevents harmful microbes from entering systemic circulation and contributes to metabolic regulation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="112"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The real goal is not quick fixes but lifestyle habits that reduce chronic metabolic stressors and support these innate systems over a lifetime. Actionable takeaways backed by science include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="114"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="115"&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Limit added sugars, refined carbs and excess saturated fats —&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Research links these to fatty liver, metabolic dysfunction and gut disturbances.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stay physically active throughout the day — &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;Even modest movement improves liver metabolism and gut motility.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Support your microbiome with fibre-rich foods and fermented foods &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;that promote SCFA production.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage metabolic conditions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; such as obesity and diabetes to lower risk for liver and gut diseases.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Consider genomic lifestyle assessment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; if you have a family history of IBS, NAFLD, or other digestive/metabolic disorders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="116"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Detox” will not ever be a one-week juice cleanse or a trendy reset package. True detox is about reducing lifetime exposure to metabolic stressors, strengthening the body’s own detoxification pathways and using science-based strategies to keep the gut and liver functioning optimally. As research continues, integrating diet, movement, microbiome support, chronic disease management and personalised genomic insights promises the most effective, enduring path to real biological detoxification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="121"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note: The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult with a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment and before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 01:57:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMioAJBVV95cUxOMi1LNEY3X3M2T05Ud0hJXzltamhVRjBkTWlqUHBMMjJmc3QwbXFhQmZiY2F3RWE5d3JCRV9DU2RNaktoZDJweTVUQ2hXdkJXMjl3VGg4YXRKTWtnRlk5SE5xY2I2VmpuaUpIN2VFWWx3UUNiTUd3QXRQQ2xuUWpLbU15YjBSWkRXTDdJa2JfdGVQWlFqRkl3dWV2N18taG9IU2IybG1pdzVvaXZxdU9yQWVkR0dNMGFxMnZ2NmNublhIYk0zYU9PUkRGblhucFZnVmFKV1JBSHdodldzX3FuVXQ3R2tWM2ZCUGQ3RER5UjNEYWx5YVNhZmtkUjFpRXRyTVB3cEh6M25jRy11aXg0cjRFbTc2M3ZGRTRncGdibzbSAaYCQVVfeXFMTTZ4Y2tzc0JBQ0NkSnBaal9ibDIxNF9zb09nY01wcFhvREZaNFdKN1VJeEpySHVPeXFiOGZzTTN2TDBMNWQtYWczdGZkRXZybjNKNVBLeC15dWo2dUlXUHNsWU1JV1FFVGd0RG5CUk1hZ3hxcEQxVnpjTEhKWWctTUR5dXRlY2xhTGJxTkx1WXJxRHZRSDYzbE1iWDJMN3JQTFdkdGY1NUZVRFJNcGNtYmZCTGU5TDRnMEljUlVOMEVFalYtczJ1SWRMakwyUUZMQm1Zd0dfY0dpd1dubXlrcDJiSzB5YmFCaDJRQUxWT0poeHgwUjJGTnY0d3NVcFVjTEJnQXp0X242T2FrYXhIYzZDYjEycm14OGtndG1VQnl4TTRkdXZR</guid></item><item><title>根据医学专家的说法，这些是最适合老年人的雪铲- AOL.com</title><link>https://www.aol.com/shopping/home/article/best-snow-shovels-for-seniors-150319260.html</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;We had the first snowfall of the year in New England this week. It was just a few inches of powdery fluff, but forecasts are predicting that it will be a &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:1;pos:1" href="https://www.accuweather.com/en/winter-weather/us-winter-forecast-2025-26-snow-cold-ahead/1817344" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:cold and snowy winter;cpos:1;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;cold and snowy winter&lt;/a&gt; in many areas of the country. If you haven't already stocked up on ice melt, warm gloves, and snow shovels, now is the time to do so!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think it's safe to say no one really &lt;em&gt;enjoys&lt;/em&gt; shoveling snow, but it can be an especially challenging task for older adults. Thousands of people &lt;a data-i13n="elm:affiliate_link;sellerN:USA TODAY;elmt:;cpos:2;pos:1" href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=14bcaa59-fd9f-4864-a7d9-a27d287727bc&amp;amp;siteId=us-aol&amp;amp;pageId=1p-autolink&amp;amp;contentUuid=29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685&amp;amp;featureId=text-link&amp;amp;merchantName=USA+TODAY&amp;amp;linkText=get+hurt+shoveling+snow&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsImxhbmRpbmdVcmwiOiJodHRwczovL3d3dy51c2F0b2RheS5jb20vc3RvcnkvbGlmZS9oZWFsdGgtd2VsbG5lc3MvMjAyNS8xMi8wMi9zbm93LXNob3ZlbGluZy1ibG93aW5nLWhvdy1vbGQtaXMtdG9vLW9sZC84NzU2NzAxMzAwNy8iLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6IjI5Njk0NDA3LWI2YTktNDA0NC04MjZhLTRlYTlkZjUzODY4NSIsIm9yaWdpbmFsVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cudXNhdG9kYXkuY29tL3N0b3J5L2xpZmUvaGVhbHRoLXdlbGxuZXNzLzIwMjUvMTIvMDIvc25vdy1zaG92ZWxpbmctYmxvd2luZy1ob3ctb2xkLWlzLXRvby1vbGQvODc1NjcwMTMwMDcvIn0&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAc5bL5yJsGrHe_qP-EHvHOwSsmFTggJ6Zy_gR08bQ7sR&amp;amp;gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.usatoday.com%2Fstory%2Flife%2Fhealth-wellness%2F2025%2F12%2F02%2Fsnow-shoveling-blowing-how-old-is-too-old%2F87567013007%2F&amp;amp;spaceId=1197803369" class="link rapid-noclick-resp rapid-with-clickid etailiffa-link" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:get hurt shoveling snow;elm:affiliate_link;sellerN:USA TODAY;elmt:;cpos:2;pos:1;itc:0;sec:content-canvas"&gt;get hurt shoveling snow&lt;/a&gt; each year, and the combination of cold weather and vigorous activity can be dangerous for seniors, according to the &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:3;pos:1" href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/consumer-healthcare/what-is-cardiovascular-disease/cold-weather-and-cardiovascular-disease" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Heart Association;cpos:3;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt;. Shoveling can lead to falls, pulled muscles, and strains, as well as more serious conditions like hypothermia, angina pectoris, or even a heart attack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To minimize your risk of injury while shoveling, it's essential to have the right equipment before heading out to clean your sidewalks. That means grippy, well-fitting boots, warm gloves, and the right snow shovel. There are hundreds of shovel options out there today, so to help you find the best option, we spoke with several experts, including a board-certified interventional spine and sports medicine physician, an experienced chiropractor, and even a landscaping professional. They offered tips on find the best shovel for seniors, including several product recommendations that will work well for all ages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="commerce-rmp"&gt;&lt;div id="ebdd6aea161b4cb9bcf63f23d9d741b0"&gt;&lt;div class="commerce productModule [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:mt-9 [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:border-t [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:border-dirty-seagull [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:pt-2 [&amp;amp;+:not(.productModule)]:mt-10 col-body" id="product-module-ebdd6aea161b4cb9bcf63f23d9d741b0"&gt;&lt;div class="mt-6 text-batcave @container/p dark:text-grey-hair"&gt;&lt;div class="block"&gt;&lt;div class="relative mb-4 w-full overflow-hidden rounded-lg border border-grey-hair pb-[75%] @xl/p:pb-[56.25%]"&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="aid:amazon_B01LXEQ6UM;cpos:1;itmId:$40;ll3:product-available;ll4:productoffer-auto;pid:amazon_B01LXEQ6UM;pdid:Snow Joe Snow Shovel with 18-Inch Blade and Assist Handle;subsec:commlist;elmt:amazon;itemcost:$40;sellerN:Amazon;sec:large-product;elm:affiliate_link;itc:0;slk:$40 at Amazon;pkgt:horizontal-img;pos:1;" class="rapid-with-clickid group absolute size-full" href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&amp;amp;itemId=amazon_B01LXEQ6UM&amp;amp;siteId=us-aol&amp;amp;pageId=pnr-product-module&amp;amp;providerId=amazon&amp;amp;contentUuid=29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685&amp;amp;featureId=dynamic-offer&amp;amp;itemName=Snow+Joe+Snow+Shovel+with+18-Inch+Blade+and+Assist+Handle&amp;amp;merchantName=Amazon&amp;amp;itemSourceId=B01LXEQ6UM&amp;amp;brand=Snow+Joe&amp;amp;categoryId=5364&amp;amp;price=39.97&amp;amp;salePrice=39.97&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMDFMWEVRNlVNP3RhZz1hb2wwMTIzLTIwJmxpbmtDb2RlPW9naSZ0aD0xJnBzYz0xIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiIyOTY5NDQwNy1iNmE5LTQwNDQtODI2YS00ZWE5ZGY1Mzg2ODUiLCJvcmlnaW5hbFVybCI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFtYXpvbi5jb20vZHAvQjAxTFhFUTZVTT90YWc9eWxlMDEtMjAmbGlua0NvZGU9b2dpJnRoPTEmcHNjPTEiLCJkeW5hbWljQ2VudHJhbFRyYWNraW5nSWQiOnRydWUsInNpdGVJZCI6InVzLWFvbCIsInBhZ2VJZCI6InBuci1wcm9kdWN0LW1vZHVsZSIsImZlYXR1cmVJZCI6ImR5bmFtaWMtb2ZmZXIifQ&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAWM6S57VX654kSf_WD_q2yMGb03YB686kcWXbfYUOzu6&amp;amp;spaceId=1197803369" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" aria-label="Image for the large product module" data-aps-asin="B01LXEQ6UM" data-aps-asc-tag="aol0123-p-v-7vq-20"&gt;&lt;img alt="Image for the large product module" class="mx-auto my-0 size-full bg-white object-contain @xl/p:transition-transform @xl/p:duration-300 @xl/p:ease-in-out @xl/p:group-hover:scale-110 @xl/p:motion-reduce:group-hover:transition-none" src="https://s.yimg.com/uu/api/res/1.2/Ul__55RqPIsqgSw6A0N3Bg--~B/Zmk9c3RyaW07aD03MjA7dz0xMjgwO2FwcGlkPXl0YWNoeW9u/https://media-mbst-pub-ue1.s3.amazonaws.com/creatr-uploaded-images/2025-12/a3d3fb10-da9b-11f0-8fde-585dc5710e8c" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="absolute -right-0.5 bottom-0 rounded-bl-none rounded-br-lg rounded-tl-lg rounded-tr-none bg-white/90 px-3 py-2 text-[10px]/3 text-battleship"&gt;Snow Joe&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="commerce-desc mb-5 mt-2 space-y-6 text-base/relaxed md:text-lg/8 [&amp;amp;_li]:ml-4 [&amp;amp;_ol&amp;gt;li]:list-decimal [&amp;amp;_ol]:space-y-6 [&amp;amp;_ul&amp;gt;li]:list-disc [&amp;amp;_ul]:space-y-6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blade length:&lt;/strong&gt; 18 inches | &lt;strong&gt;Weight:&lt;/strong&gt; 3.7 pounds | &lt;strong&gt;Blade material:&lt;/strong&gt; Polycarbonate | &lt;strong&gt;Handle material: &lt;/strong&gt;Aluminum&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you're looking for a traditional shovel, experts recommend an ergonomic product with a dual-handle design. "For seniors, my shovel recommendation would preferably have a flick feature," says &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:1;pos:1;sec:large-product;subsec:commlist;pkgt:square-editorial;pos:9;cpos:1" href="https://www.discmdgroup.com/physicians/vivek-babaria-do/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Vivek Babaria;cpos:1;pos:1;sec:large-product;subsec:commlist;pkgt:square-editorial;pos:9;cpos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Vivek Babaria&lt;/a&gt;, board-certified and fellowship-trained interventional spine and sports medicine physician. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This particular model from Snow Joe has a secondary spring-assisted handle in front that acts as a fulcrum, enhancing the mechanics of shoveling while reducing stress on your back and arms. The whole shovel is lightweight, weighing less than 4 pounds, and it has a smaller blade that ensures you're not trying to pick up more than you can safely toss. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="aid:amazon_B01LXEQ6UM;cpos:1;itmId:$40;ll3:product-available;ll4:productoffer-auto;pid:amazon_B01LXEQ6UM;pdid:Snow Joe Snow Shovel with 18-Inch Blade and Assist Handle;subsec:commlist;elmt:amazon;itemcost:$40;sellerN:Amazon;pos:4;sec:large-product;elm:affiliate_link;itc:0;pkgt:horizontal-cta-1;slk:$40 at Amazon;" class="peer clear-right box-border block w-full min-w-60 rounded-[40px] px-7 text-center hover:no-underline hover:opacity-100 active:opacity-60 @xl/p:w-9/12 rapid-with-clickid commerce-cta-btn-primary bg-article-ui-button py-3 font-semibold leading-5 text-article-ui-button-label hover:bg-article-ui-button-hover hover:text-grey-hair active:bg-article-ui-button-hover active:text-grey-hair peer-[&amp;amp;]:mt-3 dark:bg-white dark:text-batcave dark:hover:bg-bob dark:focus:bg-bob dark:active:bg-bob" href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&amp;amp;itemId=amazon_B01LXEQ6UM&amp;amp;siteId=us-aol&amp;amp;pageId=pnr-product-module&amp;amp;providerId=amazon&amp;amp;contentUuid=29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685&amp;amp;featureId=dynamic-offer&amp;amp;itemName=Snow+Joe+Snow+Shovel+with+18-Inch+Blade+and+Assist+Handle&amp;amp;merchantName=Amazon&amp;amp;itemSourceId=B01LXEQ6UM&amp;amp;brand=Snow+Joe&amp;amp;categoryId=5364&amp;amp;price=39.97&amp;amp;salePrice=39.97&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMDFMWEVRNlVNP3RhZz1hb2wwMTIzLTIwJmxpbmtDb2RlPW9naSZ0aD0xJnBzYz0xIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiIyOTY5NDQwNy1iNmE5LTQwNDQtODI2YS00ZWE5ZGY1Mzg2ODUiLCJvcmlnaW5hbFVybCI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFtYXpvbi5jb20vZHAvQjAxTFhFUTZVTT90YWc9eWxlMDEtMjAmbGlua0NvZGU9b2dpJnRoPTEmcHNjPTEiLCJkeW5hbWljQ2VudHJhbFRyYWNraW5nSWQiOnRydWUsInNpdGVJZCI6InVzLWFvbCIsInBhZ2VJZCI6InBuci1wcm9kdWN0LW1vZHVsZSIsImZlYXR1cmVJZCI6ImR5bmFtaWMtb2ZmZXIifQ&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAWM6S57VX654kSf_WD_q2yMGb03YB686kcWXbfYUOzu6&amp;amp;spaceId=1197803369" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" data-aps-asin="B01LXEQ6UM" data-aps-asc-tag="aol0123-p-v-7vq-20"&gt;$40 at Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="commerce-rmp"&gt;&lt;div id="d08815c036db41029c297bf2d8f80b5b"&gt;&lt;div class="commerce productModule [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:mt-9 [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:border-t [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:border-dirty-seagull [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:pt-2 [&amp;amp;+:not(.productModule)]:mt-10 col-body" id="product-module-d08815c036db41029c297bf2d8f80b5b"&gt;&lt;div class="mt-6 text-batcave @container/p dark:text-grey-hair"&gt;&lt;div class="block"&gt;&lt;div class="relative mb-4 w-full overflow-hidden rounded-lg border border-grey-hair pb-[75%] @xl/p:pb-[56.25%]"&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="aid:amazon_B0FRNRKRGL;cpos:2;itmId:$120;ll3:product-available;ll4:productoffer-auto;pid:amazon_B0FRNRKRGL;pdid:Best Choice Products 36in Heavy-Duty 2-Wheel Snow Pusher;subsec:commlist;elmt:amazon;itemcost:$130;sellerN:Amazon;sec:large-product;elm:affiliate_link;itc:0;slk:$120 at Amazon;pkgt:horizontal-img;pos:1;" class="rapid-with-clickid group absolute size-full" href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&amp;amp;itemId=amazon_B0FRNRKRGL&amp;amp;siteId=us-aol&amp;amp;pageId=pnr-product-module&amp;amp;providerId=amazon&amp;amp;contentUuid=29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685&amp;amp;featureId=dynamic-offer&amp;amp;itemName=Best+Choice+Products+36in+Heavy-Duty+2-Wheel+Snow+Pusher&amp;amp;merchantName=Amazon&amp;amp;itemSourceId=B0FRNRKRGL&amp;amp;brand=Best+Choice+Products&amp;amp;categoryId=5362&amp;amp;price=129.99&amp;amp;salePrice=119.99&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMEZSTlJLUkdMP3RhZz1hb2wwMTIzLTIwJmxpbmtDb2RlPW9naSZ0aD0xJnBzYz0xIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiIyOTY5NDQwNy1iNmE5LTQwNDQtODI2YS00ZWE5ZGY1Mzg2ODUiLCJvcmlnaW5hbFVybCI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFtYXpvbi5jb20vZHAvQjBGUk5SS1JHTD90YWc9eWxlMDEtMjAmbGlua0NvZGU9b2dpJnRoPTEmcHNjPTEiLCJkeW5hbWljQ2VudHJhbFRyYWNraW5nSWQiOnRydWUsInNpdGVJZCI6InVzLWFvbCIsInBhZ2VJZCI6InBuci1wcm9kdWN0LW1vZHVsZSIsImZlYXR1cmVJZCI6ImR5bmFtaWMtb2ZmZXIifQ&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAd3WWbly0_YVl9miBJ5TXjKz-u77GtaZ4mamc0vWr7bh&amp;amp;spaceId=1197803369" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" aria-label="Image for the large product module" data-aps-asin="B0FRNRKRGL" data-aps-asc-tag="aol0123-p-v-7vq-20"&gt;&lt;img alt="Image for the large product module" class="mx-auto my-0 size-full bg-white object-contain @xl/p:transition-transform @xl/p:duration-300 @xl/p:ease-in-out @xl/p:group-hover:scale-110 @xl/p:motion-reduce:group-hover:transition-none" src="https://s.yimg.com/uu/api/res/1.2/JZ5Fz9eCFXCcMdgbV9YWIA--~B/Zmk9c3RyaW07aD03MjA7dz0xMjgwO2FwcGlkPXl0YWNoeW9u/https://media-mbst-pub-ue1.s3.amazonaws.com/creatr-uploaded-images/2025-12/cc3dbeb0-da9b-11f0-bfb4-2d9c00ae55e4" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="absolute -right-0.5 bottom-0 rounded-bl-none rounded-br-lg rounded-tl-lg rounded-tr-none bg-white/90 px-3 py-2 text-[10px]/3 text-battleship"&gt;Best Choice Products&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="commerce-desc mb-5 mt-2 space-y-6 text-base/relaxed md:text-lg/8 [&amp;amp;_li]:ml-4 [&amp;amp;_ol&amp;gt;li]:list-decimal [&amp;amp;_ol]:space-y-6 [&amp;amp;_ul&amp;gt;li]:list-disc [&amp;amp;_ul]:space-y-6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blade length:&lt;/strong&gt; 36 inches | &lt;strong&gt;Weight:&lt;/strong&gt; 25.5 pounds | &lt;strong&gt;Blade material:&lt;/strong&gt; Galvanized steel | &lt;strong&gt;Handle material: &lt;/strong&gt;Metal&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you have a large area to shovel — such as a long sidewalk or your driveway — a traditional shovel may not be the most efficient option. Instead, experts recommend looking for a snow pusher: "The shovels now that can push/glide instead of having to physically lift are preferred," says Dr. Babaria. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This heavy-duty snow pusher is a top choice for clearing large areas. It features a wide 36-inch blade that can be angled in either direction and is mounted on large pneumatic tires that facilitate smooth pushing. Additionally, you can adjust the height and angle of the handle, so you can a position that's comfortable for your physique. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="aid:amazon_B0FRNRKRGL;cpos:2;itmId:$120;ll3:product-available;ll4:productoffer-auto;pid:amazon_B0FRNRKRGL;pdid:Best Choice Products 36in Heavy-Duty 2-Wheel Snow Pusher;subsec:commlist;elmt:amazon;itemcost:$130;sellerN:Amazon;pos:4;sec:large-product;elm:affiliate_link;itc:0;pkgt:horizontal-cta-1;slk:$120 at Amazon;" class="peer clear-right box-border block w-full min-w-60 rounded-[40px] px-7 text-center hover:no-underline hover:opacity-100 active:opacity-60 @xl/p:w-9/12 rapid-with-clickid commerce-cta-btn-primary bg-article-ui-button py-3 font-semibold leading-5 text-article-ui-button-label hover:bg-article-ui-button-hover hover:text-grey-hair active:bg-article-ui-button-hover active:text-grey-hair peer-[&amp;amp;]:mt-3 dark:bg-white dark:text-batcave dark:hover:bg-bob dark:focus:bg-bob dark:active:bg-bob" href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&amp;amp;itemId=amazon_B0FRNRKRGL&amp;amp;siteId=us-aol&amp;amp;pageId=pnr-product-module&amp;amp;providerId=amazon&amp;amp;contentUuid=29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685&amp;amp;featureId=dynamic-offer&amp;amp;itemName=Best+Choice+Products+36in+Heavy-Duty+2-Wheel+Snow+Pusher&amp;amp;merchantName=Amazon&amp;amp;itemSourceId=B0FRNRKRGL&amp;amp;brand=Best+Choice+Products&amp;amp;categoryId=5362&amp;amp;price=129.99&amp;amp;salePrice=119.99&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMEZSTlJLUkdMP3RhZz1hb2wwMTIzLTIwJmxpbmtDb2RlPW9naSZ0aD0xJnBzYz0xIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiIyOTY5NDQwNy1iNmE5LTQwNDQtODI2YS00ZWE5ZGY1Mzg2ODUiLCJvcmlnaW5hbFVybCI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFtYXpvbi5jb20vZHAvQjBGUk5SS1JHTD90YWc9eWxlMDEtMjAmbGlua0NvZGU9b2dpJnRoPTEmcHNjPTEiLCJkeW5hbWljQ2VudHJhbFRyYWNraW5nSWQiOnRydWUsInNpdGVJZCI6InVzLWFvbCIsInBhZ2VJZCI6InBuci1wcm9kdWN0LW1vZHVsZSIsImZlYXR1cmVJZCI6ImR5bmFtaWMtb2ZmZXIifQ&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAd3WWbly0_YVl9miBJ5TXjKz-u77GtaZ4mamc0vWr7bh&amp;amp;spaceId=1197803369" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" data-aps-asin="B0FRNRKRGL" data-aps-asc-tag="aol0123-p-v-7vq-20"&gt;$120 at Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="commerce-rmp"&gt;&lt;div id="2cfd45195c19411485592f16493101df"&gt;&lt;div class="commerce productModule [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:mt-9 [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:border-t [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:border-dirty-seagull [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:pt-2 [&amp;amp;+:not(.productModule)]:mt-10 col-body" id="product-module-2cfd45195c19411485592f16493101df"&gt;&lt;div class="mt-6 text-batcave @container/p dark:text-grey-hair"&gt;&lt;div class="block"&gt;&lt;div class="relative mb-4 w-full overflow-hidden rounded-lg border border-grey-hair pb-[75%] @xl/p:pb-[56.25%]"&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="aid:amazon_B073V482GX;cpos:3;itmId:$230;ll3:product-available;ll4:productoffer-auto;pid:amazon_B073V482GX;pdid:Earthwise 40-Volt Cordless Electric Snow Shovel;subsec:commlist;elmt:amazon;itemcost:$255;sellerN:Amazon;sec:large-product;elm:affiliate_link;itc:0;slk:$230 at Amazon;pkgt:horizontal-img;pos:1;" class="rapid-with-clickid group absolute size-full" href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&amp;amp;itemId=amazon_B073V482GX&amp;amp;siteId=us-aol&amp;amp;pageId=pnr-product-module&amp;amp;providerId=amazon&amp;amp;contentUuid=29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685&amp;amp;featureId=dynamic-offer&amp;amp;itemName=Earthwise+40-Volt+Cordless+Electric+Snow+Shovel&amp;amp;merchantName=Amazon&amp;amp;itemSourceId=B073V482GX&amp;amp;brand=Earthwise&amp;amp;categoryId=5364&amp;amp;price=254.69&amp;amp;salePrice=229.99&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMDczVjQ4MkdYP3RhZz1hb2wwMTIzLTIwJmxpbmtDb2RlPW9naSZ0aD0xJnBzYz0xIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiIyOTY5NDQwNy1iNmE5LTQwNDQtODI2YS00ZWE5ZGY1Mzg2ODUiLCJvcmlnaW5hbFVybCI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFtYXpvbi5jb20vZHAvQjA3M1Y0ODJHWD90YWc9eWxlMDEtMjAmbGlua0NvZGU9b2dpJnRoPTEmcHNjPTEiLCJkeW5hbWljQ2VudHJhbFRyYWNraW5nSWQiOnRydWUsInNpdGVJZCI6InVzLWFvbCIsInBhZ2VJZCI6InBuci1wcm9kdWN0LW1vZHVsZSIsImZlYXR1cmVJZCI6ImR5bmFtaWMtb2ZmZXIifQ&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAaUYymQGp0Ux0Feyw0BBb6bexFIqQmcAFPzf-xFFkexK&amp;amp;spaceId=1197803369" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" aria-label="Image for the large product module" data-aps-asin="B073V482GX" data-aps-asc-tag="aol0123-p-v-7vq-20"&gt;&lt;img alt="Image for the large product module" class="mx-auto my-0 size-full bg-white object-contain @xl/p:transition-transform @xl/p:duration-300 @xl/p:ease-in-out @xl/p:group-hover:scale-110 @xl/p:motion-reduce:group-hover:transition-none" src="https://s.yimg.com/uu/api/res/1.2/9osSHmVnMrHOvwqEhEtwpw--~B/Zmk9c3RyaW07aD03MjA7dz0xMjgwO2FwcGlkPXl0YWNoeW9u/https://media-mbst-pub-ue1.s3.amazonaws.com/creatr-uploaded-images/2025-12/f4a845a0-da9b-11f0-8e37-6f1b91508fb7" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="absolute -right-0.5 bottom-0 rounded-bl-none rounded-br-lg rounded-tl-lg rounded-tr-none bg-white/90 px-3 py-2 text-[10px]/3 text-battleship"&gt;Earthwise&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="commerce-desc mb-5 mt-2 space-y-6 text-base/relaxed md:text-lg/8 [&amp;amp;_li]:ml-4 [&amp;amp;_ol&amp;gt;li]:list-decimal [&amp;amp;_ol]:space-y-6 [&amp;amp;_ul&amp;gt;li]:list-disc [&amp;amp;_ul]:space-y-6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clearing width:&lt;/strong&gt; 16 inches | &lt;strong&gt;Max snow depth:&lt;/strong&gt; 8 inches | &lt;strong&gt;Throwing distance:&lt;/strong&gt; 32 feet | &lt;strong&gt;Weight:&lt;/strong&gt; 19 pounds &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you're willing to spend a little more, you may want to consider an electric snow shovel: "These are similar in size and style to regular shovels, yet they function more like snow throwers," says Steve Corcoran, CEO of landscaping company &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:1;pos:1;sec:large-product;subsec:commlist;pkgt:square-editorial;pos:9;cpos:3" href="https://lawnlove.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lawn Love.;cpos:1;pos:1;sec:large-product;subsec:commlist;pkgt:square-editorial;pos:9;cpos:3;elm:context_link;itc:0" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Lawn Love.&lt;/a&gt; "You push them still, but they send snow outward. So, they are a lot less physically demanding, since you aren’t actually manually shoveling in the same way."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This model from Earthwise is able to handle snow up to 8 inches deep, and it's mounted on wheels for easy pushing. It has a cordless design and adjustable front handle for better grip, and it can easily throw snow up to 30 feet. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="aid:amazon_B073V482GX;cpos:3;itmId:$230;ll3:product-available;ll4:productoffer-auto;pid:amazon_B073V482GX;pdid:Earthwise 40-Volt Cordless Electric Snow Shovel;subsec:commlist;elmt:amazon;itemcost:$255;sellerN:Amazon;pos:4;sec:large-product;elm:affiliate_link;itc:0;pkgt:horizontal-cta-1;slk:$230 at Amazon;" class="peer clear-right box-border block w-full min-w-60 rounded-[40px] px-7 text-center hover:no-underline hover:opacity-100 active:opacity-60 @xl/p:w-9/12 rapid-with-clickid commerce-cta-btn-primary bg-article-ui-button py-3 font-semibold leading-5 text-article-ui-button-label hover:bg-article-ui-button-hover hover:text-grey-hair active:bg-article-ui-button-hover active:text-grey-hair peer-[&amp;amp;]:mt-3 dark:bg-white dark:text-batcave dark:hover:bg-bob dark:focus:bg-bob dark:active:bg-bob" href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=66ea567a-c987-4c2e-a2ff-02904efde6ea&amp;amp;itemId=amazon_B073V482GX&amp;amp;siteId=us-aol&amp;amp;pageId=pnr-product-module&amp;amp;providerId=amazon&amp;amp;contentUuid=29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685&amp;amp;featureId=dynamic-offer&amp;amp;itemName=Earthwise+40-Volt+Cordless+Electric+Snow+Shovel&amp;amp;merchantName=Amazon&amp;amp;itemSourceId=B073V482GX&amp;amp;brand=Earthwise&amp;amp;categoryId=5364&amp;amp;price=254.69&amp;amp;salePrice=229.99&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsInN0b3JlSWQiOiI2NmVhNTY3YS1jOTg3LTRjMmUtYTJmZi0wMjkwNGVmZGU2ZWEiLCJsYW5kaW5nVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuYW1hem9uLmNvbS9kcC9CMDczVjQ4MkdYP3RhZz1hb2wwMTIzLTIwJmxpbmtDb2RlPW9naSZ0aD0xJnBzYz0xIiwiY29udGVudFV1aWQiOiIyOTY5NDQwNy1iNmE5LTQwNDQtODI2YS00ZWE5ZGY1Mzg2ODUiLCJvcmlnaW5hbFVybCI6Imh0dHBzOi8vd3d3LmFtYXpvbi5jb20vZHAvQjA3M1Y0ODJHWD90YWc9eWxlMDEtMjAmbGlua0NvZGU9b2dpJnRoPTEmcHNjPTEiLCJkeW5hbWljQ2VudHJhbFRyYWNraW5nSWQiOnRydWUsInNpdGVJZCI6InVzLWFvbCIsInBhZ2VJZCI6InBuci1wcm9kdWN0LW1vZHVsZSIsImZlYXR1cmVJZCI6ImR5bmFtaWMtb2ZmZXIifQ&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAaUYymQGp0Ux0Feyw0BBb6bexFIqQmcAFPzf-xFFkexK&amp;amp;spaceId=1197803369" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" data-aps-asin="B073V482GX" data-aps-asc-tag="aol0123-p-v-7vq-20"&gt;$230 at Amazon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="commerce-rmp"&gt;&lt;div id="4b4ba86894534cf89fe241dd41c303cc"&gt;&lt;div class="commerce productModule [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:mt-9 [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:border-t [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:border-dirty-seagull [&amp;amp;+.productModule]:pt-2 [&amp;amp;+:not(.productModule)]:mt-10 col-body" id="product-module-4b4ba86894534cf89fe241dd41c303cc"&gt;&lt;div class="mt-6 text-batcave @container/p dark:text-grey-hair"&gt;&lt;div class="block"&gt;&lt;div class="relative mb-4 w-full overflow-hidden rounded-lg border border-grey-hair pb-[75%] @xl/p:pb-[56.25%]"&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="aid:manual_29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685_1765905047130;cpos:4;itmId:$1,649;ll3:product-available;ll4:productoffer-manual;pid:manual_29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685_1765905047130;pdid:EGO POWER+ 24-in Two-stage Self-propelled Battery Snow Blower;subsec:commlist;elmt:chooseForMe;itemcost:$1,649;sellerN:Lowe's;sec:large-product;elm:affiliate_link;itc:0;slk:$1,649 at Lowe's;pkgt:horizontal-img;pos:1;" class="rapid-with-clickid group absolute size-full" href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=ba84e34b-21a4-4d54-b349-5490609c35f4&amp;amp;siteId=us-aol&amp;amp;pageId=pnr-product-module&amp;amp;contentUuid=29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685&amp;amp;featureId=manual-entry&amp;amp;itemName=EGO+POWER%2B+24-in+Two-stage+Self-propelled+Battery+Snow+Blower&amp;amp;merchantName=Lowe%27s&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsImxhbmRpbmdVcmwiOiJodHRwczovL3d3dy5sb3dlcy5jb20vcGQvRUdPLTI0SU4tMi1TVEFHRS1TTk9XLVRIUk9XRVItS0lULzEwMDMxMzA3MjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6IjI5Njk0NDA3LWI2YTktNDA0NC04MjZhLTRlYTlkZjUzODY4NSIsIm9yaWdpbmFsVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cubG93ZXMuY29tL3BkL0VHTy0yNElOLTItU1RBR0UtU05PVy1USFJPV0VSLUtJVC8xMDAzMTMwNzIwIn0&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAf8uPcpUW483E_t3MWJBM7YAHnFg3Qp9QtaD8A3lrSDv&amp;amp;gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lowes.com%2Fpd%2FEGO-24IN-2-STAGE-SNOW-THROWER-KIT%2F1003130720&amp;amp;spaceId=1197803369" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank" aria-label="Image for the large product module"&gt;&lt;img alt="Image for the large product module" class="mx-auto my-0 size-full bg-white object-contain @xl/p:transition-transform @xl/p:duration-300 @xl/p:ease-in-out @xl/p:group-hover:scale-110 @xl/p:motion-reduce:group-hover:transition-none" src="https://s.yimg.com/uu/api/res/1.2/3H5MV1PpXBpWUsfMacImog--~B/Zmk9c3RyaW07aD03MjA7dz0xMjgwO2FwcGlkPXl0YWNoeW9u/https://s.yimg.com/os/creatr-uploaded-images/2025-12/1f8b5ef0-daa2-11f0-8ff3-affbc1d93acd" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p class="absolute -right-0.5 bottom-0 rounded-bl-none rounded-br-lg rounded-tl-lg rounded-tr-none bg-white/90 px-3 py-2 text-[10px]/3 text-battleship"&gt;Lowes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="commerce-desc mb-5 mt-2 space-y-6 text-base/relaxed md:text-lg/8 [&amp;amp;_li]:ml-4 [&amp;amp;_ol&amp;gt;li]:list-decimal [&amp;amp;_ol]:space-y-6 [&amp;amp;_ul&amp;gt;li]:list-disc [&amp;amp;_ul]:space-y-6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clearing width:&lt;/strong&gt; 24 inches | &lt;strong&gt;Max snow depth:&lt;/strong&gt; 20 inches | &lt;strong&gt;Throwing distance:&lt;/strong&gt; 50 feet | &lt;strong&gt;Weight:&lt;/strong&gt; 150 pounds&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For seniors who live in an area that gets a lot of snow each year, it's worth upgrading to a snow blower to effortlessly clear your sidewalks and driveways. My 65-year-old father purchased this EGO POWER+ model around two years ago, and he raves about it every winter. Its self-propelled design moves forward automatically, and it's able to easily clear snow up to 20 inches deep. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This two-stage snow blower runs on dual 56-volt batteries, so there's no need to mess around with gas in the cold weather. It's easy to adjust how far it throws snow, as well as the chute angle, and it even has bright LED headlights for visibility during storms. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;a data-ylk="aid:manual_29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685_1765905047130;cpos:4;itmId:$1,649;ll3:product-available;ll4:productoffer-manual;pid:manual_29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685_1765905047130;pdid:EGO POWER+ 24-in Two-stage Self-propelled Battery Snow Blower;subsec:commlist;elmt:chooseForMe;itemcost:$1,649;sellerN:Lowe's;pos:4;sec:large-product;elm:affiliate_link;itc:0;pkgt:horizontal-cta-1;slk:$1,649 at Lowe's;" class="peer clear-right box-border block w-full min-w-60 rounded-[40px] px-7 text-center hover:no-underline hover:opacity-100 active:opacity-60 @xl/p:w-9/12 rapid-with-clickid commerce-cta-btn-primary bg-article-ui-button py-3 font-semibold leading-5 text-article-ui-button-label hover:bg-article-ui-button-hover hover:text-grey-hair active:bg-article-ui-button-hover active:text-grey-hair peer-[&amp;amp;]:mt-3 dark:bg-white dark:text-batcave dark:hover:bg-bob dark:focus:bg-bob dark:active:bg-bob" href="https://shopping.yahoo.com/rdlw?merchantId=ba84e34b-21a4-4d54-b349-5490609c35f4&amp;amp;siteId=us-aol&amp;amp;pageId=pnr-product-module&amp;amp;contentUuid=29694407-b6a9-4044-826a-4ea9df538685&amp;amp;featureId=manual-entry&amp;amp;itemName=EGO+POWER%2B+24-in+Two-stage+Self-propelled+Battery+Snow+Blower&amp;amp;merchantName=Lowe%27s&amp;amp;custData=eyJzb3VyY2VOYW1lIjoiV2ViLURlc2t0b3AtVmVyaXpvbiIsImxhbmRpbmdVcmwiOiJodHRwczovL3d3dy5sb3dlcy5jb20vcGQvRUdPLTI0SU4tMi1TVEFHRS1TTk9XLVRIUk9XRVItS0lULzEwMDMxMzA3MjAiLCJjb250ZW50VXVpZCI6IjI5Njk0NDA3LWI2YTktNDA0NC04MjZhLTRlYTlkZjUzODY4NSIsIm9yaWdpbmFsVXJsIjoiaHR0cHM6Ly93d3cubG93ZXMuY29tL3BkL0VHTy0yNElOLTItU1RBR0UtU05PVy1USFJPV0VSLUtJVC8xMDAzMTMwNzIwIn0&amp;amp;signature=AQAAAf8uPcpUW483E_t3MWJBM7YAHnFg3Qp9QtaD8A3lrSDv&amp;amp;gcReferrer=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.lowes.com%2Fpd%2FEGO-24IN-2-STAGE-SNOW-THROWER-KIT%2F1003130720&amp;amp;spaceId=1197803369" rel="noopener nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;$1,649 at Lowe's&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 class="caas-jump-link-heading" id="tips-for-safely-shoveling-snow"&gt;Tips for safely shoveling snow&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having the right tools alone isn't enough to keep you safe while shoveling. It's also important to use proper technique and pace yourself while out in the cold winter weather.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here are a few snow shoveling safety tips for seniors:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Warm up beforehand:&lt;/strong&gt; "A good stretch before you begin is essential to avoid injury. Head, neck, back, shoulders and hips should all be warmed up prior to shoveling," says Dr. Babaria. You may also want to walk in place for a few minutes to warm up your body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alternate sides when tossing:&lt;/strong&gt; "If lifting and throwing, seniors should alternate sides and distance they are going to throw," he explains. "Use proper bending techniques to avoid throwing out your back." Remember: Lift with your knees, not your back!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Invest in proper winter gear:&lt;/strong&gt; "Choose good footwear too — having a solid base to avoid slipping can ensure your foundation helps you push, pull, and throw," recommends chiropractor &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:4;pos:1" href="https://www.drlhands.com/meet-dr-lief-hands/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Lief Hands;cpos:4;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Lief Hands&lt;/a&gt;. If you need new winter footwear, we've rounded up the &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:5;pos:1" href="https://www.aol.com/shopping/style/article/best-winter-boots-165756559.html" data-ylk="slk:best snow boots;cpos:5;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;best snow boots&lt;/a&gt; for men and women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don't pick up large scoops:&lt;/strong&gt; "The smaller [shovel] blade is actually safer — it suppresses how much snow you can heave at once, preserving the low back and shoulders," says Dr. Hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take breaks as needed: &lt;/strong&gt;"I tell patients this all the time: Stop if you feel short of breath or your back starts to ache. Warning signs can be hard to see past the cold weather," says Dr. Hands. The snow isn't going anywhere, so take a break and come back later if needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ask for help:&lt;/strong&gt; If there's a lot of snow or you're not feeling well, there are many resources available to help with snow removal. Check with your local town government — many cities have shoveling assistance programs to help keep seniors safe during the winter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2 class="caas-jump-link-heading" id="our-experts"&gt;Our experts&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-i13n="cpos:6;pos:1" href="https://www.discmdgroup.com/physicians/vivek-babaria-do/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Vivek Babaria;cpos:6;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Vivek Babaria&lt;/a&gt; is a board-certified and fellowship-trained interventional spine and sports medicine physician. He has substantial experience in interventional spine care and sports and regenerative medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a data-i13n="cpos:7;pos:1" href="https://www.drlhands.com/meet-dr-lief-hands/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Lief Hands;cpos:7;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Lief Hands&lt;/a&gt; is a a Doctor of Chiropractic at Precise Chiropractic &amp;amp; Rehabilitation. He's worked in the medical field for more than 20 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steve Corcoran is the CEO of landscaping company &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:8;pos:1" href="https://lawnlove.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Lawn Love;cpos:8;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Lawn Love&lt;/a&gt;, which offers snow removal services in several states around the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prices were accurate at the time of publication. Curious about how we test and choose products at AOL? Here’s &lt;a data-i13n="cpos:9;pos:1" href="https://www.aol.com/lifestyle/how-we-review-products-and-deals-at-aol-shopping-202047873.html" data-ylk="slk:a quick explanation;cpos:9;pos:1;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;a quick explanation&lt;/a&gt;, from our editors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 01:33:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNYWZkaE9XemtNT2NvclhxU2pxMkxCQzlwY3k5OTVfb1VQYWQtLU1VSmh0cDYwYjVDUDhnMTVEWGV1akVUUldzOUZXSmx2SGE1c2c4Q2kzYlhxMW5TdWFoVlBVX0pUTVBhN09ya042dDB1Y0tfenc0bHRQMnVaM3J5TEx0NDBXNnp4WmN0NG1yWQ</guid></item><item><title>吃得干净，锻炼，但仍然没有减肥？美国文档揭示了真正的罪魁祸首-如何找到-印度时报</title><link>https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/life-style/health-fitness/health-news/not-losing-weight-american-doc-reveals-the-real-culprit-insulin-resistance/articleshow/126042269.cms</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="_s30J clearfix  "&gt;&lt;div class="MwN2O"&gt;&lt;div class="vdo_embedd"&gt; &lt;div class="T22zO"&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="0"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;You switched to a clean, nutritious, and well-balanced diet, made regular exercise a non-negotiable ritual, and yet the scale will not budge? Guess what? There is a solid reason why your weight is stuck. In a video shared on Instagram, Dr Johnny Hadac, a Family Medicine and Lifestyle Medicine doctor trained at Lake Erie College of Osteopathic Medicine, revealed the root cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="4"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This is for anyone who is struggling to lose weight, no matter how many calories you count, no matter how much you move your body, you just feel like you cannot lose weight no matter what. You're probably dealing with something very common, and it actually affects 40% of the United States population," the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="8"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="9"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Why do you struggle with losing weight?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="10"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are doing everything right and yet the weight is stuck, the reason could be a common condition called insulin resistance, Dr Hadac said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="12"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="13"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What is insulin resistance?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="14"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insulin is a key hormone that regulates your blood sugar levels. According to Diabetes UK, insulin resistance occurs when your &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.diabetes.org.uk/about-diabetes/looking-after-diabetes/treatments/insulin/resistance" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;body’s cells do not respond properly to insulin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;. So, instead of keeping your blood sugar levels stable and within a healthy range, your blood sugar levels can rise. Insulin resistance can increase your risk of type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="19"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the United States, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK507839/" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;insulin resistance affects about 40% of adults&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; aged 18 to 44, according to an analysis of NHANES data from 2021, based on HOMA-IR measurements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="23"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="24"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Carbohydrates and insulin resistance&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="25"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Hadac, one of the main drivers of insulin resistance is eating too many carbohydrates. "Every time you eat carbohydrates, your blood sugar will spike, also driving an insulin spike. The average American eats about 250 to 300 grams of carbohydrates a day," the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="27"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="29"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;ID@undefined &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Caption not available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="35"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;ID@undefined &lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Caption not available.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="40"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is far more than what the body needs. "And this is why I teach my patients so much about macronutrients. You see, carbohydrates and protein have the same amount of calories per gram. It's four."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="42"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, if you eat more protein, you will not feel as hungry. "But if you ate 300 grams of protein a day, you would not ever leave the couch because of how full you are. The difference between carbs and protein is that protein naturally raises GLP levels, makes you feel fuller for longer, and helps you reduce your cravings and that food noise," the doctor said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="45"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="cdatainfo modify_cdata_list_style id-r-component " data-pos="46"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What you can do&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="47"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of loading up on carbohydrates, Dr Hadac suggested focusing on getting adequate protein in each meal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="49"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Get protein in every meal:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; "So one of the easiest things you can start focusing on is getting more protein in your diet. Aiming for three meals a day, with 40 to 50 grams of protein in each of those meals," the doctor said. A 2024 study published in the journal Obesity Science &amp;amp; Practice found that people who consumed &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/osp4.764" rel="noopener nofollow noreferrer" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" target="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;greater amounts of protein and fibre&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; had the greatest success at losing weight over 25 months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="55"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Start fasting:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Dr Hadac said one can also try fasting. "If you wake up, put creamer in your coffee, then have a dessert right before bed, and you eat all day long, you're going to constantly have blood sugar spikes and insulin spikes. So fasting can help reduce those insulin levels and help you with meal consistency and timing," he said. The doctor suggested fasting for 14 hours, from 7 p.m. to 9 a.m. "During fasting hours, stick to water, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/topic/black-coffee" styleobj="[object Object]" class="" commonstate="[object Object]" frmappuse="1"&gt;black coffee&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, or green tea. If you are a menstruating woman, fast only during your follicular phase, not your luteal phase."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="61"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Move more: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;The doctor also recommended prioritising movement. "The more muscle mass you have in your body, the better your metabolism will run because it's an active organ. The more you move your body, the more blood sugar your muscles will actually use for energy, reducing those blood sugar levels. So if you're dealing with insulin resistance, increase your protein, reduce your carbs, start fasting, and move your body. It's the easiest thing ever, and you will have great results in 30 days," he said. The doctor suggested moving for at least 30 minutes a day, doing weight training, or trying walking, biking, or any other form of consistent movement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="67"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over time, these changes can help you lose weight. While these steps may help, it is important to understand that your body is different, and it is best to seek professional help that can be tailored to your specific needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="69"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="strong em" data-ua-type="1"&gt;Note:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="em" data-ua-type="1"&gt; The information provided in this article is for educational purposes only and is not intended as medical advice. Always consult a qualified healthcare professional before starting any new medication or treatment, or before changing your diet or supplement regimen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="72"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="id-r-component br" data-pos="73"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 01:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAJBVV95cUxOam5uSmZ6bW1TZi1ZNzlQQmoyUnNPX2xwU09UNGp6UjB3eGdyOGNfR0VYSUliYnFfVTdPN1oyNlpvODVHa1pIM3pOSEpaM3ZQU3V5MnNINUJmbGFsV2VCTTB2WndpT2JVTlRZaEdJemtMX08zekpjYWtrSlhZYk1tUmFpLW8zM1NHb1NuSmVZbXJfSzFwY3dMUE0tZnpvQUJ1MkhwZ0ZTaElFaGRMeU5CVHNLajNxUzJBMXdUY1RRRTh6dTZidy1FZkVRT2d5YWNVNzFFeks3ZXQyc0EweEVBd2ZRZFd6VDVHV0pTbC1ENWhrVHBTc3dFY210WVFwdWs0eGsxNg</guid></item><item><title>想要更年轻、更健康的大脑吗？这种类型的锻炼可以有所帮助。-安克雷奇每日新闻</title><link>https://www.adn.com/alaska-life/advice/2025/12/17/want-a-younger-healthier-brain-this-type-of-exercise-can-help/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="adn-article-body default  teads_enabled"&gt;&lt;figure class="c-media-item"&gt;&lt;img data-chromatic="ignore" alt="" class="c-image" loading="lazy" src="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/FNGPRWFLBBHRZBT6XO4KVDN4LU.jpg?auth=6235516fe07d9db123c421b1cd0f01fa24f8f965c9ff724a933a23eb5b6ed941&amp;amp;width=800&amp;amp;height=533" srcset="https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/FNGPRWFLBBHRZBT6XO4KVDN4LU.jpg?auth=6235516fe07d9db123c421b1cd0f01fa24f8f965c9ff724a933a23eb5b6ed941&amp;amp;width=274&amp;amp;height=182 274w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/FNGPRWFLBBHRZBT6XO4KVDN4LU.jpg?auth=6235516fe07d9db123c421b1cd0f01fa24f8f965c9ff724a933a23eb5b6ed941&amp;amp;width=400&amp;amp;height=266 400w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/FNGPRWFLBBHRZBT6XO4KVDN4LU.jpg?auth=6235516fe07d9db123c421b1cd0f01fa24f8f965c9ff724a933a23eb5b6ed941&amp;amp;width=768&amp;amp;height=511 768w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/FNGPRWFLBBHRZBT6XO4KVDN4LU.jpg?auth=6235516fe07d9db123c421b1cd0f01fa24f8f965c9ff724a933a23eb5b6ed941&amp;amp;width=1024&amp;amp;height=682 1024w, https://www.adn.com/resizer/v2/FNGPRWFLBBHRZBT6XO4KVDN4LU.jpg?auth=6235516fe07d9db123c421b1cd0f01fa24f8f965c9ff724a933a23eb5b6ed941&amp;amp;width=1440&amp;amp;height=959 1440w"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="c-media-item__fig-caption"&gt;&lt;span class="c-media-item__caption"&gt;(iStock / Getty Images) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;If you need another reason to visit the gym this winter, a new study of almost 1,200 healthy, middle-aged men and women found that those with more muscle mass tended to have younger brains than those with less muscle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The findings, which were presented in Chicago this month at the annual meeting of the Radiological Society of North America, add to growing evidence that building and maintaining muscle mass as we age could be key to building and maintaining brain health, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The researchers also found that those with high levels of deep belly fat had older brains, raising&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;questions about the potentially negative effects of some types of body fat on the brain and how important it may be to combine weight training with weight loss, if we would like our brains to stay youthful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;- - -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Why exercise is good for brains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The idea that exercise is good for our brains is hardly new. Past studies in rodents have shown that after exercise, the animals’ brains teem with a neurochemical called brain-derived neurotrophic factor, or BDNF. Sometimes referred to as “Miracle-Gro for the brain,” BDNF helps spark the creation of new neurons. So it’s not surprising that after exercise, mouse and rat brains typically sprout two or three times as many new brain cells as the brains of sedentary animals. The exercising animals also ace rodent intelligence tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;People who exercise also show large increases in BDNF in their bloodstreams afterward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Other studies have shown that as few as 25 minutes a week of walking, cycling, swimming or similar exercise can be strongly linked to greater brain volume in older people, while taking as few as 3,000 steps a day helps slow cognitive decline in people at high risk for Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;But most of this research involved aerobic exercise and the brain effects of endurance. Fewer studies have looked at the role of muscle mass. Many questions also remain about the role of body fat on brain health, especially the deep, interior fat around our bellies known as visceral fat, which can increase inflammation throughout the body, including, potentially, in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;- - -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Is your brain young or old?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;For the new study, scientists at Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis and other institutions decided to look deep inside people’s body tissues and brains with magnetic resonance imaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;They turned to existing whole-body scans of 1,164 healthy men and women in their 40s, 50s or early 60s. “To understand dementia risk, we’ve got to focus on midlife,” said Cyrus Raji, an associate professor of radiology and neurology at Washington University School of Medicine and the study’s senior author. It’s in middle age that we typically start to develop - or avoid - most of the common risk factors for later dementia, he said, making it a critical time period to study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The scientists used artificial intelligence to analyze the scans and determine people’s total muscle mass and body fat. The body fat was characterized as either visceral or subcutaneous, a different type of fat found just beneath our skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The researchers figured out the apparent age of people’s brains using algorithms based on scans of tens of thousands of other brains. These provided benchmarks of typical brain structure and volume for someone of any age. People’s brains could either match the benchmarks for their chronological age, or look like those of people younger or older. Older-looking brains face heightened risks for early cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;- - -&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;More muscle means younger brains&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The researchers found that the amounts of people’s muscle mass and their visceral fat were both strongly linked to their apparent brain age, though in opposing ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;“The larger the muscle bulk, the younger-looking the brain,” Raji said. “And the more visceral fat that was present, the older-looking the brain.” People whose ratio of visceral fat to muscle mass was especially high - meaning they had a relatively large level of visceral fat and low muscle mass - tended to have the oldest-looking brains. (Subcutaneous fat was not linked to brain age in any way.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The study didn’t look at how muscle and fat affect brains, but both tissues release a variety of biochemicals that can travel to the brain and jump-start various processes there, Raji said. The substances from muscles tend to promote the creation and integration of brain cells and neuronal connections; those from visceral fat do the reverse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;On a practical level, the findings underscore that resistance exercise “is super important” for healthy brain aging, Raji said. Most of us begin losing muscle mass in middle age, but strength training can slow or even reverse that decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Shedding visceral fat is likewise a good idea for our brains, he said. Both aerobic and resistance exercise will target visceral fat. Using weight-loss drugs such as Wegovy and other GLP-1 drugs can also substantially reduce visceral fat. But many people taking the drugs will drop muscle mass, Raji said - unless they also lift weights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;The study has limitations. It hasn’t been published or peer-reviewed. Because it’s not an experiment, it also can’t show that more muscle and less belly fat cause brains to age more slowly - only that those conditions are all linked to each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;But its findings are plausible and align with those of a growing number of other studies, said Fang Yu, director of the Roybal Center for Older Adults Living Alone with Cognitive Decline at Arizona State University in Phoenix. She studies exercise and aging but was not involved with the new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="c-paragraph sans-serif"&gt;Essentially, the study’s message is simple, actionable and even rhymes: If you want a younger, healthier brain, Raji said, “strength train.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Anchorage Daily News</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:45:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisgFBVV95cUxQdlJ1QWFySDJDT1I3cFJvNFhWb19qSEhTbmxtU1lfSWNLR3pBcm1zSDhleW1ITWNOMk1YRkwyLUNPTzNtQWV5cHVLNkRHSm9LRFlXNGlIc3phQWlyMzBSRTZvcWptN1EwZnkzLW1ZZUowTTdCZDV1cndWZGNrUS1WeDM2aS1UMUU4VEtKd2NwSk1jbTU3VERBY0tBM2xXWHg3UW1XUF9LQVp2NHlMa1pXQmV3</guid></item><item><title>随着犹他州、亚利桑那州和南卡罗来纳州病例增加，麻疹疫情不会在2025年结束- NBC新闻</title><link>https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/measles-outbreaks-no-end-2025-cases-mount-utah-arizona-south-carolina-rcna249743</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-9c34e1" class="body-graf"&gt;As measles &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/health/health-news/measles-south-carolina-quarantine-utah-arizona-us-rcna248435" target="_blank"&gt;continues to spread&lt;/a&gt; in the United States, it’s likely that the outbreaks that broke records in 2025 will continue into the new year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-f8d56a" class="body-graf"&gt;In &lt;a href="https://dph.sc.gov/diseases-conditions/infectious-diseases/measles-rubeola/2025-measles-outbreak" target="_blank"&gt;South Carolina&lt;/a&gt;, 168 people, mostly schoolchildren, are in quarantine. Most of the state's 138 cases confirmed since September, nearly all in unvaccinated people, have been centered in Spartanburg County in the northwestern part of the state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a7d103" class="body-graf"&gt;“As we identify new cases, and if those cases have susceptible contacts, that’s a new 21-day quarantine period,” Dr. Linda Bell, state epidemiologist for the state Department of Public Health, said Wednesday at what has become a weekly news briefing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-a972cb" class="body-graf"&gt;That is, anyone who is unvaccinated and therefore vulnerable to measles exposures occurring now will be in quarantine through the holidays.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-811cd8" class="body-graf"&gt;According to &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/data-graphics/map-kindergartner-vaccination-rates-are-lowest-rcna229455" target="_blank"&gt;NBC News data&lt;/a&gt;, the K-12 vaccination rate for measles-mumps-rubella (MMR) in Spartanburg County was 90% for the 2024-25 school year, below the 95% level doctors say is needed to protect against an outbreak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7ec4f1" class="body-graf"&gt;Bell said the vaccination rate has been falling for several years, similar to other areas in the United States. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-e6eb6e" class="body-graf"&gt;Based on NBC News' investigation, &lt;a href="https://www.nbcnews.com/specials/vaccine-divide/" target="_blank"&gt;The Vaccine Divide&lt;/a&gt;, in the states collecting data for the MMR vaccine, 67% of counties and jurisdictions have immunization rates below 95%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-538117" class="body-graf"&gt;Bell said at the briefing that there was no indication the South Carolina outbreak was spreading yet to nearby states, such as North Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-099f9c" class="body-graf"&gt;Since the latest surge in cases, which began in late summer in the &lt;a href="https://epi.utah.gov/measles-response/" target="_blank"&gt;bordering areas of southwestern Utah&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.azdhs.gov/preparedness/epidemiology-disease-control/measles/index.php" target="_blank"&gt;Arizona &lt;/a&gt;and, more recently, in South Carolina, the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention has taken a low profile, with nearly all public outreach about the nationwide outbreaks coming from local and state health departments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5d6f3c" class="body-graf"&gt;It’s a stark contrast to how the agency has previously communicated about infectious diseases like measles. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-301ca0" class="body-graf"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/41380254/" target="_blank"&gt;study published last week&lt;/a&gt; uncovered an “emerging health communication void” regarding measles and measles vaccines in the CDC’s social media accounts. The agency posted about measles 10 times on its social media channels from January through August, according to the study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-722a8b" class="body-graf"&gt;During the same period from 2021 to 2024, the CDC posted an average of about 46 times each year, the study found. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-edfaa8" class="body-graf"&gt;Andrew Nixon, a spokesman for the Department of Health and Human Services (which oversees the CDC), said in an email that the “CDC has developed and distributed updated communication materials, including multilingual resources, to help communities respond to ongoing outbreaks.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-4d09b5" class="body-graf"&gt;The CDC sends teams to investigate infectious disease hot spots only if states request it. Bell said the South Carolina Public Health Department hasn’t asked for extra help from the agency to contain the outbreak. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-feeb7d" class="body-graf"&gt;Separately, the measles outbreak largely straddling the border between Arizona and Utah also continues to swell. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-28ad09" class="body-graf"&gt;The Utah Department of Health and Human Services reports 125 cases, with 21 diagnosed just in the last three weeks. According to the health department, there were multiple measles exposures last week in the southwestern part of the state, including at an elementary school, an urgent care facility, a pediatrician’s office and a pediatric dentistry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-60d3e0" class="body-graf"&gt;The Arizona Department of Health Services reports 190 cases, nearly all in Mohave County, which borders Utah. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c55398" class="body-graf"&gt;Nearly all of those cases, 97%, occurred among people who weren’t vaccinated against the virus. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-d59ec5" class="body-graf"&gt;As of Wednesday, the United States had logged 1,958 measles cases in 2025, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/measles/data-research/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;latest update from the CDC&lt;/a&gt;. That’s just 168 cases shy of a previous high of 2,216 recorded in 1992.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-88ec0b" class="body-graf"&gt;There have been 49 outbreaks (defined as three or more related cases) reported in 2025. In 2025, 222 people, 11% of the 1,958 cases, were sick enough to be hospitalized, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-b15134" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;Three people, an adult in New Mexico and two young girls in Texas, have died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NBC News</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:41:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiwAFBVV95cUxOb1ZIWjZ0UUM2Z3lvUnV3a00ya0JESEtaYnMzRmR6VmU3Z0xQTnlnRTBaR3pvNWl6UEhzLW1zcl9fV2VseDhHTEZpZXdXRFd1cFVGSlpLb1dOY0ZSQlh3NS1HcEpqSzdmLTVCM3hVWm5LclBjZXJhZnh4ZTdXV3lDSGNRU0tQUFBOZGhfaHVqRC14VnVMTUtFY1pSbzZxeFpQRFMtQjMyQndDM2FodUFjNnlGZkJXTmM2Wm50RmkwblM</guid></item><item><title>每年12月“提前到来”有一个科学原因- ScienceAlert</title><link>https://www.sciencealert.com/theres-a-scientific-reason-december-arrives-sooner-every-year</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;How is it December already? What happened to 2025? And how did we suddenly jump from eating Easter eggs to putting up Christmas trees?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand why our perception of time seems to bend and warp, we need to dig into how our brains tell time in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term "&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/ive-researched-time-for-15-years-heres-how-my-perception-of-it-has-changed-215499"&gt;time perception&lt;/a&gt;" is actually a bit of a misnomer, because time itself isn't "out there" to be perceived.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/your-brain-goes-through-5-distinct-epochs-massive-study-finds"&gt;Your Brain Goes Through 5 Distinct Epochs, Massive Study Finds&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we perceive a colour, a sound, a flavour or a touch, specialised sensory organs detect something in the environment: the wavelength of a light particle that enters the eye, the frequency of a sound wave that enters the ear, the presence of different chemicals in the mouth and nose, or the pressure of an object against our skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is no parallel for time – no "time particle" for the brain to detect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How brains deal with time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our brains don't perceive time – they infer it. Like the ticking of a clock, the brain estimates the passage of time by keeping track of change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But unlike a clock, the brain does not have regular ticks to count. To infer how much time has passed, the brain simply adds up how much happened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you fill a time interval with exciting stuff, it seems to last longer. In the lab, a briefly presented flickering image &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1167/6.12.8"&gt;seems to last longer&lt;/a&gt; than a static image of the same duration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://images.theconversation.com/files/707641/original/file-20251210-64-curvv5.jpg?ixlib=rb-4.1.0&amp;amp;rect=0%2C0%2C6000%2C4000&amp;amp;q=45&amp;amp;auto=format&amp;amp;w=754&amp;amp;fit=clip" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;Brains estimate time by keeping track of change. (&lt;a class="source" href="https://www.pexels.com/photo/night-city-traffic-motion-blur-with-officer-35081258/"&gt;Jean-Guillaume Starnini/Pexels&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is also why witnesses of highly intense events (such as car accidents) frequently report that time seems to slow down. Indeed, in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1371/journal.pone.0001295"&gt;one well-known study&lt;/a&gt;, research participants fell backwards into a net from a height of more than 30 metres.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When they were subsequently asked to estimate the duration of their terrifying experience, they reported durations more than a third longer than when they judged someone else's fall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The intense arousal of the first-hand experience amplifies attention, in turn causing the brain to store dense, rich memories of events as they unfold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Afterwards, when it needs to estimate how much time passed during the event, this unusually dense recollection of unfolding events causes the brain to overestimate how much time passed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Time… flies?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand what happened to November and the rest of 2025, we also need to distinguish between telling time retrospectively (how much time has passed) versus prospectively (how fast time is passing now).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As every child knows, time spent waiting at the dentist passes much more slowly than time spent playing with a new toy. But why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Again, a key part of the story is how much is happening – and, specifically, what you're paying attention to. The more you pay attention to time itself, the more slowly it seems to pass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/newsletter?utm_source=promo_generic_health"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg" alt="Subscribe to ScienceAlert's free fact-checked newsletter" class="alignnone wp-image-182810 size-medium" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-642x273.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-768x326.jpg 768w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final-600x255.jpg 600w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/11/Generic-Health-Promo-Final.jpg 850w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The old adage states that time flies when you're having fun, but it doesn't necessarily need to be fun. Whatever you're attending to just needs to distract you from the passage of time. Keep your mind engaged, whether it's work or play, and time will slip away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But try staring at a clock for even five minutes, and you will feel how endless that seems, unless you let your mind wander. Boredom slows time right down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Routine makes the years fly by&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This disconnect between prospective and retrospective time perception also explains the saying "&lt;a href="https://gretchenrubin.com/articles/secret-of-adulthood-the-days-are-long-but-the-years-are-short/"&gt;the days are long but the years are short&lt;/a&gt;", a phenomenon that tends to increase as we age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When we are young, lots of things are new: we go to school for the first time, enter a first relationship, start our first job. All these novel events form a rich store of memories that the brain later looks back on to conclude that a lot has happened, so a lot of time must have passed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, when we get older, a lot of our daily tasks become more routine: bring the kids to school, go to work, cook dinner. As some previously novel parts of our day become routine, they become less interesting. Boring jobs cause time to slow down, creating the impression that the days crawl.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-hidden-brain-state-before-sleep-may-be-the-key-to-human-genius"&gt;A Hidden Brain State Before Sleep May Be The Key to Human Genius&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paradoxically though, because these routine tasks are less exciting and novel, they leave weaker and less vivid memory traces. When our older brain therefore looks back to infer how much time has passed since the start of the year, it concludes that not much has happened, so it doesn't feel very long ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, this is at odds with our conscious knowledge that it's already December, and we are left wondering how the year flew by.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How do I slow down time, then?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Slowing down time &lt;em&gt;as you're experiencing&lt;/em&gt; it is very easy, although completely dissatisfying: just get bored. Go wait at red traffic lights. Count to ten thousand in your head. Watch paint dry, as they say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, slowing down &lt;em&gt;retrospective&lt;/em&gt; time is a little more difficult. Essentially, you need to make sure that come December, you have a year's worth of memories to show for it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One way to do this is to prevent memories from fading, and the best way to do that is to rehash them. &lt;a href="https://www.abc.net.au/news/2022-01-29/how-to-stick-to-regular-journalling/100777232"&gt;Write things down&lt;/a&gt; in a diary or journal. Look back and reminisce. Keep your memories alive, and you'll keep your past alive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other way to ensure you've got a year's worth of memories at year's end takes a little more initiative, but is a lot more inspiring. Because the best way to prevent the year from feeling like it flew by, is to fill it with lots of exciting memories of new, unique experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So explore. Go adventuring. Do something crazy – something you'll never forget.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Your internal clock will thank you for it.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/268982/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/hinze-hogendoorn-969047"&gt;Hinze Hogendoorn&lt;/a&gt;, Professor, Visual Time Perception, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/queensland-university-of-technology-847"&gt;Queensland University of Technology&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/why-is-time-going-so-fast-and-how-do-i-slow-it-down-268982"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:17:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilAFBVV95cUxONk95NWo2dlJZX0p4MUpGUG1QR3FhVWFyN1laVHpGbm5LVFNoOVN6VG4yRV81OFMyLWpta1pKY3h0bXU2bTVHM0U5TTBLN1dmZHNkR1hfMkNaZjJMMXpNeVlEXzFmdDh0aXdubEdGcG5kMmx0TkdnMHM4cFVGeWt6NTZUazZsQUpIZUxqMlVVc1pzZ194</guid></item><item><title>关于谁是最孤独的一代的令人惊讶的事实-英国广播公司</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cn0kz1wpnq5o</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;The surprising truth about the generations that suffer loneliness the most&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-6 bbhBdd"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/04d8/live/0227c6e0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.png.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/04d8/live/0227c6e0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.png.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/04d8/live/0227c6e0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.png.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/04d8/live/0227c6e0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.png.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/04d8/live/0227c6e0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.png.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/04d8/live/0227c6e0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.png.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/04d8/live/0227c6e0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.png.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/04d8/live/0227c6e0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.png.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Luke Mintz profile image" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Luke Mintz&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;BBC News&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 eRlINq"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/8f9a/live/bb6ca550-da6f-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/8f9a/live/bb6ca550-da6f-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/8f9a/live/bb6ca550-da6f-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/8f9a/live/bb6ca550-da6f-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/8f9a/live/bb6ca550-da6f-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/8f9a/live/bb6ca550-da6f-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/8f9a/live/bb6ca550-da6f-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/8f9a/live/bb6ca550-da6f-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="BBC Lonely people standing apart" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;BBC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;b id='it-is-a-chilly-october-evening-in-2021-that-adam-becket-remembers-most-sharply.-he-was-26,-and-had-moved-to-bristol-a-year-earlier-to-start-a-"dream-job"-in-the-race-cycling-industry.-so-far,-he-had-struggled-to-make-friends.' class="sc-d16436d-0 gnUCoQ"&gt;It is a chilly October evening in 2021 that Adam Becket remembers most sharply. He was 26, and had moved to Bristol a year earlier to start a "dream job" in the race cycling industry. So far, he had struggled to make friends.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I wasn't alone all the time, but […] I was a bit of an outsider," he remembers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;As he headed home, the streets were full of Halloween partygoers in monster and cat costumes. "I walked past people turning up to friend's houses, people running into shops to buy beer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"All the pubs were full. It just [felt] like a different world that you're not part of. And you feel like you can never be part of it."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That night, he felt like the only person experiencing serious loneliness. In fact, it is becoming a defining feature of his generation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Conversations around social isolation tend to focus on the elderly, especially around Christmas. But by some measures, people in their 20s are the loneliest group in Britain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/29cd/live/f4cc9130-d9c4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/29cd/live/f4cc9130-d9c4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/29cd/live/f4cc9130-d9c4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/29cd/live/f4cc9130-d9c4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/29cd/live/f4cc9130-d9c4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/29cd/live/f4cc9130-d9c4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/29cd/live/f4cc9130-d9c4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/29cd/live/f4cc9130-d9c4-11f0-a8dc-93c15fe68710.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Adam Becket Left: an image of Adam Becket on a walk. Right: Adam Becket on a bicycle on a hill" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Adam Becket&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;'I wasn't alone all the time, but… I was a bit of an outsider,' says Adam - his loneliness eased after he joined running and cycling clubs&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;According to Office for National Statistics (ONS) research published last month, 33% of Britons aged 16 to 29 reported feeling lonely "often, always or some of the time" - the highest of all age groups (17% of over-70s said the same thing).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This year, the World Health Organization reviewed various studies published across the world and found that young adults and adolescents report the highest levels of loneliness too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The data is complex, and there are indications that, in some countries, among the very oldest group (over-85s), loneliness shoots up and could match that of 18-to-30s. But analysts say that in most research, young adults shine through as a particularly isolated group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Adults between 18 and 24 are the most lonely - followed by older people," says Prof Andrea Wigfield, director of the Centre for Loneliness Studies at Sheffield Hallam University. "It's a growing problem."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But why has this happened - and is there a solution?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;The problem of 'scattering'&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Increasingly, experts say the modern world is to blame. Many twenty-somethings live in house-shares where they do not know or like their housemates. Work increasingly is done from home and friends are often spoken to on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;It is not all bleak. Thanks to the internet, young adults enjoy access to friendships from all over the world. But broadly speaking, experts say, the image of gregarious twenty-something life presented in sitcoms like Friends needs urgent correction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/aca8/live/71c080a0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/aca8/live/71c080a0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/aca8/live/71c080a0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/aca8/live/71c080a0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/aca8/live/71c080a0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/aca8/live/71c080a0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/aca8/live/71c080a0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/aca8/live/71c080a0-d9b3-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="NBC Universal via Getty Images A still from the show Friends, with characters standing around in an apartment" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;NBC Universal via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;The 1990s sitcom 'Friends' paints a sociable picture of life for twenty-somethings - but according to young adults who have spoken to the BBC, along with academics, charity bosses and doctors, the 20s is a primary decade of loneliness&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We tend to romanticise young adulthood as a carefree time - when it's usually the most miserable time in people's lives," says Prof Richard Weissbourd, a lecturer in education at Harvard University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In some ways, early adulthood has always been a time of instability. Young adults tend to leave their childhood home and move around. Friends depart, and family ties weaken. These transitory life events can, for some, lead to intense loneliness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"A big problem is the scattering - everybody you ever knew now lives in a million different places," says Dr Meg Jay, a clinical psychologist and author of The Twenty-Something Treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This "scattering" proved difficult for Adam Becket. He had a rich social life when he lived in London in his early 20s - but after moving to Bristol, he had to make friends from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Not only did I not know anyone, I didn't know where to start meeting people either. You can't just go up to someone and be like, 'Can I join in this fun?' It's easy to spiral into self-doubt and self-flagellation - 'I'm clearly not interesting or cool, or the right kind of person.'"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 djqsWD"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Things improved when he joined running and cycling clubs and met people that he "clicked with" - though he says his loneliness still comes and goes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;The Bowling Alone thesis&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Today, there is also a set of new, distinctly modern factors that could be making the problem worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In many parts of the world, people are getting married and having children later (or not at all). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The average age of first marriage in the UK is now 31, according to the ONS, up from 1970 when it was 23 for men and 21 for women. Young adults tend to be more reliant on friends for emotional connection - and if those friends don't deliver, loneliness can follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Weissbourd points to a broader fragmenting of communities too. In rich countries, membership of civic institutions - like churches, community groups, or trade unions - has dropped since the 1970s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This is sometimes known as the Bowling Alone thesis, named after an influential 1995 essay by political scientist Robert Putnam, who observed that more young Americans were bowling on their own rather than in teams, a symbol of a wider collapse of social relations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Twenty-somethings - who might have left their childhood home but not yet started their own family - can feel that decline of community most sharply, says Prof Weissbourd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"We live in an increasingly individualistic society. I think loneliness is a symptom of our failure to care for each other."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7577/live/1e8da770-d9c5-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7577/live/1e8da770-d9c5-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7577/live/1e8da770-d9c5-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7577/live/1e8da770-d9c5-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7577/live/1e8da770-d9c5-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7577/live/1e8da770-d9c5-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7577/live/1e8da770-d9c5-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7577/live/1e8da770-d9c5-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images A black and white image of young men and women bowling." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;In the 1950s young Americans mostly bowled in teams; by the 1990s, more people bowled alone - a trend highlighted by Robert Putnam's famous essay&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This resonates with Zeyneb, 23, who lives alone in Cheltenham. Her own feelings of loneliness peaked last year during her master's degree. With only a few hours of teaching each week, she struggled to find meaningful connections with her classmates. And with her family far away in Romania, she now spends much of her time alone while she looks for a job. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"It does feel cripplingly lonely when everyone has their own thing to do."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She craves what psychologists call a "third place": a social setting like a park or library that is different from your "first place" (home) or your "second place" (work or university). "We don't really have that space to meet people," she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The closest thing she can think of is her gym - but virtually everyone there wears headphones, she tells me, and few make eye contact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;The urban houseshare paradox&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Then there is the post-pandemic rise in working from home. Though young adults in the UK don't work from home as often as older generations - 28% of 16-to-29-year-olds worked from home at least some of the time in the first quarter of 2025, compared with 54% of 30-to-49-year-olds, one study suggests - remote work can hit people in their 20s particularly hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Work from home has been, in my opinion, a nightmare for twenty-somethings," says Dr Jay. "It's really hard to make friends when you don't leave the house."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Nor do shared living situations always help. There is something of a paradox here, as young adults are the most likely to live with other people. (In England and Wales only 5% of people in their early 20s live alone, versus 49% of over-85s, suggests the ONS.) But living under the same roof as others doesn't always seem to make young adults any less lonely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Some of my most pitiful memories of my 20s were being stuck living with people that I didn't like," recalls Dr Jay. "If I was having a hard time, they didn't care, they were too wrapped up in themselves."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Of course this isn't the case for all house-shares - but she thinks having an emotionally distant flatmate can make people "even more lonely" than if they lived alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;'Compare and despair' on smartphones&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;All of this is complicated by smartphones and social media. This year, the average British 18-to-24-year-old spent six hours and 20 minutes online every day, according to the media regulator Ofcom, higher than other adult age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some might assume that apps like Instagram and Snapchat contribute to feelings of loneliness because they encourage people to speak online rather than in person - but the data doesn't cleanly support this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;What is certainly true, say some experts, is that social media &lt;i id="amplifies" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;amplifies&lt;/i&gt; pre-existing feelings of loneliness because of what Dr Jay calls the "compare and despair" factor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"You feel like, 'Everybody seems to have best friends and they're all skydiving in Dubai - what's wrong with me, I didn't see anyone all weekend.'"&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/e514/live/d5e626a0-d9ba-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/e514/live/d5e626a0-d9ba-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e514/live/d5e626a0-d9ba-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/e514/live/d5e626a0-d9ba-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/e514/live/d5e626a0-d9ba-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/e514/live/d5e626a0-d9ba-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/e514/live/d5e626a0-d9ba-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/e514/live/d5e626a0-d9ba-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Getty Images Four men stand in a queue, looking at their smartphones." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;The average young adult in the UK spends 6 hours and 20 minutes online every day, according to media regulator Ofcom&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Yet it is also possible that reporting biases are playing a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Studies about loneliness are mostly based on self-report surveys (meaning people are simply asked whether they feel lonely). And Prof Weissbourd says it is plausible that young adults, who tend to be more fluent in the language of mental health and therapy, are more likely than older people to describe themselves as lonely in surveys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He thinks reporting biases may explain a "piece" of the puzzle - but certainly not all of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Prof Wigfield also thinks the high level of young-adult loneliness is a real phenomenon, not a statistical mirage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="subheadline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h2 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 gXmhTb"&gt;The 'lottery' of social prescribing&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;At first, David Gradon's story was fairly typical. In his late 20s, his friends moved away from London. "My social circle really shrunk," he remembers - and he developed symptoms of depression. It was an NHS counsellor who suggested this could be loneliness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;He tried meeting people over dating apps (a "terrible" idea) and joined a tag rugby club, but injured his leg in the first session. Increasingly despondent, he organised a park walk on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;One autumn day in 2021, Mr Gradon and 11 strangers met at Hampstead Heath in north London. He organised more walks and in time this became his full-time job. He now runs The Great Friendship Project, a non-profit group to combat young adult loneliness, which runs social events for under-35s across London.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Everyone's in that same boat. And actually, that brings down barriers. Because you know you're not going to be judged," he explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/7336/live/bc1d8fc0-d9b4-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/7336/live/bc1d8fc0-d9b4-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7336/live/bc1d8fc0-d9b4-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/7336/live/bc1d8fc0-d9b4-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/7336/live/bc1d8fc0-d9b4-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/7336/live/bc1d8fc0-d9b4-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/7336/live/bc1d8fc0-d9b4-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/7336/live/bc1d8fc0-d9b4-11f0-aae2-2191c0e48a3b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="The Great Friendship Project A group of people stand in a park, some of them wearing dinosaur costumes." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;The Great Friendship Project&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;David Gradon's non-profit group organises park walks and other events for under-35s in London&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Council-funded youth clubs operate around the country. Most are currently aimed at teenagers and children, but Laura Cunliffe-Hall, head of policy at charity UK Youth, wants to see more clubs for people in their early 20s. She argues that youth work should serve everyone up to the age of 25.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Funding, she says, is the barrier. Local authority spending on youth services in England fell by 73% between 2010/11 and 2023/24, according to the charity YMCA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Some argue that spending money on friendship services can save money over the long term, because the health consequences of long-term loneliness can be severe. Prof Wigfield says that chronic loneliness is linked to inflammation, and can increase the risk of cardiovascular disease and dementia in later life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In recent years the NHS has invested in "social prescribing", where GPs connect patients with certain mental health problems to charity-run services in their area - like art classes or gardening. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;More than one million people (of all ages) were referred to NHS social prescribing services in 2023, a recent study found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But Prof Wigfield says infrastructure remains patchy. "It really is a lottery in terms of where you live [and] whether the GP has knowledge of local services."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/85db/live/ad0b3960-d9b4-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/85db/live/ad0b3960-d9b4-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/85db/live/ad0b3960-d9b4-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/85db/live/ad0b3960-d9b4-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/85db/live/ad0b3960-d9b4-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/85db/live/ad0b3960-d9b4-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/85db/live/ad0b3960-d9b4-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/85db/live/ad0b3960-d9b4-11f0-b67b-690eb873de1b.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="The Great Friendship Project People walking through a London park" class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;The Great Friendship Project&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;Virtually all attendees come alone, meaning everyone's "in the same boat", says David Gradon of The Great Friendship Project&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Looking ahead to the next decade, Dr Jay sees signs of hope. For one, she thinks working from home has "lost some of its lustre" among twenty-somethings. (Several large employers - including Barclays and WPP - asked staff to spend longer in the office this year.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Jay also notes that some high-profile people are turning against social media - though she says there is not yet much evidence of a significant fall in usage among young adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"I'd love to see more of a backlash against [social media], but it's just so in our pockets," she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Then there are those who find their solution to loneliness in unexpected places. For Zeyneb, the best antidote to social isolation was adopting a black cat, Olive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"She's quite cuddly," says Zeyneb. "She knows when I need time with her. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Without her, I would have been much lonelier."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;i id="top-picture-credit:-getty." class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Top picture credit: Getty.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/bbcindepth" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="bbc-indepth" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;BBC InDepth&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="is-the-home-on-the-website-and-app-for-the-best-analysis,-with-fresh-perspectives-that-challenge-assumptions-and-deep-reporting-on-the-biggest-issues-of-the-day.-you-can-now-sign-up-for-notifications-that-will-alert-you-whenever-an-indepth-story-is-published--" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt; is the home on the website and app for the best analysis, with fresh perspectives that challenge assumptions and deep reporting on the biggest issues of the day. You can now sign up for notifications that will alert you whenever an InDepth story is published - &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/articles/cj6x46j8g5do" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="click-here-to-find-out-how." class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;click here to find out how.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 00:05:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE1COHBKQUsxeDBvb2NoazVzRVkxczJwVGVjajRtSHhpNnV2QVEtM1ExelM1bm9sMUlSczg3WUVmT1ZrYi1icklta1pmUFh1YjBRbUdyQ2pxakNzUdIBX0FVX3lxTE8tNDJjZ0xWc0taOTd3X1ctRVpFWldOSVBKejlYSDVZMk5EZUZLNHZVUW1BLW95XzJaMDhFQ1VZbngwbGhtQTZOSGM5MGtzSC1aSjlBZk0wM25mVXIwQjFN</guid></item><item><title>H5N1 ：印度科学家预测禽流感如何传播给人类- BBC</title><link>https://www.bbc.com/news/articles/cgl66ez489po</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 hNbOGD"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 idLnWK"&gt;Indian scientists predict how bird flu could spread to humans&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline" class="sc-573fa0e8-0 bWRWzH"&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors" class="sc-573fa0e8-11 cOQNNv"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0" class="sc-573fa0e8-5 gXJgDY"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="sc-573fa0e8-7 gqeTMs"&gt;Soutik Biswas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-testid="byline-contributors-contributor-0-role-location" class="sc-573fa0e8-8 bIfajQ"&gt;India correspondent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gtLOOD"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5294/live/489c62e0-da51-11f0-a8f0-851857e2c194.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5294/live/489c62e0-da51-11f0-a8f0-851857e2c194.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5294/live/489c62e0-da51-11f0-a8f0-851857e2c194.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5294/live/489c62e0-da51-11f0-a8f0-851857e2c194.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5294/live/489c62e0-da51-11f0-a8f0-851857e2c194.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5294/live/489c62e0-da51-11f0-a8f0-851857e2c194.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5294/live/489c62e0-da51-11f0-a8f0-851857e2c194.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5294/live/489c62e0-da51-11f0-a8f0-851857e2c194.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Tribune News Service via Getty Images Bronze turkey hens roam in a fenced grassy area after being fed at All Grass Farms in Dundee. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Tribune News Service via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;More than two million turkeys have been culled in the US since late August due to avian flu&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;For years, scientists have warned that bird flu - better known as H5N1 - could one day make the dangerous leap from birds to humans and trigger a global health crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Avian flu - a type of influenza - is entrenched across South and South-East Asia and has occasionally infected humans since emerging in China in the late 1990s. From 2003 to August 2025, the World Health Organization (WHO) has &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.paho.org/en/documents/epidemiological-update-avian-influenza-ah5n1-americas-region-15-october-2025?utm_source=chatgpt.com" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; 990 human H5N1 cases across 25 countries, including 475 deaths - a 48% fatality rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In the US alone, the virus has struck more than 180 million birds, spread to over 1,000 dairy herds in 18 states, and infected at least 70 people - mostly farmworkers - causing several hospitalisations and one death. In January, three tigers and a leopard died at a wildlife rescue centre in India's Nagpur city from the virus that typically infects birds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Symptoms in humans mimic a severe flu: high fever, cough, sore throat, muscle aches and, at times, conjunctivitis. Some people have no symptoms at all. The risk to humans remains low, but authorities are watching H5N1 closely for any shift that could make it spread more easily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;That concern is what prompted new peer-reviewed modelling by Indian researchers Philip Cherian and Gautam Menon of Ashoka University, which simulates how an H5N1 outbreak might unfold in humans and what early interventions could stop it before it spreads. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In other words, the&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://link.springer.com/article/10.1186/s12889-025-25358-5" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt; model &lt;/a&gt;published in the BMC Public Health journal uses real world data and computer simulations to play out how an outbreak might spread in real life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"The threat of an H5N1 pandemic in humans is a genuine one, but we can hope to forestall it through better surveillance and a more nimble public-health response," Prof Menon told the BBC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A bird flu pandemic, researchers say, would begin quietly: a single infected bird passing the virus to a human - most likely a farmer, market worker or someone handling poultry. From there, the danger lies not in that first infection but in what happens next: sustained human-to-human transmission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Because real outbreaks start with limited, messy data, the researchers turned to &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://bharatsim.ashoka.edu.in/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;BharatSim&lt;/a&gt;, an open-source simulation platform originally built for Covid 19 modelling, but versatile enough to study other diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/5a75/live/2a266e10-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/5a75/live/2a266e10-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5a75/live/2a266e10-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/5a75/live/2a266e10-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/5a75/live/2a266e10-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/5a75/live/2a266e10-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/5a75/live/2a266e10-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/5a75/live/2a266e10-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Hindustan Times via Getty Images A worker at National Zoological Park sprays pesticides at the entrance gate to sanitize the premises as bird flu spread in the zoo area on 1 September, 2025 in New Delhi, India. " class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Hindustan Times via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;A bird flu outbreak in a Delhi zoo shut down the facility for a few days in August&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The key takeaway for policymakers is how narrow the window for action can be before an outbreak spirals out of control, the researchers say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The paper estimates that once cases rise beyond roughly two to 10, the disease is likely to spread beyond primary and secondary contacts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Primary contacts are people who have had direct, close contact with an infected person, such as household members, caregivers or close colleagues. Secondary contacts are those who have not met the infected person but have been in close contact with a primary contact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If households of primary contacts are quarantined when just two cases are detected, the outbreak can almost certainly be contained, the research found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But by the time 10 cases are identified, it is overwhelmingly likely that the infection has already spread into the wider population, making its trajectory virtually indistinguishable from a scenario with no early intervention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;To keep the study grounded in real-world conditions, the researchers chose a model of a single village in Namakkal district, Tamil Nadu - the heart of India's poultry belt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Namakkal is home to more than 1,600 poultry farms and some 70 million chickens; it produces over 60 million eggs a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;A village of 9,667 residents was generated using a synthetic community - households, workplaces, market spaces - and seeded with infected birds to mimic real-life exposure. (A synthetic community is an artificial, computer-generated population that mimics the characteristics and behaviours of a real population.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;In the simulation, the virus starts at one workplace -  a mid-sized farm or wet market - spreads first to people there (primary contacts), and then moves outward to others (seconday contacts) they interact with through homes, schools and other workplaces.  Homes, schools and workplaces formed a fixed network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;By tracking primary and secondary infections, the researchers estimated key transmission metrics, including the basic reproductive number, R0 - which measures how many people, on average, one infected person passes the virus on to. In the absence of a real-world pandemic, the researchers instead modelled a range of plausible transmission speeds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Then they tested what happens when different interventions - culling birds, quarantining close contacts and targeted vaccination - kicked in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The results were blunt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Culling of birds works - but only if done before the virus infects a human. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;If a spillover does occur, timing becomes everything, the researchers found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Isolating infected people and quarantining households can stop the virus at the secondary stage. But once tertiary infections appear - friends of friends, or contacts of contacts - the outbreak slips out of control unless authorities impose much tougher measures, including lockdowns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Targeted vaccination helps by raising the threshold at which the virus can sustain itself, though it does little to change the immediate risk within households.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gXrNRM"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="image" class="sc-5340b511-1 cMIbKV"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20251210-151139-37baf2dfdd-web-2.36.1-1/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-5340b511-0 gUePlo hide-when-no-script" aria-label="image unavailable"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/9690/live/d2e150b0-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/9690/live/d2e150b0-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9690/live/d2e150b0-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/9690/live/d2e150b0-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/9690/live/d2e150b0-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/9690/live/d2e150b0-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/9690/live/d2e150b0-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/9690/live/d2e150b0-d92e-11f0-983a-fdbf166801c4.jpg.webp" loading="lazy" alt="Bloomberg via Getty Images Chicks at a poultry farm in Kachhawa village, near Karnal, Haryana, India." class="sc-5340b511-0 hLdNfA"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-5340b511-2 jVqbAn"&gt;Bloomberg via Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 Qwxkf"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 gnQokQ"&gt;India's poultry industry is one of the world's largest&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dPVOKT"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The simulations also highlighted an awkward trade-off. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Quarantine, introduced too early, keeps families together for long stretches - and increases the chance that infected individuals will pass the virus to those they live with. Introduced too late, it does little to slow the outbreak at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The researchers say this approach comes with caveats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The model relies on one synthetic village, with fixed household sizes, workplaces and daily movement patterns. It does not include simultaneous outbreaks seeded by migratory birds or by poultry networks. Nor does it account for behavioural shifts - mask-wearing, for instance - once people know birds are dying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Seema Lakdawala, a virologist at Atlanta-based Emory University, adds another caveat: this simulation model "assumes a very efficient transmission of influenza viruses".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"Transmission is complex and not every strain will have the same efficiency as another," she says, adding that scientists are also now starting to understand that not all people infected with seasonal flu spread the virus equally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;She says emerging research shows that only a "subset of flu-positive individuals actually shed infectious influenza virus into the air". &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;This mirrors the &lt;a target="_self" href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-51447143" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;super-spreader phenomenon&lt;/a&gt; seen with Covid-19, though it is far less well characterised for flu - a gap that could strongly influence how the virus spreads through human populations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;What happens if H5N1 becomes successful in the human population?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;Dr Lakdawala believes that it "will cause a large disruption likely more similar to the &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/emergencies/situations/influenza-a-%28h1n1%29-outbreak?utm_source=chatgpt.com" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;2009 [swine flu] pandemic&lt;/a&gt; rather than Covid-19".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;"This is because we are more prepared for an influenza pandemic. We have known licensed antivirals that are effective against the H5N1 strains as an early defence and stockpiled candidate&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.who.int/teams/global-influenza-programme/vaccines/who-recommendations/zoonotic-influenza-viruses-and-candidate-vaccine-viruses" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt; H5 vaccines&lt;/a&gt; that could be deployed in the short term."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;But complacency would be a mistake. Dr Lakdawala says if H5N1 becomes established in humans, it could re-assort - or intermingle - with existing strains, amplifying its public-health impact. Such mixing could reshape seasonal influenza, triggering "chaotic and unpredictable seasonal epidemics".&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;The Indian modellers say the simulations can be run in real time and updated as data come in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;With refinements - better reporting delays, asymptomatic cases - they could give public-health officials something priceless in the early hours of an outbreak: a sense of which actions matter most, before the window for containment snaps shut.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 eZyhnA"&gt;&lt;i id="follow-bbc-news-india-on" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Follow BBC News India on &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.instagram.com/bbcnewsindia/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="instagram" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Instagram&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="," class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;, &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.youtube.com/@bbcnewsindia/featured" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="youtube," class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;YouTube,&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt; &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://x.com/BBCIndia" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="x" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;X&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="and" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt; and &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/bbcindia/" class="sc-f9178328-0 iCaRzc"&gt;&lt;i id="facebook" class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;Facebook&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i id="." class="sc-d16436d-0 iVdNuz"&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 23:56:02 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTFBYeDhIZ0tyYXBIUjN6RzdQLTFlT05oTkFTLTlSSHdYOG9SVjZwT21lVHF3a1ZURjRxa0NrQ1YtYnZfRlREbkVMX3FOUDh4QjVTczk0WGdyemJPd9IBX0FVX3lxTE1mbTc0bWczN0R4ZGRGNWpWaUhLVklKSEdpQWNTTXlmSXJJWGFTeDdsSWFjLVFYemxCdnJfWkpJUXlOcFBic0dRNGJLR0NZbW1TQ01seWtfYVNjc0pFU09R</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，洛杉矶森林大火后心脏病发作增加-《卫报》</title><link>https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2025/dec/17/los-angeles-wildfires-heart-attacks</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-hdpgoq"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In the first 90 days after the devastating Palisades and Eaton fires that destroyed entire Los Angeles neighborhoods, there was a 46% increase in ER visits for heart attack symptoms at LA’s Cedars-Sinai hospital, according to a &lt;a href="https://www.jacc.org/doi/10.1016/j.jacc.2025.10.079" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;newly released study&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“Rates of heart attacks in January 2025 actually surpassed heart attack rates during all the prior Januaries, even during the Covid years,” Dr Susan Cheng, director of public health research at Cedars-Sinai and the study’s senior author, told the Guardian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Residents in the zip codes directly affected by the January wildfires or located adjacent to a fire-affected area also reported a 24% increase in pulmonary illness and a staggering 118% increase in blood test abnormalities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Palisades fire was the &lt;a href="https://www.wildfirela.org/history/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;most destructive fire&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/los-angeles" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt; history, destroying 6,800 structures and killing 12 people. To the east, the Eaton fire devastated the neighborhood of Altadena, with 19 confirmed deaths. More than &lt;a href="https://www.fire.ca.gov/incidents/2025/1/7/eaton-fire/updates/262ba0be-593a-463c-94b1-a15d1e7f2a1e" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;9,400 structures&lt;/a&gt; were destroyed across Altadena and neighboring Pasadena and Sierra Madre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The findings, which were released in the Journal of the American College of Cardiology, are part of &lt;a href="https://lafirehealth.org/data/" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;a research project&lt;/a&gt; on the short- and long-term impact of the fires on human health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Cedars-Sinai medical center is located approximately 10 and 20 miles from the epicenters of the Palisades and Eaton fires, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“What we saw during the wildfires was an excess of respiratory illness showing up in our ER that matched the worst years of Covid,” Cheng said. “And that was striking.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While some increased respiratory illness was expected due to the effects of wildfire smoke,Cheng said she was surprised not only by the percentage of increase, but also by the jump in heart attack incidences and blood test abnormalities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“For a very large number of people, the January wildfire exposures led to a biochemical or metabolic stress on the body that likely affected, not just one, but multiple organ systems,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The blood test data came from patients who reported physical symptoms that did not have a clear diagnosis, such as dizziness without clear signs of dehydration or chest pains without other signs of a heart attack. Cheng noted that the patients’ blood tests revealed subtle abnormalities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“The blood tests could show their electrolytes were a little bit off, like sodium, potassium, or there’s a slight imbalance in their protein levels,” she said. “Or there’s a slight change in markers of kidney and liver function.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Palisades and Eaton fires were particularly harmful to human health due to their classification as a “wildland-urban interface fire (WUI)”. This type of fire spreads more easily than a wildfire-only or urban-only fire, burning a combination of organic materials and industrial fuels, such as plastic, batteries, and electronics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While the data collected by Chang and her colleagues is a start, there are still many questions left to be answered on the long-term effects of January’s fires on human health. “There’s a lot of work to do,” she said. “We’re still working hard to put the pieces together.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 23:53:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiwFBVV95cUxQaEwxdlNHd1N3czBWeDJESHJTU1hENVVpQ0lVY0pjS3h2VWZnTENmOXBLZkstYk5WekpEb3BYWUt0SmdpczlvZmFBaHZiTlA5REM3MEw0NUk3R1Y2YkNuZnpDWUJqSnBZVm9xd296ZlpsQUs2R1Fxc2s2OTd2Y2V4R2l0eEZNMG9TSkxz</guid></item><item><title>被亚特兰大地铁皮肤科医生毁容的男子家庭获得了5680万美元的$ - WSB-TV</title><link>https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/atlanta/family-man-disfigured-by-metro-atlanta-dermatologist-awarded-568-million/ZEL7NJ5RHRBVLL2RSTMUNRUULE/</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="default__ArticleBody-sc-tl066j-1 jPcFTl article-body-wrapper"&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;FULTON COUNTY, Ga. — A jury awarded more than $50 million to the estate of Vietnam veteran Tony Waldrop after finding that a doctor disfigured him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;In 2013, Waldrop was suffering from skin cancer on his right ear and was getting treated at the VA for years with no problems. But he needed an appointment quicker than the VA could provide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[DOWNLOAD: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.wsbtv.com/smart-tv/" title=""&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free WSB-TV News app for alerts as news breaks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;“The VA couldn’t see him in time for this. He needed to be seen sooner than later, so he got a referral from the VA, and they sent him to Dr. Payne, who is also a vet,” attorney Lloyd Bell told &lt;b&gt;Channel 2’s Tyisha Fernandes&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more" class="taboola-read-more"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;The dermatologist did a procedure where he removed some tissue, but the cancer came back in the same spot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;“When it grew back, Dr. Payne cut it out, but then he throws the tissue away and doesn’t send for biopsy. He thought it was a cyst,” Bell said. “Well, that’s a bad idea if you deal with a high-risk cancer patient, because when he grew back again a month and a half, two months later, it had invaded deep into his face.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;TRENDING STORIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;It disfigured Waldrop and his family says he spent the next eight years suffering before he died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-read-more-8" class="taboola-read-more-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;Last week, a Fulton County jury found that Dr. Payne was negligent in his medical treatment and awarded his estate $56.8 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;“I hope it says that people need to check themselves and check their views of their infallibility, and, like I said, doctors are just like everybody else where they have to keep their guard up that they’re not getting overly confident and that they are staying humble,” Bell said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph"&gt;&lt;b&gt;[SIGN UP: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="https://membercenter.wsbtv.com/newsletters"&gt;&lt;b&gt;WSB-TV Daily Headlines Newsletter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;]&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="default__StyledText-sc-tl066j-0 gJuxXh body-paragraph body-copyright"&gt;©2025 Cox Media Group&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WSB-TV</author><pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 23:41:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi2AFBVV95cUxQeUM2V0JQelVFYjdKSWM3RTJLaVJQazlGRFFDS0JZN2xWLVlrSWtmRVZCS1pGcjRMeERFUkpsR3JmWng4cnU3QnRFMS1meGtpNkpUMjBJU1NBQUx1ZHIyeHF5UENkOUdhd0FjVG44U3ZGNXBoblNYRk1wRnJRYWRxRkRNRGZKMldRbGV5LU9MWFVOb2pmZHBxcXlRY0k0d05ya3lxSTQ0UHVUMHgtemJTLVNWSzR1ZzFUZ296dmJJNG5LUjR1eEZpSml4UzJjQjVQQjQ3SExxTXXSAewBQVVfeXFMUElfb3BmT2ZNOEVCemkzaS1RUkktSkhmcU04VjlIZnRUdEFBcEIwYkZ5c1YwclFlYUIxLVBPY1p1d3dTNzNQd003RnJjWFhvMklkeVNzeVJSdmFtbGRXMVZhVF9hRm5vcTlCQmNoSUxsNnRGRVBZeGNuS0FlanBUanM4TlhKdTdFT0taRzBDblJ5WG9vSzRSS3M5Y05aNDVnbHJVYmduMnJpTXNPQ1dXQ3Z6Z1ZWeFhYeDNDQjNvMGIwVzkwRDhyamJrY05oZGlfMXBXdUFSNFB4dm01NXpMaEVKQWxndHd4WEtXUko</guid></item></channel></rss>