<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>哈佛大学将锂流失与阿尔茨海默病联系起来的研究为LI带来了希望-新闻日</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE13NEVpYm1zZDNoNE43azBrT05vREliWmdTdXpGNDJZNEFWOXZwT1RiVjN0QlN4bmJocDhRV3czdTJyTmlrTVVtdDFqa3VMUk5aNVdYdlE3WXBKRy1Za2tNajVoREpJWmpnMHFpMEs4Y0NSd1NlZkdfX0lPRTYtanc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="continue-reading ContinueReading_continue-reading__uTArZ active ContinueReading_active__SOMMR"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new Harvard Medical School study linking the loss of the metal lithium to Alzheimer’s disease is giving some hope to Long Island advocates, who said Friday it was a field where more breakthroughs were needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The seven-year study could help doctors detect the disease earlier in people, provide new treatments and give scientists a better understanding of the human brain, according to researchers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is "the most hopeful thing that we've had in a while," said Tori Cohen, executive director of the Long Island Alzheimer's and Dementia Center in Westbury. "This type of information ... I feel should be jumped on."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lauren Vlachos, executive director of the Alzheimer's Disease Resource Center in East Islip, called the finding "an exciting moment in Alzheimer's research."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The recent Harvard study showing lithium orotate reversing Alzheimer’s-like changes in mice is a major breakthrough, offering renewed hope for treatment and even prevention," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vlachos said it was crucial to continue funding research, but also to move such findings into clinical trials. "Discovery is only part of the equation," she said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One expert on Long Island cautioned the study was a preliminary finding and people should not go out and start taking lithium pills.&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Marc Gordon, chief of neurology for Northwell’s Zucker Hillside, North Shore University Hospital and Long Island Jewish Medical Center, said the study was "interesting."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I’m concerned that people are going to completely misinterpret it and think that they've got to start popping lithium carbonate and get toxic," he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, led by Dr. Bruce A. Yankner, a professor of genetics and neurology at Harvard Medical School, found that researchers could reverse Alzheimer's in mice and restore brain functions using small amounts of the compound lithium orotate. The amount given was enough to mimic the metal’s natural level in the brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results of the study were reported in the scientific journal Nature on Wednesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The obvious impact is that because lithium orotate is dirt cheap, hopefully we will get rigorous, randomized trials testing this very, very quickly," Matt Kaeberlein, former director of the Healthy Aging and Longevity Research Institute at the University of Washington, who did not participate in the study, told The Washington Post. "And I would say that it will be an embarrassment to the Alzheimer’s clinical community if that doesn’t happen right away."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yankner, who is also the co-director of the Paul F. Glenn Center for Biology of Aging Research at Harvard, told The Post: "I do not recommend that people take lithium at this point, because it has not been validated as a treatment in humans. We always have to be cautious because things can change as you go from mice to humans."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yankner said other labs still needed to validate the findings of the study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cohen said the fact the study was done with mice "doesn't mean that it can't be ... taken seriously" and possibly applied to humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class=""&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alzheimer’s is a form of dementia that affects memory, thinking and behavior. More than 7 million people in the United States over the age of 65 have Alzheimer's, according to the Alzheimer's Association, a Chicago-based nonprofit which predicts that number will rise to almost 13 million by 2050.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although there have been some recent breakthroughs in treating Alzheimer's, researchers have not discovered a medication to stop or reverse it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Patients with bipolar disorder are often prescribed lithium, and some previous research has suggested it could help with Alzheimer’s and also serve as an antiaging medication. One 2017 study in Denmark suggested that lithium found in drinking water could be associated with a lower incident of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;With The Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="byline Byline_byline__7W6Ao ux Byline_ux__K0907 bot Byline_bot__Vn8AK"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
	Bart Jones has covered religion, immigration and major breaking news at Newsday since 2000. A former foreign correspondent for The Associated Press in Venezuela, he is the author of “HUGO! The Hugo Chavez Story from Mud Hut to Perpetual Revolution.”
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Newsday</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 23:03:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE13NEVpYm1zZDNoNE43azBrT05vREliWmdTdXpGNDJZNEFWOXZwT1RiVjN0QlN4bmJocDhRV3czdTJyTmlrTVVtdDFqa3VMUk5aNVdYdlE3WXBKRy1Za2tNajVoREpJWmpnMHFpMEs4Y0NSd1NlZkdfX0lPRTYtanc</guid></item><item><title>新冠肺炎疫情重返美国和欧洲--《耶路撒冷邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiZ0FVX3lxTFBZTmw5OEdIbnVmNUlfSjhYaHFKRjhORm0wb1k0V2JXOEZfSUx1SUlWLWxTdHNFM2gtLUlhZVZkb1E4bmRXWi1LUG5oTW1LMUJVS2hxaVhBT0VXZlJkRWpFMnhUQnAydjg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="menu-title" role="button" aria-expanded="false" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;JERUSALEM POST EN ESPANOL&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span class="arrow "&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" fill="none" viewbox="0 0 16 16"&gt;&lt;path stroke="#CB133E" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" stroke-width="1.7" d="m5.335 13.333 5.333-5.334-5.333-5.333"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Jerusalem Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 22:57:41 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiZ0FVX3lxTFBZTmw5OEdIbnVmNUlfSjhYaHFKRjhORm0wb1k0V2JXOEZfSUx1SUlWLWxTdHNFM2gtLUlhZVZkb1E4bmRXWi1LUG5oTW1LMUJVS2hxaVhBT0VXZlJkRWpFMnhUQnAydjg</guid></item><item><title>天然化合物组合恢复老化的脑细胞-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMickFVX3lxTE0yN1NBMDFkckF3VzhEXzQ2a3VWbjRtelBZN1NVRmcxejctRjlFTGVaRlA5YkNrTTdrQWNESF9JZXB4dFhuQVQxRXpHcklRZ0ZjMmhzd2lDYi1sYVVGZnl0MTU1bHNjR2Y1SjFLZDI1UjdNdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;Scientists have identified a natural compound combination that reverses aging-related brain cell decline and removes harmful Alzheimer’s-linked proteins. The treatment, combining nicotinamide (vitamin B3) and the green tea antioxidant epigallocatechin gallate, restores guanosine triphosphate (GTP) levels—critical for neuronal energy and protein cleanup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In aged neurons, the restored energy boosted protein clearance, reduced oxidative stress, and reactivated key cell trafficking pathways. The findings suggest a potential non-drug strategy for combating Alzheimer’s, though more work is needed to optimize delivery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Energy Restoration:&lt;/strong&gt; Nicotinamide and green tea antioxidant revived GTP levels in aged neurons to youthful levels.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protein Clearance Boost:&lt;/strong&gt; Treatment improved the brain’s ability to remove toxic amyloid beta aggregates.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Non-Pharmaceutical Potential:&lt;/strong&gt; Findings point to a supplement-based approach for Alzheimer’s prevention or therapy.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;UC Irvine&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Researchers at the University of California, Irvine have identified a promising nonpharmaceutical treatment that rejuvenates aging brain cells and clears away the buildup of harmful proteins associated with Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a paper published recently in the journal &lt;em&gt;GeroScience&lt;/em&gt;, the UC Irvine team reports that a combination of naturally occurring compounds – nicotinamide (a form of vitamin B3) and epigallocatechin gallate (a green tea antioxidant) – can reinstate levels of guanosine triphosphate, an essential energy molecule in brain cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-112113"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-770x514.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-293x196.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience.jpg" alt="This shows neurons." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-770x514.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-293x196.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/suppliments-aging-brain-neuroscience-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;“We found that restoring energy levels helps neurons regain this critical cleanup function.” Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In tests on neurons in a dish, the treatment reversed age-related cellular deficits and improved the brain cells’ ability to clear damaging amyloid protein aggregates, an Alzheimer’s hallmark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“As people age, their brains show a decline in neuronal energy levels, which limits the ability to remove unwanted proteins and damaged components,” said lead author Gregory Brewer, adjunct professor of biomedical engineering at UC Irvine. “We found that restoring energy levels helps neurons regain this critical cleanup function.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers used a genetically encoded fluorescent sensor called GEVAL to track live guanosine triphosphate levels in neurons from aged Alzheimer’s model mice. They discovered that free GTP levels declined with age – particularly in mitochondria, the cells’ energy hubs – leading to impaired autophagy, the process by which cells eliminate damaged components.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when aged neurons were treated for just 24 hours with nicotinamide and epigallocatechin gallate, GTP levels were restored to those typically seen in younger cells.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This revival triggered a cascade of benefits: improved energy metabolism; activation of key GTPases involved in cellular trafficking, Rab7 and Arl8b; and efficient clearance of amyloid beta aggregates. Oxidative stress, another contributor to neurodegeneration, was also reduced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This study highlights GTP as a previously underappreciated energy source driving vital brain functions,” Brewer said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By supplementing the brain’s energy systems with compounds that are already available as dietary supplements, we may have a new path toward treating age-related cognitive decline and Alzheimer’s disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He cautioned, “More work is going to be required to find the best way to administer this treatment, since a recent clinical trial involving UC Irvine researchers showed that oral nicotinamide was not very effective because of inactivation in the bloodstream.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brewer’s collaborators were Ricardo Santana, a UC Irvine associate specialist in biomedical engineering, and Joshua McWhirt, a UC Irvine junior specialist who’s now a Ph.D. candidate at the Medical University of South Carolina.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Funding: &lt;/strong&gt;Funding was provided by the National Institutes of Health and the UC Irvine Foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this supplements and brain aging research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#52302230373e3e1227313b7c373627" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Brian Bell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://uci.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;UC Irvine&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Brian Bell – UC Irvine&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://dx.doi.org/10.1007/s11357-025-01786-4" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Treatment of age-related decreases in GTP levels restores endocytosis and autophagy&lt;/a&gt;” by Gregory Brewer et al. &lt;em&gt;GeroScience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Treatment of age-related decreases in GTP levels restores endocytosis and autophagy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Age-related declines in neuronal bioenergetic levels may limit vesicular trafficking and autophagic clearance of damaged organelles and proteins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Age-related ATP depletion would impact cognition dependent on ionic homeostasis, but limits on proteostasis powered by GTP are less clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We used neurons isolated from aged 3xTg-AD Alzheimer’s model mice and a novel genetically encoded fluorescent GTP sensor (GEVAL) to evaluate live GTP levels in situ.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We report an age-dependent reduction in ratiometric measurements of free/bound GTP levels in living hippocampal neurons. Free GTP colocalized in the mitochondria decreased with age accompanied by the accumulation of free GTP-labeled vesicular structures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The energy dependence of autophagy was demonstrated by depletion of GTP with rapamycin stimulation, while bafilomycin inhibition of autophagy raised GTP levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twenty-four-hour supplementation of aged neurons with the NAD precursor nicotinamide and the Nrf2 redox modulator EGCG restored GTP levels to youthful levels and mobilized endocytosis and lysosomal consumption for autophagy via the respective GTPases Rab7 and Arl8b.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This vesicular mobilization promoted the clearance of intraneuronal Aβ aggregates, improved viability, and lowered protein oxidative nitration in AD model neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our results reveal age- and AD-related neuronal GTP energy deficits that impair autophagy and endocytosis. GTP deficits were remediated by an external NAD precursor together with a Nrf2 redox modulator which suggests a translational path.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 19:53:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE0yN1NBMDFkckF3VzhEXzQ2a3VWbjRtelBZN1NVRmcxejctRjlFTGVaRlA5YkNrTTdrQWNESF9JZXB4dFhuQVQxRXpHcklRZ0ZjMmhzd2lDYi1sYVVGZnl0MTU1bHNjR2Y1SjFLZDI1UjdNdw</guid></item><item><title>口交如何导致咽喉癌，迈克尔·道格拉斯分享了他被诊断时的反应- UNILAD</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxQSnYtUmRkT3hkSnJXWWNHbks1SWZwVllVWTlibUV4dkI4YXFlMW9IeTF0ZTVUZGFLaTRhVnlQRkp6T2JwSjJ1cC1aOXZib3o1M3dTRTZ3X2pnLU96bGhrSWhQSU00a2RrVjRUemdHWWV4a3FRTmJhYUxCQV8zbS1PdWs3US05Um0wODJvVDZGQWZPeG5NVDNjc3hpakk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After Michael Douglas shared how he developed throat cancer due to acts carried out in the bedroom, a study has revealed that oral sex can actually cause tumors.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The New Jersey-born &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/celebrity"&gt;actor&lt;/a&gt; and film producer was &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/news/health/michael-douglas-throat-cancer-oral-intercourse-explained-963062-20250807"&gt;diagnosed with the devastating disease&lt;/a&gt; back in August 2010, and three years later he revealed in a bombshell interview with The Guardian that it was due to his excursions &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/sex-and-relationships"&gt;under the sheets&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The celeb told the news outlet he suffered from oral discomfort for months and made various trips to medical appointments, until a friend's &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/health"&gt;doctor&lt;/a&gt; in Montreal examined his mouth and found the glaring problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="floating-video-player_container__u4D9_"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"I will always remember the look on his face," Douglas, who is married to Catherine Zeta-Jones, said. "He said: 'We need a biopsy.' There was a walnut-size tumor at the base of my tongue that no other doctor had seen."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;What caused it was going down on his partners during sex - the &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/science"&gt;scientific&lt;/a&gt; word is 'cunnilingus'.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Michael Douglas, pictured with wife Catherine Zeta-Jones, is now cancer-free (Daniele Venturelli/Getty Images for The Red Sea International Film Festival)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"Without getting too specific, this particular cancer is caused by something called HPV [human papillomavirus], which actually comes about from cunnilingus," explained the two-time &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/oscars"&gt;Oscar-winner&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;He wasn't fibbing either, as one study published back in the naughties found strong evidence linking oral sex to the spread of human papillomavirus (HPV), which may lead to throat &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/cancer"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; in both men and women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The research identified having multiple oral sex partners as the leading sexual behavior increasing the risk of HPV-related throat cancer, even more than smoking or alcohol use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;Douglas himself had a pretty wild time in the 90s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;The study involved 100 patients newly diagnosed with the disease and showed those with prior HPV infection were 32 times more likely to develop it. Risk also rose with smoking, drinking, and having over six oral sex partners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="article-image_articleImage__eyzAn"&gt;&lt;cite class="image-credit_imageCredit__YMlqS"&gt;Throat cancer can be attributed to having multiple oral sex partners in a lifetime (Getty stock)&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;In fact, those that had more than six oral sex partners in their lifetime were 8.6 times more likely to develop HPV-linked cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;However, science information officer at Cancer research &lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" href="https://www.unilad.com/uk-news"&gt;UK&lt;/a&gt;, Dr Julie Sharp, noted that the study was rather small.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"There is conflicting evidence about the role of HPV, and this rare type of throat cancer," she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;“As this was a small study, further research is needed to confirm these observations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;"We know that after age, the main causes of mouth cancer are smoking or chewing tobacco or betel nut, and drinking too much alcohol."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="text_text__nEn66"&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you’ve been affected by any of these issues and want to speak to someone in confidence, contact the American Cancer Society on 1-800-227-2345 or via their &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a class="anchor_link__6t7IO" target="_blank" rel="noopener" href="https://www.cancer.org/about-us/online-help/contact-us.html#:~:text=Call%20us%20at%201%2D800%2D227%2D2345&amp;amp;text=Ask%20us%20how%20you%20can,patient%2Drelated%20programs%20or%20resources"&gt;&lt;em&gt;live chat feature&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;available 24/7 every day of the year.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>UNILAD</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 15:46:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxQSnYtUmRkT3hkSnJXWWNHbks1SWZwVllVWTlibUV4dkI4YXFlMW9IeTF0ZTVUZGFLaTRhVnlQRkp6T2JwSjJ1cC1aOXZib3o1M3dTRTZ3X2pnLU96bGhrSWhQSU00a2RrVjRUemdHWWV4a3FRTmJhYUxCQV8zbS1PdWs3US05Um0wODJvVDZGQWZPeG5NVDNjc3hpakk</guid></item><item><title>​从迷迭香水到口香糖： 5种令人惊讶的磨练大脑和提高记忆力的方法-印度时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikwJBVV95cUxPYUh6ZTEzQUg2d0F3c0MxSS1aa1FrVHdvUHo2WWZaUk8xdUpMVmdsRHRrNkliaVhEZk0wUVBSZkhURVQyNXNNMl9jYnJkVWV6Q1p0dFhXZEk0YnpmdGk3MzNqY0JLZVBBcF9HM1IxcGtZZ0Z5MTlrRko1WHJCd2pMalRxdFlaSUozTE5oYjBnWVAwa2g4dUNVbloxWVBjNWloYllmeU5LbldEbnZUZkZFLWRxQkhkMjlGQjRFdkJHai10NlpXbzhsWWljd1QtbzZqYUJwRjNZcURvWW9nb21CTTlWdnNJZG9lTXFNQW1PS0FwdFI0a19DYk1Ecjg5c0xUSE9jZXNwcVI1VndULTZESkxiNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="COQxt" data-ua-type="1"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;We all have those moments when we forget the purpose of us walking into that room, or spend way too much time trying to remember a name that just seems out of reach. While these moments are common, they don’t have to be permanent. Small, everyday, thoughtful changes in our daily habits can make a real difference, some of which include, rest, movement or even scent, but each remedy has the potential to support a clearer and focused mind.&lt;br&gt;Scroll down to discover memory-boosting remedies!&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:33:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikwJBVV95cUxPYUh6ZTEzQUg2d0F3c0MxSS1aa1FrVHdvUHo2WWZaUk8xdUpMVmdsRHRrNkliaVhEZk0wUVBSZkhURVQyNXNNMl9jYnJkVWV6Q1p0dFhXZEk0YnpmdGk3MzNqY0JLZVBBcF9HM1IxcGtZZ0Z5MTlrRko1WHJCd2pMalRxdFlaSUozTE5oYjBnWVAwa2g4dUNVbloxWVBjNWloYllmeU5LbldEbnZUZkZFLWRxQkhkMjlGQjRFdkJHai10NlpXbzhsWWljd1QtbzZqYUJwRjNZcURvWW9nb21CTTlWdnNJZG9lTXFNQW1PS0FwdFI0a19DYk1Ecjg5c0xUSE9jZXNwcVI1VndULTZESkxiNA</guid></item><item><title>人们正在分享卑鄙的健康威胁，这些威胁实际上正在摧毁你的身体- buzzfeed.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTFBUbFgzUlZCaDVNRU81RFVOMjU3STR3Ny1hdTFBRTdjZXpnRnlCeVowR3RhYzlmTWM1WWowQVdhQmJ6czhVcnl1NEZ0SlpKQlNxQWN0dlpvdld6R2R1UXVNSGFyNkNCNF9XV2hBdmNoNWprT2dJV1hvSnI1cUtTS00?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="subbuzz buzz-width--standard__subbuzz buzz-type--list__subbuzz subbuzz-text
  subbuzz-index-14
  
  
  
  
  " data-keywords="cleaning" data-module="subbuzz-text"&gt;
  
  &lt;p id="138917702" class="subbuzz-anchor"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;h2 class="subbuzz__header subbuzz__header--standard subbuzz__title "&gt;
    
      &lt;span class="subbuzz__number"&gt;12.&lt;/span&gt;
    

    
      &lt;span class="js-subbuzz__title-text"&gt;"&lt;a href="https://www.health.harvard.edu/heart-health/how-does-sleep-apnea-affect-the-heart" target="_blank"&gt;Sleep Apnea&lt;/a&gt;. People think it's just snoring and annoying, but it's WAY worse."&lt;/span&gt;
    
  &lt;/h2&gt;



&lt;p&gt;"When you're asleep and have obstructed breathing, your body panics a little bit, releasing a bit of adrenaline into your bloodstream to wake you up enough to breathe. With Apnea, this can happen hundreds of times a night. Adrenaline is not good for you 300 times a night. It's great if you get surprised by a wild animal and need to run away or climb a tree, but otherwise, no good for you at all. It debilitates almost every major organ and metabolic system in your body. Long-term repeated exposure can really mess you up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you even THINK you might have a problem, get it checked out."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;–&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/1l51rha/comment/mwe4b3y/?utm_source=share&amp;amp;utm_medium=web3x&amp;amp;utm_name=web3xcss&amp;amp;utm_term=1&amp;amp;utm_content=share_button" target="_blank"&gt;u/JetScreamerBaby&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>buzzfeed.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 14:31:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTFBUbFgzUlZCaDVNRU81RFVOMjU3STR3Ny1hdTFBRTdjZXpnRnlCeVowR3RhYzlmTWM1WWowQVdhQmJ6czhVcnl1NEZ0SlpKQlNxQWN0dlpvdld6R2R1UXVNSGFyNkNCNF9XV2hBdmNoNWprT2dJV1hvSnI1cUtTS00</guid></item><item><title>为什么一些80岁的人有50岁的记忆-神经科学新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMic0FVX3lxTE1tM0dyWExBbG9BaDJ6emhZNFB4NXU4eG1KMGVPR3pMRXRxdjdPVV96WWM1QTJBYmpnT3VsZlBYMzR2YXpqNE5yWFl3NEtmWlc2Z3NibHUwcEluVkhVeDNoTjl5YzR5aS1lVm1VZWhkUkVTV3M?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content body-color clearfix link-color-wrap"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary: &lt;/strong&gt;For 25 years, scientists have studied “SuperAgers”—people aged 80 and above whose memory rivals those decades younger. Research reveals that their brains either resist Alzheimer’s-related plaques and tangles or remain resilient despite having them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These individuals maintain a youthful brain structure, with a thicker cortex and unique neurons linked to memory and social skills. Insights from their biology and behavior could inspire new strategies to protect cognitive health into late life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Facts&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exceptional Memory:&lt;/strong&gt; SuperAgers score like 50–60-year-olds on memory tests despite being 80+.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain Structure:&lt;/strong&gt; They have thicker cortex regions and unique neurons linked to social and memory functions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cognitive Protection:&lt;/strong&gt; Resistance or resilience to Alzheimer’s pathology helps preserve function.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;Northwestern University&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For 25 years, scientists at Northwestern Medicine have been studying individuals aged 80 and older — dubbed “SuperAgers” — to better understand what makes them tick. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These unique individuals, who show outstanding memory performance at a level consistent with individuals who are at least three decades younger, challenge the long-held belief that cognitive decline is an inevitable part of aging. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="wp-block-image size-full"&gt;&lt;picture fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="wp-image-112100"&gt; &lt;source type="image/webp" srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne.jpg.webp 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-300x200.jpg.webp 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-770x513.jpg.webp 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-1155x770.jpg.webp 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-370x247.jpg.webp 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-293x195.jpg.webp 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-150x100.jpg.webp 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" src="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne.jpg" alt="This shows an older woman and a brain." srcset="https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne.jpg 1200w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-300x200.jpg 300w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-770x513.jpg 770w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-1155x770.jpg 1155w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-370x247.jpg 370w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-293x195.jpg 293w, https://neurosciencenews.com/files/2025/08/superagers-memory-neuroscicne-150x100.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 1200px) 100vw, 1200px"&gt; &lt;/picture&gt;&lt;figcaption class="wp-element-caption"&gt;SuperAgers score at least 9 out of 15 on a delayed word recall test — on par with individuals in their 50s and 60s. Credit: Neuroscience News&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the quarter-century of research, the scientists have seen some notable lifestyle and personality differences between SuperAgers and those aging typically — such as being social and gregarious — but “it’s really what we’ve found in their brains that’s been so earth-shattering for us,” said Dr. Sandra Weintraub, a professor of psychiatry and behavioral sciences and neurology at Northwestern University Feinberg School of Medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By identifying biological and behavioral traits associated with SuperAging, the scientists hope to uncover new strategies to promote cognitive resilience and delay or prevent Alzheimer’s and other diseases that cause cognitive decline and dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our findings show that exceptional memory in old age is not only possible but is linked to a distinct neurobiological profile. This opens the door to new interventions aimed at preserving brain health well into the later decades of life,” said Weintraub, corresponding author of a new paper summarizing the findings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper will be published in a perspective piece in Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia: The Journal of the Alzheimer’s Association as part of the journal’s special issue commemorating the 40th anniversary of the National Institute on Aging’s Alzheimer’s Disease Centers Program and the 25th anniversary of the National Alzheimer Coordinating Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SuperAger brains are resilient, resistant &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term “SuperAger” was coined by Dr. M. Marsel Mesulam, who founded the Mesulam Center for Cognitive Neurology and Alzheimer’s Disease at Northwestern in the late 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since 2000, a cohort of 290 SuperAger participants has passed through the Mesulam Center’s doors, and the scientists have autopsied 77 donated SuperAger brains. Some of the brains contained amyloid and tau proteins (also known as plaques and tangles), which are known to play key roles in the progression of Alzheimer’s disease, but others didn’t develop any. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What we realized is there are two mechanisms that lead someone to become a SuperAger,” Weintraub said. “One is resistance: they don’t make the plaques and tangles. Two is resilience: they make them, but they don’t do anything to their brains.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;key findings:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="wp-block-list"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Exceptional memory performance:&lt;/strong&gt; SuperAgers score at least 9 out of 15 on a delayed word recall test — on par with individuals in their 50s and 60s.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Youthful brain structure:&lt;/strong&gt; Unlike typically aging brains, SuperAgers show no significant thinning of their cortex — the outer layer of the brain — and even have a thicker anterior cingulate cortex than younger adults. This crucial region of the brain plays a significant role in integrating information related to decision-making, emotion and motivation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unique cellular traits:&lt;/strong&gt; SuperAgers have more von economo neurons, which are specialized cells linked to social behavior, and larger entorhinal neurons, which are critical for memory, than their typically aging peers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sociability as a common trait:&lt;/strong&gt; Despite having diverse lifestyles and varying approaches to exercise, SuperAgers tend to be highly social and report strong interpersonal relationships.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;‘&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brain donation can offer scientific immortality’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the Mesulam Center, SuperAgers are evaluated annually and may choose to donate their brains for post-mortem evaluation by Northwestern scientists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Many of the findings from this paper stem from the examination of brain specimens of generous, dedicated SuperAgers who were followed for decades,” said co-author Dr. Tamar Gefen, associate professor of psychiatry and behavioral sciences at Feinberg, director of Feinberg’s Laboratory for Translational Neuropsychology and a neuropsychologist at the Mesulam Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I am constantly amazed by how brain donation can enable discovery long after death, offering a kind of scientific immortality.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.brain.northwestern.edu/join/SuperAging.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Learn more about how to join the SuperAger research registry&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The perspective piece is titled, “The First 25 Years of the Northwestern SuperAging Program.” Other Northwestern authors include Dr. Mesulam and Changiz Geula, research professor of cell and developmental biology and neuroscience at Feinberg and a member of the Mesulam Center. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading"&gt;About this aging and memory research news&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Author: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#78130b19150d1d140b17163816170a0c100f1d0b0c1d0a16561d1c0d" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Kristin Samuelson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Source: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://northwestern.edu" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Northwestern University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact: &lt;/strong&gt;Kristin Samuelson – Northwestern University&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Image: &lt;/strong&gt;The image is credited to Neuroscience News&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="has-background"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Original Research: &lt;/strong&gt;Open access.&lt;br&gt;“&lt;a href="https://alz-journals.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/alz.70312" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The First 25 Years of the Northwestern SuperAging Program&lt;/a&gt;” by Sandra Weintraub et al. &lt;em&gt;Alzheimer’s &amp;amp; Dementia&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;hr class="wp-block-separator has-text-color has-pale-cyan-blue-color has-alpha-channel-opacity has-pale-cyan-blue-background-color has-background"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Abstract&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The First 25 Years of the Northwestern SuperAging Program&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During late life, “average” does not mean “intact.” For example, cross-sectional data from a common word list learning test show that average delayed word recall raw score at age 80 (5/15) is approximately half that at age 56 to 66 (9/15).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cognitive and neurobiological dissolution is therefore implicitly incorporated into concepts of the aging brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This position is being challenged through investigations on “superaging,” a term that was coined at the Northwestern Alzheimer’s Disease Research Center (ADRC) to define persons ≥ 80 years with delayed word recall raw scores &lt;em&gt;at least equal&lt;/em&gt; to those of individuals 20 to 30 years younger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the first 25 years of this program we established that superagers constitute not only a neuropsychological but also a neurobiological phenotype distinctive from cognitively average age peers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With respect to brain structure, superagers have cortical volumes no different than neurotypical adults 20 to 30 years younger in contrast to neurotypical peers who do show such age-related shrinkage; they also have a region in the cingulate gyrus that is thicker than younger neurotypical adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With respect to cellular biology, superagers have fewer Alzheimer’s disease–type changes in the brain, greater size of entorhinal neurons, fewer inflammatory microglia in white matter, better preserved cholinergic innervation, and a greater density of evolutionarily progressive von Economo neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the future, deeper characterization of the superaging phenotype may lead to interventions that enhance resistance and resilience to involutional changes considered part of average (i.e., “normal”) brain aging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This line of work is helping to revise common misperceptions about the cognitive potential of senescence and has inspired investigations throughout the United States and abroad.&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Neuroscience News</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMic0FVX3lxTE1tM0dyWExBbG9BaDJ6emhZNFB4NXU4eG1KMGVPR3pMRXRxdjdPVV96WWM1QTJBYmpnT3VsZlBYMzR2YXpqNE5yWFl3NEtmWlc2Z3NibHUwcEluVkhVeDNoTjl5YzR5aS1lVm1VZWhkUkVTV3M</guid></item><item><title>罕见的西澳大利亚州疟疾病例促使进一步研究该地区的蚊子-西雅图时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxQbDBqNlh3ckdOUjRBNUZTNnZVcF9QMnhYdkpqM1Y3dWVGQy1yWnJZQmZwdUx0UjdUNHZLMnJKdzQwLXRJcnU4RnRSMVRBa1dFakRwbm5USDMzVmhsRGt6dF9YZWdqaUdEXzllNnRxQTZEWlZ3c2ZWTS1EanlXUi1FS3h3OS02YzI5Zjh1VEV4dVhTRHIwUE4yYWowZUFQdkQzSlN1anNfcmJxeGZRR2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-content" class="article-content entry-content"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Local health officials are still investigating how a Pierce County woman who hadn’t traveled recently &lt;a href="https://www.seattletimes.com/seattle-news/health/malaria-possibly-contracted-in-wa-would-be-states-first-case/" class="content-link"&gt;might have contracted malaria&lt;/a&gt; — but however it happened, the situation involved an “unusual sequence of events.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The case is rare for a few reasons, said Dr. James Miller, health officer of the Tacoma-Pierce County Health Department, which &lt;a href="https://tpchd.org/news/we-are-investigating-possible-locally-acquired-case-of-malaria/" target="_blank" class="content-link external"&gt;announced the news &lt;/a&gt;Wednesday. It’s Washington state’s first locally acquired case, meaning the woman was most likely bitten here by a malaria-infected mosquito, which would have gotten malaria after biting someone else with the disease, who had traveled recently and perhaps contracted malaria abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If that were the case, it would be a “very unusual sequence of events” Miller said, “which is why we’re doing this more extensive investigation for this case than we would typically for a travel-acquired malaria case.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mosquito-borne disease does not spread from person to person, nor does it spread between mosquitoes, so risk to the general public is low, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The patient is receiving treatment, Miller said, but declined to give more details about her condition. He noted it’s common for people with malaria to be hospitalized, as the disease can cause very serious infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chance of the malaria-infected mosquito biting another person in the county is “pretty low,” Miller reiterated. “But of course, malaria is a serious disease. That’s why we’re taking this seriously and doing a full investigation.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The investigation includes, in the meantime, a plan to work with the state Department of Health to set up mosquito traps all over the county and collect data from them. It’s unlikely they’ll find the malaria-infected mosquito that bit the Pierce County patient, Miller acknowledged, but the data is useful in gauging how many other mosquitoes might be carrying the malaria parasite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The main purpose is really just to get a sense of … the burden for the population of Anopheles mosquitoes, which is the set of species that can transmit malaria,” Miller said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of the investigation also looks at other patients in Washington recently diagnosed with malaria, to see if there could be any potential connections, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the United States, malaria cases are usually linked to travel, mainly from sub-Saharan African countries, and regions of South America and Southeast Asia, &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/malaria/prevention/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link external"&gt;according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;/a&gt;. Anopheles mosquitoes, which are in Pierce County and Washington, can transmit malaria across the U.S. if they bite someone infected with the disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U.S. sees about 2,000 to 2,500 cases per year, and &lt;a href="https://doh.wa.gov/public-health-provider-resources/notifiable-conditions/malaria" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link external"&gt;Washington sees 20 to 70 reports of malaria&lt;/a&gt; in travelers each year, according to the state Department of Health. In 2023, the U.S. saw its first locally acquired malaria case in 20 years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ten cases were reported across four states — &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/volumes/73/wr/mm7342a2.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link external"&gt;Florida, Texas, Maryland and Arkansas&lt;/a&gt; — from May to October 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So far this year, 19 cases of travel-associated malaria have been reported in Washington state, according to DOH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, Miller said, mosquito populations are starting to shrink in Pierce County and throughout the state at this point in the year. Mosquitoes like warm weather and being near water to breed, so they prefer early summer, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When temperatures fall, populations also decline, Miller said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="userMessagingInset" class="user-messaging animate"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, people should try to take basic precautions to avoid getting bit, he said, including: wearing bug spray, removing standing water in yards and considering long pants or long sleeves if in a place there are mosquitoes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And if traveling to a &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/yellow-book/hcp/preparing-international-travelers/yellow-fever-vaccine-and-malaria-prevention-information-by-country.html" target="_blank" class="content-link external"&gt;country where there’s risk of malaria&lt;/a&gt;, think about precautionary measures such as taking medication before, during and after your trip.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The disease typically causes fever, chills, body aches, headaches and fatigue. Without treatment, it &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/malaria/php/surveillance-report/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link external"&gt;can be fatal&lt;/a&gt;, Miller said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If people recognize these symptoms or suspect malaria, health officials recommend seeking early testing and treatment. The disease can be treated with antimalarial drugs. &lt;/p&gt;    &lt;p id="userMessagingIn-story"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        
  &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxQbDBqNlh3ckdOUjRBNUZTNnZVcF9QMnhYdkpqM1Y3dWVGQy1yWnJZQmZwdUx0UjdUNHZLMnJKdzQwLXRJcnU4RnRSMVRBa1dFakRwbm5USDMzVmhsRGt6dF9YZWdqaUdEXzllNnRxQTZEWlZ3c2ZWTS1EanlXUi1FS3h3OS02YzI5Zjh1VEV4dVhTRHIwUE4yYWowZUFQdkQzSlN1anNfcmJxeGZRR2c</guid></item><item><title>人民药店：疱疹病毒与阿尔茨海默病之间有联系吗？ - OregonLive.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixgFBVV95cUxQb3lLVFloYWJMa3lMNHkzdW9pdllNaGxod3lGOC0wRE9Db19YTEU3YkJHaVhrMklDYjU0OHZOVGx0dWF3Ry03emlsUkZpUFpTUTAyUWJMWFVoMEhaOURvUVoyRzNTQk1KVmpObjNxUk90amVXT3ZaTEN2Q1FyWk9CZFE5b3pXcWtoNDRVUFVrMnBwb19Gc1h2WGVWWXV3Ni1sbzVBazdpY0VXUFRSSFVnT1J2clF5eWJwa25HeFVzcHIxNk1pTHfSAdoBQVVfeXFMTmJqeTdpY1RVVERZNVZoVTJDNmZXb0J4ZzRrQlNpUmdJNklDU0dsd2c0SjNoa1JVUWhQX1JMTVU1Nk1wdTJMVV9hOTI0UXZmdnBqLUVkd1BqZ1RNcTkwblZsRTh2Rk5EM3lNLWFsU0pZZTZmZURaY2tPdjJHZUszalVTZFc4RnEzb3doRnFMU2JfRE1hSGhvRjBMYTIwRHcxVkRmS1NZektXb1IzTTlYLV9fb3V4MXJaaDUtc053UF90X0hITVNvZVphRmoxdDdjTkJKTDNBbmVCVEE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="BWVOY24CQBDELDXQ6NXPISPPEE"&gt;Q. I had chicken pox as a child and shingles as an adult. I have gotten the Shingrix vaccine. For an occasional cold sore, I use acyclovir, but I take L-lysine daily for prevention. Has anyone studied this as an alternative prevention against Alzheimer’s disease?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="62FT2YPZYVEHRC4PRRPGRQDXWE"&gt;As I understand it, the herpes virus might be a contributing factor. Since L-lysine is available without a prescription in the U.S., it could be an alternative to antiviral drugs for many people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HYX7NPUHSFHXPMOCDNSVHZZHSA"&gt;A. The link between herpes virus infection and AD is tantalizing, but it has not yet been firmly established. What we know about L-lysine is that it can help reduce outbreaks of cold sores due to herpes (Viruses, June 2, 2023). According to the scientists, the effective dose of this dietary supplement is at least 1 gram per day. We found no studies of L-lysine being used to prevent AD.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5EVWBTU5L5ACFHWUICHCFAIOQA"&gt;L-lysine is an essential amino acid. Another amino acid, arginine, counteracts the antiviral action of lysine. As a result, L-lysine appears to be more effective if people reduce their intake of arginine from sources such as legumes, nuts and meat like turkey, chicken or pork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RM2L4IZXVRE6DPNYFRZIXB76AI"&gt;It was smart of you to get vaccinated against shingles. The varicella zoster virus that causes both chicken pox and shingles has also been implicated in AD. Studies in Wales and Australia indicate that older people vaccinated against shingles are less likely to develop AD than their neighbors who were not vaccinated (Nature, April 2, 2025; JAMA, April 23, 2025). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM" data-fusion-component="FGETUJH3HVFI7MSM2JXJU3CXBM"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AW27S6DSHFCL3LRTWJSJCAN7NU"&gt;Q. I have read that there is now an epinephrine nasal spray called neffy for severe allergic reactions or even anaphylaxis. It requires a prescription and is pricey. Why not use over-the-counter Primatene Mist instead? It’s far less expensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DEXAM7NQ3FFRXIKIYALXO7OUXI"&gt;A. Anaphylaxis is a life-threatening allergic reaction. It must always be treated as a medical emergency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="HWGBRUAKGFH6XLTVQMY3I7NX5Q"&gt;Epinephrine auto-injectors such as EpiPen or Adrenaclick deliver a specified dose of epinephrine immediately into the bloodstream. German scientists studied Primatene Mist to see if it could be used as a substitute treatment for anaphylaxis and found it is not suitable (Journal der Deutschen Dermatologischen Gesellschaft, May 2009). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JF7WMR57UVAULCBW4SMLVD74DY"&gt;On the other hand, neffy was developed specifically to immediately provide an appropriate dose of epinephrine. Experimenting with a money-saving alternative may not be wise when the outcome could be death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JV6MCHOH2VEWXPLJQLBNMTAT4M"&gt;&lt;i&gt;In their column, Joe and Teresa Graedon answer letters from readers. Write to them in care of King Features, 628 Virginia Drive, Orlando, FL 32803, or email them via their website: www.PeoplesPharmacy.com. Their newest book is “Top Screwups Doctors Make and How to Avoid Them.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>OregonLive.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixgFBVV95cUxQb3lLVFloYWJMa3lMNHkzdW9pdllNaGxod3lGOC0wRE9Db19YTEU3YkJHaVhrMklDYjU0OHZOVGx0dWF3Ry03emlsUkZpUFpTUTAyUWJMWFVoMEhaOURvUVoyRzNTQk1KVmpObjNxUk90amVXT3ZaTEN2Q1FyWk9CZFE5b3pXcWtoNDRVUFVrMnBwb19Gc1h2WGVWWXV3Ni1sbzVBazdpY0VXUFRSSFVnT1J2clF5eWJwa25HeFVzcHIxNk1pTHfSAdoBQVVfeXFMTmJqeTdpY1RVVERZNVZoVTJDNmZXb0J4ZzRrQlNpUmdJNklDU0dsd2c0SjNoa1JVUWhQX1JMTVU1Nk1wdTJMVV9hOTI0UXZmdnBqLUVkd1BqZ1RNcTkwblZsRTh2Rk5EM3lNLWFsU0pZZTZmZURaY2tPdjJHZUszalVTZFc4RnEzb3doRnFMU2JfRE1hSGhvRjBMYTIwRHcxVkRmS1NZektXb1IzTTlYLV9fb3V4MXJaaDUtc053UF90X0hITVNvZVphRmoxdDdjTkJKTDNBbmVCVEE</guid></item><item><title>肺科医生揭示了有助于改善睡眠质量的5个习惯：更换枕套，不含咖啡因等|健康-印度斯坦时报-印度斯坦时报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgJBVV95cUxQSHlJbW5NZ3gzZjdFcXlxaGtzc05ZTF9vLTVPLU5kdDNjMHd2LUJ2UGNVQlZidl9maWhrTnFzYU5PZG5OOXAwcDMwX3ZwQkFKX0tkSENRSTNyMWNEbUU5RHhqS2VPck1tWGk1OEpRN1pZbzU1YWwyQWlOb0N3YlNCVjlHSG9jZWhUMUVsdE1UUmRQbFBBdk9tcl9aU2t5R3h5a3JLb2FjM19EdnBUempKeS1LZE5kUy15anFYdkplWlB6ZzkzWmtYLUxDTzRoWjVjS3JzRnZHM0ZrSEc3LVV3WW54VHlOVGM5bFIxTlNkaVkyUGtfY3dLaXk1MEFtWkVIYnlMNWFn0gGLAkFVX3lxTE9kQl9KdVJyeElYRzdWc29kSDVtSzZYaHFMMWNuT25vRzJOUDgwNjFZMXcwOTlSQlZuaHN5U2ZWVlFQS1BSQ1lyM1JKWjJCT3RMMktXZ3RidU5sSWFQR2hveThNMTJCaHJGVHhtY2xhRFc5Rnc1LVd5MUNaTjZzS1lLSExGS0tVdW9ZdGtQNlA5Uk5uSllRMHlGMTRhaF84eGd5S1RDdkhQTXM1WnRJeUt2cnVQd045NzFvRnliYnFPVUJmZTdZUE9VS0E5WDQ1Nkc4OW9hNHVtMlRzdEdlMkpfbGVPYzR5Z3JMSTd5OHZURFAyQ3VqQ3U3cHVtT2lqb0t6YWJZNTRQSWJoRQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="storyMainDiv" class="fullStory tfStory current videoStory story__detail storyAf101754740980914 " data-vars-storyid="101754740980914" data-story-section="lifestyle" data-story-subsection="health" data-vars-author="Adrija Dey" data-premium-story="false" data-performance-type="not-set"&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoTopPageBanner dHide"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="stickyCard"&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;h1 class="hdg1"&gt;Pulmonologist reveals 5 habits that help improve sleep quality: Change pillow cover, no caffeine and more&lt;/h1&gt;  &lt;div class="actionDiv flexElm topTime"&gt; &lt;p class="dateTime secTime storyPage"&gt;Updated on: Aug 09, 2025 06:28 pm IST &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="googleFollow mHide"&gt; &lt;button class="htEchoShareBarDesk"&gt;&lt;/button&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;h2 class="sortDec"&gt;It’s not just about the number of hours, you also need good quality sleep. If your sleep is light, know the essential habits that help get better quality sleep.&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;div class="storyDetails taboola-readmore"&gt; &lt;div class="detail " dataid="/lifestyle/health/pulmonologist-reveals-5-habits-that-help-improve-sleep-quality-change-pillow-cover-no-caffeine-heavy-meals-101754740980914.html"&gt; &lt;div class="storyParagraphFigure"&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/mind-still-buzzing-late-at-night-and-can-t-sleep-try-these-5-yoga-poses-to-help-you-unwind-and-relax-before-bed-101754576315548.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Sleep"&gt;Sleep&lt;/a&gt; is restorative for overall wellbeing, acting as the bedrock for good health. But when sleep gets compromised, the ripple effects can be felt throughout the body and mind. This is where your habits leading up to bedtime count. Sleep is more than just clocking in the recommended eight hours; the quality also matters, substantially.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;figure class=""&gt; &lt;span class=""&gt; &lt;picture&gt; &lt;source media="(max-width:767px)" srcset="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/09/550x309/sleep_1754741870752_1754741870898.jpg" alt="A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that " title="A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that "&gt;&lt;/source&gt; &lt;img src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/09/550x309/sleep_1754741870752_1754741870898.jpg" alt="A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that " title="A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that "&gt; &lt;/picture&gt; &lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;A good and comfotable sleep necessitates cummulative of habits that&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p id="readMoreFTUser"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Despite getting the recommended hours of sleep, if you are still tossing and turning, changing sides, flipping pillows to the cold side, or counting sheep to fall asleep, then the quality of sleep may be poor. Let's take a closer look at what may help you sleep better.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt-10 mb-10 htEchoRecirculationWidget"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="mt10 mb10 htEchoArticlePromo"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="predictorShow mb20" data-vars-predictor="true" data-vars-quiz="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="quizShow mb20" data-vars-minimized="false" data-vars-predictor="true"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ALSO READ: &lt;a class="backlink" target="_blank" href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health/pumpkin-seeds-for-better-sleep-a-complete-guide-to-their-nutritional-value-and-how-to-add-to-your-diet-101740382726632.html" data-vars-page-type="story" data-vars-link-type="Manual" data-vars-anchor-text="Pumpkin seeds for better sleep: A complete guide to their nutritional value and how to add to your diet"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pumpkin seeds for better sleep: A complete guide to their nutritional value and how to add to your diet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Waseem Ud Din, Consultant Pulmonologist at Ujala Cygnus Group of Hospitals, told HT Lifestyle about the value of sleep hygiene. He elaborated, “Sleep hygiene refers to the daily habits and environment that support deep, restorative sleep. It’s not just about getting eight hours, it’s about setting up your body and mind to sleep well. When sleep suffers, everything from focus and mood to immunity can take a hit.” Certain habits help in preparing the body and mind to achieve deep, restorative sleep.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dr Waseem shared 5 habits that you need to make a note of if you are seeking deep sleep:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;1. Regularly changing pillow covers and bedsheets&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/09/original/pillow_1754742980992.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Change your pillow cover to reduce skin discomfort.(Shutterstock)" title="Change your pillow cover to reduce skin discomfort.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Change your pillow cover to reduce skin discomfort.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clean your pillow cover and bedsheets every week to prevent the buildup of dust, sweat, and allergens.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;These irritants can lead to skin discomfort and sinus problems that interrupt your sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keeping your bedding fresh not only feels better but also helps create a healthier sleep environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;2. Go to bed and wake up at same time&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Go to bed and wake up at the same time every day, including weekends.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This consistent routine helps regulate your body’s internal clock and improves the quality of your sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;3. No screen before bed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Blue light from phones, tablets, and TVs can disrupt melatonin production, making it harder to fall asleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Turn off screens at least one hour before going to bed.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;4. Turn your bedroom dark&lt;/h2&gt;  &lt;figure class="inlineIMG"&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;img data-src="https://www.hindustantimes.com/ht-img/img/2025/08/09/original/dark_bedd_1754743127930.jpg" class="lazy" src="https://images.hindustantimes.com/default/550x309.jpg" alt="Turn your bedroom dark for restful sleep.(Shutterstock)" title="Turn your bedroom dark for restful sleep.(Shutterstock)"&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;figcaption&gt;Turn your bedroom dark for restful sleep.(Shutterstock)&lt;/figcaption&gt; &lt;/figure&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Keep your bedroom dark, cool, quiet, and clutter-free.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Using blackout curtains or white noise machines can further promote restful sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;5. Avoid caffeine or heavy meals before bed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Caffeine can stay in your system for hours.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Heavy food may cause gut discomfort that disrupts sleep.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Opt for lighter meals earlier in the evening.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Note to readers: This article is for informational purposes only and not a substitute for professional medical advice. Always seek the advice of your doctor with any questions about a medical condition.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;    &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="recommendedSliderContextual" id="recommendedSliderContextual-101754740980914" data-vars-story_id="101754740980914" data-vars-story_section="lifestyle" data-vars-author="Adrija Dey" data-vars-story_headline="Pulmonologist reveals 5 habits that help improve sleep quality: Change pillow cover, no caffeine and more"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;input type="checkbox" class="trendTopsSHow" id="trendTopsSHow-101754740980914"&gt; &lt;div class="trendTops"&gt;  &lt;div class="trendInlineSeo"&gt;&lt;p&gt; Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;label class="moreBtn1" for="trendTopsSHow-101754740980914"&gt;&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="followHT trendSeo__1"&gt; &lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="htEchoEOALite"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;div class="bottomSeoParaEcho1"&gt; &lt;div id="bottomSeoParaEcho"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch every big hit, every wicket with Crick-it, a one stop destination for Live Scores, Match Stats, Quizzes, Polls &amp;amp; much more. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cricket?utm_source=endofarticle&amp;amp;utm_medium=web&amp;amp;utm_campaign=crickitlaunch"&gt;Explore now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catch your daily dose of &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/fashion"&gt;Fashion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/entertainment/music/taylor-swift"&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/festivals"&gt;Festivals&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/travel"&gt;Travel&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/relationships"&gt;Relationship&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt;, &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/recipe"&gt;Recipe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; and all the other Latest &lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle News&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p&gt; on Hindustan Times Website and APPs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;div class="mb5 mt5" id="bottomBreadCrumb"&gt; &lt;div class="breadcrumbs"&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Home_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/" data-vars-event-cta="News"&gt;News&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Lifestyle_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle" data-vars-event-cta="Lifestyle"&gt;Lifestyle&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt; &lt;a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/lifestyle/health" class="breadcrumbclick" data-vars-event-label="Health_clicked" data-vars-event-action="/lifestyle/health" data-vars-event-cta="Health"&gt;Health&lt;/a&gt; &lt;span&gt;/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt; Pulmonologist reveals 5 habits that help improve sleep quality: Change pillow cover, no caffeine and more &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="bottomSeoParaEcho pb0"&gt; &lt;label class="moreBtn" for="trendTopsSHow-101754740980914" id="spanSeeLessEcho"&gt;See Less&lt;/label&gt; &lt;/p&gt;  &lt;/div&gt;   &lt;p class="relatedStoryCricket"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="saranyuPlayer" id="saranyu-player"&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p class="relatedStory2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="us-ad align-center mb10 mt10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="htEchoShortsEntryPoint" data-size="enlarged"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p class="affiliate-shop-now" id="affiliate-shop-now"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Hindustan Times</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:58:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgJBVV95cUxQSHlJbW5NZ3gzZjdFcXlxaGtzc05ZTF9vLTVPLU5kdDNjMHd2LUJ2UGNVQlZidl9maWhrTnFzYU5PZG5OOXAwcDMwX3ZwQkFKX0tkSENRSTNyMWNEbUU5RHhqS2VPck1tWGk1OEpRN1pZbzU1YWwyQWlOb0N3YlNCVjlHSG9jZWhUMUVsdE1UUmRQbFBBdk9tcl9aU2t5R3h5a3JLb2FjM19EdnBUempKeS1LZE5kUy15anFYdkplWlB6ZzkzWmtYLUxDTzRoWjVjS3JzRnZHM0ZrSEc3LVV3WW54VHlOVGM5bFIxTlNkaVkyUGtfY3dLaXk1MEFtWkVIYnlMNWFn0gGLAkFVX3lxTE9kQl9KdVJyeElYRzdWc29kSDVtSzZYaHFMMWNuT25vRzJOUDgwNjFZMXcwOTlSQlZuaHN5U2ZWVlFQS1BSQ1lyM1JKWjJCT3RMMktXZ3RidU5sSWFQR2hveThNMTJCaHJGVHhtY2xhRFc5Rnc1LVd5MUNaTjZzS1lLSExGS0tVdW9ZdGtQNlA5Uk5uSllRMHlGMTRhaF84eGd5S1RDdkhQTXM1WnRJeUt2cnVQd045NzFvRnliYnFPVUJmZTdZUE9VS0E5WDQ1Nkc4OW9hNHVtMlRzdEdlMkpfbGVPYzR5Z3JMSTd5OHZURFAyQ3VqQ3U3cHVtT2lqb0t6YWJZNTRQSWJoRQ</guid></item><item><title>您的户外空气质量监视器可以为每个人带来更安全的空气-有线</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTFBTM1BobURDOFE4c2VyN2JCV1BMZDBXYnB5YTdkN3JLNUFUYTc4ZW9uREZkTVd5M1E2aXN6UGFnWW8tREM0SzhRMHJYSkFYV1FWYUxBc191SVJ1bEhXSEhGX3VJSmZ4emdpTGRDd0xGWHZFclhhVnp0bFpob3U?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class="lead-in-text-callout"&gt;It wasn’t that&lt;/span&gt; long ago that few people were monitoring the air—not the government, not its citizens. Today, weather apps provide estimates of outdoor air quality, and the government’s own air quality monitoring website, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.airnow.gov/how-to-use-this-site/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.airnow.gov/how-to-use-this-site/"}' href="https://www.airnow.gov/how-to-use-this-site/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;AirNow&lt;/a&gt;, has an easy-to-use zip code portal and &lt;a data-offer-url="https://fire.airnow.gov/#6/41/-98" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://fire.airnow.gov/#6/41/-98"}' href="https://fire.airnow.gov/#6/41/-98" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;fire and smoke map&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;There are real health benefits to owning an &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-indoor-air-quality-monitors/#:~:text=Purifier%20for%20You-,Best%20Indoor%2DOutdoor%20Option,-PHOTOGRAPH%3A%20KAT%20MERCK"&gt;air quality monitor&lt;/a&gt;. Each US state is responsible for developing its own monitoring &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/amtic/state-monitoring-agency-annual-air-monitoring-plans-and-network-assessments"&gt;plan&lt;/a&gt;. Even in densely populated urban areas, outdoor air monitors owned by federal, state, and local jurisdictions might be geographically spread out, leaving monitoring gaps that don't accurately capture the air quality beyond one’s front door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="AssetEmbedWrapper-fkZDUs kHRAYC asset-embed"&gt;&lt;p class="CaptionWrapper-jYrTxZ bkfwbX caption AssetEmbedCaption-fyuOdR eXMqGf asset-embed__caption" data-testid="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE CaptionCredit-eowWKH deqABF kpqIso kpuElq caption__credit"&gt;Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Outdoor air quality monitors are not just for understanding the air quality when the odor of smoke fills your home—an outdoor monitor can keep you informed. America has been in the air quality monitoring business for less than a century. In the not-so-distant past, citizens died due to unregulated and unchecked air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="Container-VgtPr ekoLDG"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Once more, Trump’s EPA is seeking to weaken current A&lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/"}' href="https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;ir Quality Index&lt;/a&gt; standards, the numbers that decide what is good, moderate, or unhealthy air, along with repealing the regulations on emissions of greenhouse gases. Those actions will lead to dirtier air and less reliable data. Like &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/story/best-disposable-face-masks-n95-kn95-kf94-surgical/"&gt;face masks&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.wired.com/gallery/best-air-purifiers/"&gt;air purifiers&lt;/a&gt;, an outdoor air quality monitor is no longer a niche appliance but an electronic canary in the modern coal mine of a bad-air world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="feature-large-callout" class="CalloutFeatureLargeWrapper-cAQNly bLNMaC"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardBody-hIYvDT cYxZHF product-embed" data-item='{"ctaHref":"https://cna.st/p/8uvTiuNRgn5tyRjNWiSy546tbR1Y8S6C9LTLxtHtcGyQeGaAh8S5PTWd9VconBL363nQVWYpRsmQXdXowPR3UJ7KpfBtsvn4ynkrcRMZ84y4QaxAxqSziRF8idi1dt6FzoRd6LAHxwGcJhA7ZAT5ATcHSF9tRbyhUXMLbxUUR4ygMQKd2B7odDc45QcGJTiJLBSFrgkLhQNALAP6Dhz6aSmNohd5avRw27Md7a7mve8RACQFwBLokgZJD4","dangerousDek":"","productBrand":"PurpleAir","dangerousHed":"Zen","embedSize":"feature-medium","isFirstProduct":true,"image":{"altText":"Purple Air Zen, a white air quality monitor with glowing green ring light around the edge, sitting outside on a windowsill beside potted plants","credit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","sources":{"sm":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":720,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_720,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_120,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_240,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_320,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_640,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 640w"},"md":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":720,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_720,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_120,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_240,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_320,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_640,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 640w"},"lg":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":748,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_748,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_120,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_240,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_320,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_640,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 640w"},"xl":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":748,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_748,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_120,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_240,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_320,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/67ec4890bfa28313e182e550/4:3/w_640,c_limit/PurpleAir-Zen-Air-Quality-Monitor-Reviewer-Photo-SOURCE-Kat-Merck.-(no-border).jpg 640w"}}},"isSponsored":false,"offerRetailer":"Purpleair","offerUrl":"https://www2.purpleair.com/products/purpleair-zen","contentType":"product","productId":"677fe3511de8aa366d74938b","showOfferUrl":false,"showPriceOnButton":true,"showAffiliateDisclaimerOnFirstProduct":false,"dangerousCredit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","showLocalisedOffers":true,"isUpcEnabled":true,"showClampedProductDescription":true,"productDescriptionLineLength":5,"hasReadMoreFeature":false,"index":1,"hasAffiliateLinkDisabled":false,"isMobileView":false,"hasMultipleImageSupport":true,"showImageCreditText":true,"showMultipleImageCount":4,"hasProsConsFeature":false,"hasRatingFeature":false,"pros":[],"cons":[],"rating":"","shouldUseAmazonPrimeDayLiveAPIData":true,"id":"677fe3511de8aa366d74938b","brand":{"name":"PurpleAir"},"offers":[{"offerUrl":"https://www2.purpleair.com/products/purpleair-zen","price":"$299","currency":"USD","purchaseUri":"https://cna.st/p/8uvTiuNRgn5tyRjNWiSy546tbR1Y8S6C9LTLxtHtcGyQeGaAh8S5PTWd9VconBL363nQVWYpRsmQXdXowPR3UJ7KpfBtsvn4ynkrcRMZ84y4QaxAxqSziRF8idi1dt6FzoRd6LAHxwGcJhA7ZAT5ATcHSF9tRbyhUXMLbxUUR4ygMQKd2B7odDc45QcGJTiJLBSFrgkLhQNALAP6Dhz6aSmNohd5avRw27Md7a7mve8RACQFwBLokgZJD4","sellerName":"Purpleair","countryCode":"US","offerId":"677fe39418f35ad1547d9525","reducedPrice":""}],"component":"unified_product_card","total_index":1,"hasMultipleImage":false,"componentType":true,"showProsConsData":false,"videoIds":[],"offersLength":1}'&gt;&lt;div id="677fe3511de8aa366d74938b" class="UnifiedLandscapeProductCardWrapper-lpCYz hyRKMF"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardContainer-jfmyrc hJJXyx"&gt;&lt;div class="upcSingleImageWrapper-bMOWWA jGaikA"&gt;&lt;p class="UnifiedProductCardImageCreditText-IXcDI cYcQnj"&gt;Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Back in January, I woke up to find my PurpleAir Zen outdoor air quality monitor glowing bright red. This happened over several days, and I was confused because the numbers were well over 100 and yet there wasn’t an air quality alert for the area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The annual AQI for my &lt;a href="https://a816-dohbesp.nyc.gov/IndicatorPublic/data-explorer/air-quality/?id=2023#display=map"&gt;neighborhood&lt;/a&gt; is under 50—considered good air. For context, an AQI of 100 or more is unhealthy for sensitive groups, and an AQI of 150 is unhealthy for everyone. I mentioned the unhealthy air to a friend who reminded me that New York City recently installed a &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/brooklyn-concrete-recycling-plant-dust-noise/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/brooklyn-concrete-recycling-plant-dust-noise/"}' href="https://www.cbsnews.com/newyork/news/brooklyn-concrete-recycling-plant-dust-noise/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;concrete recycling center&lt;/a&gt; a few blocks from my home. The literal &lt;a href="https://council.nyc.gov/shahana-hanif/2025/01/20/columbia-street-waterfront-residents-demand-city-shut-down-concrete-recycling-facility-over-dust-health-concerns/"&gt;dust-up&lt;/a&gt; the center caused, including failure to inform the neighborhood about its existence, might be the culprit for the recent uptick in bad air, from the &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.osha.gov/sites/default/files/publications/3221_Concrete.pdf" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.osha.gov/sites/default/files/publications/3221_Concrete.pdf"}' href="https://www.osha.gov/sites/default/files/publications/3221_Concrete.pdf" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;concrete dust&lt;/a&gt; created by the recycling center. At that point the recycling center had yet to implement irrigation to mitigate the dust plumes. The data from my outdoor monitor fed into PurpleAir’s crowdsourced real-time &lt;a data-offer-url="https://map.purpleair.com/air-quality-who-aqg?opt=%2F1%2Flp%2Fa10%2Fp600%2FcC0#7.53/44.244/-69.173" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://map.purpleair.com/air-quality-who-aqg?opt=%2F1%2Flp%2Fa10%2Fp600%2FcC0#7.53/44.244/-69.173"}' href="https://map.purpleair.com/air-quality-who-aqg?opt=%2F1%2Flp%2Fa10%2Fp600%2FcC0#7.53/44.244/-69.173" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;map&lt;/a&gt;. On the map, I could see other nearby PurpleAir monitors, and the ones closest to the concrete recycling center tended to have worse air quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Invisible Danger&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In July, after a year of mounting protests and political pressure, the city announced that it would &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.newsbreak.com/news-12-1587832/4108408236611-cobble-hill-residents-breathe-a-sigh-of-relief-after-city-announces-closure-of-concrete-recycling-plant" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.newsbreak.com/news-12-1587832/4108408236611-cobble-hill-residents-breathe-a-sigh-of-relief-after-city-announces-closure-of-concrete-recycling-plant"}' href="https://www.newsbreak.com/news-12-1587832/4108408236611-cobble-hill-residents-breathe-a-sigh-of-relief-after-city-announces-closure-of-concrete-recycling-plant" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;relocate&lt;/a&gt; the concrete recycling center. What would have happened if residents hadn’t seen the dust clouds or noticed the gray film collecting on their cars? What if they couldn’t see what was all around them? &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/pm-pollution/particulate-matter-pm-basics#PM" target="_blank"&gt;PM 2.5&lt;/a&gt; is the invisible solids and liquids that are in the air. The tiniest form can enter the deepest parts of the lungs, passing into the bloodstream. There, they can cause a host of &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/pm-pollution/health-and-environmental-effects-particulate-matter-pm"&gt;illnesses&lt;/a&gt;, respiratory distress, and &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0953620513001040"&gt;cardiovascular disease&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-testid="feature-large-callout" class="CalloutFeatureLargeWrapper-cAQNly bLNMaC"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardBody-hIYvDT cYxZHF product-embed" data-item='{"ctaHref":"https://cna.st/p/HqPtkHbE1vfvuLcV8bSv1rMGDSyGBfBPcqG4nui5VQJM63kkiRRJy2gzUdnnvJrEVTe6nUqHZKEQHrzALU2iVw4o9FXV8me7CoGgG8hc51M67AH9vfUoXvmfwqr2RQ4LM8SXAXBTmf2wsBYnHyzUqT5dHCV7nk1rSsHhEv6RViyKAx5M6naKtSx248is9WkYsDGZTsFnDwgfDRhGBisG2mJR7wRRMoxpTXfHbHqTPCT3cF1DxVcKGno87pK8LSgytJbhXYGn1qxpYeRgqbUVAKShveDJWgiCUEF612T2JuWZRLqVt8cByZJcpv","dangerousDek":"","productBrand":"IQAir","dangerousHed":"Outdoor Air Quality Monitor","embedSize":"feature-medium","isFirstProduct":false,"image":{"altText":"Image may contain: Adapter, Electronics, and Furniture","credit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","sources":{"sm":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":720,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_720,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_120,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_240,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_320,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_640,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 640w"},"md":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":720,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_720,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_120,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_240,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_320,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_640,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 640w"},"lg":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":748,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_748,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_120,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_240,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_320,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_640,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 640w"},"xl":{"aspectRatio":"4:3","width":748,"url":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_748,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png","srcset":"https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_120,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 120w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_240,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 240w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_320,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 320w, https://media.wired.com/photos/6876eca84a197ac30b2af8fa/4:3/w_640,c_limit/IQAir%20Air%20Visual-SOURCE-Lisa%20Wood%20Shapiro.png 640w"}}},"isSponsored":false,"offerRetailer":"Amazon","offerUrl":"https://www.amazon.com/AirVisual-Outdoor-Temperature-Humidity-Pressure/dp/B09H3RXDTZ/ref=sr_1_1?","contentType":"product","productId":"686c29a8f24ef4a6bf8a6fbc","showOfferUrl":false,"showPriceOnButton":true,"showAffiliateDisclaimerOnFirstProduct":false,"dangerousCredit":"Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro","showLocalisedOffers":true,"isUpcEnabled":true,"showClampedProductDescription":true,"productDescriptionLineLength":5,"hasReadMoreFeature":false,"index":2,"hasAffiliateLinkDisabled":false,"isMobileView":false,"hasMultipleImageSupport":true,"showImageCreditText":true,"showMultipleImageCount":4,"hasProsConsFeature":false,"hasRatingFeature":false,"pros":[],"cons":[],"rating":"","shouldUseAmazonPrimeDayLiveAPIData":true,"id":"686c29a8f24ef4a6bf8a6fbc","brand":{"name":"IQAir"},"offers":[{"offerUrl":"https://www.amazon.com/AirVisual-Outdoor-Temperature-Humidity-Pressure/dp/B09H3RXDTZ/ref=sr_1_1?","price":"$300","currency":"USD","purchaseUri":"https://cna.st/p/HqPtkHbE1vfvuLcV8bSv1rMGDSyGBfBPcqG4nui5VQJM63kkiRRJy2gzUdnnvJrEVTe6nUqHZKEQHrzALU2iVw4o9FXV8me7CoGgG8hc51M67AH9vfUoXvmfwqr2RQ4LM8SXAXBTmf2wsBYnHyzUqT5dHCV7nk1rSsHhEv6RViyKAx5M6naKtSx248is9WkYsDGZTsFnDwgfDRhGBisG2mJR7wRRMoxpTXfHbHqTPCT3cF1DxVcKGno87pK8LSgytJbhXYGn1qxpYeRgqbUVAKShveDJWgiCUEF612T2JuWZRLqVt8cByZJcpv","sellerName":"Amazon","countryCode":"US","offerId":"686c29d3f6550babcf093aba","reducedPrice":""}],"component":"unified_product_card","total_index":1,"hasMultipleImage":false,"componentType":true,"showProsConsData":false,"videoIds":[],"offersLength":1}'&gt;&lt;div id="686c29a8f24ef4a6bf8a6fbc" class="UnifiedLandscapeProductCardWrapper-lpCYz hyRKMF"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardContainer-jfmyrc hJJXyx"&gt;&lt;div class="upcSingleImageWrapper-bMOWWA jGaikA"&gt;&lt;p class="UnifiedProductCardImageCreditText-IXcDI cYcQnj"&gt;Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsContainer-jzIVFy dEeeEw"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetailsWrapper-ieavYi jwXcRS"&gt;&lt;div class="UnifiedProductCardDetails-dTZxUl hEAQFX"&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardBrandName-kmvqXz deqABF fmYMxY jpHfSL upc-brandName"&gt;IQAir&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardNameWrapper-fsdgKv deqABF eCPEdo izjkDw"&gt;&lt;h3 id="upc_686c29a8f24ef4a6bf8a6fbc" type="embed" class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE UnifiedProductCardName-jDmuEE deqABF ctbzXQ hdWBHD"&gt;Outdoor Air Quality Monitor&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;In early 2024, the Biden administration strengthened the National Ambient Air Quality Health Standards (NAAQS) for particulate matter, a move that set “the level of the primary (health-based) annual PM 2.5 standard at 9.0 micrograms per cubic meter (µg/m&lt;sup&gt;3&lt;/sup&gt;) to reflect new science on harms caused by particle pollution.” This changed the window of what is considered “good” air on the &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/"}' href="https://www.airnow.gov/aqi/aqi-basics/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;Air Quality Index&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;Those EPA guidelines are almost double those of the World Health Organization &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/feature-stories/detail/what-are-the-who-air-quality-guidelines"&gt;guidelines&lt;/a&gt;, which are a stricter 5 PM 2.5. &lt;a href="https://www.epa.gov/newsreleases/trump-epa-announces-path-forward-national-air-quality-standards-particulate-matter#:~:text=Particulate%20Matter%20(PM2.-,5)%20to%20Aid%20Manufacturing%2C%20Small%20Businesses,tape%20holding%20back%20American%20exceptionalism."&gt;Trump’s EPA&lt;/a&gt; is reconsidering the Biden administration's PM 2.5 standards. To quote EPA administrator Zeldin, “All Americans deserve to breathe clean air while pursuing the American dream. Under President Trump, we will ensure air quality standards for particulate matter are protective of human health and the environment while we unleash the Golden Age of American prosperity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;The Trump administration also wants to &lt;a data-offer-url="https://www.regulations.gov/document/EPA-HQ-OAR-2025-0124-0001" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://www.regulations.gov/document/EPA-HQ-OAR-2025-0124-0001"}' href="https://www.regulations.gov/document/EPA-HQ-OAR-2025-0124-0001" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;repeal greenhouse gas emissions&lt;/a&gt; regulations. According to a statement from the EPA, “The EPA is further proposing to make a finding that GHG emissions from fossil fuel-fired power plants do not contribute significantly to dangerous air pollution.” &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/B9780128229286000095"&gt;Scientific research&lt;/a&gt; states otherwise. And so, as outdoor air becomes less regulated, it has the potential to get dirtier and make &lt;a href="https://ehp.niehs.nih.gov/doi/full/10.1289/ehp.1509676"&gt;people sick&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="paywall"&gt;Too Close to Home&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p class="paywall"&gt;This past spring, the smell of campfire filled my home. I peered out my fourth-floor window to see my neighbor’s illegal fire pit three backyards over. I watched the colors on my PurpleAir Zen outdoor monitor change from green to yellow to crimson over the course of an hour. When I logged onto the crowd-sourced PurpleAir real-time map, I could see that my outdoor air quality was an unhealthy 160 PM 2.5 and that a few blocks away, air quality was good at under 30 PM 2.5. There’s nothing surprising about a fire pit generating air pollution, but I didn’t realize how intense and localized that air pollution could be, even though I was four stories up in a half-a-city-block-sized area. This is air quality on a microscale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="AssetEmbedWrapper-fkZDUs kHRAYC asset-embed"&gt;&lt;p class="CaptionWrapper-jYrTxZ bkfwbX caption AssetEmbedCaption-fyuOdR eXMqGf asset-embed__caption" data-testid="caption-wrapper"&gt;&lt;span class="BaseWrap-sc-gzmcOU BaseText-eqOrNE CaptionCredit-eowWKH deqABF kpqIso kpuElq caption__credit"&gt;Photograph: Lisa Wood Shapiro&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WIRED</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:34:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTFBTM1BobURDOFE4c2VyN2JCV1BMZDBXYnB5YTdkN3JLNUFUYTc4ZW9uREZkTVd5M1E2aXN6UGFnWW8tREM0SzhRMHJYSkFYV1FWYUxBc191SVJ1bEhXSEhGX3VJSmZ4emdpTGRDd0xGWHZFclhhVnp0bFpob3U</guid></item><item><title>一名青少年足球运动员在脑震荡后出现了数月的症状。医生发现了一种罕见的脑部畸形。- CBS新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMikgFBVV95cUxNRHFjWXNlWHhBRkZGUFVneWMxVWp1b3k3UWIwYUdjT1BjQS1xc1RsZHJOUEhwXzdZQm9ET0tYaGtzdXNtajBKR1ZmaUdXa2MySTg1WFBQckF4MV9VY3RwR19TMXF2S3d0ckROWXUzTURVdTdtZWZMQnc1Z3pkbEFuOHBaNWhGeDFvVlpzcVhYY1lSUdIBlwFBVV95cUxPaTZ4ZWU3MlNjZVRqbW1YZUMwNTJRVW45V1JYd0tXMkhZTHVHUF9QT1ZSY3kxeTJzZjIxV3RIWkhvX1BFc1V6OVJWY2FnVXJhYW1rdWFEN0FFM2dMamQwT2FySnRUQmZGMXEwTEx5dEFiNHRlOHpFUmNtbVVTSXhoXzBWNXBqNndaV2xRZ0RsMVp0Zm1HRTFz?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;section class="content__body"&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Logan Coleridge was used to taking hits in football. He'd been playing since he was 6 years old and had sustained several &lt;span class="link"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/football-new-helmets-reduce-concussions-cte/" target="_blank" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;concussions&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. But after a helmet-to-helmet impact during his freshman year of high school in August 2023, he started having debilitating symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The New Jersey teen said he was very dizzy and had trouble balancing. His memory was "terrible," and he had a "severe" light sensitivity, he said, along with "terrible headaches." Previously a strong student, he now struggled to focus in the classroom and couldn't remember school assignments or what he read in class. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I've got concussions in my past, and it wasn't like a normal one," Logan said. "I knew it was something else." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/9ab1c183-c863-4fef-b720-26be765fafa7/thumbnail/620x728/c69a1b07e8923ab60919a3028363a07e/logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg#" alt="logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg " srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/9ab1c183-c863-4fef-b720-26be765fafa7/thumbnail/620x728/c69a1b07e8923ab60919a3028363a07e/logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/9ab1c183-c863-4fef-b720-26be765fafa7/thumbnail/1240x1456/e8bda2ae9f78307dc2d63b942d957ef0/logan-coleridge-no-9.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Logan Coleridge (#9) on the field.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;More alarmingly, Logan wasn't getting better. Several months of physical therapy had no effect, said Becky Coleridge, Logan's mom. A neurologist who had been treating Logan since his diagnosis with abdominal migraines the year before prescribed two medications, both of which had negative side effects. An orthopedic doctor suggested looking at his neck. Other practitioners had no answers. Coleridge wanted doctors to prescribe an MRI, but wasn't able to get one. Meanwhile, Logan was missing school almost every week. Over-the-counter medications couldn't dull the headaches, and they were becoming more frequent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In early spring 2024, Logan was able to see a concussion specialist after a particularly bad headache kept him from going to school. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The first thing he said was 'Nobody's given this kid an MRI?'" Becky Coleridge remembered. The specialist prescribed the scan, as well as an X-ray of Logan's neck. The Coleridges thought the scans might show Logan had an issue with his occipital nerve, which runs from the neck to the scalp. &lt;/p&gt;

    
&lt;p id="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" data-ad="mpu-plus-outstream-middle" class="ad-mpu-plus-outstream-middle ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='"mpu-plus-outstream-middle"'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The results were much harder to hear: Logan was diagnosed with an arteriovenous malformation, or AVM. It was a condition that he and his parents had never heard of before. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Everything we read was very scary," Becky Coleridge said. "At that moment, we realized the danger he had been in." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/67a3229a-84a5-4eaa-b0ee-548828a778c3/thumbnail/620x710/4903f4fb42fea400e6e3336bab6777bd/img-8052.jpg#" alt="img-8052.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/67a3229a-84a5-4eaa-b0ee-548828a778c3/thumbnail/620x710/4903f4fb42fea400e6e3336bab6777bd/img-8052.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/67a3229a-84a5-4eaa-b0ee-548828a778c3/thumbnail/1240x1420/109ba89cc57b1d6ef0bc305857629a82/img-8052.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;The Coleridge family. &lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;What is an arteriovenous malformation? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;An AVM is an abnormal tangle of blood vessels in the brain, said Dr. Andrew Russman, head of the Cleveland Clinic's stroke program, who was not involved in Logan's care. AVMs put "a lot of pressure on the vein side" and can produce a variety of symptoms, he said. The biggest risk with an AVM is rupture, where the vessels burst and cause bleeding in the brain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a case like Logan's, where the AVM hasn't ruptured, there can still be symptoms. Those symptoms can affect a person's motor skills, sensory and visual perception, language abilities and the way they walk, Russman said. The effects can vary depending on where in the brain the AVM has formed, Russman said. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc3" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",3]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Coleridges had two options to treat Logan: Radiation therapy, a non-invasive technique that uses focused radiation beams to target and slowly destroy the AVM, or surgery. Radiation therapy could take too long, the family decided, and so they decided to have Logan treated by Dr. Howard Riina, a cerebrovascular neurosurgeon at NYU Langone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/2484440c-a91b-4cd3-8b65-e7bad875203c/thumbnail/620x629/05b2f3ec7decbc75791a5259d415896b/logan-coleridge-avm.jpg#" alt="logan-coleridge-avm.jpg " class=" lazyload" srcset="https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/2484440c-a91b-4cd3-8b65-e7bad875203c/thumbnail/620x629/05b2f3ec7decbc75791a5259d415896b/logan-coleridge-avm.jpg 1x, https://assets2.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/2484440c-a91b-4cd3-8b65-e7bad875203c/thumbnail/1240x1258/c5f2db71a5fca39862dd28f04a104bf4/logan-coleridge-avm.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Logan Coleridge's AVM.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge / NYU Langone

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"He couldn't go to school. His whole life was impacted by these headaches," Riina said. "They wanted an immediate solution." &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Riina said the AVM, which was on a "headache spot" in the occipital region of the brain, was likely the root of Logan's symptoms. People are born with AVMs, Riina said, and they grow as the body grows, which can cause increased symptoms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Obviously, you don't want to have multiple things going on in your head, but the concussion is what led to the imaging, which led to the diagnosis of the AVM, which was probably what was causing the headaches all along," he said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Raising awareness and "focusing on a new beginning" &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Logan underwent surgery on July 17, 2024, nearly a year after his symptoms began. Riina performed a craniotomy and removed the AVM. Three days later, Logan was discharged from the hospital to continue his recovery at home. Logan said it was a "lonely" way to spend his summer vacation. Even as his recovery progressed, he couldn't participate in the sports he loved. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I couldn't really do the things that I love normally doing, like exercising, playing football was a big thing for me. I was just stuck in bed, pretty much having minimal activity," Logan said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class="embed embed--type-image is-image embed--float-none embed--size-medium"&gt;
    
                                    
      &lt;span class="img embed__content"&gt;&lt;img src="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/d487edeb-98dc-4ba1-86b0-b75d840396b9/thumbnail/620x725/255c0ebc497ada6dad8cc71e6fd24dfe/logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg#" alt="logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg " srcset="https://assets3.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/d487edeb-98dc-4ba1-86b0-b75d840396b9/thumbnail/620x725/255c0ebc497ada6dad8cc71e6fd24dfe/logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg 1x, https://assets1.cbsnewsstatic.com/hub/i/r/2025/08/01/d487edeb-98dc-4ba1-86b0-b75d840396b9/thumbnail/1240x1450/f2a657243d12b0d1734c29b52bfd03c5/logan-coleridge-recovering-in-kimmel.jpg 2x" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;

      
          &lt;figcaption class="embed__caption-container"&gt;
        
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__caption"&gt;Logan Coleridge recovering at NYU Langone after surgery.&lt;/span&gt;
        
                  &lt;span class="embed__credit"&gt;
            
                Becky and Barry Coleridge

                          &lt;/span&gt;
              &lt;/figcaption&gt;
      &lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, Logan has only the occasional headache, and the pain can be treated with medication. He has follow-ups at NYU Langone, but Riina said everything has come back clear. The Coleridges are working to encourage early testing: Becky Coleridge said she wishes Logan had received an MRI earlier so that months of suffering and confusion could have been avoided. &lt;/p&gt;

    
    
&lt;p id="leader-plus-inc4" data-ad="leader-plus-inc" class="ad-leader-plus-inc ad-wrapper " data-ad-unit='["leader-plus-inc",4]'&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This year has been a complete turnaround, Logan said. He no longer misses school. He celebrated his 16th birthday and took driving lessons. This summer, he spent almost every day at the beach with friends. This month, he's gearing up for a return to the football field. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The whole experience was a fork in the road for me that I had to get through," Logan said. "I'm leaving that time in my life in the past and focusing on a new beginning." &lt;/p&gt;

      

                    
        
      
                  
    

    


    
      
    
  

          
  
        
      &lt;div class="content-author"&gt;
      &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/team/kerry-breen/" class="content-author__name" data-invalid-url-rewritten-http=""&gt;Kerry  Breen&lt;/a&gt;

      &lt;div class="content-author__bio"&gt;
        &lt;div class="content-author__full-information"&gt;
          &lt;p class="content-author__text"&gt;Kerry Breen is a news editor at CBSNews.com. A graduate of New York University's Arthur L. Carter School of Journalism, she previously worked at NBC News' TODAY Digital. She covers current events, breaking news and issues including substance use.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;
      &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/section&gt;

  
  

  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>CBS News</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:00:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMikgFBVV95cUxNRHFjWXNlWHhBRkZGUFVneWMxVWp1b3k3UWIwYUdjT1BjQS1xc1RsZHJOUEhwXzdZQm9ET0tYaGtzdXNtajBKR1ZmaUdXa2MySTg1WFBQckF4MV9VY3RwR19TMXF2S3d0ckROWXUzTURVdTdtZWZMQnc1Z3pkbEFuOHBaNWhGeDFvVlpzcVhYY1lSUdIBlwFBVV95cUxPaTZ4ZWU3MlNjZVRqbW1YZUMwNTJRVW45V1JYd0tXMkhZTHVHUF9QT1ZSY3kxeTJzZjIxV3RIWkhvX1BFc1V6OVJWY2FnVXJhYW1rdWFEN0FFM2dMamQwT2FySnRUQmZGMXEwTEx5dEFiNHRlOHpFUmNtbVVTSXhoXzBWNXBqNndaV2xRZ0RsMVp0Zm1HRTFz</guid></item><item><title>家长建议：我找到了爸爸的Reddit账号。我希望我从来没有读过它。- Slate Magazine</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxQZWZLamJjbE9FREFqNkhENERNWVN2N2ZxQ1hodVc0Nk9vZXdpamRPVHppR0tnbG5mZlgybGM0czNwOFpHdXBrRUY3em8tS0Y0bXYyWmwxRTlKVGU5SnpORHg5YmJsWS14LUNJRGxwOEMwUEgtZ2hJbnY4WENHUDVLcE53?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="16" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bjb14000owtm74fbsl4zx@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Care and Feeding is Slate’s parenting advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have a question for Care and Feeding? &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://forms.gle/4BXEw8Wtcd7aAyXh9"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Submit it here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bm709003m3b79i92iz2jh@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Care and Feeding,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="72" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bky1v00123b79nm86xv6o@published"&gt;I’m a 15-year-old girl, the older of two siblings. I was using the family computer and wanted to check my Reddit, and that’s when I found out that Dad has a Reddit account too. I didn’t snoop then, but I did write down his account name and then checked it out on my phone later.&lt;br&gt;I shouldn’t have done that. I should have realized it was private because he had never mentioned it.&lt;/p&gt;



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="107" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bl3t000183b79ajj2ip3a@published"&gt;A lot of his posts were heavy. They consisted of complaints about his life, how he resents his family, and then feels guilty about feeling so resentful. How he can’t stand Mom anymore but thinks it’s important to put up a good front for us kids, and how he wishes just once his kids would come to him with something other than a problem we expected him to solve. He said some nasty things specifically about me, too, about some personal incidents I don’t want to share here, but that I had shrugged off as just normal interactions—I hadn’t realized how much I had hurt his feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bl661001e3b796kznxyt2@published"&gt;I feel like I’d know the answer to the question of what to do about this (NOTHING) if that was all there was to it. It wasn’t meant for my eyes, I know. But the thing is, there’s also this undercurrent about how terrible he feels for having these thoughts and feelings and how he needs to “stay strong” for his family. It makes me really uneasy and worried about him. I had no idea he was going through any of this. I feel like I pried open his diary! I don’t know what to do now. Should I just pretend I saw nothing? Or should I tell him?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="4" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bl8xi001k3b79pfgcfptz@published"&gt;—Really Stepped Into It&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blets001y3b79wm4s995v@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Stepped,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="123" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blgn000253b79eunxdanu@published"&gt;Is there an adult you feel close to, who knows and loves your father—but who is not your mother—with whom you could talk this over? It’s really beyond the scope of what a 15-year-old should be doing for a parent for you to take responsibility for your father’s mental health—and to carry the burden of guilt you now feel for having “snooped.” Of course, if your dad put all of this on Reddit—&lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; your whole family shares one computer—he had to know, at some level, that someone (if not everyone) in the family would read it. At the very least, he was making his confessions in a public space: Reddit is not a diary, as much as it may sometimes feel like one.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="150" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bliva002c3b79igstsakc@published"&gt;I don’t know why people reveal their most private thoughts to strangers on the internet (this may be a generational blind spot of mine; I am acquainted with a number of 40-somethings who seem to share &lt;em&gt;everything&lt;/em&gt;, no matter how private, on Facebook), but I do know that writing about (what sounds like) one’s depression on a shared computer is a not-so-subtle cry for help from those who have access to it. &lt;em&gt;You&lt;/em&gt; are not the right person to help him, but his best friend or a sibling of his might be. (And for all you know, he is just using Reddit to blow off steam. Some of those 40-somethings I mentioned definitely use Facebook that way. I read their posts and become alarmed—then learn that they’re just fine, really; they were just having “a dramatic moment.” Again, I’ll acknowledge that this mystifies me. But it is apparently a thing.)&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="46" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blld9002j3b791t2xtql2@published"&gt;In the meantime, can you make every effort to be kind to your dad? You might even approach him with something other than a problem for him to solve. It won’t fix him—as I say, it’s not for you to fix him—but it certainly couldn’t hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3bln64002q3b79y13rv8i5@published"&gt;&lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;—Michelle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cme3blzse003c3b79919stloi@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
More Advice From Slate

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="109" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3blx8800343b79f8wj2q12@published"&gt;Up until two weeks ago, my husband “Jeff” (39) was a model family man and father to “Jenny” (8) and “Kyle” (6). About the only problem in our marriage was his insomnia, and while it was difficult to deal with him getting up 5-6 times a night, every night, it was hardly his fault. Still, after over a decade of trying to treat the insomnia with nothing working except for drugs that had side effects worse than the insomnia itself, we eventually decided on adding a bedroom annex to the home office, and Jeff sleeping there instead of with me. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2022/11/insomnia-sleep-apart-marriage.html"&gt;Ever since then, he’s been half-assing as a father.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Advice" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cme3bjb14000rwtm7zk2fct1u@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Never miss new Advice columns&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;The latest sex, parenting, and money advice from our columnists delivered to your inbox three times a week.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate Magazine</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxQZWZLamJjbE9FREFqNkhENERNWVN2N2ZxQ1hodVc0Nk9vZXdpamRPVHppR0tnbG5mZlgybGM0czNwOFpHdXBrRUY3em8tS0Y0bXYyWmwxRTlKVGU5SnpORHg5YmJsWS14LUNJRGxwOEMwUEgtZ2hJbnY4WENHUDVLcE53</guid></item><item><title>我每天都吃木犀壳-这是好处- VOGUE</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiYkFVX3lxTE01QkkzME0tRTU4eGt3dGRWclhuQ0lrVlZRaW5fWmdSdXZ1MHBkV19kZVpadnVZMldqVlc2UDVzTWJBZHFFWGQtdlVuQVVNb0tDTjczQXJ3S2lPMVhfZ21obUln?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body__inner-container"&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the positive effect goes beyond the bowels: psyllium husks could help reduce the risk of diseases such as bowel cancer, &lt;a data-offer-url="https://kjim.org/journal/view.php?doi=10.3904/kjim.2019.049" class="external-link" data-event-click='{"element":"ExternalLink","outgoingURL":"https://kjim.org/journal/view.php?doi=10.3904/kjim.2019.049"}' href="https://kjim.org/journal/view.php?doi=10.3904/kjim.2019.049" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt;, and type 2 diabetes in the long term because fiber allows sugar from food to be absorbed more slowly into the bloodstream. “If you combine psyllium husks with a protein-rich meal, this can keep blood sugar levels even more stable,” Werner says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;How to eat psyllium husks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to psyllium husks, less is more, especially at the beginning. In fact, Werner often sees her patients make the same mistake time and again—they either take too much at once or don’t drink enough water. “Always work up to it slowly, and take plenty of fluids,” she advises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To that end, she recommends starting with one small spoonful a day (or less), and then slowly working your way up “day by day, and week by week.” If you notice that you don’t tolerate the psyllium husks well, simply reduce the amount. “One teaspoon to a large glass of water is a good starting point for many people,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, Werner does have one caveat—she prefers not to pre-soak her husks, unlike me: “To be honest, I find the goo in water quite disgusting,” she laughs. Instead, she prefers to simply stir the psyllium husks into smoothies, yogurt, or &lt;a href="https://www.vogue.com/article/oatmeal-benefits" target="_blank"&gt;oatmeal&lt;/a&gt;. “I now take one to two teaspoons, sometimes even a tablespoon a day—but I’ve worked my way up to it really slowly,” she say.s&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What to look for when shopping for psyllium husks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Werner recommends hulled psyllium husks versus whole psyllium seeds. Since they contain just the outer shell of the seed, “they are usually better tolerated and swell up more,” she explains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also advises buying organic quality and checking the list of ingredients: “Ideally, they should really only contain psyllium husks—no additives, no flavorings. This is often a good indicator that the products are less contaminated with harmful substances.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Have a beauty or wellness trend you're curious about? We want to know! Send&lt;/em&gt; Vogue'&lt;em&gt;s senior beauty &amp;amp; wellness editor an email at beauty@vogue.com.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Vogue</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiYkFVX3lxTE01QkkzME0tRTU4eGt3dGRWclhuQ0lrVlZRaW5fWmdSdXZ1MHBkV19kZVpadnVZMldqVlc2UDVzTWJBZHFFWGQtdlVuQVVNb0tDTjczQXJ3S2lPMVhfZ21obUln</guid></item><item><title>一项新的研究表明，这种令人惊讶的乳制品选择可以支持更健康的衰老-食品和葡萄酒</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihgFBVV95cUxQbm5GQW9jU2xxdHB1WjhRNlhKTFVHWUxHYmlEWUVLM0ozcGFHNDlxanIyUTh1X3NOZTg4TUpNdzJmUWFZdzRxQXdYYWxJemtjdjUwei1jWGN1SnBvUFo4S28tX1RFd0tBVWhXSmJYSVdJUHowTG9TdnJRZzl1OHhzTlpuSnBQdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-page_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-page mntl-block structured-content" data-sc-sticky-offset="90" data-sc-ad-label-height="24" data-sc-ad-track-spacing="100" data-sc-min-track-height="250" data-sc-max-track-height="600" data-sc-breakpoint="50em" data-sc-load-immediate="4" data-sc-content-positions="[1, 1250, 1550, 1950, 2350, 2750, 3150, 3550, 3950]" data-bind-scroll-on-start="true"&gt;&lt;div id="mntl-sc-block_1-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block foodandwine-sc-block-callout--summary mntl-sc-block-universal-callout--tips mntl-sc-block-universal-callout theme-summary callout--bordered" data-text="Key points" data-tracking-id="mntl-sc-block-callout" data-tracking-container="true"&gt;
&lt;div class="mntl-sc-block-universal-callout__body"&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A new study from researchers in China analyzed the impact of consuming different types of milk on muscle and bone health while aging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;This study used mice to learn about the relationship between sarcopenia, age-related muscle loss, and four different dairy milks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Findings revealed that goat milk (in particular low-fat goat milk and low-fat fortified goat milk) was more effective at supporting muscle regeneration and reducing inflammation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_2-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; If it seems like everyone is going wild for protein these days, you're not imagining things. According to &lt;a href="https://www.cargill.com/2025/consumers-are-seeking-more-protein-for-health-and-taste-in-2025" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Cargill’s 2025 Protein Profile&lt;/a&gt;, 61% of Americans increased their protein intake in 2024. As &lt;a href="https://www.grandviewresearch.com/industry-analysis/protein-fortified-food-products-market-report" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="2"&gt;Grand View Research&lt;/a&gt; noted in its 2025 report, the "global protein-fortified food products market size was estimated at $66.8 billion in 2023 and is projected to reach $101.62 billion by 2030."
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_3-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_4-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; However, according to one new study, you may not need to rely solely on pricey protein-fortified foods and powders to support muscle health. Simply switching up the milk you drink every day could help.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_5-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_6-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; In July, researchers from Peking University and Hyproca Nutrition in China published their findings in the journal &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/fsn3.70540" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;Food Science &amp;amp; Nutrition&lt;/a&gt;, giving greater insight into four dairy products and whether they have the potential to delay the progression of sarcopenia, or age-related muscle loss. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_7-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_8-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "Sarcopenia, characterized by progressive loss of muscle mass and strength, poses a significant public health challenge. However, the specific role of dairy products in preventing sarcopenia is not well understood," the scientists shared. Studies like this are key to finding solutions for a problem that many of us may face. As one research overview explained, on average, 5–13% of people between 60 and 70 years of age are affected by &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3060646/" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;sarcopenia&lt;/a&gt;. For people over 80, that increases to 11–50%.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_9-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_10-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block foodandwine-sc-block-embed mntl-sc-block-universal-embed mntl-sc-block-embed--youtube"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_11-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_12-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; To figure out which dairy products can help stave off sarcopenia, the researchers fed dairy-enriched diets to mice for eight weeks. The mice were split into six groups: normal control, sarcopenia, goat whole milk, goat low-fat milk, goat fortified vitamin D, calcium low-fat milk, and bovine (cow) whole milk.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_13-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_14-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The normal control group was given saline throughout the trial — a salt and water solution that acts as a placebo — while the other five groups received dexamethasone injections to induce sarcopenia. At the same time, four groups were fed the milk in their group name. This means that one group did have induced sarcopenia without receiving a dairy supplement, acting as a sarcopenia control group.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_15-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_16-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; The team then measured the test subjects' grip strength, weight, bone mineral density, &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/articles/24058-autophagy" data-component="link" data-source="inlineLink" data-type="externalLink" data-ordinal="1"&gt;autophagy&lt;/a&gt; (the process that allows your body to reuse and recycle damaged cells), muscle morphology (the size and shape of the muscles), metabolism, inflammation, and gut microbial health. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_17-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_19-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_20-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; They found that while all types of milk helped the mice regain muscle mass and bone strength, the fortified low-fat goat’s milk — a version with added vitamin D and calcium — was most effective. As the researchers explained, the goat milk boosted muscle-building signals in the body and lowered levels of key inflammation markers linked to muscle loss. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_21-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_22-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; They also noticed one more critical finding in the gut. All of the dairy-fed mice showed shifts in their microbiome, with increases in the beneficial bacteria Leuconostoc. However, only the goat milk-fed mice showed an increase in Lactococcus and Acinetobacter bacteria, which could help reduce inflammation and support the body's metabolism. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_23-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_24-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; Need all of this boiled down to simpler terms?
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_25-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_26-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; "This study demonstrates that different types of dairy products have distinct effects on muscle metabolism, autophagy, inflammation, and gut microbiota in sarcopenia," the authors concluded. "Goat milk, particularly its low-fat and vitamin D/calcium-fortified variants, showed greater benefits in promoting muscle regeneration and reducing inflammation compared to bovine milk, highlighting the importance of dairy composition." 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_27-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_29-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_30-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; It is important to note that many commercial cow milks are fortified with Vitamins A and D, but the researchers do not provide commentary on whether this might come closer to offering the same muscle-regenerating benefits as fortified goat milk.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_31-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-adslot mntl-block"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p id="mntl-sc-block_32-0" class="comp mntl-sc-block mntl-sc-block-html"&gt; This study was conducted on mice, so the hypothesis has not been proven with humans. Nevertheless, it's one reason to search for goat milk the next time you're strolling through the grocery store or seek out a farmers market to start chatting with your local goat farmer about a regular supply.
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Food &amp; Wine</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:54:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihgFBVV95cUxQbm5GQW9jU2xxdHB1WjhRNlhKTFVHWUxHYmlEWUVLM0ozcGFHNDlxanIyUTh1X3NOZTg4TUpNdzJmUWFZdzRxQXdYYWxJemtjdjUwei1jWGN1SnBvUFo4S28tX1RFd0tBVWhXSmJYSVdJUHowTG9TdnJRZzl1OHhzTlpuSnBQdw</guid></item><item><title>老年人疫苗：以下是医生向50岁及以上人群推荐的疫苗-旧金山纪事报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxOdHZGTVpORVJyWDEySlhIMF9pclNJX01HQlBUMFNmdG8zbTA2Uk1Mc2xPT3VQNUFWQjRWR2JPMmpydF9CTGFOLWxKMk1CSXhaaXVFa1ptN3JfLXRGTnA2bzFGa3FyNUhRbm5CQWxDUXJnb1dvMFFqUzdLN3JFVGswYVFZblZyN21xb0NmUVotZENsUWJ6QmE0bjNnWkNSWHc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="rel"&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:-mx40 lg:-mx56 x100vw sm:cw-80 lg:cw-112 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gwendolyn Evans, 77, receives a flu shot from nurse Jailynn De La Cruz at the Kaiser Permanente adult vaccine clinic in San Francisco last  September. Doctors recommend an annual flu shot because influenza can be very dangerous in older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stephen Lam/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vaccine development over the past decade has produced a host of new formulations targeted toward older adults, many of whom remain committed to immunizations amid a national climate of simmering mistrust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adult immunizations start at about age 50 for otherwise healthy individuals, and the shots protect against not just death, but complications from serious illness that can be life-altering. Some immunizations are highly recommended for everyone; others may be less critical but worth talking over with a clinician about an individual’s needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Our biggest job as geriatricians is keeping people safe: safe from falls, safe from accidents, safe from abuse — and safe from illnesses that won’t be as severe,” said Dr. Lawrence Ma, a Stanford geriatrician. “Vaccines may not prevent you from getting sick, but they prevent you from getting really sick.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="A300" data-large-id="CONCERT1" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh300px lg:ais"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nationally, vaccines are not having a moment. U.S. Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has long spoken out against certain childhood vaccines, and after taking office, he &lt;a href="https://www.sfchronicle.com/news/article/ousted-vaccine-panel-members-say-rigorous-science-20794645.php" data-link="native" class=""&gt;filled the federal immunization advisory board&lt;/a&gt; with members who were vaccine skeptics. Most recently, he &lt;a href="https://www.sfchronicle.com/news/article/rfk-jr-pulls-500-million-in-funding-for-vaccine-20803827.php" data-link="native" class=""&gt;canceled funding for research into mRNA vaccines&lt;/a&gt;, which played a lifesaving role in the COVID pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Generally, though, Kennedy and others in President Donald Trump’s administration have not disparaged vaccines for older adults.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Vaccines are important public health issues — for the individual and the community as a whole,” said Dr. Yuwen Winnie Xu, a family medicine doctor with Kaiser San Francisco. “They’re highly effective at preventing infectious diseases, and they also reduce the severity of disease and the risk of complications and long-term issues.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a population, older adults remain interested in immunizations. That support probably comes from growing up in a time when illnesses such as polio and measles circulated widely — older adults may have seen firsthand the benefits of immunization. They also may be more generally protective of their increasingly fragile health than other age groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot’s changed in the immunization field over the past decade, though — from updated recipes of old shots to brand-new vaccines hitting the market. To help older adults understand which vaccines are available and what they do, Bay Area physicians and infectious disease experts weighed in on their favorites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="CONCERT1" data-large-id="CONCERT2" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh300px ais lg:f lg:jcc lg:mnh300px lg:ais"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Pneumoccocal&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;This shot’s on the top of all of the lists, mostly because pneumococcal pneumonia is so deadly for seniors. Until late last year, the shot was recommended for everyone 65 and older — it’s now advised for everyone 50 and up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pneumococcal vaccine is usually given in one dose to adults, and it protects against multiple bacterial strains. It’s been upgraded over the years to add more strains, and there are now several different formulations available. The vaccine is about 60% to 75% effective against severe illness, and no booster is recommended.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Pneumococcal was called the ‘old person’s friend’ because it caused people to die very quickly,” said Dr. Peter Chin-Hong, a UCSF infectious disease expert. The worst complications tend to occur in patients age 75 and up, but even 50-year-olds can have tough outcomes, Chin-Hong said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;RSV&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The RSV vaccine was approved for older adults in 2023 and is now recommended for everyone 75 and older; patients age 50 to 75 should talk to their doctor about getting the shot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="B300" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shot, which is given in one dose, is about 85% effective at preventing serious lower-respiratory illness, and at least so far seems to be long-lasting — there is no current booster recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shot arrived just as doctors were starting to better appreciate how dangerous RSV could be for older adults, Chin-Hong said. “It was like the bronze medalist of infectious diseases, behind influenza and COVID,” he said. “We didn’t pay much attention to it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now RSV is understood to potentially cause much more serious symptoms and complications, particularly in very old adults. One recent study showed a significantly increased risk of stroke or heart attack after patients were hospitalized for RSV.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We used to think, ‘It’s just a bad cold,’ but we’re recognizing that these big systemic infections that cause a lot of underlying inflammation can have downstream consequences,” Ma said. “Really the vaccine is there to prevent those big inflammatory cascades.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure class="rel f m0 fdc -mx20 sm:mx0 x100vw sm:x100 mb32"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="mediaCaptionAria" class="f fdc g2 rel pt8 px20 sm:px0 rel"&gt;&lt;span class="photoCaption c-gray700 block ya"&gt;&lt;div data-server-side-rendered="true" class="r12zgbl0"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nurse Michael Russ II administers a flu shot at the Kaiser adult vaccine clinic in San Francisco last September.  The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention recommend annual flu shots for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class="photoCredit c-gray600 block rel z1 mt2 mr48"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stephen Lam/S.F. Chronicle&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Influenza&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flu shot is not always the most effective — some years, it’s well south of 50% protective against severe illness — but influenza is so pervasive and can be so dangerous in older adults that doctors still recommend it. The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention recommend annual flu shots for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="CONCERT2" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh300px ais lg:none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adults 65 and older should get a high-dose or adjuvanted vaccine to give their immune system an extra boost, Chin-Hong said. He added that annual flu shots are more important than getting regular COVID vaccines because influenza mutates so frequently, so people are constantly being exposed to new strains that they are more vulnerable to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also worries about the H5N1 bird flu, which could mutate to better spread among humans — flu shots, he hopes, will prevent it from getting a foothold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Shingles&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current shingles vaccine was approved in 2017 and is recommended for everyone 50 and older. Adults who got the pre-2017 version of the shot should talk to their doctor about getting the newer one, which is about 80% to 90% effective at preventing shingles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not just shingles that the shots protect against, though. Some people who get shingles develop severe nerve pain that can last months or even a year. “One of my patients described it as a constant sunburn,” said Ma, and couldn’t wear a bra for a year. Some patients have had to take strong pain medications for extended periods of time, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="pt16 sy16 bb bt b-gray300 mb32"&gt;&lt;div class=""&gt;&lt;p class="uiTextSmall f aic jcc"&gt;Article continues below this ad&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-block-type="ad" data-small-id="S300" data-unit="hnp-sfchronicle.com/article_dtc" class="f jcc mnh250px sm:mnh600px ais lg:none"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;There’s another potential upshot to the shingles vaccine: Early studies have shown it may protect against dementia too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;COVID-19&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;These vaccines are still on the table, but older adults who are up to date on the latest formulation do not need to get a new one. People age 65 and up should get two doses of the current vaccine; those younger should get one dose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A person who is 50 to 65 who is otherwise healthy is going to do fine with COVID because they’ve had so many rounds of exposure,” Chin-Hong said. “Most of the bad stuff in COVID is in people who are older than 75 who didn’t get a shot in the last year. But it’s not a dangerous vaccine, so if someone wants to get it any time, I’m all for it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The rest&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;All adults should stay up to date on their tetanus shots — given every decade — and pertussis, which is given with tetanus. Pertussis generally does not cause severe illness in adults of any age, but it can cause an annoying, long-lasting cough. And the disease can be very serious in infants, so older adults who will be around babies should make sure they’re vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some adults may also need mpox or hepatitis vaccines, but those are generally recommended for certain individuals depending on their background or lifestyle, or only advised during outbreaks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In all cases, Ma notes that vaccines for older adults are meant not just to save lives but to preserve quality of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="r1udwkp5 d1uy5mhj articleBody mb32" data-block-type="text" data-dropcap="false"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Any illness can really start the downward spiral,” Ma said. “Even if you don’t die, if you’re sick enough to be bedbound you can lose muscle mass. A younger person may be able to recover from that, but someone who is older and frailer, that could be the very beginning of loss of independence. It could derail your life as it is now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn top"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="y1px x100 abs bgn bottom"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>San Francisco Chronicle</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:01:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxOdHZGTVpORVJyWDEySlhIMF9pclNJX01HQlBUMFNmdG8zbTA2Uk1Mc2xPT3VQNUFWQjRWR2JPMmpydF9CTGFOLWxKMk1CSXhaaXVFa1ptN3JfLXRGTnA2bzFGa3FyNUhRbm5CQWxDUXJnb1dvMFFqUzdLN3JFVGswYVFZblZyN21xb0NmUVotZENsUWJ6QmE0bjNnWkNSWHc</guid></item><item><title>幼儿父母需要了解的高度传染性夏季疾病- NJ.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiuwFBVV95cUxQSEhxbWZDb2JOZDZSdUlPd0l2NTFmSGJ6dlRZb29Rb1hnYUd3RFJJaG1hRmVqcWVMZWVnXzJMWlFMczFOT3N1QjZlWF93azdaWWZfcnUteGRuN3haTWNHZE9jWExfWHdxTWJoY2txdnNUTnVEM2FqZnF3VEJjUFVnNy1peVJzQkJXMWswNUlWLVJlSzdjOENNRUhxQjM3ZVJLNG81alNMV0pNMDNpWlZvSzc1SjdrVEJNY2tB0gHPAUFVX3lxTE5iWTNKbDFpeEJHdmlrbkh0b3ZLVk9rWk04MVQzZlRCb0lBaWNabDZJalktYldFRlRtRUFMa1RVUmNQYjMyMGZzNFZyNkdlR2xHMzJJODYzZ3BJYVBKM2R0N29UZl9HeEZ0bGxfbkpZdTItWG1rSWlzY1Q3VUJZUlg5Yml6OTcyV1ZFbkJkS2lKWi11aEtFZDNJelFPYVpvTUU0OFMtaExTWldfMU9NYUNIQlFCQUdDNmh6aVB0Z2gzQUxlSXBGbGpjUlZqTlU4RQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content   "&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="QBWJUST3PZE47JS5IMH6MECN7Y"&gt;When summer comes around, you can count on a few things. A Bruce Springsteen spotting at the Jersey Shore. Energy bills &lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/news/2025/08/my-energy-bill-is-insane-how-recent-price-hikes-temperature-spikes-are-hurting-nj-residents.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer" title="https://www.nj.com/news/2025/08/my-energy-bill-is-insane-how-recent-price-hikes-temperature-spikes-are-hurting-nj-residents.html"&gt;going up&lt;/a&gt;. And lots of kids getting sick with hand, foot, and mouth disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-1" data-gaid="inarticle-1"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="33TJ5RE26FAVTPMTT4VG5IEUWA"&gt;Doctors are currently seeing a surge in cases of the disease, which is more common in the summer and early fall, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-2" data-gaid="inarticle-2"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="DEZ5H7U4DRCODERPIZSWSC74JY"&gt;“Everyone feels like they know somebody who has it, one way or the other,” said Katharine Clouser, a pediatrician at Hackensack University Medical Center who also serves as president of the New Jersey Chapter of the American Academy of Pediatrics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-3" data-gaid="inarticle-3"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="5KOJ7KXXXRC3DMDZFRGFDTKIPM"&gt;The United States doesn’t currently track individual cases of the disease, so it’s hard to get an exact case count. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-4" data-gaid="inarticle-4"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="P4J7UQ44KFEGTM7V2CFYLLELR4"&gt;But in a statement sent to NJ Advance Media, a spokeswoman for the New Jersey Department of Health said, “Compared to recent years, for reasons that are not clear, we have seen an increase in the number of HFMD outbreaks from May to July of this year.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-5" data-gaid="inarticle-5"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NQCRYSTF6JGXPERU24P4GHYJXE"&gt;As of Aug. 1, 127 outbreaks of hand, foot and mouth disease have been reported statewide, according to data provided by the state health department. That’s more than quadruple the number of outbreaks reported during the same time period last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-6" data-gaid="inarticle-6"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="RZX77Y3H3BFCXBIL2UUTCGLSQA"&gt;Hand, foot and mouth disease is caused by viruses that belong to the enterovirus family, according to the CDC. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-7" data-gaid="inarticle-7"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6VNT6EFOCBG57IIOT7TUJS5QTY"&gt;There are many types of enterovirus, but coxsackievirus is typically the most common cause of hand, foot and mouth disease in the U.S. It mostly causes illness in babies and children under the age of 5, with outbreaks frequently occurring in childcare and preschool settings. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-8" data-gaid="inarticle-8"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="AYUGSCY44VB4DLY23ABJS2RLWU"&gt;Most adults have already been exposed to many enteroviruses in their lifetime and so they have built up immunity. But, that doesn’t mean it’s impossible for adults to get sick. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-9" data-gaid="inarticle-9"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="V4OI2HLMABGEJKSUOTT52F7YFI"&gt;“Anyone of any age really can be infected by hand, foot and mouth disease,” said Clouser. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-10" data-gaid="inarticle-10"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="2OJFYE4Y7RHNFG6WWH3RCJRHXA"&gt;If someone is exposed to the highly contagious illness, symptoms usually develop within three to five days. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-11" data-gaid="inarticle-11"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WPJQH2PIL5ACNPZMADCEAXBM4M"&gt;Symptoms include fever, sore throat, painful mouth sores that blister, and a skin rash commonly found on the hands and feet. The rash may also appear on the knees, elbows, buttocks or genital areas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-12" data-gaid="inarticle-12"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="77N52566ANCIFLSDU2ULD4HFM4"&gt;Most kids have mild symptoms and get better on their own in seven to 10 days. However, in rare cases the illness can cause serious complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-13" data-gaid="inarticle-13"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="N5BG24OG4FDLFOAUKXZXIV6OZI"&gt;“Any virus can be serious,” said Clouser. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-14" class="middleParagraph" data-gaid="inarticle-14"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="6PEVJKWJDZCCFGJO5RTS6QGRRU"&gt;If a parent starts to notice that their kid is refusing liquids, going to the bathroom less, and sleeping more, Clouser said “that would be a reason to seek medical attention.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-15" data-gaid="inarticle-15"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="NGOOUSWFGZCWDO6VEBEK7ZNADE"&gt;Hand, foot and mouth disease is highly contagious and spreads three main ways:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-16" data-gaid="inarticle-16"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="article__unordered-list"&gt;&lt;li id="RDEMGQ4P7ZFPFGBF7OJEAAIOPQ"&gt;&lt;span&gt;By touching an infected person or making other close contact, like kissing, hugging, or sharing cups or eating utensils.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="3LVABWDQCNATFFEL5ASRALHO54"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Through touching objects and surfaces with the virus on them, like doorknobs or toys, then touching your eyes, nose, or mouth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li id="3LSWUWTRLJEYVKHM3RQMXSQF5A"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Through respiratory droplets after a sick person coughs, sneezes, or talks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-17" data-gaid="inarticle-17"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WOU3GKAZ45HJRM7MX4BAT7WKTI"&gt;Although rare, people can also get the virus by swallowing recreational water, like in swimming pools. This can happen if the water is not properly treated with chlorine, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-18" data-gaid="inarticle-18"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="WITA4PJ2PVA3HHPF4HHEWX3JDE"&gt;A sick person is most contagious during the first week of illness and should stay away from others during this time. This means keeping kids out of childcare and school until the fever is gone and mouth sores have healed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-19" data-gaid="inarticle-19"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="D3UIEYOCPJDSRLDFHRINPK35CI"&gt;While hand, foot and mouth disease may make people feel self-conscious, Clouser said people shouldn’t feel ashamed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-20" data-gaid="inarticle-20"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="GWEK2J5HW5BKLFQFHAKGHPJXCE"&gt;“It’s nothing to be embarrassed about. It’s just a virus, and the best way to keep them at bay is to talk to your friends. Tell them ‘Jenny’s got hand, foot and mouth. We saw you last weekend, just be on the lookout,’”Clouser said. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-21" data-gaid="inarticle-21"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="VGL7FRMOHZA4XF55K4EXFALH44"&gt;“Just make sure you’re being honest with those around you, so we can prevent this spread,” said Clouser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-22" data-gaid="inarticle-22"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="EPU3ZNOVK5EK7JQJRTJYTGCF6A"&gt;There is no vaccine in the U.S. to protect against the viruses that cause hand, foot and mouth disease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-23" data-gaid="inarticle-23"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="PTLOTEXLPVHOJAS27FKBYQ6UHM"&gt;The best way to prevent catching or spreading the illness is to practice good hygiene, clean and disinfect surfaces, and avoid close contact with others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-24" data-gaid="inarticle-24"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-enter:4FKJGX6T6BGFFF6SR5E6PDAZOU" data-fusion-component="4FKJGX6T6BGFFF6SR5E6PDAZOU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="fusion-static-exit:4FKJGX6T6BGFFF6SR5E6PDAZOU" data-fusion-component="4FKJGX6T6BGFFF6SR5E6PDAZOU"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-25" data-gaid="inarticle-25"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="JDZB7HTYRRHITMBYYV4PVBBUXA"&gt;&lt;i&gt;Our journalism needs your support. Please subscribe today to&lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt; NJ.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-26" data-gaid="inarticle-26"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--left" id="ZZT64DQ5RVF3NH3A34MCKL2B4U"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nj.com/staff/jroman/posts.html" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;Jackie Roman&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt; may be reached at &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:jroman@njadvancemedia.com" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;jroman@njadvancemedia.com&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;. Find &lt;/i&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/NJ.com" target="_blank" rel=""&gt;&lt;i&gt;NJ.com on Facebook&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;i&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="inarticle-27" data-gaid="inarticle-27"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="article__paragraph article__paragraph--center skimlinks"&gt;If you purchase a product or register for an account through a link on our site, we may receive compensation.&lt;span&gt; By using this site, you consent to our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/user-agreement.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;User Agreement&lt;/a&gt; and agree that your clicks, interactions, and personal information may be collected, recorded, and/or stored by us and social media and other third-party partners in accordance with our &lt;a href="https://www.advancelocal.com/advancelocalUserAgreement/privacy-policy.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NJ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiuwFBVV95cUxQSEhxbWZDb2JOZDZSdUlPd0l2NTFmSGJ6dlRZb29Rb1hnYUd3RFJJaG1hRmVqcWVMZWVnXzJMWlFMczFOT3N1QjZlWF93azdaWWZfcnUteGRuN3haTWNHZE9jWExfWHdxTWJoY2txdnNUTnVEM2FqZnF3VEJjUFVnNy1peVJzQkJXMWswNUlWLVJlSzdjOENNRUhxQjM3ZVJLNG81alNMV0pNMDNpWlZvSzc1SjdrVEJNY2tB0gHPAUFVX3lxTE5iWTNKbDFpeEJHdmlrbkh0b3ZLVk9rWk04MVQzZlRCb0lBaWNabDZJalktYldFRlRtRUFMa1RVUmNQYjMyMGZzNFZyNkdlR2xHMzJJODYzZ3BJYVBKM2R0N29UZl9HeEZ0bGxfbkpZdTItWG1rSWlzY1Q3VUJZUlg5Yml6OTcyV1ZFbkJkS2lKWi11aEtFZDNJelFPYVpvTUU0OFMtaExTWldfMU9NYUNIQlFCQUdDNmh6aVB0Z2gzQUxlSXBGbGpjUlZqTlU4RQ</guid></item><item><title>牙医揭示了早上刷牙的正确时间-现在不是你想象的时候- AOL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMidkFVX3lxTE1JQklTVXJKSDJpU3JxWXFld01zSnc2UGpLREh6enVNbHdBa05qczB2ejYwSk1ZOFY2bUJOSzlubER0RTdnZWIwU25LV283ZFEzVUloWjVzLUNUZTAyTFpKRjFtTlE3YVVJeTU5UzJUMXVsbEVEZ0E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;figure class="caas-figure"&gt;&lt;p class="caption-wrapper caption-aligned-with-image"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="caption-collapse"&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;Should You Brush Your Teeth Before Or After Breakfast?&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class="photo-credit"&gt;DBenitostock - Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, you brush your teeth every morning, but could you be brushing at the wrong time? It turns out there &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a correct time to brush, according to dentists. “Brushing your teeth in the morning is not just about fresh breath — it is a crucial part of protecting your oral and overall health,” says &lt;a href="https://bhdentalarts.com/about/meet-dr-rajpal/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Anjali Rajpal, DMD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Anjali Rajpal, DMD&lt;/a&gt;, the founder of Beverly Hills Dental Arts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, there’s a growing amount of research that shows your dental health goes beyond your teeth and gums. “Good oral health is intricately tied into good overall health and wellness,” says &lt;a href="https://www.beachwoodendo.com/meet-us/dr-steven-katz/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Steven J Katz, DDS, MS;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Steven J Katz, DDS, MS&lt;/a&gt;, the president of the &lt;a href="https://www.aae.org/patients/findmyendodontist/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Association of Endodontists;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;American Association of Endodontists&lt;/a&gt;. “Brushing, flossing and regular dental visits protect not just your mouth, but your heart, lungs, brain and more.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before you get out your toothbrush, use the following tips to maximize your dental routine and time your tooth-brushing perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should you brush before or after breakfast?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both dentists we talked to agreed that if you only brush once in the morning, it’s best to do it right after you wake up — before you have anything to eat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In addition to getting rid of that horrible morning breath, it is important to brush your teeth in the morning to remove the plaque and bacteria that developed overnight,” says Dr. Katz. That’s because when you’re sleeping, your body doesn’t produce as much saliva as it does when you’re awake so there’s no liquid in your mouth to rinse off bacteria throughout the night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If left on your teeth, it will lead to tooth decay and gum disease,” adds Dr. Katz. “And if you breathe with your mouth open while you sleep — as opposed to breathing through your nose — brushing first thing in the morning is even more important, because &lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/22734-mouth-breathing" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:breathing through your mouth;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;breathing through your mouth&lt;/a&gt; dries out the oral tissues, reduces salivary flow and increases plaque build-up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brushing beforehand also “coats your teeth with protective fluoride, hydroxyapatite, calcium phosphate or other minerals that may be in your preferred toothpaste,” says Dr. Rajpal. This “protects your teeth from acid attacks when you eat breakfast, especially if it is something sugary or acidic, says Dr. Rajpal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should you brush again after breakfast?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Probably, but there are a few things to keep in mind so it’s best to double-check with your dentist. “It is not recommended if you have exposed roots, thin enamel or tooth sensitivity because frequent brushing could aggravate it,” says Dr. Rajpal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/14684979/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research suggests;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Research suggests&lt;/a&gt; it's also best to wait 30 minutes after eating or drinking, especially if you’ve had acidic &lt;a href="https://www.womenshealthmag.com/food/a65256285/drink-coffee-live-longer-study-ampk/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:coffee;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;coffee&lt;/a&gt; or juice. “Brushing too soon after acid exposure can actually damage your enamel, which becomes temporarily softened,” says Dr. Rajpal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, you need to consider &lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; you brush your teeth. “The appropriate technique is crucial,” says Dr. Katz. “Brushing too aggressively can lead to gum recession, erosion of the enamel and sensitivity. Speak to your dentist and/or hygienist about the appropriate brushing technique.” They may recommend using a soft-bristled brush with light pressure and avoiding abrasive toothpaste like some that contain baking soda, charcoal or whitening agents, according to Dr. Rajpal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If over-brushing is a concern for you and “if you really want a clean, fresh mouth after breakfast or coffee but have already brushed before, try just rinsing instead with a refreshing natural or alcohol-free mouthwash,” says Dr. Rajpal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Should you also brush after lunch?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“For most people, brushing twice a day, morning and night, is enough to maintain good oral health,” says Dr. Rajpal. “However, brushing after lunch can be a smart move if you are prone to cavities or gum disease; you have eaten something sticky, sugary or acidic; you are wearing braces, aligners, or other appliances that trap food; or you will not be able to brush again for many hours possibly due to a long work shift or travel.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to do a better job of brushing your teeth&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take your oral health care to the next level with these tips for brushing your teeth:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul class="caas-list caas-list-bullet"&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Floss first.&lt;/strong&gt; Dr. Katz recommends flossing before you brush your teeth. &lt;a href="https://aap.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1002/JPER.17-0149" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Research;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; has found that people who floss first remove more plaque from between their teeth and have higher concentrations of fluoride in the plaque.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Don’t rush it. “&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/19723429/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Most people brush for 30 to 45 seconds, but you need a full 2 minutes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Most people brush for 30 to 45 seconds, but you need a full 2 minutes&lt;/a&gt; to properly clean all surfaces of every tooth,” says Dr. Rajpal. “Try using a timer or a song to pace yourself.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Angle your toothbrush.&lt;/strong&gt; “Always hold your brush at a 45-degree angle toward the gumline — not flat against your teeth,” says Dr. Rajpal. “This helps clean where plaque starts, right where the teeth and gums meet.” While you’re at it, make sure you brush your tongue, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you go electric, buy the right one.&lt;/strong&gt; “A $3 manual toothbrush can outperform a $200 electric one if you are using proper technique, brushing long enough and being thorough,” says Dr. Rajpal. “However, if you prefer, a good electric toothbrush often includes timers and pressure sensors to protect your gums.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skip the rinse.&lt;/strong&gt; “After brushing, spit but don’t rinse with water right away,” says Dr. Rajpal. “This leaves fluoride or other toothpaste minerals on your teeth longer, allowing it to strengthen enamel more effectively.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Toss old brushes.&lt;/strong&gt; “Replace your toothbrush or electric brush head every 3 months — or sooner if the bristles are frayed,” says Dr. Rajpal. Store your current brush upright in open air and not enclosed in a case where bacteria can thrive, she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The bottom line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brush your teeth right before bed and right when you wake up and floss daily. See your dentist for regular checkups and don’t ignore pain or sensitivity in your mouth. “Nothing looks, functions or feels like our own teeth,” says Dr. Katz. “Teeth are essential for speech, eating and our all-important smiles. In addition, maintaining healthy teeth leads to &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC11169959/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:improved cardiovascular health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;improved cardiovascular health&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10955347/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reduced risk of diabetes;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;reduced risk of diabetes&lt;/a&gt; and enables &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10870735/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:better cognitive function;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;better cognitive function&lt;/a&gt;. In short, keeping your natural teeth isn’t just about comfort or cosmetics, it’s an investment in your long-term well-being.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You Might Also Like&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMidkFVX3lxTE1JQklTVXJKSDJpU3JxWXFld01zSnc2UGpLREh6enVNbHdBa05qczB2ejYwSk1ZOFY2bUJOSzlubER0RTdnZWIwU25LV283ZFEzVUloWjVzLUNUZTAyTFpKRjFtTlE3YVVJeTU5UzJUMXVsbEVEZ0E</guid></item><item><title>高蛋白饮食可能导致癌症：你应该吃多少-每日邮报</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAJBVV95cUxNcnFYUG54eDU4UWFYNG1rNWFWVUF4Q1ROS2hxcl9CaENOeWhvSC1CUUNIZDRGZ0RxTFI1X29fYzEyZjBaMFEteXRCajNCRV9SdWJVcVR6eXh6N2pUZ2IwbFdDNERuMVozQkRpVWhvX0JrY3NfSDhFMnczU0l1b1l4TTR1YVdEUzdMY19XeUJJaGNqZVlyYWdZd2M4VW5seFpObTVUYTF3cjB4el9qUk1QSEJPbUZkblBkUEYxd3c1RkF4cFZTZGtGYTVkamFxWUNRVS1wZXNIXzU5STIxaURqaTB5M3JYWVlnSEZCampoVzJWX1QxM1JwaWc0enFCT0VXSGptQWhsTDZQM0dlR1lnYmhROFlPTC1t?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A social media trend encouraging women to double their protein intake could be putting them at risk of a range of cancers, one of Britain’s top diet experts has warned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Increasing protein levels has been touted as a way to build muscle and protect against mid-life diseases such as osteoporosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In recent years, the number of supermarket products with ‘added protein’ has surged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to market research firm Mintel, the number of food and drink launches claiming to be high-protein nearly doubled between 2016 and 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the same time, social media is awash with influencers advising viewers on how to boost their protein intake – with menopausal women, who are prone to muscle loss, often targeted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But claims that women need to eat significantly more protein during &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/menopause/index.html" id="mol-31f15f30-74ff-11f0-9400-03163cbeacc0"&gt;menopause&lt;/a&gt; are not only misleading, they could be harmful, warns nutritionist Dr Federica Amati. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Going through the menopause puts women at higher risk of developing osteoporosis and makes it harder to gain and maintain muscle mass,’ says Dr Amati, one of the scientists behind the popular diet app ZOE. ‘But simply increasing your protein intake won’t address this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;But claims that women need to eat significantly more protein during menopause are not only misleading, they could be harmful, warns nutritionist Dr Federica Amati&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Research shows that high intakes of animal protein in mid-life are associated with cancer. For most women, eating more and more protein is not the answer to staying healthy after menopause.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;UK guidelines recommend adults consume about 0.75g of protein per kilogram of body weight. For the average 72kg woman, that equates to approximately 54g a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts agree this is relatively easy to meet: a typical 150g chicken breast contains around 36g of protein, an egg about 6g, a 170–200g serving of Greek yogurt up to 20g, and a portion of kidney beans between 7g and 10g.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Yet some influencers recommend as much as 150g a day to ‘help prevent’ bone fractures and muscle decline in later life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In one Instagram post, an American doctor with 1.3 million followers outlines a daily meal plan that includes egg whites, protein shakes, beef sticks and large servings of meat – totalling more than 140g of protein. And in a TikTok clip viewed more than 430,000 times a UK-based influencer boasts of eating 130g of protein daily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘As a personal trainer and a woman navigating perimenopause, I base my meals around some form of protein,’ her caption reads. ‘Our bodies don’t process and metabolise protein the same way as they did in our 20s and 30s, so we need to eat more of it.’ She adds: ‘If I reach 150g, I’m really pleased with myself.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;UK guidelines recommend adults consume about 0.75g of protein per kilogram of body weight. For the average 72kg woman, that equates to approximately 54g a day&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But Dr Amati says this approach is misguided. ‘Our protein needs do change over time – but the highest requirement is during infancy and childhood, not menopause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘As we age, we produce less growth hormone, so simply eating more protein doesn’t prevent muscle loss. In fact, studies suggest that higher protein intake after the age of 50 can raise the risk of cancer.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A 2014 study from the University of Southern California involving more than 6,000 adults over 50 found that a high-protein diet – where protein accounted for roughly 20 per cent of total calories – was linked to increased risks of cancer, diabetes and mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Adults with the highest protein intake were four times more likely to die of cancer compared with those on a low-protein diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other research suggests that tumours, including melanoma and breast cancer, may grow faster if a patient is on a high-protein diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This, Dr Amati explains, is due to overstimulation of a key cellular pathway responsible for growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Cancer is the uncontrolled proliferation of cells – so overactivating this pathway increases the risk,’ she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Cancer is the uncontrolledproliferation of cells – so overactivating this pathway increases the risk,’ she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Protein from animal sources carries additional risks, she warns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;‘Up to 80 per cent of the protein we eat in the UK comes from animals. But research from Denmark shows that animal protein is richer in certain amino acids that promote fat cell growth and produce compounds linked to heart disease. These amino acids have also been shown to damage cells and tissues, and are linked to neurodegenerative diseases and cancer.’&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;However, cutting back too far is not advised either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Amati says middle-aged women should aim for 1.2g to 1.4g of protein per kg of body weight – more than the NHS guidance, but still easily achievable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She also encourages shifting towards plant-based protein sources, which help boost fibre intake. These include beans, peas, nuts, seeds and oats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:55:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAJBVV95cUxNcnFYUG54eDU4UWFYNG1rNWFWVUF4Q1ROS2hxcl9CaENOeWhvSC1CUUNIZDRGZ0RxTFI1X29fYzEyZjBaMFEteXRCajNCRV9SdWJVcVR6eXh6N2pUZ2IwbFdDNERuMVozQkRpVWhvX0JrY3NfSDhFMnczU0l1b1l4TTR1YVdEUzdMY19XeUJJaGNqZVlyYWdZd2M4VW5seFpObTVUYTF3cjB4el9qUk1QSEJPbUZkblBkUEYxd3c1RkF4cFZTZGtGYTVkamFxWUNRVS1wZXNIXzU5STIxaURqaTB5M3JYWVlnSEZCampoVzJWX1QxM1JwaWc0enFCT0VXSGptQWhsTDZQM0dlR1lnYmhROFlPTC1t</guid></item><item><title>科学家确定身体和组织开始迅速衰老的年龄-今日医学新闻</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxPNm52NVpvSVVqQ2VsaTNBZHlmdGhTU2pBUG5vS1ZLOU5YRnhtY3VteVZ4cjEtM2ZmeVZxSHpRLXl4dWhrYUpESTkwVW1tYW5ySE41VzN1Y2g1dEM2TDktZGhvRTRicFN1WElzUm1QS2xaRG53SGtPalJXODFwN2lIQmF1TzhPbzFqRldzSVUtWGJvYko4LTEtWXdoMTFCWFE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-12va8w7"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;figure class="css-yhe8zq"&gt;&lt;span class="css-rwmw5v"&gt;&lt;span class="css-mjp0j9"&gt;&lt;picture class="css-16pk1is"&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/breathless-mature-woman-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 1190px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/breathless-mature-woman-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 750w" media="(min-width: 990px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;source srcset="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/breathless-mature-woman-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg 879w" media="(min-width: 768px)"&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;img src="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/breathless-mature-woman-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg" alt="A middle aged woman holds her knees, her body slightly bent over, catching her breath after a run outside" class="css-1jytyml"&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;hl-share-overlay class="css-1mqo1cs"&gt;&lt;a class="icon-hl-pinterest css-11oz8gb" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer nofollow" data-event="Any Page|Image Pinterest Click|Icon Clicked" data-element-event="OPEN|CONTENTBLOCK|Any Page|Article Body|BUTTON|Image Widget Pinterest Click|" href="https://www.pinterest.com/pin/create/button/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.medicalnewstoday.com%2Farticles%2Fstudy-finds-turning-point-when-body-starts-aging-rapidly&amp;amp;media=https%3A%2F%2Fmedia.post.rvohealth.io%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fsites%2F3%2F2025%2F08%2Fbreathless-mature-woman-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg&amp;amp;description=Scientists%20pinpoint%20age%20when%20body%20and%20tissues%20start%20aging%20rapidly" title="Share on Pinterest" data-pin-custom="true" data-share-url="https://media.post.rvohealth.io/wp-content/uploads/sites/3/2025/08/breathless-mature-woman-1296x728-header-1024x575.jpg"&gt;&lt;span class="css-z1zfa"&gt;Share on Pinterest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-share-overlay&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;figcaption class="css-13b3g0x"&gt;The human body experiences rapid changes around age 50, according to a new study. Maskot/Getty Images&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Past studies show that human aging doesn’t necessarily happen at the same pace throughout our life. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;There is still much to discover about the aging process, especially when it comes to how it impacts the body’s organs.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A new study found that by focusing on aging-related protein changes in the body, there is an acceleration in aging of organs and tissues around the age of 50. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And of these proteins, scientists found that expressions of 48 of them linked to diseases increased with age, such as cardiovascular and liver disease. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;While we can try to slow it down, human aging is something we currently can’t stop from happening. However, past studies show that aging doesn’t necessarily happen at the same pace throughout our life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, there are certain ages when a person’s body may experience a burst of aging. Previous studies show that the body may undergo rapid aging around the &lt;hl-trusted-source source="Nature" rationale="Highly respected journal,Expert written journal,Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s43587-024-00692-2" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;ages of 44 and 60&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;And there is still much to discover about the aging process, especially when it comes to how it impacts the body’s organs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Aging, as a systemic, degenerative process that spans multiple organs and biological strata, remains one of the most profound unresolved questions in the life sciences,” &lt;a href="http://english.ioz.cas.cn/sourcedb/scs/202310/t20231030_431110.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Guang-Hui Liu, PhD&lt;/a&gt;, regenerative medicine researcher at the Chinese Academy of Sciences, explained to &lt;em&gt;Medical News Today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Throughout the extended human lifespan, two fundamental issues persist: Do all organ systems adhere to a unified aging rhythm? Does a molecular spatiotemporal hub exist that orchestrates organism-wide senescence? Despite their centrality to understanding the essence of aging, these questions have long lacked systematic, empirical resolution.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Liu is the corresponding author of a new study recently published in the journal &lt;hl-trusted-source source="Cell" rationale="Peer reviewed journal"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/abstract/S0092-8674(25)00749-4?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0092867425007494%3Fshowall%3Dtrue;" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Cell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt; that has found that by focusing on aging-related protein changes in the body, they can get a clearer picture of how the body’s organs and tissues age over time, including an aging acceleration around the age of 50. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this study, researchers analyzed 516 samples of 13 types of human tissues collected from 76 organ donors between the ages of 14 and 68 who had passed away from traumatic brain injury. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The tissue samples included cardiovascular, digestive, respiratory, &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/endocrine-system-function" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;endocrine&lt;/a&gt;, and musculoskeletal samples, as well as immune system, skin, and blood samples. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, researchers documented the types of proteins found in the organ and tissue samples, allowing them to create what Liu called “a &lt;a href="http://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8473418/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;proteomic&lt;/a&gt; aging atlas” that spans 50 years of human life. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Covering seven physiological systems and thirteen pivotal tissues, the atlas presents a panoramic, dynamic portrait of organismal aging from a protein-centric perspective,” Liu explained. “The more than 20,000 proteins encoded by the &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/gene-vs-genome" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;genome&lt;/a&gt; serve as the structural bedrock of cells; their dynamic networks exquisitely orchestrate physiological homeostasis and act as the principal executors of virtually every biological process.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Consequently, systematically charting a panoramic, lifespan-wide atlas of proteomic dynamics and dissecting the reprogramming rules of protein networks at organ- and system-level scales are pivotal for accurately identifying the core drivers of aging and for establishing precise intervention targets,” he added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the study’s conclusion, researchers found that the biggest aging changes in the body’s organs and tissues seems to occur around age 50. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The critical aging window&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Ages 45–55 are identified as a landmark inflection point: most organ proteomes undergo a ‘molecular cascade storm,’ with differentially expressed proteins surging explosively, marking this interval as the critical biological transition window for systemic, multi-organ aging.” &lt;br&gt;— Guang-Hui Liu, PhD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Notably, the aortic proteome is reshaped most dramatically; its &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7169381/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;secretome&lt;/a&gt; and the circulating plasma proteome evolve in tight concordance, indicating that senescence-associated secreted factors (senokines) may serve as the hub mechanism broadcasting aging signals throughout the body,” Liu explained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additionally, Liu and his team found that expressions of 48 of the proteins linked to diseases, including cardiovascular disease, fatty liver disease, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC9963026/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;tissue fibrosis&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/liver-tumor" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;liver-related tumors&lt;/a&gt;, increased with age. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Organ aging is the essence of human chronic disease; each geriatric illness is merely a specific manifestation of this underlying organ aging,” Liu added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; had the opportunity to speak with &lt;a href="https://www.memorialcare.org/providers/cheng-han-chen" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Cheng-Han Chen, MD&lt;/a&gt;, a board certified interventional cardiologist and medical director of the Structural Heart Program at MemorialCare Saddleback Medical Center in Laguna Hills, CA, about this study. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This study found that protein changes in the body associated with aging seem to accelerate roughly around age 50, depending on the type of body tissue. This is an interesting finding that helps us better understand the types of biochemical changes that underlie aging and potentially provide targets for therapy at different stages of someone’s life.” &lt;br&gt;— Cheng-Han Chen, MD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Science is only beginning to understand the biological mechanisms involved in aging,” Chen said. “Studies like this help us to identify the basis of normal aging, and in turn provides insight into how deviations in normal biology lead to diseases such as cardiovascular disease and fatty liver disease. Ultimately, this will help us understand how to keep our patients healthy and aging well. It may also help us to develop new therapies for diseases that result from accelerated aging.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Future research should attempt to expand on these findings in more diverse demographic groups and as well as in other important organs such as the brain and kidneys,” he added. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-testid="tabbed-article-section" class="css-1avyp1d"&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;MNT&lt;/em&gt; also talked to &lt;a href="https://doctors.hackensackmeridianhealth.org/provider/manisha-santosh-parulekar/1319173" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Manisha Parulekar, MD&lt;/a&gt;, chief of the Division of Geriatrics at Hackensack University Medical Center in New Jersey, about this research. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;blockquote class="is-layout-flow wp-block-quote-is-layout-flow css-34gtoi"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How aging affects the whole body&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The idea that our cells lose the ability to maintain a healthy and functional proteome (the collection of proteins) is a cornerstone of modern aging theory. The accumulation of misfolded proteins, like &lt;hl-trusted-source source="PubMed Central" rationale="Highly respected database from the National Institutes of Health"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK459119/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;amyloids&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/hl-trusted-source&gt;, is the classic example, best known in neurodegenerative diseases like &lt;a href="https://www.medicalnewstoday.com/articles/159442" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener" class="content-link css-90fpmc"&gt;Alzheimer’s disease&lt;/a&gt;. This study’s finding of widespread amyloid accumulation across many tissues confirms that this isn’t just a brain-specific problem but a systemic feature of aging.”&lt;br&gt;— Manisha Parulekar, MD&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“This research is about transforming medicine from a reactive, disease-focused model to a proactive, health-focused one,” she continued. “By understanding the what and the when of aging, we can develop the tools to compress morbidity — allowing people to live not just longer, but healthier and more vibrant lives.” &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;“A longitudinal study, following the same individuals over decades will be helpful,” Parulekar added when asked what she would like to see as next steps for this research. “This would track their personal proteomic changes over time, allowing us to study genetic and lifestyle differences between people and providing additional confirmation for the ‘age 50 inflection point’.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;span class="css-zya54r"&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Medical News Today</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:35:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxPNm52NVpvSVVqQ2VsaTNBZHlmdGhTU2pBUG5vS1ZLOU5YRnhtY3VteVZ4cjEtM2ZmeVZxSHpRLXl4dWhrYUpESTkwVW1tYW5ySE41VzN1Y2g1dEM2TDktZGhvRTRicFN1WElzUm1QS2xaRG53SGtPalJXODFwN2lIQmF1TzhPbzFqRldzSVUtWGJvYko4LTEtWXdoMTFCWFE</guid></item><item><title>房客专栏|一种疾病袭击了我的整个身体。我的医生告诉我要减肥。-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxNalFZT2ZiLU5zaWotckpCVE9HclE2SlZ6bGpNMDZaQXBRTlVGQlY4WEdkaTdDYXY3SXcwUEJRdFBLTWFsUHRoRVNxVXBmODgwZ2xJNVZsSVg2VkxyeUtkMmYway1zdGx6WFhXTXFsakhjUWtwd3JfRnBGN2s0eXhkVU9nNmFzYkNyak5LVEUycUtXZmh2b0xr?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="K2QDRKE2MFBNNM5MCIZXHYZTAU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In 2022, I gained 40 pounds in one year and was tired all the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7PPOUFUCFNCK3MTR5QB2AHLD7Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Before these changes, at 47, I biked and walked everywhere in my Los Angeles neighborhood. I wrote articles frequently. And I raised my daughter with ease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AF6L7RQKTNF7ZPDGSNKUPC6RP4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;When I told my doctor about my health issues, she sighed, reeled off obesity risks and admonished, “Lose weight. &lt;i&gt;For your daughter&lt;/i&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QXC5UO3DRRD63PI3EI6MFCGCPA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I also met with several other doctors, most of whom blamed stress, weight gain or age for my poor health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CHYJUV3DQRAVDIMDKUZGWFWXWI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;It took three years, thousands of dollars and two inches of height for me to get the right diagnosis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3NN657XFNZE5XKV3GZRMT2BO54" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My health journey may read like a medical mystery, but it wasn’t. At least seven doctors saw my abnormal lab results over three years, and only the very last one followed the protocol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="FRQ43IG7A5FXNJTZSADG7YEGSI" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="FRQ43IG7A5FXNJTZSADG7YEGSI" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Weight gain and anemia&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RYO44DLXJNFRVM4L5PAREFX4SU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My 2022 labs were flagged for high calcium. But my doctor said everything was “normal” and prescribed metformin, a diabetes drug sometimes used off-label for weight loss. I wasn’t diabetic, just overweight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3NT2K6GEO5AUNMRLPN5LB7AAGM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I took the metformin and logged every calorie, but the weight wouldn’t budge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LT5PVJUY7VGI3E6HTWR7MFZLNE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;By 2023, my periods turned erratic and were so heavy I sometimes changed tampons every hour and thought I was hemorrhaging. But my gynecologist didn’t seem to believe me when I told them how much blood I was losing, saying, “If that were true, you’d be dead.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OHZLQWEFFFELJIENI3ZA47QH4Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;On a trip, breathless, I could not make it up a small hill near the Tower of London and begged my family to slow down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MJTERZLHHBGFZNFXCFRDRM3DSA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In 2024, I found a new primary care doctor, who promised to treat “the whole person.” She, too, urged me to keep losing weight. I started a GLP-1 injection, paying $550 a month out of pocket that insurance wouldn’t cover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LEV6NURXNVA6LK4NHFIKCNXNKQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The weight began to drop, but soon I was breathless again just making my bed or showering. I returned to my doctor, insistent that something was still not right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="5LB3JDMYF5GVREG6LG5BMSIPYI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Fresh labs showed severe anemia from chronic blood loss. After trying iron pills, iron infusions and tranexamic acid to clot the bleeding, I opted for a uterine artery embolization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3MC2ILJNTFDAJC4OETL3XJ45WQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The pain was excruciating. But it worked, the anemia was resolved, and my hematologist wrote in my chart: “Patient says she can’t remember the last time she felt this good.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GUCV6IMEBFEWHOJKSBZ4VGYGRE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But by fall, I had severe hot flashes, night sweats and persistent insomnia. Again, I went for tests. My thyroid was fine, and my hormones did not indicate menopause. My chart notes read: “Weight. Stress.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ODEHS2TNUJEMHDMV3TQHNPCRGA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Desperate, I turned to hormone replacement therapy. It soon calmed the flashes and sweats, but not the insomnia, exhaustion, or the new symptom of extreme thirst. Even with hormones balanced, I lay awake for hours, my nerves frayed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="V3XGFLIVLJECTN3RBREZIPXKGM" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="V3XGFLIVLJECTN3RBREZIPXKGM" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Memory loss and anxiety&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MYS34Y7JVFGK3BYRCESGAGI3JQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;By early 2025, I thought I was losing my mind. I was certainly losing my memory. Names and words escaped me. I lived in a state of buzzing exhaustion that left me unable to work, drive safely or attend my daughter’s school events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CMGTIQRKBBFRHGY3HS7WEBCERA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The weight kept dropping. Now I was lighter, but workouts I’d once conquered were impossible. My bones and joints began to scream with pain. Lying down was all that felt good, and, soon, lying down was all I did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="T4VE7DJYMJEB5OVWGFI4AU663A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I once read four papers a day and suggested story ideas to publications constantly. Now, I could barely scan headlines, much less summon the mental acuity to generate ideas, and when I did manage to write, my brain was so fried that I collapsed afterward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GMYKPSYMYNGJ3BKAJOYG23JYQQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Sleep became torture. I woke up hourly throughout the night. By morning, I was too exhausted to get my daughter to school. My partner took over every aspect of the household.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="J7OHY7U4KRF2BA7Y3XD4XVS3MQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Then, a crawling, physical anxiety began tearing through me at random.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="FALRIOVLCJDK7FT6VO55H7IFOY" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="FALRIOVLCJDK7FT6VO55H7IFOY" data-testid="article-header"&gt;A chance diagnosis based on calcium spikes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WX5JHGMI4FG6JPMY6QI43XHCP4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In April, I saw a new doctor who was covering for my regular one. I’d lost all the weight, but I cried explaining how my body felt hijacked by relentless dread and anxiety. She prescribed a beta blocker for my racing heart and, crucially, drew blood for new tests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NDMAFOXZFZACXGMVHOIFQVVVRE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The next day she messaged me: “Your calcium is elevated. We need to check your parathyroid.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="T2IRANRNYZFUBNTSGDY6ARXC5Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I raced to my medical records. My calcium had been steadily climbing since 2022. I could chart each new terrible symptom alongside every spike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AUSUUB2LCNCYNP7UDQ7Q2NVXCQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A follow-up test confirmed my parathyroid hormone (PTH) was elevated. It was textbook biochemical primary hyperparathyroidism (PHPT).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RTKFHE2PLRGQVAGPRUUEQ2MKIY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There are four tiny rice-size glands near your thyroid, called the parathyroid glands. They have one job: to regulate the calcium and phosphorus in your blood. Calcium builds bones and teeth, but it’s also the electrical current powering the heart, muscles and brain and is essential for nerve signaling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FLQQUPQVIBC45DACF6B6U3O7OQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If even one of those glands goes rogue, often because a benign tumor raises the parathyroid hormone, it tricks the body into pulling more calcium from bones, weakening the skeleton, damaging kidneys, disrupting heart function and altering mood. It also comes with a&lt;a href="https://www.hyperparathyroidmd.com/hyperparathyroidism-symptoms/" target="_blank"&gt; host of possible symptoms&lt;/a&gt;: fatigue, insomnia, thirst, memory issues, hair loss — symptoms doctors call “nonspecific” because they &lt;a href="https://www.southwestparathyroid.com/blog/why-your-doctor-doesn-t-recognize-the-symptoms-of-parathyroid-disease#:~:text=In%20addition%20to%20%E2%80%9Cstones%2C%20bones,just%20%E2%80%9Cmild%E2%80%9D%20calcium%20elevations." target="_blank"&gt;overlap with hundreds of other conditions&lt;/a&gt;. Left untreated, PHPT is progressive and even fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="43IMQDA32FFMVNI4ZECNCNYKVQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;PHPT is the third most common endocrine disorder after diabetes and thyroid disease, &lt;a href="https://www.niddk.nih.gov/health-information/endocrine-diseases/primary-hyperparathyroidism" target="_blank"&gt;affecting about 100,000 Americans each&lt;/a&gt; year. Historically, PHPT was diagnosed by late-stage symptoms: kidney stones or fractures. Now, routine blood tests catch elevated calcium levels earlier. (Some experts warn that calcium even &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@drmichaelljohnson1/video/7355875607881796910?_r=1&amp;amp;_t=ZT-8y55OxCg31p" target="_blank"&gt;at 10 mg/dL&lt;/a&gt; can signal trouble.) But this means many patients now present with “nonspecific” symptoms, so doctors may ignore mildly elevated calcium and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/a-bad-diagnosis/2015/08/24/b17606c2-12ac-11e5-89f3-61410da94eb1_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;miss the parathyroid connection&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="K4FYDURXTJHE3HFSMS3JDZ3JBE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The&lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/jbmr/article/37/11/2293/7512381" target="_blank"&gt; standard of care&lt;/a&gt; for elevated calcium is clear: Repeat the calcium test, and check the parathyroid hormone. That protocol is posted on the websites of most major hospitals, including the one where I was a patient.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7JDSCH2FFZH4PLPCHHBAJEVCXQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Yet one&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6738291/" target="_blank"&gt; study&lt;/a&gt; found half of the patients with high calcium got no further testing, and even when both calcium and PTH were high — the definition of PHPT — 40 percent still went undiagnosed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="T3XBHM56MVHFRIX2CU4ISXDVFM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Delayed diagnosis is costly, because managing PHPT damage&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6561104/#:~:text=Failure%20to%20diagnose%20primary%20hyperparathyroidism,and%20under%2Dreferral%20to%20surgeons." target="_blank"&gt; costs far more&lt;/a&gt; than its &lt;i&gt;only&lt;/i&gt; cure: a parathyroidectomy to remove the bad gland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="3YK6ZQETIFDQJHCYWUWSSB6H7Y" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="3YK6ZQETIFDQJHCYWUWSSB6H7Y" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Lost inches&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="QIIEFBARA5HCNNE7GUIYNDF6NE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;And then, I learned I was shorter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CIBUT2EIP5E5PCKZODXJIABMHU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;At my next follow-up, a nurse measured my height. As I stood up as straight as I could, pain shot through my mid-back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KNJWFOQP5BG73CWMIQ5P3B24BA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“5’9,” she said. “What?!” I blurted. “I’m 5’11.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3Y6FHJY5KZF6DPEXAZBT57NNRA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Maybe you were measured with shoes on before,” she said, shrugging. We lose about a half-inch of height per decade after age 40, yet I’d lost two inches in a year from bone loss from hypercalcemia, or excess calcium, and probably from &lt;a href="http://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/1555067/" target="_blank"&gt;muscle deconditioning&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4NJK5XDCP5EATICLIJHQJBASTU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A bone density scan delivered the final blow: I now had osteopenia. My bones were thinner, more fragile and prone to fracture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="OOJOLVHXNJAAVEZWXQB7YL2H3E" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="OOJOLVHXNJAAVEZWXQB7YL2H3E" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Surgery for primary hyperparathyroidism&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MRPYBWAADZDUXABUQRWX7MUWGA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To cure the condition, I needed a parathyroidectomy and opted for an approach in which the surgeon uses a smaller incision, explores all four glands, removes the bad one and confirms success by checking hormone levels during surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XLAXAXFCHNGVHOOX7YBC2MYRZQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My doctor, &lt;a href="https://larianmd.com/about-dr-larian/" target="_blank"&gt;Babak Larian&lt;/a&gt;, a head and neck surgeon and the clinical chief of the division of otolaryngology at Cedars-Sinai Hospital in Los Angeles, said his cure rate is up to 98 percent with this technique. (It’s important to find a highly skilled surgeon, and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3224988/" target="_blank"&gt;research suggests&lt;/a&gt; the outcomes are better if you use a doctor who performs more than 50 of these procedures each year.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="E5ZGJDJADZH3ZFOBALEVXN3UUY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My PTH dropped to normal within minutes, confirming success. Recovery was mild: some pain, a sore throat, a small scar, and a strict regimen of calcium supplementation until my remaining glands took over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2KFVI43SBFBELP53VVW7BCBRS4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Soon, the world snapped back into focus. I slept deeply within a week, the bone and joint pain vanished. My back still aches from bone loss, but I can walk the block, do laundry and remember things again&lt;del&gt;.&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="AG7JELMTJBGOVL3BVOBURJBS2E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;My thoughts have cleared enough to read, converse and write this essay. On the Fourth of July, I even made it to the beach and a barbecue. I have a long road of physical therapy ahead, but it feels as if my life has been handed back to me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="WFQMCKRPIFGLBBP55N2EBJJU5Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I asked my surgeon why no one talks about this condition. “Because it’s not sexy,” he said. “Angelina Jolie would have to get this disease for people to notice. I call it an orphan disease.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RM3JIORJ6VCYJF337FSX3HQYUA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;And why do so many doctors miss it? It may be training.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="YEHHOMUUH5AETBUOUPYUSFIBPY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In medical school, students spend only&lt;a href="https://www.endocrinepractice.org/article/S1530-891X(22)00486-4/fulltext" target="_blank"&gt; 20 to 60 hours&lt;/a&gt; on all endocrine diseases, memorizing the mnemonic “stones, bones, groans and moans,” short for kidney stones, bone pain (or fractures), abdominal pain and neurocognitive changes. PHPT is diagnosed by blood tests, so doctors who rely on the mnemonic may overlook biochemical results.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MLTDFZJLIJCRXGPSDVKRCECLQ4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Women are&lt;a href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK441895/" target="_blank"&gt; three to four times as likely&lt;/a&gt; to have PHPT and don’t often present with kidney stones but with brain fog or mood changes, symptoms &lt;a href="https://www.parathyroid.com/blog/top-5-symptoms-of-hyperparathyroidism-in-women#:~:text=And%20since%20we%20know%20women,a%20fog%20that%20lifts%20overnight%E2%80%9D." target="_blank"&gt;easily dismissed&lt;/a&gt; as menopause or issues with mental health. Older patients are often told it’s “&lt;a href="https://www.parathyroid.com/blog/the-top-10-symptoms-of-hyperparathyroidism-presented-with-real-patient-examples" target="_blank"&gt;just aging&lt;/a&gt;.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="TKMCZHIR7JCW5B5BZITS2VDNJI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The experience has infuriated me. I believe doctors saw my weight gain and age and made assumptions that allowed them to look no further. I chased every symptom but the true cause and may have even had a surgery I did not need because of high calcium’s &lt;a href="https://www.factsaboutfertility.org/endocrine-disorders-and-menstrual-disturbances-a-review/" target="_blank"&gt;impact on my menstrual cycles&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="D3BVDML7LBDEBNG2L2ZKHK26UI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;I’m not alone. Parathyroid support forums are&lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Parathyroid_Awareness/" target="_blank"&gt; full of people&lt;/a&gt; who’ve suffered longer than I did, dismissed while losing their minds and bodies to “nonspecific symptoms” or told their calcium wasn’t high enough to explain their symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="E47KV6AOW5BWHH4CN5VERQHU6I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;They urge people, and now I do, too: If your calcium is high and your doctor dismisses it, find another doctor. I can’t get back the years — or probably the inches — I lost. But maybe telling my story will help someone else keep theirs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:31:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxNalFZT2ZiLU5zaWotckpCVE9HclE2SlZ6bGpNMDZaQXBRTlVGQlY4WEdkaTdDYXY3SXcwUEJRdFBLTWFsUHRoRVNxVXBmODgwZ2xJNVZsSVg2VkxyeUtkMmYway1zdGx6WFhXTXFsakhjUWtwd3JfRnBGN2s0eXhkVU9nNmFzYkNyak5LVEUycUtXZmh2b0xr</guid></item><item><title>伯克郡西尼罗河病毒引发的担忧与日俱增- WFMZ.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi1gFBVV95cUxQZC1CeTJ1b2dwbkV1U3FVRFZjMWxUM2E0VWRqRm1iRkN0Q2ZfeDhKRmRtX25rWVRpRXN3Wm55WjZRbzNLLW15Q203d2FsVFJHRnE3M0t2VWFDRHVUTHFTTXYxZUFUOFdtelc0T1dONEo0eTJqTGdhZ2RCTGt2eXZkZFFUWndFdkVHeFlOd21JT3FLaWZkVWdOUnRnbHZwTk96OHRGUlAxeG9mT2FFcHBYV1JLUkp1aV9oZGhxZWMzSC1ESGM4RmxpdW5OMWR3V05uWG9Hbmx3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" itemprop="articleBody" class="asset-content  subscriber-premium" false&gt;
                                &lt;meta itemprop="isAccessibleForFree" content="true"&gt;
                                
                                
                                &lt;p&gt;READING, Pa. - West Nile virus continues to cause concerns in the Berks area, after mosquitoes in several areas test positive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"That's very concerning about viruses," says Aamiah Switon, Reading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over at city park, during a friendly game of basketball, worry unfolds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"It's actually very concerning, because like being outside is like a fun activity, and I don't want it to harm me in any relationship with any form, shape or way," says Jalen Whaream, Reading.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials say mosquitos in Reading and Shillington tested positive for West Nile Virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I don't even like it. I don't even like bugs like that. But now, knowing there's viruses going around that's very concerning. I've had some broad spray," Switon says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The West Nile Virus is most commonly spread through a bite from an infected mosquito. Fortunately, most people infected with West Nile virus do not feel sick. About 1 out of 150 infected people develop a serious, sometimes fatal, illness, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/west-nile-virus/index.html" target="_blank"&gt;CDC&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And while the current risk of transmission is low, officials say continued virus activity could require an adult mosquito control, known as truck spray, in the affected area, the city says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_middle" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"I might stay home," Switon says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The city says residents are encouraged to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Stay indoors during dusk-to-dawn mosquito activity hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Wear long sleeves, pants, and closed-toed shoes outdoors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Use insect repellent containing at least 30% DEET.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;- Remove standing water from their property to eliminate mosquito breeding sites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the CDC, symptoms can include fever, headache, body aches, vomiting, diarrhea, or rash.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are no vaccines to prevent or medicines to treat West Nile virus disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="tncms-region-article_instory_bottom" class="tncms-region hidden-print"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                                
                                
                            &lt;/div&gt;

                            

                            
    


                            
    


                            
                                &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WFMZ.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:03:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi1gFBVV95cUxQZC1CeTJ1b2dwbkV1U3FVRFZjMWxUM2E0VWRqRm1iRkN0Q2ZfeDhKRmRtX25rWVRpRXN3Wm55WjZRbzNLLW15Q203d2FsVFJHRnE3M0t2VWFDRHVUTHFTTXYxZUFUOFdtelc0T1dONEo0eTJqTGdhZ2RCTGt2eXZkZFFUWndFdkVHeFlOd21JT3FLaWZkVWdOUnRnbHZwTk96OHRGUlAxeG9mT2FFcHBYV1JLUkp1aV9oZGhxZWMzSC1ESGM4RmxpdW5OMWR3V05uWG9Hbmx3</guid></item><item><title>锂如何从7Up转变为精神疾病的治疗—可能还有阿尔茨海默氏症-《华盛顿邮报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinAFBVV95cUxPeHNYVWl1S1FqRHNxalFMNWR6UEdhaXEyN3FBZldZMU9Tb1QyU3dQc1hGQWN0dDE5UkZ3SGtGVUk2NUFKVk8xWWFZRXJONzVSZ1Rzdnc1WDdFNm9lUEcyMklJN09YTWtvYkZsdC1kNWN2RWpyeEkzcGRUMEt6M3pGX2NVNEJ0WlA2LVUwZ1RWdW80UVlLVWFENnlpalA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="U6NGJRUHAVBD7AURRISXUMGHJU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2025/08/06/lithium-reverses-alzheimers-mice/?utm_campaign=wp_the7&amp;amp;utm_medium=email&amp;amp;utm_source=newsletter&amp;amp;carta-url=https%3A%2F%2Fs2.washingtonpost.com%2Fcar-ln-tr%2F4406f76%2F689484deaed508115aca0314%2F62d55c2a560643501904a9ea%2F59%2F108%2F689484deaed508115aca0314"&gt;study &lt;/a&gt;this week in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41586-025-09335-x"&gt;Nature &lt;/a&gt;found that the loss of lithium, a naturally occurring element in the brain, could be an early sign of Alzheimer’s and a powerful driver of the disease, which afflicts more than 7 million Americans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MRDTC4RDRNGOFMSHXQ2FVYCR7Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The study, led by Bruce A. Yankner, a professor of genetics and neurology at Harvard Medical School, found that lithium is important to the health of all  the major types of brain cells in mice. Depletion of lithium in the brain also seems to be a factor in almost all of the major deterioration that occurs with Alzheimer’s disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KVJK76GBF5FLFCWQ63HV3NO3MA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;While the latest study of lithium is novel in pointing toward a potential Alzheimer’s treatment, the use of lithium to treat other conditions is not. Here’s a look at what it has worked for and how its use is being researched in new ways.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="list-header-JEQCBXAFSZD6PCNCCSODA6VKV4-3" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;h2 id="JEQCBXAFSZD6PCNCCSODA6VKV4" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="JEQCBXAFSZD6PCNCCSODA6VKV4" data-testid="article-header"&gt;What is lithium?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#secondary-nav" class="skip-link sr-only sr-only-focusable black underline brad-md pa-lg mb-xs border-box font-sans-serif font-bold"&gt;Return to menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="53LQYKE7PVGHJB2CNWEQOJMPCE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lithium, soft and silvery, is nature’s lightest metal, enabling it to store energy at high density and discharge electrons rapidly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DX9T3K8UU52BX7HCGBZE77AE1G" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“This is the basis of the lithium battery that powers our phones, laptops and electric vehicles,” Yankner said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ADRQ47QZUZEQNCKDUTRBI7L4GI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Less well known is that the original formulation of the soft drink 7Up contained lithium; the drink was marketed under the name Bib-Label Lithiated Lemon-Lime Soda. The lithium was removed in 1948 after the &lt;a href="https://www.psychiatrictimes.com/view/lithium-past-present-and-future"&gt;Food and Drug Administration banned&lt;/a&gt; the use of lithium citrate in soft drinks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SEOAI6TYZRALZFB2ML3HCB2WBA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;As of 2024, Australia was the world’s largest producer of lithium, though Bolivia, Chile and Argentina are known as the “lithium triangle.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="list-header-BTFEVA76ABGRFEQ6WXHLXH4HRQ-8" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;h2 id="BTFEVA76ABGRFEQ6WXHLXH4HRQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="BTFEVA76ABGRFEQ6WXHLXH4HRQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;How has lithium been used for mental health treatment?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#secondary-nav" class="skip-link sr-only sr-only-focusable black underline brad-md pa-lg mb-xs border-box font-sans-serif font-bold"&gt;Return to menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MFD37JP5LZBT3JDVJVKVK5JE5A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A form of lithium, lithium carbonate, has been widely prescribed in the treatment of bipolar disease&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;in the United States since it was first approved by the FDA in 1970. It is believed to be a mood stabilizer and can also be prescribed for long-term treatment of depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2LG3XUNAG5FRXOMMI7XCTFDQEA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;While the precise mechanism of lithium carbonate isn’t known, it is believed to suppress stress in the brain and help restore neuroplasticity — the brain’s ability to change and adapt as we get older. One of the findings of the Nature study was that our brains contain a small amount of naturally occurring lithium.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2OGLMZASQJGETKUBZJW7MIAYSQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There are cases of lithium being used in psychiatry going back to the mid-19th century, but the study of lithium for mood disorders took a larger step in the late 1940s when an Australian psychiatrist, John Cade, found that it helped many bipolar patients stabilize quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3E4GGKQZ7VHZPFEMHFBXPHSN5I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“It’s been around for decades, and we have a lot of research and a lot of evidence supporting its use,” said Elizabeth Hoge, a professor of psychiatry at Georgetown University School of Medicine. “The most important thing is that it does help patients. We know that it works from randomized, controlled trials.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="3IHWR7BSNRGULC5LHI7ZZSJGZI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Hoge said the use of lithium does require &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0140673614618420#:~:text=Lithium%20treatment%20is%20associated%20with,and%20regular%20long%2Dterm%20monitoring."&gt;monitoring&lt;/a&gt; of renal and thyroid function, which can decline in some cases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OK4L7M7XIFFVFFDCXXDEFQJTTI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Balwinder Singh, an assistant professor of psychiatry at the Mayo Clinic, said lithium remains the “gold standard” medication for bipolar disorder, though it is under-prescribed in his view. About 10 to 15 percent of Americans with bipolar disorder take lithium, compared with about 35 percent of patients in &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10813799/#:~:text=This%20review%20included%2055%20articles,e.g.%2C%20lower%20suicide%20risk)."&gt;Europe&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FLUHDY2D7VFLLBZZRNOUCCVEIU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Lithium is the only mood stabilizer consistently shown to reduce suicidality in individuals with bipolar disorder,” according to a recent comment Singh wrote in the journal &lt;a href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/lanpsy/article/PIIS2215-0366(25)00026-4/abstract"&gt;Lancet Psychiatry&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2TZ5RLIREZCMPM7FZC4UP5KGKI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Although lithium has been widely prescribed and its use is supported in many studies,&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S0165032722003962?via%3Dihub"&gt; a 2022 paper&lt;/a&gt; argued that its effect on bipolar depression, a part of bipolar disorder, does not represent a statistically significant improvement over a placebo or antidepressants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="list-header-NBYXGUTOPJFUHLP3ODQVR6UPGE-17" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;h2 id="NBYXGUTOPJFUHLP3ODQVR6UPGE" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="NBYXGUTOPJFUHLP3ODQVR6UPGE" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Why is lithium being researched for Alzheimer’s?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#secondary-nav" class="skip-link sr-only sr-only-focusable black underline brad-md pa-lg mb-xs border-box font-sans-serif font-bold"&gt;Return to menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VSYXBRNOVRGW5MV45UWHXOQXCI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lithium had been investigated previously as a potential Alzheimer’s treatment and antiaging medication. A &lt;a href="https://psychiatryonline.org/doi/10.1176/appi.pn.2017.10a17#:~:text=Sc.%2C%20of%20the%20University%20of,but%20this%20association%20was%20nonlinear."&gt;2017 study&lt;/a&gt; in Denmark found that the presence of lithium in drinking water might be linked to a lower incidence of dementia in the population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="432MJIP32JG2RN7ETSAMCR7JEM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Yankner’s lab became interested in lithium after measuring the levels of 30 different metals in the brain and blood of people who were cognitively healthy, people in a very early stage of dementia and people with full-blown Alzheimer’s disease. Of the 30 metals, only lithium changed significantly among the three groups.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="76LSB4DJHBFOZFFY3OS3G5MCMM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Lithium maintains the connections and communication lines that allow neurons in a healthy brain to talk with one another. The metal also helps form the myelin that coats and insulates the communication lines and helps microglial cells clear cellular debris that can impede brain function. All this adds up to promoting good memory function both in mice and in humans, researchers said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-testid="list-header-NN3IPKIRVNEBTEJI5QSTXDIQUQ-21" tabindex="0"&gt;&lt;h2 id="NN3IPKIRVNEBTEJI5QSTXDIQUQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="NN3IPKIRVNEBTEJI5QSTXDIQUQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;How could the research translate to treatment?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a href="#secondary-nav" class="skip-link sr-only sr-only-focusable black underline brad-md pa-lg mb-xs border-box font-sans-serif font-bold"&gt;Return to menu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="6UGYQESATBEXFIA5RQZZP7LL4A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Yankner’s lab found that small amounts of the compound lithium orotate were able to reverse a mouse model of Alzheimer’s disease and restore brain function. Researchers said the discovery should be enough to spur clinical trials for testing the compound in people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HPEHNDE6WBE4HNE3UIUJNEXRDM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But Yankner said he could not recommend at this point that people start taking lithium because its use for Alzheimer’s has not been validated in people, and “things can change as you go from mice to humans.” Lithium can also be toxic if not regulated properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text grid-center grid-body" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ZA66D7HYGFDKDGQGEWHCC22ZOY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;And because this research is nascent, it’s unlikely that a treatment will be available anytime soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:01:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinAFBVV95cUxPeHNYVWl1S1FqRHNxalFMNWR6UEdhaXEyN3FBZldZMU9Tb1QyU3dQc1hGQWN0dDE5UkZ3SGtGVUk2NUFKVk8xWWFZRXJONzVSZ1Rzdnc1WDdFNm9lUEcyMklJN09YTWtvYkZsdC1kNWN2RWpyeEkzcGRUMEt6M3pGX2NVNEJ0WlA2LVUwZ1RWdW80UVlLVWFENnlpalA</guid></item><item><title>忘记10000步—尝试我的3-4-5步行锻炼，提升您的心血管健康和情绪-汤姆指南</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi0wFBVV95cUxNdnBkb09UTklmM1E4dkhTUUlueEh3V1BEQ19vOFhReC0zak9nWlB0ZF91aXNoOFZqQzY2dHo0b18zOGF1RW1vbnBDRmk0TWEwQmFkbC1MbTFuWnhXUi05SmJVYzVUVXA0OXd5UVJCUURCSl9fU3RYQjg3T0xydHB5Z3ItdUJJdFFLeXl6cmlBMjI0QTBWeVpwck1NX2lDTkdJNEdsU04yanl4NE5iWVZiSkJNSnNmdFQ2N3AwV05mdUhSV3BpZTZZR2dfVUhvdXdxTnJr?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p id="4df4167d-f126-44e4-a9b2-76e97188d22d"&gt;I’ll start this article with a strong caveat — I’m not a personal trainer or a walking coach, I’m a fitness editor and enthusiast, who reviews gear and tests new workouts for a living.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like the rest of the fitness world, I’ve recently been swept up in the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/i-tried-the-japanese-walking-method-for-a-week-and-im-hooked" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/i-tried-the-japanese-walking-method-for-a-week-and-im-hooked"&gt;Japanese walking method&lt;/a&gt; hype, and it’s changed my walking workouts for good, but after a month, I found myself thinking, what's next?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-seasonal" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="4df4167d-f126-44e4-a9b2-76e97188d22d-2"&gt;In order to get fitter and stronger, you need to keep progressing your workouts. With walking workouts, this is pretty easy — you simply walk faster, add weight in the form of a weighted vest (or in my case, a baby strapped to your torso in a sling), walk up hill, or increase the time you spend walking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, if you’re looking for a new walking workout to try this summer, why not give my 3-4-5 walking method a go? Read on to find out exactly how to do it. As a reminder, if you’re returning to workouts following an injury or pregnancy, it’s always a good idea to get signed off by a medical professional before taking on a new routine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-70a14b3f-17db-4684-a743-60acdfe3b071" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="what-is-the-3-4-5-walking-workout-3"&gt;What is the 3-4-5 walking workout? &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="004b0b89-2a3f-4b95-9e1a-8d7c0144ccfd"&gt;Similar to the Japanese Walking Method, my 3-4-5 workout is also a form of HIIT training that involves changing the pace throughout the session. I found it best to program the walking workout on my &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/tag/apple-watch" data-auto-tag-linker="true" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/tag/apple-watch"&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt; beforehand (here’s &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/i-created-the-japanese-walking-workout-on-my-apple-watch-heres-how-to-do-it" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/wellness/fitness/i-created-the-japanese-walking-workout-on-my-apple-watch-heres-how-to-do-it"&gt;how to build a custom workout on your Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;), but you can do the same on most of the &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/us/best-fitness-trackers,review-2066.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/us/best-fitness-trackers,review-2066.html"&gt;best fitness trackers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you don’t have a fitness tracker, just use a stopwatch or the stopwatch on your smartphone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here’s how to do it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-GnuXkk6u6w25opbFZhZVQb" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-GnuXkk6u6w25opbFZhZVQb slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get instant access to breaking news, the hottest reviews, great deals and helpful tips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;ul id="4ba35ab6-f576-4f7d-8fa5-51bd0a8757f1"&gt;&lt;li&gt;Walk for three minutes at a low intensity. This should be a 4/10 effort — you’re still moving, but you should easily be able to hold a conversation with someone next to you.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Then walk four minutes at a high intensity. This is a 7/10 walking effort — you should be working hard.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Repeat this 5 times. You’ll walk for 35 minutes in total.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;figure class="van-image-figure inline-layout" data-bordeaux-image-check id="2b36b008-297d-4930-9fb4-d9c4d742ff09"&gt;&lt;figcaption itemprop="caption description" class=" inline-layout"&gt;&lt;span class="credit" itemprop="copyrightHolder"&gt;(Image credit: Shutterstock)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;a id="elk-799f9042-f7b3-4fc6-9005-0a73073bdb82" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h2 id="i-ve-been-doing-the-3-4-5-walking-workout-for-a-week-here-are-the-benefits-3"&gt;I’ve been doing the 3-4-5 walking workout for a week — here are the benefits &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="da3d684a-cbcf-4b95-9e34-11cdf837f6b8"&gt;As you might have spotted, this progresses the Japanese walking method by increasing the time spent walking at a faster pace and adding five minutes to the workout. Here’s what I noticed:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-the-extra-60-seconds-of-work-makes-all-the-difference"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The extra 60 seconds of work makes all the difference&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="05345aab-ff78-48d5-ab54-91ec38dd03d5"&gt;60 seconds doesn’t sound like a long time, until you’re having to power through another minute of walking at a fast pace. The extra minute of work made this feel like a step up from the three-minute intervals involved in the Japanese walking method. It’s enough to keep your heart rate elevated for a little bit longer, and I felt like I’d worked harder and burned more calories during this walking workout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the benefits of adding intervals to your walks is raising your heart rate. This helps lower your blood pressure and cholesterol, and increases your aerobic capacity compared to walking continuously at a moderate pace for the same time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’re also likely to burn more calories than you would if you just walked at a moderate pace for 35 minutes, which is useful if you're &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.tomsguide.com/how-to/how-to-lose-weight-and-get-in-shape-by-walking" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.tomsguide.com/how-to/how-to-lose-weight-and-get-in-shape-by-walking"&gt;walking for weight loss&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-knowing-how-many-times-i-was-repeating-the-intervals-helped" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-knowing-how-many-times-i-was-repeating-the-intervals-helped"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Knowing how many times I was repeating the intervals helped &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="e2bb837d-8ff9-47d3-8f71-012f8327305c"&gt;I’ve run five marathons, and one thing that always gets me through the final miles is counting. From mile 20, I’ll count each step to 100, then start again, or work out how many minutes of running I have left and count down. It helps keep my mind busy when the going gets tough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I also use a similar technique in my speed workouts when running, counting down the intervals, work, or laps of the track left. I liked counting down from five during this workout — knowing I only had one interval or four minutes of work left allowed me to push my pace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-it-raised-my-heart-rate-and-boosted-my-mood" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-it-raised-my-heart-rate-and-boosted-my-mood"&gt;&lt;span&gt;It raised my heart rate and boosted my mood &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p id="5f077647-65d7-4fa2-b0d3-fe9c902cda56"&gt;I’m not walking to lose weight, but using it as a way to rebuild my fitness postpartum, and keep moving on days when my toddler doesn’t go to daycare, and I can’t head out for a run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s also a great form of active recovery, and stops my legs getting too stiff between running and strength training sessions. I have to walk my dog every day, so why not mix it up and make it more of a workout?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as raising my heart rate and leaving me feeling like I’d done a workout, not just rambled along with a podcast, my 3-4-5 walking workout left me with all those happy, post-workout endorphins flowing through my body before I sat down at my desk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a fun challenge, and one you can do for free, from anywhere. Do it on a treadmill, with a friend or a dog, in your local park, or up a hill if you want to really work your legs. All you need is a comfy pair of sneakers and 35 minutes. Happy walking!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Follow &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US%3Aen" data-url="https://news.google.com/publications/CAAqKAgKIiJDQklTRXdnTWFnOEtEWFJ2YlhObmRXbGtaUzVqYjIwb0FBUAE?hl=en-US&amp;amp;gl=US&amp;amp;ceid=US%3Aen" target="_blank" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Tom's Guide on Google News&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; to get our up-to-date news, how-tos, and reviews in your feeds. Make sure to click the Follow button.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a id="elk-more-from-tom-s-guide" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;h3 class="article-body__section" id="section-more-from-tom-s-guide"&gt;&lt;span&gt;More from Tom's Guide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;a id="elk-eb1654b7-696a-4ba4-bece-737026090927" data-url="" href="" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;aside data-model-name="Apple Watch Series 10" data-widget-type="multimodelreview" data-render-type="editorial" class="hawk-base"&gt;&lt;div class="hawk-multi-model-review-container"&gt;&lt;div class="hawk-multi-model-review-retail-container"&gt;&lt;p class="hawk-title-container"&gt;Today's best Apple Watch Series 10 deals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/aside&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Tom's Guide</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 10:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi0wFBVV95cUxNdnBkb09UTklmM1E4dkhTUUlueEh3V1BEQ19vOFhReC0zak9nWlB0ZF91aXNoOFZqQzY2dHo0b18zOGF1RW1vbnBDRmk0TWEwQmFkbC1MbTFuWnhXUi05SmJVYzVUVXA0OXd5UVJCUURCSl9fU3RYQjg3T0xydHB5Z3ItdUJJdFFLeXl6cmlBMjI0QTBWeVpwck1NX2lDTkdJNEdsU04yanl4NE5iWVZiSkJNSnNmdFQ2N3AwV05mdUhSV3BpZTZZR2dfVUhvdXdxTnJr</guid></item><item><title>它们影响着40%的人口。没有人会认真对待他们。- Slate杂志</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxNcWI0ZVZiN2c3YllkaWN5ZlQyOVgwTzN2QkxXNnpGdGpsakl6Vzh3YmZYQldVa3poSUt0bE5sOXF4ZXR0Rk1yLXBkeUdOMklkOWJFbXdLZ1FPZi1Gd09HVE9YZm01S0hPcmJwLW1kUERiSmt6eEdxOHg0OE1TdmY4c3d2ZkdVQlV1SjNNTVljdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="129" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6f9t0029cym6rvzc9ydo@published"&gt;On one of the most memorable days of my life, I walked into a doctor’s office with an incipient migraine and walked out half an hour later pain-free. It was the early ’90s, and I’d been suffering from the headaches—often accompanied by nausea and vomiting, occasionally somewhat eased by ibuprofen—since the age of 14. I can’t recall why on that day I decided to request an appointment, but I can still see the doctor fumbling with the wrapping of a cartridge encasing a hypodermic needle filled with a new drug. She got migraines, too, she’d told me, so when she placed the cartridge on my arm and pressed the button delivering the shot, we both exhibited the curious anticipation of experimenters, wondering if something miraculous was in the offing.&lt;/p&gt;

  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="105" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6ydo000o357afbb0aip8@published"&gt;It was. Within five minutes, the nagging throb that had bloomed on my right temple a few hours earlier had vanished. That made us both giddy. Whether the new drug, sumatriptan (marketed as Imitrex), also worked for that doctor, I’ll never know. But I was lucky. Over the decades that followed, sumatriptan has reliably tamed the migraines that have intermittently plagued me, rescuing me from countless hours of misery. Whenever anyone complains about Big Pharma or fantasizes about having been born in an earlier era, my ironclad response is that I can’t imagine my life without sumatriptan—or, rather, I can, and the thought is chilling.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="124" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6yfz000p357aoax6hew9@published"&gt;I’m lucky. As the journalist Tom Zeller Jr. recounts in his illuminating new book, &lt;a href="https://bookshop.org/a/2181/9780358507758"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Headache&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, people with migraines or cluster headaches (Zeller’s own affliction) often find that recommended treatments either don’t work or decline in effectiveness over the course of months. Cluster headaches, like migraines, are called “primary headaches,” Zeller explains, “meaning the head pain and accompanying battery of other neurological effects constitute disorders unto themselves, rather than symptoms of some other underlying disease.” Even the fairly common migraine is poorly understood by those who don’t get them. I once worked with a colleague who was convinced I was being careless with my health because I didn’t regard my headaches as symptoms of some grave condition that could, and ought, to be cured.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section data-uri="slate.com/_components/product/instances/cme3a7xxz001z357a8jiai7tt@published" class="product " data-product-name="&amp;lt;em&amp;gt;The Headache: The Science of a Most Confounding Affliction—and a Search for Relief&amp;lt;/em&amp;gt;" data-product-price="$27.89"&gt;
    
  &lt;div class="product__info"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="product__description"&gt;
      By Tom Zeller Jr. Mariner Books.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;


  &lt;p class="disclaimer" data-word-count="19" data-uri="slate.com/_components/disclaimer/instances/cme3a7yfk002d357ayere4nev@published"&gt;
    Slate receives a commission when you purchase items using the links on this page.
    Thank you for your support.
  &lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="91" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6z8s0010357ajbw46zyr@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Headache&lt;/em&gt; is an account of what we have learned about migraine and cluster headaches (less than you’d think) and the state of research developing treatments. The newest of those treatments are blockers that inhibit the uptake of calcitonin gene-related peptide, CGRP, a “key chemical messenger in the nervous system’s pain communication pathway,” according to Zeller. Researchers knew that CGRP could induce migraines in experimental subjects (all praise the sacrifices of those heroes!), and this new class of drugs binds to the chemical to prevent it from binding to neural receptors.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="134" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zbb0011357a7sdg11tr@published"&gt;Cluster headaches are relatively rare, but migraines are not, and one study calculated the cost to the U.S. economy of migraines alone is as much as $1 trillion. Yet research into the causes and cures for primary headaches has been sluggish, for reasons that are highly contested. While the medical explanations in &lt;em&gt;The Headache&lt;/em&gt; occasionally made my eyes glaze over, Zeller’s accounts of feuds among headache researchers and their combined wrath at what they insist is inadequate National Institutes of Health funding for their work offers a delectable blend of dish and substance. When one scientist likened migraine research to a massive Airbus plane requiring four fully fueled engines to get it off the ground, Zeller asked him what, exactly, was keeping the plane on the tarmac. “Too many female passengers,” was the reply.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="138" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zhk0012357akvwvuqfc@published"&gt;Female migraineurs outnumber their male counterparts by 3 to 1, while the gender breakdown is reversed for cluster headaches. Many headache experts believe that this explains why migraine isn’t taken seriously by the medical establishment, whose tendency to dismiss pain in female patients has been well documented. Zeller observes that cluster headache sufferers, by contrast, tend to hide their condition, something he himself did during an early stint at the New York Times&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;The Headache&lt;/em&gt; includes the story of an air traffic controller who concealed his cluster headaches for three decades, knowing that the condition would trigger an automatic medical disqualification from a job he loved. He resorted to keeping his medications (which did not impair his performance) secret and ducking out of work during an episode to inhale oxygen from a tank he kept in his car.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;figure data-uri="slate.com/_components/image/instances/cme3aqnlr007e357agq500338@published" class="image image--right" data-editable="imageInfo"&gt;
&lt;figcaption class="image__meta"&gt;
&lt;span class="image__caption"&gt;Tom Zeller&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="image__credit"&gt;Kristine Paulsen&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="187" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zjs0013357awcsrulpp@published"&gt;For Zeller’s part, he found it difficult to admit how debilitated he was by a disorder that many people conflate with the discomfort caused by a hangover. Cluster headaches, however, are often ranked among the worst pain a human can experience. While migraineurs tend to retreat to dark quiet rooms to wait out their affliction, people with cluster headaches are restless, often pacing, rocking, and pounding their heads. While cluster headaches don’t last all day like a migraine, they can recur every day or multiple times per day within the window of a period that can last weeks or months, followed by a period of remission. In &lt;em&gt;The Headache, &lt;/em&gt;Zeller relates the story of a young man whose cluster headaches proved so relentless and tormenting that he took his own life, grimly confirming the disorder’s nickname: suicide headaches. Zeller himself recounts a period when, while working on a demanding story, he experienced a cluster attack and resorted to “medicating myself with absurd tides of chemical experimentation and excess,” ranging from caffeine, steroids, and magnesium to a CGRP blocker called verapamil—a drug on which he overdosed, passing out.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="181" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zm60014357aorphcbgz@published"&gt;Though we have different kinds of headaches, there’s much that’s familiar to me in Zeller’s account. I, too, have found it difficult to convey just how disabling a mere headache can be. And I certainly recognized Zeller’s almost superstitious hoarding of medication doses, splitting them to stretch the supply, and the way Zeller would “jealously count those blue injections like a Scrooge, worrying over their limited number, wondering whether they’d last.” These drugs are the treasure we require to placate an angry god. Insurance companies can be stingy with the number of doses they allow per month, so it’s imperative to keep renewing the prescription regularly, even in the absence of headaches, so that you hit any future bad period with an ample supply. The fear of running out is petrifying—although, thankfully, well in the past for me now that sumatriptan has gone generic and can be bought online. The more recently developed CGRP blockers, however, can be brutally expensive. And most primary headache medications only work for half the people who try them, and then often only half the time.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="155" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zom0015357akhjz65q4@published"&gt;Maddeningly, scientists still can’t say what causes primary headaches. Fierce debate rages among them over whether these are disorders of the vascular system—dilated blood vessels pressing against nerves—or of the central nervous system, arising from some dysfunction in the brain. The hypothalamus, which regulates the autonomic nervous system, seems implicated in cluster headaches, with their mysterious link to the body’s circadian rhythms. Migraines vary widely from person to person, but also in the same person during the course of a lifetime. My migraines once were synced to hormonal cycles. Now they only come at night, and especially when it rains or the humidity tops 75 percent. Or when my blood sugar gets too low. Or when I drink wine. I never experienced migraine aura—a disturbance in vision—until about 15 years ago. Now, my eyesight will occasionally be marred by a crescent of shimmering silver triangles (a classic migraine aura), but with no subsequent headache attached.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  



  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="119" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zr30016357aowvy3zdh@published"&gt;No wonder headache scientists are stumped, although several of the sources Zeller spoke with also complained that the stigma attached to primary headaches as an “unserious” medical condition has kept gifted researchers away from the field. Former NIH director Story Landis told Zeller that the agency—which has demonstrably underfunded headache research relative to the impact primary headaches have on society—simply didn’t get enough high-quality grant proposals in the area. Landis suggested, Zeller writes, “that headache researchers had been poorly conditioned by industry to focus on pills and shots, rather than foundational science,” such as identifying the cause or causes of the disorders. But if Big Pharma is the only source of funding for headache research, who can blame them?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="108" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cme3a6zti0017357aojan5x70@published"&gt;When an advocate for headache sufferers asked Zeller what he’d learned in all his admirably extensive research for &lt;em&gt;The Headache,&lt;/em&gt; the author found himself stammering and backtracking, qualifying his own suffering as not “the worst of what cluster headaches can inflict on a person,” adding that “there are bigger problems.” Then he pulled up. For millions of people of all races and genders—including Zeller himself!—primary headaches are a literal torment. Though I seldom endure that myself now, I remember all too well what a full-blown migraine was like. “It’s not just a headache” is the answer Zeller finally comes up with, and on that we should all &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;agree.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup   " data-list="Culture" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cme3a6f9t002ccym6x2xlwprs@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Get the best of culture&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get the best of movies, TV, books, music, and more.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate Magazine</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxNcWI0ZVZiN2c3YllkaWN5ZlQyOVgwTzN2QkxXNnpGdGpsakl6Vzh3YmZYQldVa3poSUt0bE5sOXF4ZXR0Rk1yLXBkeUdOMklkOWJFbXdLZ1FPZi1Gd09HVE9YZm01S0hPcmJwLW1kUERiSmt6eEdxOHg0OE1TdmY4c3d2ZkdVQlV1SjNNTVljdw</guid></item><item><title>这种常见的抗恶心药可能会改变难以治疗的乳腺癌的游戏规则- SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxORmE5alFLc2hOR2MwblZnX1JUWlprdzRSb1dpM1R0WVBXT1cxZ1VPSWJNbFotWjlkUzM2dE04MTlnWmI5aUJqSXlRTDhQNjY3M3NoMFJ0aE5EaVV6Uk5tMm82VFNTS0theFlmVFV4QzBWeU5DWkVCdy1NOFdqRWFKQUVWRFprOFNZc0tobnl4WmFHQS1FamJNaWVMcFJGMFlnZGRKMjBJRWRqbFJPR2swZQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:11:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxORmE5alFLc2hOR2MwblZnX1JUWlprdzRSb1dpM1R0WVBXT1cxZ1VPSWJNbFotWjlkUzM2dE04MTlnWmI5aUJqSXlRTDhQNjY3M3NoMFJ0aE5EaVV6Uk5tMm82VFNTS0theFlmVFV4QzBWeU5DWkVCdy1NOFdqRWFKQUVWRFprOFNZc0tobnl4WmFHQS1FamJNaWVMcFJGMFlnZGRKMjBJRWRqbFJPR2swZQ</guid></item><item><title>FDA可能不会续签针对幼儿的辉瑞新冠疫苗-《卫报》</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxNcWpBQzNxeTJGZU5keV80OTRMODJZb3ViMnI4SEtzcEhpdHhrVHdSR1Q4OF9CYlJLclU2cEt4S1llbHF4UmdOeVlCS3JQeS00UHdSMnI4SkUwbjdPd3dHWXJTT2ZEcVdUSXNjQ3RsSkNkRWE3TU1qWGpjWFNPNzFrQUJmOU1qNVQ1endGaW1R?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Pfizer’s Covid vaccine for young children may not be renewed by the US Food and Drug Administration (FDA) this fall, prompting Moderna to fill possible gaps in supply, according to an email obtained by the Guardian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The move would pull the only remaining Covid vaccine for all children under five from the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"us-news","tags":[{"id":"us-news/us-news","type":"Keyword","title":"US news"},{"id":"world/coronavirus-outbreak","type":"Keyword","title":"Coronavirus"},{"id":"business/pfizer","type":"Keyword","title":"Pfizer"},{"id":"us-news/healthcare","type":"Keyword","title":"US healthcare"},{"id":"world/world","type":"Keyword","title":"World news"},{"id":"science/science","type":"Keyword","title":"Science"},{"id":"business/business","type":"Keyword","title":"Business"},{"id":"science/medical-research","type":"Keyword","title":"Medical research"},{"id":"society/vaccines","type":"Keyword","title":"Vaccines and immunisation"},{"id":"society/society","type":"Keyword","title":"Society"},{"id":"business/pharmaceuticals-industry","type":"Keyword","title":"Pharmaceuticals industry"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"profile/melody-schreiber","type":"Contributor","title":"Melody Schreiber"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/us-news","type":"Tracking","title":"US News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"us-news/2025/aug/09/pfizer-covid-vaccine-fda-children-dfa","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Moderna vaccine is only approved for children with one or more health conditions, and the pediatric Covid vaccine from Novavax is only available for children aged 12 and up with health conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“It certainly would create a hole in the availability of vaccines,” said Georges Benjamin, executive director of the American Public Health Association.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“And to do it this late in the season – I think clearly it’s inappropriate.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;According to an email from the National Center for Immunization and Respiratory Diseases (NCIRD), Pfizer said the FDA recently informed the pharmaceutical company that it may not renew the emergency use authorization for its pediatric Covid vaccine for the 2025 respiratory season.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The email was sent on Friday to state and local vaccination grantees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Pfizer vaccine is given to children between the ages of six months and four years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Pfizer expects its Covid vaccine for children aged five to 11 to be fully licensed this fall, the email said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) is “in discussions” with Moderna about rapidly increasing its Covid vaccine supply for young children, according to the email.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;That includes internal planning about volume, timing, and potential supply gaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We are working to ensure there will be sufficient supply,” said Chris Ridley, a Moderna spokesperson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The CDC, the US Department for Health and Human Services (HHS), and Pfizer did not respond to media inquiries by publication time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;In July, Moderna received FDA approval of its Covid pediatric shot. But the vaccine was only approved for children with one or more health conditions that make them more vulnerable to Covid. This move could limit access to Covid vaccines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We already have a low number of people using the vaccines to start with,” Benjamin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“There hasn’t been enough promotion of vaccinations for kids, and then you have Mr [Robert F] Kennedy’s [Jr] unscientific statements about the safety and efficacy of vaccines, particularly Covid vaccines, for both pregnant women and kids. It has muddied the waters of what people know about the safety and efficacy of the vaccine.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;The vaccine is extremely effective, especially against hospitalization and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Yet only 5.6% of children aged six months to four years are vaccinated against Covid, and about 15% of children aged five to 17 are vaccinated, according to the CDC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;While older adults have the highest rates of hospitalization and death, children continue seeing &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/php/covid-net/index.html" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;hospitalization rates&lt;/a&gt; from Covid similar to rates in 2020 and 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;And there are other concerns with Covid infection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;“We don’t know the long-term impact for kids who have gotten Covid as a disease. We do know it does cause a multi-systemic inflammatory process in a number of kids, which is very severe, and we don’t know the long-term implications for long Covid in kids,” Benjamin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-130mj7b"&gt;Covid cases are &lt;a href="https://www.theguardian.com/world/2025/aug/05/us-covid-cases-rising" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;rising&lt;/a&gt; in many parts of the US amid other vaccine restrictions proposed and implemented by health officials.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 09:01:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxNcWpBQzNxeTJGZU5keV80OTRMODJZb3ViMnI4SEtzcEhpdHhrVHdSR1Q4OF9CYlJLclU2cEt4S1llbHF4UmdOeVlCS3JQeS00UHdSMnI4SkUwbjdPd3dHWXJTT2ZEcVdUSXNjQ3RsSkNkRWE3TU1qWGpjWFNPNzFrQUJmOU1qNVQ1endGaW1R</guid></item><item><title>随着“Stratus”变种爆发， COVID-19病例激增- Axios</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiggFBVV95cUxNLUFGMGpBa3p4OGxYWE5Tb2oxTDJvUDZHNm16aUd4d3ZPWDQ5UW1YaHY3eFhsemhZWjhvMWVMZ3hIczB4VlVLb0lGc0ZHc1ZYcEFBeDFGakFDNTBnZzh6V0ZrOEt3VGlSZ09rZXo2T1o4c0Fvd2VGZGptUlcyU1dZWnB3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Axios</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 05:53:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiggFBVV95cUxNLUFGMGpBa3p4OGxYWE5Tb2oxTDJvUDZHNm16aUd4d3ZPWDQ5UW1YaHY3eFhsemhZWjhvMWVMZ3hIczB4VlVLb0lGc0ZHc1ZYcEFBeDFGakFDNTBnZzh6V0ZrOEt3VGlSZ09rZXo2T1o4c0Fvd2VGZGptUlcyU1dZWnB3</guid></item><item><title>凯瑟琳·帕克希尔讣告（ 2025年） -伊利诺伊州萨沃伊-新闻公报- Legacy.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgFBVV95cUxQV2oxQmZrOEpPYmtSaHZaaUFfRngwdjJjYk1vbjdJamsyUE05YnZ3ZFE2ZnVWX2VFN3V5VnJNMk53MDRBVW9jRU1iX2RzTFRuWUtxekUyX0Y3ejFSS1k3eUZYLThSUy1Bdy1IT2F5eHU5LU9pazVibTROZWgwblppS2JoUHUxMjBja2FBVUx1cDZTeEFlV1NqWlpR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div data-component="ObituaryParagraph" font-family='"PT Serif", serif' font-size="5,5,5,5,8" overflow="visible" class="Box-sc-ucqo0b-0 kbVUcj ObituaryText___StyledTextBase-sc-12f7zd1-0 inFMmj"&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHAMPAIGN - Katherine Dunn Parkhill passed away peacefully, surrounded by her family, on Aug. 5, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Katie was born on Oct. 16, 1961, to Bernard and Chris Dunn in Urbana. She spent a happy childhood in Champaign with her sister, Cari, and a close-knit group of friends. Katie attended Carrie Busey Elementary, Edison Middle School and Champaign Central High School. Summers were especially meaningful, spent at Lake Geneva, Wis. - a beloved family tradition that continues today with her children, grandchildren, and longtime friends in Belvidere Park.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Katie attended the University of Colorado in Boulder, where she was a proud member of the Pi Beta Phi sorority. Her years in Boulder sparked a lifelong love for Colorado - its mountains, seasons, and spirit - which she nurtured through countless ski trips and summer bike rides. After graduating, Katie began her career in Chicago, where she worked in sales for a company specializing in retail security technology. Her quick wit, warm demeanor, and natural ease with people made her a standout in the field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 17, 1988, Katie married the love of her life, David Parkhill, in Lake Geneva. The couple settled in Denver where they welcomed their son, Joseph Bergen, in 1990. Not long after, they returned to Champaign and grew their family with the arrival of their daughter, Rachel Christine Parkhill, in 1993.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back in her hometown, Katie became deeply involved in the community. She gave generously of her time and energy to a variety of organizations, including the Junior League of Champaign-Urbana, CU Mentoring, Crisis Nursery, The Art Club, Mother's Morning Out Board, and Children's Home and Aid of Illinois. Later, she brought her talent and enthusiasm to Checkered Moon, where she lit up the shop - and everyone in it - with her joy and style.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Katie was always entertaining and enjoyed playing cards and games with her friends and family. An excellent athlete, she played tennis most of her life. Tuesdays were reserved for "The Babes," her USTA team that played together for many years. She also enjoyed learning new activities like golf, pickleball, mahjong, and bridge in her later years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Katie loved to travel, and she and David were fortunate to explore many wonderful places together. But her favorite place, always, was wherever her family - and her beloved golden retrievers - were. A devoted mother, daughter, wife and friend, Katie poured her heart into raising Joey and Rachel, and her wit, kindness and vibrant spirit made her unforgettable to all who knew her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her three grandsons - Brodie, Parker and Jack - were the light of her life and the greatest joy in her final years. Katie will be remembered for the love she gave, the laughter she inspired, and the legacy of grace, warmth, and generosity she leaves behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Katie was preceded in death by her father, Bernard Dunn of Champaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She is survived by her husband, David; son, Joey (Shelby) Parkhill of Morrison, Colo.; her daughter, Rachel (Bill) Sanvidge of Champaign; her grandsons, Brodie and Parker Sanvidge and Jack Parkhill; her mother, Christine Dunn of Champaign; her sister, Cari Dunn of Auburn, Ala.; and her in-laws, Marilyn and Bergen Parkhill of Champaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A funeral service will be held in her memory at 2 p.m. Friday, Aug. 22, at First Presbyterian Church of Champaign. A celebration of life will follow from 3:30 to 5:30 p.m. at the Champaign Country Club, 1211 S. Prospect, Champaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of flowers, please consider making a memorial contribution to the Champaign Parks Foundation, 706 Kenwood Road, Champaign, IL 61821 or online by clicking on "Donate Now" at &lt;a href="http://champaignparks.org/about-us/foundation/" rel="sponsored" text-decoration="underline" class="Box-sc-ucqo0b-0 Link-sc-1u14kdb-0 HtmlContent___StyledLink-sc-ngx07-0 gduWLe jLFkis hRYGv"&gt;champaignparks.org/about-us/foundation/&lt;/a&gt;. Clark Park was a special place for Kate and her family, and donations in her honor can be directed to that park to help fund the newly renovated playground. Donations can also be made to the Katie Parkhill Fund, which supports the Mills Breast Cancer Institute, via the Carle Health Center for Philanthropy, 611 W. Park St., Urbana, IL 61801 or &lt;a href="http://carle.org/giving/make-a-gift." rel="sponsored" text-decoration="underline" class="Box-sc-ucqo0b-0 Link-sc-1u14kdb-0 HtmlContent___StyledLink-sc-ngx07-0 gduWLe jLFkis hRYGv"&gt;carle.org/giving/make-a-gift. &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Condolences may be offered at &lt;a href="http://morganmemorialhome.com" rel="sponsored" text-decoration="underline" class="Box-sc-ucqo0b-0 Link-sc-1u14kdb-0 HtmlContent___StyledLink-sc-ngx07-0 gduWLe jLFkis hRYGv"&gt;morganmemorialhome.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p font-family='"Open Sans", sans-serif' data-component="ObituaryEndorsementText" font-size="16px" class="Box-sc-ucqo0b-0 TextBase___StyledBox-sc-10uela0-0 jyiPuH fpGVBx"&gt;Published by The News-Gazette on Aug. 9, 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Legacy.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 05:04:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxQV2oxQmZrOEpPYmtSaHZaaUFfRngwdjJjYk1vbjdJamsyUE05YnZ3ZFE2ZnVWX2VFN3V5VnJNMk53MDRBVW9jRU1iX2RzTFRuWUtxekUyX0Y3ejFSS1k3eUZYLThSUy1Bdy1IT2F5eHU5LU9pazVibTROZWgwblppS2JoUHUxMjBja2FBVUx1cDZTeEFlV1NqWlpR</guid></item><item><title>确认狂犬病狐狸叮咬阿特莫尔居民；第二人也正在接受治疗- NorthEscambia.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxORFVkZlNUUDBuZ205SW9rZ3lheGVXOUxiNHIxM01ZVU1qNjJFVEgtV1BMT1h1ZmV2dzZ1aWxKeDFvVFNFal9QOFJVbnBSYUZpR1pOdEhlX1B3VVhhNU9faUJNdE5BMzhpWE5vdlRGRU4tbFhkSTJUSXdFZlZ1RElVSTZZYl9SSDhOMDhRcDQ3OG5YSDNodjN4M1ktbmNoWkl6TjdxMkVUNEFkR19OVWFocg?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="contentleft"&gt;
	
		&lt;p class="breadcrumb"&gt;
				
		&lt;/p&gt;
		
				&lt;h1&gt;Confirmed Rabid Fox Bites Atmore Resident; Second Person Also Being Treated&lt;/h1&gt;

		
	
		&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.northescambia.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/rabiesalert11.jpg"&gt;&lt;img class="alignnone size-large wp-image-593487" title="rabiesalert11" src="http://www.northescambia.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/08/rabiesalert11-540x258.jpg" alt=""&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An Escambia resident was attacked and bitten by a fox on August 7 outside the victim’s residence on Highway 31 in Atmore. Another person was present at the time of the incident and came in direct physical contact with the fox. The Escambia County Sheriff’s Department was notified of the incident, and a rabies investigation was begun.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The fox was taken to the Alabama Department of Public Health (ADPH) Bureau of Clinical Laboratories, where it was confirmed positive for rabies. Rabies is a viral disease that can be fatal if untreated. Both persons are receiving appropriate medical attention, and the victim is receiving post-exposure prophylaxis. No additional exposures have been identified at this time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Although rabies is primarily found in wild animals, since widespread vaccination of domestic animals began over 70 years ago, it continues to be a risk and a public health threat,” Dr. Dee W. Jones, State Public Health Veterinarian, said. “Although attacks such as this by rabid wildlife are rather uncommon, it highlights the risk rabies continues to pose and hopefully reminds people to be aware of the risks and continue to vaccinate their pets.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is very common for domestic animals and pets to have contact with a wild rabid animal. Alabama state law requires that dogs, cats and ferrets 12 weeks of age and older be current with rabies vaccination. Rabies vaccines are also available for horses and other livestock if recommended by a veterinarian. Vaccinating animals reduces the risk of rabies infection should exposure occur; thus, vaccinations protect animals, as well as their owners and caretakers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="Flomaton%20Police%20Warn%20Residents%20of%20Possible%20Rabid%20Fox%20Sightings"&gt;RELATED STORY: Flomaton Police Warn Residents of Possible Rabid Fox Sightings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		



		
	 			



		
		
				
	&lt;/div&gt;








		
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NorthEscambia.com</author><pubDate>Sat, 09 Aug 2025 04:39:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxORFVkZlNUUDBuZ205SW9rZ3lheGVXOUxiNHIxM01ZVU1qNjJFVEgtV1BMT1h1ZmV2dzZ1aWxKeDFvVFNFal9QOFJVbnBSYUZpR1pOdEhlX1B3VVhhNU9faUJNdE5BMzhpWE5vdlRGRU4tbFhkSTJUSXdFZlZ1RElVSTZZYl9SSDhOMDhRcDQ3OG5YSDNodjN4M1ktbmNoWkl6TjdxMkVUNEFkR19OVWFocg</guid></item></channel></rss>