<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>GNews Health</title><link>https://news.google.com/</link><description></description><generator>rfeed v1.1.1</generator><docs>https://github.com/svpino/rfeed/blob/master/README.md</docs><item><title>医生在结肠癌爆发方面取得巨大突破-每日邮报 | Doctors make huge breakthrough in colon cancer explosion - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPQ05OU2NmaDgyYnYwbUU3eVpTZ0x0SEU2MWNmU2hQei1fQ3lJV0pBeV82QzNPNENJTFQyaGRBTVRWMDJMc05KUVl6a2Z6V2tITUFOOVlaMnlJRjg3dTktam5oWDFMYnB5eXNBYUVFSzRKR09lTzgtQXNWcnNZR21Fd3JaZVlvMDJrNkdFTnYwc3RuU21hY3BTV1FHMGJZdWR0Z05OdnU5Sl83QWM?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;As doctors search for the cause of a mystery rise in colon cancers in young people, a new study has pinpointed two simple ways you can lower your risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Eating within an eight-hour time window and practicing mindfulness was found to shed fat and reduce harmful inflammation in the gut &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14761627/colon-cancer-rates-linked-alcohol-smoking-young-people.html"&gt;linked to the disease.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the eight-week trial, participants also saw improvements to their insulin and blood-sugar levels, which are both believed to play a role in &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14809655/test-early-onset-colon-cancer-symptoms-experts-epidemic.html"&gt;the formation of colon tumors.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The University of &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/illinois/index.html" id="mol-410067e0-4c47-11f0-a7cd-f9ea195159ad" class=""&gt;Illinois&lt;/a&gt; researchers described the results as 'promising', given how easy both habits are to follow and how quick the benefits seem to take effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Volunteers in the study were between the ages of 18 and 40 - the age group for whom colon cancers are rising quickest - and had obesity. They also scored high for psychological stress. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is thought that being overweight and stressed out triggers chronic inflammation and hormonal imbalances in the body, creating a perfect storm for &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-3d08edf0-4c52-11f0-a7cd-f9ea195159ad" class=""&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; formation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study saw volunteers restricted to eating between 12 - 8 p.m. and practice a basic daily mindfulness routine involving breathwork and sitting quietly with closed eyes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In eight weeks, those who stuck to both habits lost an average of 4.2 lbs compared to just 0.2 lbs in the control group who made no lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Bailey Hutchins of Tennessee, pictured, died of colon cancer earlier this year at age 26&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The former also saw improvements to their stress scores, insulin and glucose levels, as well as a drop in visceral fat mass - the most dangerous type of fat linked to cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;No significant changes were observed in the control group. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Writing in the paper, the research team said: 'This study was feasible and well accepted by the participants. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Results were promising, indicating a potential synergy between time restricted eating and mindfulness for improving anthropometric, metabolic and colonic inflammation among young adults with obesity and moderate to severe perceived stress.'&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study of 42 participants also looked at the effects of following just one of the habits, finding less pronounced health benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The results were published in the journal Nutrition. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Participants who took part in mindfulness exercises followed the 'Mindfulness for Beginners' program in the Calm app.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It involved a series of short, guided daily meditations about 10 minutes each, which involved simple, practical steps like focusing on breath, noticing thoughts and calming the body. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Carly Barrett (pictured right), from Kentucky, was diagnosed with colon cancer at age 24 after detecting blood in her stool and suffering from abdominal pain. She is still battling the disease&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It is thought that mindfulness reduces food cravings by changing how the brain responds to urges. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When people practice mindfulness, they learn to observe cravings as passing sensations without immediately acting on them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This weakens the link between feeling a craving and reaching for food or other substances such as alcohol or drugs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Studies using brain imaging show that mindfulness dampens activity in the brain’s reward and craving centers, such as the amygdala and striatum, while strengthening self-control regions like the prefrontal cortex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It comes amid an alarming rise in so-called early-onset colon cancers in people under the age of 50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rates among Americans in their 20s and 30s are expected to double by 2030 compared to 2010. In teens, cases have surged 500% since the early 2000s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Rising rates of obesity are thought to be a factor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In 2000, the overall adult obesity rate was around 20% compared to around 40% now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But doctors say that does not tell the whole story.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Diets high in processed foods, which have been linked to inflammation, have also been suggested as a driver, as has rising stress levels in young people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Other possible causes include the foodborne pathogen E. coli, gut changes linked to antibiotic use and changes to maternal health.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;More mothers are now obese and older when they give birth, which may cause biological changes to their children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It's not just colon cancer that is rising in young people - rates of several types of cancer have been trending upwards in recent decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14695689/colon-cancers-doctors-alarmed-rise-sharply-young-people.html"&gt;In a study published in May&lt;/a&gt;, researchers discovered 13 other cancers were found to be rising in under 50s: stomach,  pancreatic, bone and joint cancers, melanoma, breast, cervical, uterine, testicular, kidney and four types of cancers of the lymph system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 16:10:54 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqwFBVV95cUxPQ05OU2NmaDgyYnYwbUU3eVpTZ0x0SEU2MWNmU2hQei1fQ3lJV0pBeV82QzNPNENJTFQyaGRBTVRWMDJMc05KUVl6a2Z6V2tITUFOOVlaMnlJRjg3dTktam5oWDFMYnB5eXNBYUVFSzRKR09lTzgtQXNWcnNZR21Fd3JaZVlvMDJrNkdFTnYwc3RuU21hY3BTV1FHMGJZdWR0Z05OdnU5Sl83QWM</guid></item><item><title>“刀片喉咙” ：随着夏季升温， COVID水平上升，一些人报告了不愉快的症状-水星新闻 | ‘Razor blade throat’: As summer heats up, COVID levels rise and some report unpleasant symptom - The Mercury News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxObjM2TXZCU3FEc3dDbWlQTWJDTm0zZXhJN0EwR01BYmVwTW83MWtHanJfUTRtZlp2NnNOc0xmdVpUOHRaWVRFcF85WUpRd2pxXzBUS3R2Y2l3a3RsS1lveHBwYmYwN1RQdk9Cc3J0cjdqb2c4SGVoaW9Fc05MVnBYOU9jdHYwSDRyRVBITDhR0gGTAUFVX3lxTE5LYTdrZUJxQkJ5ajdWWDFnaHluajZXbm5VeXNQSmZubEpReFhkNENFVmFFeWZlNDJjakZUTFZZUDU4ckJXRFlwUmthUFoxc010T0NNTFQwLVhPNjF3eUlHSEZrX19IZjVWbkN1NlRBbGk5T205RkFVN3pNZTdWSmhMalhqVzVSNXZMaXFJT1QtanN2bw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="body-copy mng-subscriber-content"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The newest variant, NB.1.8.1, also known as Nimbus, is now widespread in California.            &lt;/p&gt;


			&lt;p class="time mng-originally-published"&gt;Originally Published: &lt;time datetime="2025-06-18 04:00:27"&gt;June 18, 2025 at 4:00 AM PDT&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Mercury News</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:57:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxObjM2TXZCU3FEc3dDbWlQTWJDTm0zZXhJN0EwR01BYmVwTW83MWtHanJfUTRtZlp2NnNOc0xmdVpUOHRaWVRFcF85WUpRd2pxXzBUS3R2Y2l3a3RsS1lveHBwYmYwN1RQdk9Cc3J0cjdqb2c4SGVoaW9Fc05MVnBYOU9jdHYwSDRyRVBITDhR0gGTAUFVX3lxTE5LYTdrZUJxQkJ5ajdWWDFnaHluajZXbm5VeXNQSmZubEpReFhkNENFVmFFeWZlNDJjakZUTFZZUDU4ckJXRFlwUmthUFoxc010T0NNTFQwLVhPNjF3eUlHSEZrX19IZjVWbkN1NlRBbGk5T205RkFVN3pNZTdWSmhMalhqVzVSNXZMaXFJT1QtanN2bw</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，青少年心理健康的真正风险是“成瘾性使用” ，而不仅仅是屏幕时间-纽约时报 | Real Risk to Youth Mental Health Is ‘Addictive Use,’ Not Screen Time Alone, Study Finds - The New York Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTE1pSlFNNjhjM1VkVjBLOEY5c1ljQnpmbmFuUl8wTDR6cm5UT1RjSk9Md2ROTlBydjJsUVlEX3RnQmZFbVpBbGY5Q2VGQlJxZlB4TVlRRFczNFhBNDNyckFjYnBsY1BaMHVuSVl6dGY4emM1aFlSY1JHUnlzS0E?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The New York Times</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 15:00:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE1pSlFNNjhjM1VkVjBLOEY5c1ljQnpmbmFuUl8wTDR6cm5UT1RjSk9Md2ROTlBydjJsUVlEX3RnQmZFbVpBbGY5Q2VGQlJxZlB4TVlRRFczNFhBNDNyckFjYnBsY1BaMHVuSVl6dGY4emM1aFlSY1JHUnlzS0E</guid></item><item><title>您手机的自拍相机现在可以检测抑郁症。操作方法- NDTV | Your Phone's Selfie Camera Can Now Detect Depression. Here's How - NDTV</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxQTm11TmM1c01ZRHBsQjZORExfdnBiQ3RCbzRkSEgtc3dETm5jTnhneUxuTUx4NGE2SEEydGMxeVhDSC1xOTlyZzdPUUVfSmsxWUNkVjVTNVV1RHlTd0s1S0lmQWk4Qy1BWklCeGZHNC1XdVJHT1hxdGotZzd1eDhnRVZaSVpjYlRwY3dsT2JRVHdIX0liUWhDeWd4SUVFRG8?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="Art-exp_wr" id="ignorediv"&gt;
                                        
                                        
                                        &lt;p&gt;A new technology is emerging that utilises the front-facing camera on devices to analyse emotions and monitor mental health. An app called Emobot is already being used by hundreds of patients to track their mood and assess the effectiveness of their depression treatment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The app analyses facial expressions throughout the day and generates a report, similar to a step count or heart rate graph. According to co-founder Samuel Lerman, Emobot is classified as a medical device in France, and the company is collaborating with psychiatrists to prescribe it to patients.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to &lt;a class="sp_lnk2" href="https://metro.co.uk/2025/06/17/now-phone-can-tell-depression-using-selfie-camera-23428483/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Metro,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the team was initially afraid people would find this too intrusive, given the app constantly watches you, and a future version will even listen to your tone of voice as you go about your day via the phone microphone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Lerman said, "The camera is open in the background all the time." So we were a bit skeptical about that aspect; however, the feedback was pretty good."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="v-ndtv"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He told &lt;a class="sp_lnk2" href="https://metro.co.uk/2025/06/17/now-phone-can-tell-depression-using-selfie-camera-23428483/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Metro&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that no photos from the camera are transmitted to a central database or stored, as they are processed locally by AI on the user's phone and deleted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This technology is similar to that being developed for office workers to check if they are really sitting at their computer or if they appear tired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We tried the emotion mapping software on display at the VivaTech conference in Paris, and a real-time image showed reporter Jen Mills as appearing both 'pleased' and 'bored' at the same time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Lerman said the app helps doctors track patients' responses to treatment as well as 'detect sudden deterioration of their mood' and relapse risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The focus on mental well-being was also evident at VivaTech 2025, where over 14,000 startups from more than 50 countries gathered. While artificial intelligence (AI) dominated the event, many of the most discussed innovations used AI and technology to improve healthcare and mental health, signalling a growing prioritisation of mental health in the tech industry.&lt;/p&gt;                                                                                
                                                                                
                                                                                                                        
                                                                                                                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                                                        

                                    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>NDTV</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:49:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxQTm11TmM1c01ZRHBsQjZORExfdnBiQ3RCbzRkSEgtc3dETm5jTnhneUxuTUx4NGE2SEEydGMxeVhDSC1xOTlyZzdPUUVfSmsxWUNkVjVTNVV1RHlTd0s1S0lmQWk4Qy1BWklCeGZHNC1XdVJHT1hxdGotZzd1eDhnRVZaSVpjYlRwY3dsT2JRVHdIX0liUWhDeWd4SUVFRG8</guid></item><item><title>“我是一名心脏病专家，这是我几乎每顿饭都会添加的一件事” - AOL.com | 'I'm a Cardiologist, and This Is the One Thing I Add to Almost Every Meal' - AOL.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMickFVX3lxTE1sXzZCV2VXOUNyWHU3RGRmeWRLMXZ5TVBrclc3bWNUMU1TRUhISG9GR3BLb09KSnNXUTdtS0ZkUXBJelR3bHVMMnAzQTZQOFNzV2MwTmFjZ3gzN1FTS003R1k1cHQteEs1WmhvSmRlNUJoUQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="caas-body"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/food/i-am-cardiologist-this-is-what-i-add-to-almost-every-meal" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:'I'm a Cardiologist, and This Is the One Thing I Add to Almost Every Meal';elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;'I'm a Cardiologist, and This Is the One Thing I Add to Almost Every Meal'&lt;/a&gt; originally appeared on &lt;a href="https://parade.com" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to the &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/healthy-living/healthy-eating/eat-smart/nutrition-basics/aha-diet-and-lifestyle-recommendations" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:American Heart Association, sticking to a balanced, nutrient-rich;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;American Heart Association, sticking to a balanced, nutrient-rich&lt;/a&gt; diet and exercise regimen can protect your heart and reduce the risk of heart disease. While it's not always the case, food &lt;em&gt;can &lt;/em&gt;be medicinal, and eating the right foods can certainly help with heart health maintenance. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ahead, cardiologists reveal the one type of food that can be particularly helpful in improving overall &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/how-many-times-a-week-to-walk-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:heart health;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;heart health&lt;/a&gt;, which they add to almost every meal.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/stethoscope" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:🩺;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;🩺&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/newsletters/healthy-now" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SIGN UP for tips to stay healthy &amp;amp; fit with the top moves, clean eats, health trends &amp;amp; more delivered right to your inbox twice a week&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://emojipedia.org/pill" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:💊;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;💊&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The Heart-Healthy Food a Cardiologist Integrates Into Most Meals&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to sticking to a heart-healthy diet, &lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/christopher-davis-md-facc-04429a103" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Christopher Davis, MD,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dr. Christopher Davis, MD&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;/a&gt; a cardiologist and chief cardiologist at &lt;a href="https://humann.com/collections/blood-pressure" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:humann;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;humann&lt;/a&gt;, says you can't go wrong with leafy greens. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Leafy greens are particularly beneficial for cardiovascular health given their dietary nitrate content, which can improve the elasticity of the vessels by supporting nitric oxide production," he tells &lt;em&gt;Parade.&lt;/em&gt; "Nitric oxide relaxes blood vessels, supports healthy blood pressure, improves circulation and protects against arterial stiffness." &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-to-never-do-when-you-first-wake-up-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:The One Thing You Should Never, Ever Do Within the First Hour of Waking Up, According to Cardiologists;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;The One Thing You Should Never, Ever Do Within the First Hour of Waking Up, According to Cardiologists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;As we age, our ability to make nitric oxide declines; so supporting this production through diet is one of the easiest and most effective ways to maintain cardiovascular function and longevity, according to Dr. Davis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Another Helpful Addition&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aside from leafy greens, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jaynemorgan" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Dr. Jayne Morgan, MD;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Dr. Jayne Morgan, MD&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;/strong&gt;cardiologist and vice president of medical affairs for &lt;a href="https://www.helloheart.com/" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Hello Heart, recommends adding fiber, especially soluble fiber,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Hello Heart, recommends adding fiber, especially soluble fiber,&lt;/a&gt; into your meals. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"Soluble supports the lowering of LDL (&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/best-way-to-measure-risk-of-heart-disease-study-may-2025" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:bad cholesterol;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;bad cholesterol&lt;/a&gt;), helps to regulate blood sugar, and helps to support a healthy blood pressure as well as healthy gut bacteria," she explains. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;When thinking about how to add this in at mealtime, soluble fiber can be found in flax seeds, chia seeds, beans and lentils, which can easily be added to soups or salads.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/spinach-impact-on-systolic-blood-pressure-according-to-cardiologists" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Adding This Leafy Green to Lunch Lowers Systolic Levels Fast, According to Cardiologists;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adding This Leafy Green to Lunch Lowers Systolic Levels Fast, According to Cardiologists&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What To Avoid if You Want To Lower Your Risk of Heart Issues&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that you know what cardiologists add to almost every meal, here's what they suggest steering clear of when it comes to maintaining cardiac health. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;For starters, you'll want to limit your consumption of &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-happens-when-you-stop-eating-red-meat" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:processed meats,;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;processed meats,&lt;/a&gt; whether that's bacon, sausage, hot dogs or even deli meats. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;"These meats are &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-not-to-do-after-eating-salty-meal" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:high in sodium;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;high in sodium&lt;/a&gt; (salt), saturated fats, and preservatives (nitrates/nitrites) and are linked to increases in blood pressure, cholesterol, and chronic inflammation in the body," Dr. Morgan says. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Aside from hot dogs, you may also want to think twice when you go to grab your next sweet treat. "Margarine sticks, pastries and cookies are usually prepared with trans fat and hydrogenated oils, which can raise your bad cholesterol (LDL) and lower your good cholesterol (HDL)," she adds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related: &lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-happens-to-your-blood-pressure-when-you-eat-blueberries-every-day" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Here's What Happens to Your Blood Pressure When You Eat Blueberries Every Day;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Here's What Happens to Your Blood Pressure When You Eat Blueberries Every Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking of sweet treats, it's worth keeping an eye on your sugary beverage consumption as well, from caramel frappuccinos to sodas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Soft drinks and high fructose corn syrup rapidly raise blood glucose, which over time contributes to insulin resistance, high triglycerides, and increased risk of metabolic and cardiovascular disease, so best to stay away from sugary drinks," Dr. Davis says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of the day, it's not one food that will drastically improve your overall cardiac health, but a myriad of lifestyle factors, including but not limited to diet, exercise and stress management, that can help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Up Next:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/health/what-not-to-do-after-eating-salty-meal" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Related: The One Thing You Should Never, Ever Do After Eating a High-Sodium Meal, According to Cardiologists;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Related: The One Thing You Should Never, Ever Do After Eating a High-Sodium Meal, According to Cardiologists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sources:&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://parade.com/food/i-am-cardiologist-this-is-what-i-add-to-almost-every-meal" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:'I'm a Cardiologist, and This Is the One Thing I Add to Almost Every Meal';elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;'I'm a Cardiologist, and This Is the One Thing I Add to Almost Every Meal'&lt;/a&gt; first appeared on Parade on Jun 18, 2025&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This story was originally reported by &lt;a href="https://parade.com/food/i-am-cardiologist-this-is-what-i-add-to-almost-every-meal" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Parade;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link rapid-noclick-resp"&gt;Parade&lt;/a&gt; on Jun 18, 2025, where it first appeared.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>AOL.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:44:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMickFVX3lxTE1sXzZCV2VXOUNyWHU3RGRmeWRLMXZ5TVBrclc3bWNUMU1TRUhISG9GR3BLb09KSnNXUTdtS0ZkUXBJelR3bHVMMnAzQTZQOFNzV2MwTmFjZ3gzN1FTS003R1k1cHQteEs1WmhvSmRlNUJoUQ</guid></item><item><title>胃溃疡细菌可能是阿尔茨海默氏症的惊喜盟友- ScienceAlert | Stomach Ulcer Bacteria Could Be a Surprise Ally Against Alzheimer's - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimwFBVV95cUxPU1lUQ1JRb01rSlNvUTQ0d3lnZE81eXpidTNNRE0xZHp6NEJPcUp5cER6TWRsT2VyVzAwNmFGbkZ5WXJUYy1GM3YzNUlDb0lXYlZKMVB1Rnl1TXhCVzZ6RDNfWkxGQXFDSTEtSXN4cXJoRVBRdk1vNjlVRGlxQkc5MVA4UVBmMlFLelU5Q3FfVUhySGZTcl83eGVEVQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Every three seconds, someone in the world develops dementia.  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IaO" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73015" data-postid="165051" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; disease is the most common form of dementia, accounting for between &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news-room/fact-sheets/detail/dementia#:%7E:text=Alzheimer%20disease%20is%20the%20most%20common%20form%20and%20may%20contribute,frontal%20lobe%20of%20the%20brain"&gt;60% and 70% of all cases&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although scientists have made significant progress in understanding the disease, there's still no cure. That's partly because Alzheimer's disease has multiple causes – many of which are &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41392-024-01911-3"&gt;still not fully understood&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two proteins which are widely believed to play central roles in Alzheimer's disease are &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/24493463/"&gt;amyloid-beta and tau&lt;/a&gt;. Amyloid-beta forms sticky plaques on the outside of brain cells. This disrupts communication between neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tau accumulate inside brain cells, where it twists into tangles. This ultimately leads to cell death. These plaques and tangles are the hallmark features of Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This understanding, known as the &lt;a href="https://ajp.amjpathol.org/article/S0002-9440(24)00407-3/fulltext"&gt;amyloid hypothesis&lt;/a&gt;, has shaped research for decades and led to treatments that aim to clear amyloid from the brain. &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(23)01077-2?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0092867423010772%3Fshowall%3Dtrue"&gt;Monoclonal antibody drugs&lt;/a&gt; have been approved in recent years for this purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But they only work in the early stages of the disease. They do not reverse existing damage and may cause serious side-effects such as brain swelling and bleeding. Most importantly, they only target amyloid-beta, leaving tau untreated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in a surprise twist, recent research published by my colleagues and me has found that a protein from &lt;em&gt;Helicobacter pylori&lt;/em&gt; – a bacteria best known for causing stomach ulcers – can block the &lt;a href="https://www.science.org/doi/full/10.1126/sciadv.ads7525"&gt;toxic buildup of both amyloid-beta and tau&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This unexpected finding may point to a new strategy for the fight against Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_143082" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-143082" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesOnNeuron_R_U_642.jpg" alt="Illustration of yellow clumps on pink nerve cells" class="size-full wp-image-143082" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesOnNeuron_R_U_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesOnNeuron_R_U_642-621x415.jpg 621w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2024/11/AmyloidPlaquesOnNeuron_R_U_642-600x401.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-143082" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Illustration of yellow amyloid-beta plaques on neurons. (Science Photo Library/Canva)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our discovery began with a very different question. We were initially studying how &lt;em&gt;H pylori&lt;/em&gt; interacts with other microbes. Some bacteria form &lt;a href="https://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/19490976.2025.2461721"&gt;protective communities called biofilms&lt;/a&gt;, which rely on amyloid assemblies (similar in structure to the plaques which form in the brain) as a structural scaffold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This led us to wonder: could &lt;em&gt;H pylori&lt;/em&gt; influence bacterial biofilms by also interfering with amyloid assemblies in humans?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We turned our attention to a well-known &lt;em&gt;H pylori&lt;/em&gt; protein called CagA. While half of the protein is known to trigger harmful effects in human cells (referred to as the C-terminal region), the other half (the protein's N-terminal region) may have protective properties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To our surprise, this N-terminal fragment, called CagAN, dramatically reduced the formation of both bacterial amyloids and biofilms in the bacterial species &lt;em&gt;Escherichia coli&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Pseudomonas&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Encouraged by these results, we tested whether the same protein fragment could block the buildup of human amyloid-beta proteins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To do this, we incubated amyloid-beta molecules in the lab: some were treated with CagAN, while others were left as normal. We then tracked amyloid formation using a fluorescence reader and an electron microscope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We found that treated samples had far less amyloid clump formation during the testing period. Even at very low concentrations, CagAN almost completely stopped amyloid-beta from forming amyloid aggregates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand how CagAN worked, we used nuclear magnetic resonance (which allows us to look at how molecules interact with each other) to examine how the protein interacts with amyloid-beta.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We also used computer modelling to investigate possible mechanisms. Remarkably, CagAN also blocked tau aggregation – suggesting it acts on multiple toxic proteins involved in Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Blocking the disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our study has shown us that a fragment from the &lt;em&gt;Helicobacter pylori&lt;/em&gt; protein can effectively block the buildup of the two proteins that are implicated in Alzheimer's disease. This suggests that bacterial proteins – or drugs modelled after them – could someday block the earliest signs of Alzheimer's.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What's more, the benefits may extend beyond Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In additional experiments, the same bacterial fragment blocked the aggregation of &lt;a href="https://advanced.onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1002/adbi.202101301"&gt;IAPP&lt;/a&gt; (a protein involved in type 2  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/diabetes" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73018" data-postid="165051" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;) and &lt;a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41419-023-05672-9"&gt;alpha-synuclein&lt;/a&gt; (linked to  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/go/IYl" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73029" data-postid="165051" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;Parkinson's&lt;/a&gt; disease). All of these conditions are driven by the accumulation of toxic amyloid aggregates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That a single bacterial fragment could interfere with so many proteins suggests exciting therapeutic potential. Though these conditions affect different parts of the body, they may be linked through cross-talk between amyloid proteins – a shared mechanism that CagAN could help disrupt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, it's important to be clear: this research is still at an early stage. All of our experiments were conducted in lab settings, not yet in animals or humans. Still, the findings open a new path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our study also uncovered the underlying mechanisms for how CagAN blocked the amyloid-beta and tau from forming amyloid aggregates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the ways in which CagAN did this was by preventing the proteins from coming together to form clumps. They also prevented small, premature amyloid aggregates from forming as well. In the future, we will continue the detailed mechanism study and evaluate the effects in animal models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These results also prompt a question: could &lt;em&gt;H pylori&lt;/em&gt;, long seen only as harmful, also have a protective side? Some studies have hinted at a connection between &lt;a href="https://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/hel.12454"&gt;&lt;em&gt;H pylori&lt;/em&gt; infection and Alzheimer's disease&lt;/a&gt;, though the relationship remains unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our discovery adds a new layer to this discussion, suggesting that part of &lt;em&gt;H pylori&lt;/em&gt; may actually interfere with the molecular events that lead to Alzheimer's disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That means in the future, we may need to take a more precise and personalised approach. Instead of aiming to eliminate &lt;em&gt;H pylori&lt;/em&gt; completely with antibiotics, it might be more important to understand, in different biological contexts, which parts of the bacterium are harmful, and which might actually be beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As medicine continues to move toward greater precision, the goal may no longer be to wipe out every microbe, but to understand how some of them might work with us rather than against us.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/259018/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/gefei-chen-2414626"&gt;Gefei Chen&lt;/a&gt;, Associate professor, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/karolinska-institutet-1250"&gt;Karolinska Institutet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/alzheimers-bacteria-that-causes-stomach-ulcers-may-protect-the-brain-our-new-research-indicates-259018"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:05:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimwFBVV95cUxPU1lUQ1JRb01rSlNvUTQ0d3lnZE81eXpidTNNRE0xZHp6NEJPcUp5cER6TWRsT2VyVzAwNmFGbkZ5WXJUYy1GM3YzNUlDb0lXYlZKMVB1Rnl1TXhCVzZ6RDNfWkxGQXFDSTEtSXN4cXJoRVBRdk1vNjlVRGlxQkc5MVA4UVBmMlFLelU5Q3FfVUhySGZTcl83eGVEVQ</guid></item><item><title>根据一项令人震惊的新研究- Earth.com ，大麻对心脏的影响比可卡因更严重 | Cannabis is worse for the heart than cocaine, according to a shocking new study - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTE9fYVVZTy0tMWt0WkdHdHVOZzhZNjY0MkJnUHdkeTdULUhCVlpHTTVfUHV0UjJpTHdySzY4VmpUcUUyVWc0Rk1jWjN3UTRmY2Q3bGNmdEhmTlQ5NEFKaWw2VlBjNjlkNkVCRVh1d0oyT2l4M1JKeXVhXzIwX2c?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannabis is everywhere now. It’s in pharmacies, parties, pain clinics, and political speeches. Many use it to sleep better, relax, or deal with pain. Some cannabis users even see it as a natural alternative to pills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, while the world embraced cannabis, heart doctors started noticing something else. A new study published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Heart&lt;/em&gt;, based on data from over 432 million people, has revealed a clear &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cannabis-extract-cbd-proven-highly-effective-at-killing-mosquitoes/"&gt;connection&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who use cannabis have a much higher risk of heart attacks, strokes, and even dying from heart disease. That’s not fear-mongering – it’s data from .&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-more-people-are-using-stronger-cannabis"&gt;More people are using stronger cannabis &lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In over half of the states in the U.S., and in some countries in Europe, like France, doctors can give cannabis to patients as medicine, but using it just for fun is still illegal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though it’s not allowed for fun, many young people in France still use it a lot. Germany recently changed its laws and now lets people use cannabis recreationally, starting in April 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now more people use cannabis, and the products they’re using are stronger than before. Today’s cannabis has more &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-reveal-the-most-complete-cannabis-genome-yet/"&gt;THC&lt;/a&gt;. That means stronger effects on the brain and body – especially the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cannabis-linked-to-heart-problems"&gt;Cannabis linked to heart problems&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers looked at 3,012 studies. Among them, 24 studies were focused on the link between cannabis and major heart problems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An analysis of the research showed that people who use &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cbd-reduces-the-unwanted-side-effects-of-thc/"&gt;cannabis&lt;/a&gt; have a 29 percent higher risk of heart attack, a 20 percent higher risk of stroke, and more than double the risk of dying from heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-regular-use-raises-stroke-risk"&gt;Regular use raises stroke risk&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stroke risk didn’t look the same in every study. A few didn’t find strong links, especially in people who used cannabis once or twice. But when the researchers zoomed in on heavy users or younger adults, the risk became clearer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Australia, one study found that people who used &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cannabis-use-in-any-form-directly-linked-to-significant-risk-of-heart-damage/"&gt;cannabis&lt;/a&gt; weekly were nearly five times more likely to suffer a stroke or mini-stroke. A U.S. hospital database also found increased risk, especially in people aged 25 to 34.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These results suggest that occasional cannabis use may not be a red flag. But regular use, especially while young, is when things start looking risky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cannabis-linked-to-more-heart-attacks"&gt;Cannabis linked to more heart attacks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;One study showed that cannabis users aged 15 to 22 were 36 percent more likely to have a heart attack. Another found that people using cannabis &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cannabis-use-directly-linked-to-head-and-neck-cancer/"&gt;more than once a week&lt;/a&gt; had more than double the odds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s after adjusting for tobacco, cocaine, and other drugs. Cannabis came out as the strongest predictor in a French hospital study – even stronger than &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/how-cocaine-tricks-and-hijacks-the-brain/"&gt;cocaine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s not the story we usually hear about cannabis. But these numbers speak louder than opinions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-higher-death-risk-from-heart-disease"&gt;Higher death risk from heart disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk of fatal cardiovascular events was also investigated. In one study, young patients who had heart attacks and also used cannabis were far more likely to die. The link remained consistent even after controlling for smoking and other conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another study conducted in the United States confirmed that cannabis users had a much higher chance of dying from heart-related causes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the UK, a 2024 study revealed an unexpected twist. Women, not men, faced higher risks of heart-related death from heavy cannabis use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-what-about-the-benefits-of-cannabis"&gt;What about the benefits of cannabis?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannabis has shown several proven medical benefits, especially when used under a doctor’s guidance. One of its most recognized uses is for managing chronic pain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People with conditions like arthritis, multiple sclerosis, or nerve-related injuries often find relief through cannabis-based treatments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The plant’s compounds – mainly THC and &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cannabis-extract-cbd-proven-highly-effective-at-killing-mosquitoes/"&gt;CBD&lt;/a&gt; – can interact with the body’s endocannabinoid system to reduce pain signals and inflammation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Medical cannabis also &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cannabis-may-ease-cancer-symptoms-like-pain-and-nausea/"&gt;helps cancer patients&lt;/a&gt; by easing nausea and vomiting caused by chemotherapy, and in some cases, it can stimulate appetite for those struggling with weight loss due to illness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors have also used cannabis to help patients with neurological disorders. In certain forms of epilepsy, especially in children, CBD-based medications have reduced the number and severity of seizures.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These examples reflect how cannabis, when used appropriately, can provide real and sometimes life-changing benefits for patients, making it easier for some to ignore the overall health implications attached to cannabis use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-experts-urge-tobacco-style-warnings"&gt;Experts urge tobacco-style warnings&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Cannabis needs to be incorporated into the framework for prevention of clinical cardiovascular disease. So too must cardiovascular disease prevention be incorporated into the regulation of cannabis markets,” noted Professor Stanton Glantz and Dr. Lynn Silver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experts emphasized that today’s cannabis is not what it used to be. It now includes potent concentrates, synthetic versions, and a growing variety of edible and inhalable forms. These may carry risks beyond the cannabinoids themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“How these changes affect cardiovascular risk requires clarification, as does the proportion of risk attributable to cannabinoids themselves versus particulate matter, terpenes or other components of the exposure,” the authors noted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Specifically, cannabis should be treated like tobacco: not criminalized, but discouraged, with protection of bystanders from secondhand exposure.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doctors should ask about cannabis use, particularly when it comes to patients with heart problems. For people using cannabis regularly, it’s time to rethink the idea that it is harmless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study is published in the journal &lt;a href="https://heart.bmj.com/content/early/2025/06/10/heartjnl-2024-325429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Heart&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:33:45 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE9fYVVZTy0tMWt0WkdHdHVOZzhZNjY0MkJnUHdkeTdULUhCVlpHTTVfUHV0UjJpTHdySzY4VmpUcUUyVWc0Rk1jWjN3UTRmY2Q3bGNmdEhmTlQ5NEFKaWw2VlBjNjlkNkVCRVh1d0oyT2l4M1JKeXVhXzIwX2c</guid></item><item><title>英国公民在摩洛哥与流浪狗接触后死于狂犬病- BBC | UK citizen dies from rabies after stray dog contact in Morocco - BBC</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9JSkphMTY1NXRmNFZTeHBzTVB0NVRoTWw3eWF2OV9HRzdpbHV2VmVTUGJ3V1pOa0g2dnU4S0p6RlVfRFBDZ3JBWkRfQXVlUTBkRVVfOFJaZ0JDUdIBX0FVX3lxTE5LZF9ZeWt5RGtBaXZUTDZIczZGRFEtLXRGWlpKcFc0b0FVVTlMQl9pTjU5Y1liSWcwRjJYWXBqcGoxWi13UTJMY2hONmZTVHJfekc0Vzc3SlBCMUxOOUtR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article&gt;&lt;p data-component="headline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 fDtfvH"&gt;&lt;h1 class="sc-f98b1ad2-0 dfvxux"&gt;Briton dies from rabies after stray dog contact&lt;/h1&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div data-component="byline-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new" class="sc-801dd632-0 eSlECZ"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="byline-new-contributors" class="sc-801dd632-12 jSIeFi"&gt;&lt;div class="sc-801dd632-5 kRoBHa"&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span class="sc-801dd632-7 lasLGY"&gt;Steve Jones &amp;amp; Rachel Russell&lt;/span&gt;&lt;p class="sc-801dd632-8 hwLppI"&gt;&lt;span&gt;BBC News, Yorkshire&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="image-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 gyQxwn"&gt;&lt;div data-testid="hero-image" class="sc-d1200759-1 kycbVO"&gt;&lt;img src="https://static.files.bbci.co.uk/bbcdotcom/web/20250616-143050-043f96f72f-web-2.23.1-5/grey-placeholder.png" class="sc-d1200759-0 dkIvM hide-when-no-script"&gt;&lt;img sizes="(min-width: 1280px) 50vw, (min-width: 1008px) 66vw, 96vw" srcset="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/240/cpsprodpb/cdf4/live/03753c60-4c43-11f0-a8b1-f318fea9c646.jpg.webp 240w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/320/cpsprodpb/cdf4/live/03753c60-4c43-11f0-a8b1-f318fea9c646.jpg.webp 320w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cdf4/live/03753c60-4c43-11f0-a8b1-f318fea9c646.jpg.webp 480w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/640/cpsprodpb/cdf4/live/03753c60-4c43-11f0-a8b1-f318fea9c646.jpg.webp 640w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/800/cpsprodpb/cdf4/live/03753c60-4c43-11f0-a8b1-f318fea9c646.jpg.webp 800w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1024/cpsprodpb/cdf4/live/03753c60-4c43-11f0-a8b1-f318fea9c646.jpg.webp 1024w,https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/1536/cpsprodpb/cdf4/live/03753c60-4c43-11f0-a8b1-f318fea9c646.jpg.webp 1536w" src="https://ichef.bbci.co.uk/news/480/cpsprodpb/cdf4/live/03753c60-4c43-11f0-a8b1-f318fea9c646.jpg.webp" loading="eager" alt="Getty Images A needle in the hands of a medic, with blue gloves in shot." class="sc-d1200759-0 dvfjxj"&gt;&lt;span class="sc-d1200759-2 gwFzuU"&gt;Getty Images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="caption-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 jvncPH"&gt;&lt;figcaption class="sc-536eff7b-0 FPsqq"&gt;The person died after contact with a dog while on holiday, according to the UK Health Security Agency (stock image)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;A person from Yorkshire has died from rabies after contact with a stray dog in Morocco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The UK Health Security Agency (UKHSA) said the person became infected while on holiday in the North African country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The agency said there was no risk to the wider public due to no documented evidence of rabies passing between people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Close contacts of the person and health workers were being assessed and offered vaccinations when necessary as a precaution, a UKHSA spokesperson added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Rabies can cause a life-threatening infection of the brain and nervous system in humans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;It is passed on through injuries such as bites and scratches from an infected animal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;It is nearly always fatal, the UKHSA said, but post-exposure treatment is "very effective" at preventing disease if given promptly after exposure to the virus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Dr Katherine Russell, from the UKHSA, said: "Human cases of rabies are extremely rare in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;"If you are bitten, scratched or licked by an animal in a country where rabies is found then you should wash the wound or site of exposure with plenty of soap and water and seek medical advice without delay."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-component="text-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dEGcKf"&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Six cases of human rabies connected to animal exposure abroad have been reported in the UK between 2000 and 2024.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;Rabies is particularly common in Asia and Africa, the UKHSA said, with people visiting affected countries advised to avoid contact with dogs, cats and other animals wherever they can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="sc-9a00e533-0 hxuGS"&gt;The agency also advised people to seek advice about the need for a rabies vaccine before travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-component="embed-block" class="sc-3b6b161a-0 dHQIrb"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>BBC</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:31:32 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiWkFVX3lxTE9JSkphMTY1NXRmNFZTeHBzTVB0NVRoTWw3eWF2OV9HRzdpbHV2VmVTUGJ3V1pOa0g2dnU4S0p6RlVfRFBDZ3JBWkRfQXVlUTBkRVVfOFJaZ0JDUdIBX0FVX3lxTE5LZF9ZeWt5RGtBaXZUTDZIczZGRFEtLXRGWlpKcFc0b0FVVTlMQl9pTjU5Y1liSWcwRjJYWXBqcGoxWi13UTJMY2hONmZTVHJfekc0Vzc3SlBCMUxOOUtR</guid></item><item><title>确诊前3年患者血液中发现的癌症早期体征- ScienceAlert | Early Signs of Cancer Found in Patient Blood 3 Years Before Diagnosis - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMinwFBVV95cUxORGF1Z1QyUjVSOTlQdWQ4OGxQSmo2SWpWXy1Ib2VnQnZVTy1YbHpEd25wdGx4LXhWdTF4MURGWTdST285RXNrY0x6VklmVVU5SGVHOHVsZV9KWmFYUWo1cUdfWVNrVjNQV09JY1VCekJGYWNoZGtqZXhIQVRKbWl6RzljUFprUTFpZVVRR203R0Zua2J1aXRDeGNBdE0xdEk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Spotting  &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/cancer" class="lar_link lar_link_outgoing" data-linkid="73077" data-postid="164985" rel="nofollow" target="_self"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; early can significantly improve the &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/these-3-strategies-can-improve-outcomes-for-cancer-patients"&gt;chances of recovery&lt;/a&gt;, and US researchers have shown that blood biomarkers may reveal tumors more than three years before a diagnosis is made.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The key lies in tiny fragments of genetic material shed by tumors. If a suitable analysis detecting these DNA signatures in the bloodstream can be rolled out at scale, it means a reliable way of catching cancer much earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Three years earlier provides time for intervention," &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/news/newsroom/news-releases/2025/06/cancers-can-be-detected-in-the-bloodstream-three-years-prior-to-diagnosis"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Yuxuan Wang, an oncology researcher at Johns Hopkins University in Maryland. "The tumors are likely to be much less advanced and more likely to be curable."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The team analyzed blood samples from 26 participants in a wider health study, who were diagnosed with cancer within six months of the sample collection. These samples were compared with blood taken from 26 other individuals who didn't develop cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically, the test looked for circulating tumor DNA, or ctDNA. Using a combination of algorithms and multiple cross-checks, &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/scientists-just-identified-hundreds-of-genes-that-could-cause-cancer"&gt;modifications&lt;/a&gt; known to be linked to tumors can be spotted, even though they're rare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For eight of the 52 study participants, cancer was flagged by the multi-cancer early detection (MCED) test put together by the researchers – that means nearly 31 percent of those who got cancer were picked up by the blood analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_164988" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-164988" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/DNARendering.jpg" alt="DNA illustration" class="wp-image-164988 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/DNARendering.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/DNARendering-600x375.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-164988" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Cancer tumors leave DNA fragments. (Josh Hawley/Moment/Getty Images)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Older samples from 3.1-3.5 years earlier were available for six of those eight people, and of those six, cancer could be detected in four individuals. The same DNA fragments from tumors had already begun to appear, being found at levels up to nearly 80 times lower than those detected by the MCED test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, there's still plenty of work to be done. The further the samples go back in time, the lower the levels of detectable ctDNA: if we're to spot cancer up to three years in advance, much more &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-blood-test-detects-deadly-brain-cancers-in-just-one-hour"&gt;sensitive blood tests&lt;/a&gt; need to be developed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This study shows the promise of MCED tests in detecting cancers very early, and sets the benchmark sensitivities required for their success," &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/news/newsroom/news-releases/2025/06/cancers-can-be-detected-in-the-bloodstream-three-years-prior-to-diagnosis"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Bert Vogelstein, an oncology researcher at the Ludwig Center at Johns Hopkins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists are doing fantastic work at identifying ways to spot cancer early, including &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/this-single-blood-test-can-detect-multiple-kinds-of-cancer-early"&gt;through blood tests&lt;/a&gt;. However, getting them successfully through trials and approved by regulators &lt;a href="https://cancerletter.com/clinical/20241025_1/"&gt;remains a challenge&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even with the hurdles ahead, there are reasons for optimism: each new study showing &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/new-study-says-a-blood-test-can-find-5-types-of-cancer-before-standard-diagnosis"&gt;early cancer diagnosis&lt;/a&gt; adds to our overall knowledge and understanding of how cancer gets started, and how it can be identified at earlier stages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add to that the progress that's being made in terms of cancer treatments – including treatments capable of &lt;a href="https://www.sciencealert.com/a-new-compound-could-help-treat-up-a-quarter-of-all-cancers"&gt;attacking multiple cancer types&lt;/a&gt; – and there are good reasons to believe that survival rates can &lt;a href="https://cancercontrol.cancer.gov/ocs/statistics"&gt;continue to rise&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Detecting cancers years before their clinical diagnosis could help provide management with a more favorable outcome," &lt;a href="https://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/news/newsroom/news-releases/2025/06/cancers-can-be-detected-in-the-bloodstream-three-years-prior-to-diagnosis"&gt;says&lt;/a&gt; Nickolas Papadopoulos, an oncology researcher at the Ludwig Center.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"Of course, we need to determine the appropriate clinical follow-up after a positive test for such cancers."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research has been published in &lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.1158/2159-8290.CD-25-0375"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cancer Discovery&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:02:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMinwFBVV95cUxORGF1Z1QyUjVSOTlQdWQ4OGxQSmo2SWpWXy1Ib2VnQnZVTy1YbHpEd25wdGx4LXhWdTF4MURGWTdST285RXNrY0x6VklmVVU5SGVHOHVsZV9KWmFYUWo1cUdfWVNrVjNQV09JY1VCekJGYWNoZGtqZXhIQVRKbWl6RzljUFprUTFpZVVRR203R0Zua2J1aXRDeGNBdE0xdEk</guid></item><item><title>根据心脏病专家的说法，降低心脏病发作风险的首要运动- TODAY.com | The No. 1 Exercise to Lower Heart Attack Risk, According to a Cardiologist - TODAY.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxPU0txVHlKUWpuMTNuSEZPMUx5NGtoczRlNlVzRjhQcVd5Zk4td0tULTBNaDM2LWtLcmVibVQyczlUUjQ0QjU4WmpXVk1OajBvX0kyUzRVT2EyWE9pbFB6cEh4RWRPMldmWW1sZVhhejFFU1R4c1NMNy1wdGFaellyOGtNYmhpNlhuRFRfQnVjOUxPLTE2aDI3ONIBVEFVX3lxTE43UWFEUXlnRFhTQkp1ZlE2MV8ydVFjb3RYOG9yWHNIU0N4cTY2WkJGVk03MnFBdEVDQ3lKemdDNTdqR3NWeG5IS3F1WDBpNXVtTUN2RQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body__content"&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-ba3d9a" class="body-graf"&gt;Exercise is famously good for the mind and body. But what type of physical activity is best to reduce your risk of a heart attack?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cfbb2a" class="body-graf"&gt;Strength training, cardio and stretching are all beneficial for health in different ways, including weight loss, a leaner body and better mood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboolaReadMoreBelow"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-3ad2cf" class="body-graf"&gt;There’s also isometric exercise, which involves contracting muscles and holding that position for a few minutes without moving — doing a &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/plank-exercise-rcna24413" target="_blank"&gt;plank&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/squat-variations-t245044" target="_blank"&gt;wall squat&lt;/a&gt;, for example. It’s static, but very intense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-41a8b9" class="body-graf"&gt;Of all these, one type of physical activity is superior for the heart, says Dr. Luke Laffin, a preventive cardiologist and co-director of the Center for Blood Pressure Disorders at the Cleveland Clinic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-b80fa0" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cardiologist Tip of the Day: Do Aerobic Exercise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5a37ef" class="body-graf"&gt;“Aerobic exercise training should be promoted above all else,” Laffin previously told TODAY.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-5024b8" class="body-graf"&gt;Also known as cardio or endurance exercise, aerobic activity makes you breathe harder and forces your heart to beat faster, which makes the heart and lungs stronger, the &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/heart/physical-activity/types" target="_blank"&gt;National Heart, Lung and Blood Institute notes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-746bf6" class="body-graf"&gt;Examples of aerobic exercise include &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/interval-walking-rcna212588" target="_blank"&gt;walking&lt;/a&gt;, hiking, jogging, swimming, riding a bike, &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/jump-rope-workout-for-beginners-rcna101016" target="_blank"&gt;jumping rope&lt;/a&gt;, tennis, &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/pickleball-best-sport-to-live-longer-rcna186956" target="_blank"&gt;pickleball&lt;/a&gt; and soccer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c6e059" class="body-graf"&gt;If you're not sure where to start, &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/specials/start-today/" target="_blank"&gt;download the Start TODAY app&lt;/a&gt; for monthly cardio plans designed by best-in-class trainers. From indoor walking routines to HIIT workouts and guided audio podcasts that will motivate you get your steps in, the Start TODAY app can help you make regular aerobic exercise a habit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-f7b6be" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why It Matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-cfbf37" class="body-graf"&gt;Study after study has shown aerobic physical activity is better than other types of exercise when it comes to lowering the risk of heart attack, Laffin said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-baf790" class="body-graf"&gt;When done regularly, it can lower a person’s risk for coronary heart disease, a condition where plaque clogs the arteries, and reduces blood flow to the heart muscle, according to the &lt;a href="https://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/health/heart/physical-activity/benefits" target="_blank"&gt;National Heart, Lung and Blood Institute&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="recommended-intersection-ref" data-activity-map="recommended-article-body-recommended" data-testid="recommended-wrapper"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-692382" class="body-graf"&gt;Aerobic exercise also &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/11926784/" target="_blank"&gt;lowers blood pressure&lt;/a&gt; in both healthy people and those who have high blood pressure, a condition that can lead to a heart attack, the &lt;a href="https://www.heart.org/en/health-topics/high-blood-pressure/health-threats-from-high-blood-pressure/how-high-blood-pressure-can-lead-to-a-heart-attack" target="_blank"&gt;American Heart Association warns&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 id="anchor-7a192a" class="body-heading"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Get Started&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-c00f65" class="body-graf"&gt;Laffin recommends at least 150 minutes of moderate intensity aerobic physical activity — which means you can still carry on a conversation while doing it — per week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-7d725c" class="body-graf"&gt;It can be broken up into “&lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/exercise-snacks-fitness-rcna56744" target="_blank"&gt;exercise snacks&lt;/a&gt;” that last a few minutes,  done over 30-minute sessions or concentrated into longer workouts. &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/health/diet-fitness/exercise-only-weekends-rcna39325" target="_blank"&gt;Exercising only on weekends&lt;/a&gt;, for example, provides similar health benefits as more frequent shorter workouts, studies have found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-576df7" class="body-graf"&gt;Here's some &lt;a href="https://www.today.com/start-today" target="_blank"&gt;Start TODAY&lt;/a&gt; exercise inspiration to try:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="anchor-478680" class="endmark body-graf"&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.today.com/expert-tip-of-the-day" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;em&gt;TODAY’s Expert Tip of the Day&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;series is all about simple strategies to make life a little easier. Every Monday through Friday, different qualified experts share their best advice on diet, fitness, heart health, mental wellness and more.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>TODAY.com</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPU0txVHlKUWpuMTNuSEZPMUx5NGtoczRlNlVzRjhQcVd5Zk4td0tULTBNaDM2LWtLcmVibVQyczlUUjQ0QjU4WmpXVk1OajBvX0kyUzRVT2EyWE9pbFB6cEh4RWRPMldmWW1sZVhhejFFU1R4c1NMNy1wdGFaellyOGtNYmhpNlhuRFRfQnVjOUxPLTE2aDI3ONIBVEFVX3lxTE43UWFEUXlnRFhTQkp1ZlE2MV8ydVFjb3RYOG9yWHNIU0N4cTY2WkJGVk03MnFBdEVDQ3lKemdDNTdqR3NWeG5IS3F1WDBpNXVtTUN2RQ</guid></item><item><title>这个简单的健身测试可以预测您的寿命-《华盛顿邮报》 | This simple fitness test might predict how long you’ll live - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQYzc0TVJjQ2dDNlozMU8wc1h5T0JfeVdURGNxYnFLZ21XMzk3RFU5M0hxX1R4bUlWUmdkbEQ2d01CdER1WncwLWpsdjgyaXhEaG1rSTFrSFVoNVhYTGtWVERqVW5wWWRmRHJsQ2FUMUx2RlJnNVdwam9PbGhETGdQQmNlU3VPQlpv?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XF433F5UTFEZ5GNPFK5PSGVIJY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A simple test of your balance, strength and flexibility, known as the sitting-rising test, could be an early indicator of &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/06/08/death-clock-ai-life-expectancy/" target="_blank"&gt;how long you’ll live&lt;/a&gt;, according to a large-scale new study of mobility and mortality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IPF3A5537FCJPKWC6UNYLSPHRM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The study, published Wednesday in the &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurjpc/article-lookup/doi/10.1093/eurjpc/zwaf325" target="_blank"&gt;European Journal of Preventive Cardiology&lt;/a&gt;, looked at how well 4,282 men and women aged between 46 and 75 could lower themselves from a standing position to the floor and then stand back up again with as little assistance as possible from their hands, knees, furniture or human helpers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MPFSMEBR25H2NMLOARRC7YPDVM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The test assesses “all the aspects of fitness that are not aerobic,” said Claudio Gil Araújo, the study’s lead author and research director at an exercise-medicine clinic in Rio de Janeiro, where the data were collected. Those aspects include muscular health, balance, flexibility and body composition, he said, each of which is important for &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/03/06/cellular-reprogramming-longevity-reverse-aging/" target="_blank"&gt;longevity and health&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GCKKYEJ2EZCMVK4HM4XTWPRHM4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In the study, middle-aged and older people who needed no support to sit or stand were about six times less likely to die of &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2025/02/24/heart-disease-strokes-cardiovascular-death/" target="_blank"&gt;heart disease&lt;/a&gt; and other cardiovascular conditions during the next decade or so than people who wobbled and had great difficulty completing the task. They also were less likely to die of other natural causes, including &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/05/27/decrease-risk-cancer-science/" target="_blank"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4AAFTVOUT5BQ7GHZ673TJFLMAU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There are many tests of balance or strength or &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/09/16/flexibility-test-aging-longevity/" target="_blank"&gt;flexibility&lt;/a&gt;, Araújo said.&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;“But what makes this test special is that it looks at all of them at once, which is why we think it can be such a strong predictor” of longevity, he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="GOIN7C2TY5HN3GD7OQHHVZSNXQ" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="GOIN7C2TY5HN3GD7OQHHVZSNXQ" data-testid="article-header"&gt;How to do the sitting-rising test&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="M5RF3HSFQ5EF7IJQTAJHFQVOLA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Want to try the sitting-rising test yourself? First find a partner. “Don’t do this test on your own,” Araújo said. Your partner will watch you, score your test and, most important, steady you if you start to topple. (If you have disabilities or serious joint problems, such as hip, spine or &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2024/05/20/strength-training-arthritis-risk-prevention/" target="_blank"&gt;knee arthritis&lt;/a&gt;, you probably shouldn’t do the test, Araújo said, since it could cause unnecessary pain or injury.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-list" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;ul class="PJLV font--article-body font-copy gray-darkest mt-0 mr-lg ml-lg mb-md list" data-contentid="IZJZQRG63VEOFGUB57FSRYYGBE" data-apitype="list"&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Clear a level space so you have room to maneuver but also, if needed, still have a wall, chair or other support nearby.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;If the floor is bare, put down a pad in case you land with a thump while sitting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Remove your shoes and socks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Stand with your feet slightly apart, then cross one foot in front of the other. Hold your arms however you’d like.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Lower yourself until you’re seated on the ground. Try not to wobble or use any support to get yourself settled, such as a hand, forearm or any part of your legs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li class="wpds-c-gtqFlz"&gt;&lt;span&gt;From this seated position, stand back up, trying to remain steady and not rely on any support, including using your hands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2V4PM6E5DJDMZHPBDBSHT7PAZU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;To score your test, start with 10 points. Your partner then subtracts one point every time you use a hand or any other support to help you lower down or rise up and half a point every time you noticeably wobble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="455SJUV6KNCQVFVJSXOJVQPOZA" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="455SJUV6KNCQVFVJSXOJVQPOZA" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Did you pass the test?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CGOPQ6U3ABB67H6NHVHCDO4AAM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In the new study, men and women who scored between 0 and 4 were far more likely to die of &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/2023/05/21/heart-disease-rising-rates-seniors/" target="_blank"&gt;cardiovascular problems &lt;/a&gt;and other natural causes during about a 12-year-long follow-up period than those scoring a perfect 10. (The scientists screened out deaths from suicides or accidents, such as car crashes, that wouldn’t be considered natural causes.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="MR3U3NCQVFFVVJ456BLQPSVMYQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Men and women scoring between 4.5 and 7.5 had about a threefold heightened risk of dying during the follow-up period, compared to those who scored a 10.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="54MLJ2R7WFFRBNQHX3AHNORAFQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A relatively low score, below about a 7.5 for healthy middle-aged and older people, “should be a cause for some concern,” Araújo said. He’s 69 and recently scored an 8.5, he said. (No one in the study group was older than 75, so it’s not clear if the findings apply to anyone 76 or older.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SREW42R745BZ5H6H6WT6PPXII4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;These new results update &lt;a href="https://academic.oup.com/eurjpc/article/21/7/892/5925784?login=false" target="_blank"&gt;a 2014 study&lt;/a&gt; from Araújo’s group that likewise showed an association between how people scored and their longevity. A score between 8 and 10 “indicated a particularly low risk of death” in subsequent years, Araújo and his co-authors wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VURDWPNVZJB3PMW22B5SUF4B6Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;That study involved about 2,000 men and women and a follow-up period of about six years. The new study doubled both the participants and follow-up time, making the updated results “that much stronger,” Araújo said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="KIBCD74LKVHC3C7HH3QUVPZTTA" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="KIBCD74LKVHC3C7HH3QUVPZTTA" data-testid="article-header"&gt;Low score can be a ‘wake-up call’&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HVJIAAPKB5DLBOB2EER6VAJH3I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The sitting-rising test is not a foolproof indicator of our health or &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2025/01/08/fitness-fatness-longevity-health/" target="_blank"&gt;longevity&lt;/a&gt;, though. It incorporates so many aspects of fitness, for one thing, it’s hard to know which are weakest if our scores are low, said Avril Mansfield, a professor of physical therapy at the University of Toronto, who studies mobility and balance. She wasn’t involved with the new study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="KMWYMHM7ZREHHFMB6MUZTGM2KA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Is the problem mostly our flexibility, strength, range of motion, balance or some combination of several of those? “Working with a professional like a physiotherapist or a clinical exercise specialist could help you identify the specific physical limitations” that are impairing your score, she said, “and design an exercise program to address those limitations.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4OJG6D6P7JENHEFJKV57FGWUT4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;This test also could be daunting or inappropriate for many people, said Lora Giangregorio, a professor at the University of Waterloo in Canada who studies falls and &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/10/17/bone-health-osteoporosis-prevention/" target="_blank"&gt;bone health&lt;/a&gt; and wasn’t involved with the study. “It requires people to get off of the floor in a prescribed way that requires very good joint mobility.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VNFXWJSC35F6VNYKITNBY2SESU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;If you have &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/health/arthritis-joint-pain-remedies/2020/10/16/5c1beab0-08a2-11eb-a166-dc429b380d10_story.html" target="_blank"&gt;joint pain&lt;/a&gt; or other disabilities or are older and feel infirm, other tests of mobility are likely to be safer and more reliable, she said. Try, for instance, &lt;a href="https://stacks.cdc.gov/view/cdc/157303" target="_blank"&gt;the 30-second chair stand test&lt;/a&gt;, which is recommended by the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;to assess physical performance in older people, she said. Simply count how many times you can rise from and sit back onto a chair seat in 30 seconds, without using your hands. Men younger than 60 should manage, at minimum, 15 and women that age at least 13. Average scores decline by one or two per decade after that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="SGSRUWU4GZC6NE4IS7GHCJO4XU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The sitting-rising test and the new study also don’t tell us why the test predicts mortality, although Araújo believes low scores indicate underlying disease and frailty. People who are inflexible also often have stiff arteries, he said, contributing to heart disease, while people with poor balance could be predisposed to &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/wellness/2023/03/09/fall-risk-older-adults-prevention/" target="_blank"&gt;serious falls&lt;/a&gt;, which can precipitate physical decline and death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EIOTMPFAWZC75K4U45ESJ6BZLI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Perhaps most important, though, a low score is a portent, but not a promise, he said. “People ask me all the time, ‘If my score is low, does that mean I’ll be dead in five years?’ I tell them, ‘Of course not,’” Araújo said. But it can be a wake-up call, he added. “It’s telling you, maybe you need to make some changes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 11:14:30 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxQYzc0TVJjQ2dDNlozMU8wc1h5T0JfeVdURGNxYnFLZ21XMzk3RFU5M0hxX1R4bUlWUmdkbEQ2d01CdER1WncwLWpsdjgyaXhEaG1rSTFrSFVoNVhYTGtWVERqVW5wWWRmRHJsQ2FUMUx2RlJnNVdwam9PbGhETGdQQmNlU3VPQlpv</guid></item><item><title>专家对可能致命的真菌发出警报，这些真菌听起来直接来自“最后的生命” ： “我们谈论的是数十万人的生命” -雅虎 | Experts sound alarm over potentially lethal fungus that sounds straight out of 'The Last of Us': 'We're talking about hundreds of thousands of lives' - Yahoo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMihAFBVV95cUxNMkJlT0VzaU9paUw4bEJjWXVVbGhzUTdud1BwdkxMTGE3SVJSdXhZS19sMnJmazVxQkFpaXZuMERpQ3BXREdOenIwVWlkbml3dXNfS0xNQ2xMM2dvWUEtc2tDV296QWxCTkJ5SjJfVUExMkZmLVdTdExFb0E1RE5NdVhaXzI?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="" data-article-body="true"&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A potentially lethal group of fungi called Aspergillus could spread worldwide, with the possibility of northerly shifts to parts of Europe, Asia, and the Americas. New research suggests that rising global temperatures may drive the health hazard to previously under-exposed regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What's happening?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;As the Financial Times &lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/506f5a03-8520-40e1-aee3-a6e6427f68c0" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:reported;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;reported&lt;/a&gt; in early May, researchers from the United Kingdom have a preprint up at Research Square that shows how the prevalence of a potential killer fungus could increase due to human-caused climate change. A warming planet is set to accelerate fungal growth and spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;On the surface, the threat sounds like something you'd watch in an apocalyptic TV series. In fact, a sensationalized brain-infecting fungus zombifies and wipes out most of the population in the video game and HBO show "The Last of Us," though that series is based on another type of fungus called Ophiocordyceps that actually has various species that specialize in taking over the brain of specific insects and animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;There is, fortunately, no species of Ophiocordyceps that targets humans, but Aspergillus is a real concern for people around the world and not a fictional creation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The spores can cause aspergillosis, affecting especially the lungs but also potentially the brain. When infections occur, mortality rates can be high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;"We're talking about hundreds of thousands of lives, and continental shifts in species distributions," &lt;a href="https://www.researchsquare.com/article/rs-6545782/v1" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:preprint;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;preprint&lt;/a&gt; co-author Norman van Rhijn, from the University of Manchester, &lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/506f5a03-8520-40e1-aee3-a6e6427f68c0" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:told;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; the Financial Times. "In 50 years, where things grow and what you get infected by is going to be completely different."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;A news release from the university &lt;a href="https://www.manchester.ac.uk/about/news/climate-change-putting-millions-more-people-at-risk-from-infection-causing-fungi/#:~:text=Novel%20projections%20show%20that%20in%2015%20years%2C%20if%20we%20rely%20on%20fossil%20fuels%20instead%20of%20clean%20power%20(scenario%20of%20SSP585%20%5Bsos.noaa.gov%5D*)%2C%20we%20are%20likely%20to%20see%20the%20significant%20spread%20of%20certain%20fungal%20pathogens%20in%20Europe" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:noted;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;noted&lt;/a&gt;, "Novel projections show that in 15 years, if we rely on fossil fuels instead of clean power, we are likely to see the significant spread of certain fungal pathogens in Europe."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;Why are increasing fungal threats concerning?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Dangerous strains of fungus like Aspergillus can grow rapidly in hot, humid conditions. The steady overheating of our planet and resulting sea level rise, stemming from the use of dirty energy sources, may be creating the ideal circumstances for infections to spread into previously unaffected areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Scientists have been warning the public about the global health catastrophes that could be on the horizon due to the potential for an explosion in fungal pathogens. Although microscopic, out-of-control fungi can pose significant threats to wellness and safety. People with compromised immune systems and preexisting conditions are often at the most risk of severe complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;And not only do warmer temps and wetter surroundings sponsor fungal growth but also other extreme weather events. &lt;a href="https://publichealth.berkeley.edu/articles/spotlight/research/deadly-fungi-toxic-tides-and-wildfire-smoke" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Wildfires can exacerbate exposures;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Wildfires can exacerbate exposures&lt;/a&gt;, disturbing soil habitats and aerosolizing spores in smoke. Following droughts and subsequent heavy rainfall, spores can be released into the air and inhaled in nearby communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Meanwhile, significant upticks in infection can drive resistance to treatments, which could leave vulnerable populations even more desperate. &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/05/24/climate/deadly-fungi-aspergillus-spread" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:According to;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;According to&lt;/a&gt; recent reporting from CNN, the World Health Organization "added Aspergillus flavus to its critical group of fungal pathogens in 2022 because of its public health impact and antifungal resistance risk."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The outlet noted that the strain can also infect and destroy crops, jeopardizing food supplies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3 class="mb-4 text-lg font-bold"&gt;What can be done to prevent and prepare for fungal threats?&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Scientists are working to understand fungal pathogens through initiatives like a &lt;a href="https://www.ft.com/content/506f5a03-8520-40e1-aee3-a6e6427f68c0" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:five-year project;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;five-year project&lt;/a&gt; at the University of California, Berkeley, which seeks to uncover factors that can affect the occurrence and severity of fungal infections. Research is also underway to reduce their spread and strengthen food security.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;The WHO issued a new report in April &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/news/item/01-04-2025-who-issues-its-first-ever-reports-on-tests-and-treatments-for-fungal-infections" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:indicating;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;indicating&lt;/a&gt; the need for faster, more reliable, and cheaper testing methods, particularly in low- in middle-income countries, where fungal threats are an especially troublesome public health concern. &lt;a href="https://www.cnn.com/2025/05/24/climate/deadly-fungi-aspergillus-spread" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:Supporting pro-environment policies;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;Supporting pro-environment policies&lt;/a&gt; that not only invest in research and development to address these threats but also prioritize and center the marginalized groups disproportionately impacted by fungal infections will be key to meaningful solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Fungal spread could be managed in residential areas with natural fungicides. And at home, individuals can reduce some risks by practicing hygiene, properly drying skin, and strengthening their immune systems to fight infection. But since Aspergillus and other fungi could continue to pose global threats, it's global health solutions — including the mitigation of human-caused climate change — that will be most needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mb-4 text-lg md:leading-8 break-words"&gt;Join our &lt;a href="https://www.thecooldown.com/future-newsletter/?recrFYLvD9xpum9Dp" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:free newsletter;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;free newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for &lt;strong&gt;good news&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;useful tips&lt;/strong&gt;, and don't miss &lt;a href="https://rb.gy/ivhzmj" rel="nofollow noopener" target="_blank" data-ylk="slk:this cool list;elm:context_link;itc:0;sec:content-canvas" class="link "&gt;this cool list&lt;/a&gt; of easy ways to help yourself while helping the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Yahoo</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:45:14 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMihAFBVV95cUxNMkJlT0VzaU9paUw4bEJjWXVVbGhzUTdud1BwdkxMTGE3SVJSdXhZS19sMnJmazVxQkFpaXZuMERpQ3BXREdOenIwVWlkbml3dXNfS0xNQ2xMM2dvWUEtc2tDV296QWxCTkJ5SjJfVUExMkZmLVdTdExFb0E1RE5NdVhaXzI</guid></item><item><title>今年首次在马萨诸塞州的蚊子中检测到西尼罗河病毒- WCVB | West Nile virus detected in mosquitoes in Mass. for first time this year - WCVB</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxQSDVYUnpuVWJGeW9sOUkxdlpxaFlTdGpVbE5qSWFSTEZ0MU45MEJWWld1N2pRWlpBb2JWZU1GWU5VWnZDc1ZNQ1dqY3pieHBVY2YtUy1pR0l0NTRCSF9meURZX3NjSkM4cF9udk5Ydi1hQlVpYzF4blVsTjNocHhRWmE3Q0dtSW1ZY2JkZ2JNbmhHOVZEdlQ1ZzZjeURHa2xTM3h4b0gzdTJLdw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article-content--body-text-raw"&gt;
						West Nile virus has been detected in mosquitoes in Massachusetts for the first time this year, the Massachusetts Department of Public Health announced Tuesday.The presence of the virus was in a mosquito sample collected on Saturday in Shrewsbury.“Mid-June is earlier than we typically first find West Nile virus-infected mosquitoes in Massachusetts. WNV activity is very difficult to predict in advance, which is why the mosquito surveillance system is so important,” said Public Health Commissioner Dr. Robbie Goldstein.The virus is usually transmitted to humans through the bite of an infected mosquito. There were 19 human cases of West Nile virus in 2024. Last year, the virus was first detected in mosquito samples collected in late June. No human or animal cases of West Nile virus have been detected so far this year. At this time, there is no evidence of Eastern equine encephalitis, another arbovirus that occurs sporadically in Massachusetts. There were four human cases of EEE in 2024.While West Nile virus can infect people of all ages, people over the age of 50 are at higher risk for severe disease. Most people infected will have no symptoms. Symptoms tend to include fever and flu-like illness. In rare cases, more severe illness can occur.  
					&lt;/p&gt;
	
					&lt;div class="article-content--body-text"&gt;
						&lt;strong class="dateline"&gt;SHREWSBURY, Mass. —&lt;/strong&gt; 													&lt;p&gt;West Nile virus has been detected in mosquitoes in Massachusetts for the first time this year, the Massachusetts Department of Public Health announced Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presence of the virus was in a mosquito sample collected on Saturday in Shrewsbury.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;“Mid-June is earlier than we typically first find West Nile virus-infected mosquitoes in Massachusetts. WNV activity is very difficult to predict in advance, which is why the mosquito surveillance system is so important,” said Public Health Commissioner Dr. Robbie Goldstein.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The virus is usually transmitted to humans through the bite of an infected mosquito. There were 19 human cases of West Nile virus in 2024. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year, the virus was first detected in mosquito samples collected in late June. No human or animal cases of West Nile virus have been detected so far this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this time, there is no evidence of Eastern equine encephalitis, another arbovirus that occurs sporadically in Massachusetts. There were four human cases of EEE in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;p&gt;While West Nile virus can infect people of all ages, people over the age of 50 are at higher risk for severe disease. Most people infected will have no symptoms. Symptoms tend to include fever and flu-like illness. In rare cases, more severe illness can occur.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="cream-inline-rec" class="cream-inline hidden"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;


							
											&lt;/div&gt;
	
	
						
						
																			

																				&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>WCVB</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:12:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxQSDVYUnpuVWJGeW9sOUkxdlpxaFlTdGpVbE5qSWFSTEZ0MU45MEJWWld1N2pRWlpBb2JWZU1GWU5VWnZDc1ZNQ1dqY3pieHBVY2YtUy1pR0l0NTRCSF9meURZX3NjSkM4cF9udk5Ydi1hQlVpYzF4blVsTjNocHhRWmE3Q0dtSW1ZY2JkZ2JNbmhHOVZEdlQ1ZzZjeURHa2xTM3h4b0gzdTJLdw</guid></item><item><title>他定制的癌症疗法在美国国立卫生研究院的冰箱里。他可能无法及时得到它。-《华盛顿邮报》 | His custom cancer therapy is in an NIH freezer. He may not get it in time. - The Washington Post</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijwFBVV95cUxOUHI5eVVzUEhBT21kVXNkaTR0SzNTeDZ6XzN6aVgtS3lBTHZZQXlhbmxsLW1fdFpTNkNVME5oODdNNEt1d0dsNFk0Vlp3ZFZBNVhSOEtLTWp3QkJPZXRRbXVJU1RtQnhUc3BBN1kwNWRydEFRdUxQZXpmYmp2LU5aNzZKb3FXcmJSWXNrLTlJWQ?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="meteredContent grid-center"&gt;&lt;div class="teaser-content"&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JTB219J5253VT850JJ3NYDHGC8" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Richard Schlueter, 56, was planting cucumbers and squash in his community garden plot in Greensboro, Georgia, in May when he tore open a bag of soil and heard a pop. His collarbone&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;had snapped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="NDMFAU3X2RD33K4MO7FQP34SHE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In early June, a scan revealed that the cancer that started in his tonsils was racing through his bones. That day, he&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;called a medical team at the &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2025/03/05/nih-trump-turmoil-grants/"&gt;National Institutes of Health&lt;/a&gt; that had created an experimental cell therapy, custom-made to attack his cancer as part of a clinical trial. He needed it. Now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-subscribe-cta" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="7IUTFDGVOVGKTKEAXIJIZHF4KU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Instead, he received more bad news: His therapy would be delayed at least a month because of staff cuts at NIH.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="E7ZA32GA5BERJBSOSPXQAYR3VI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A week later, Schlueter and his wife, Michelle, saw NIH Director Jay Bhattacharya push back on &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2025/06/09/nih-scientists-bethesda-declaration-trump/"&gt;concerns raised&lt;/a&gt; by his own staff that the ouster of essential employees and other disruptions to the biomedical research agency were harming science and patients. Bhattacharya said on X that objections raised in a document called the Bethesda Declaration contained &lt;a href="https://x.com/NIHDirector_Jay/status/1932137905939431769"&gt;“fundamental misconceptions”&lt;/a&gt; about NIH’s new direction. Each &lt;a href="https://x.com/NIHDirector_Jay/status/1932137914143473689"&gt;termination &lt;/a&gt;was being reviewed, and some workers were reinstated, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EVQEFDWQ35EIDDQOFKR5YMX6T4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But the Schlueters had a front-row seat to the effects of the job losses. Richard’s therapy was in a freezer, nearly ready to go. All along, they had been told the final step of preparation takes three to four weeks. But on June 3, his NIH doctor informed him that it would now take eight to 10 weeks because of cuts to essential lab personnel — a painful illustration of the life-and-death stakes of the administration’s approach to shrinking the government workforce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-topic-follow-interstitial" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RPVOBV2JOBD5VNPSBBX6GR7IPU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“I’m petrified. I have to do something,” Richard said. “My cancer is on the move.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="EUP7VJCV65ACZLUF5FR3PV5ZIU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The Washington Post &lt;a href="https://www.washingtonpost.com/science/2025/04/06/nih-firings-cancer-immunotherapy-treatment/"&gt;first reported in early April &lt;/a&gt;that the production of specialized immune-cell therapies for metastatic cancer patients was delayed. Two highly skilled technicians who prepared cells for treatments were fired in the probationary purge in February, according to Steven Rosenberg, an NIH immunotherapy pioneer who leads multiple trials. He declined to say how many patients were affected, but his team now treats one patient per week, down from two or three before the cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="OXRUKAHA5ZGJ7PYN7RQAAASQSY" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“There are some patients who might have to wait until September,” Rosenberg said. “These are all patients with metastatic cancer that is progressive. You can imagine the difficulty as we have to tell them these things.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4E5B7UQ63NANPFGSE5VSUPUXQQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;An official with the Department of Health and Human Services, which oversees NIH, said the agency had ways of addressing the delays. Rosenberg has been granted permission to hire contractors or to request help from other scientists from across NIH, said the official, who spoke on the condition of anonymity to criticize an employee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HXII36IIINENHJZSKDY75VKMNU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Rosenberg said he has been working urgently to try to rehire a scientist who was fired since he was given permission to do so last week, but the federal contracting process is slow and the scientist has been interviewing for other jobs. He noted that to prepare the cells for patients requires special training that takes four to six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="E67KUXIYENGAHLOK3TPTHTXDGI" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="E67KUXIYENGAHLOK3TPTHTXDGI" data-testid="article-header"&gt;National Institutes of Hope&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HKHVOVZ26NEC7HN34G4QCRN3IA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Richard’s cancer nightmare started with what he thought was acid reflux.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="R5K7C5KKVNBFLL63YKLDVAF2PE" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A few weeks after his annual physical in January 2024, he noticed a metallic taste in the back of his throat. Looking in the bathroom mirror, he saw little white pustules on one of his tonsils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="FDYCZPHSFREGFNL5CWW22NU6J4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;A scan and biopsy showed it was head and neck squamous cell carcinoma, but an oncologist told him it was treatable, with an excellent chance of success. Unless it spread.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VHKBXR7JRND2LNGOKY2MUKYCHQ" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;On Richard’s 55th birthday, March 11, 2024, he began chemotherapy and proton therapy. He had always taken good care of his health and was diligent with his treatments. But a scan in July revealed that the cancer had spread to his lungs and part of his chest cavity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="XMYT3XNVK5ESNOLX7TGJ6RQLXA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“It was heart-wrenching, and it was difficult,” said Richard, a founding partner of an Atlanta law firm. “I’m a fact-finder, and I spend a lot of time researching and trying to find a path to remission or a potential cure. And it’s a pretty bleak outlook.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="VI3NSCQUVRAVPCTQB5XW6327WI" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Richard’s efforts led him to NIH, where he felt blessed to qualify for a trial led by Rosenberg. Doctors would take a biopsy of his cancer and find and isolate immune cells called TIL, tumor-infiltrating lymphocytes. They would use lab tests to select the cells that recognized Richard’s cancer and expand the population. Then, they would reinfuse them into his body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DEIIPXFS4FBURITQ4NP3NUDDWA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;There are no guarantees with clinical research. Patients who qualify for the trial have exhausted standard treatments. But it gave the Schlueters something they had been missing: hope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="PJZNAAPJ3ZDGFJ4U7PNPC6EN6I" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“Patients often refer to us not as the National Institutes of Health, but the National Institutes of Hope,” Rosenberg said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="L5BMEE6L5RF5FK3H2E6IMSTE7E" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In January, Richard went to NIH for surgery to remove two tumors in his lungs and begin the process of isolating and testing the TIL cells. He read the NIH credo — to improve the human condition throughout the world — emblazoned on a wall of the Clinical Center and was so moved that he sent a photo of it to his three children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="RIWPPSJKSFEJPFELNWJJOJVF4Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“The staff, the physicians, the amount of empathy, care and mission that I’ve experienced over four visits to their research hospital has been just super gratifying,” Richard said. “In many ways, I’m a guinea pig that may be helping other people. But I also have the byproduct that if it works, it will help me.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="JRPTHP2UC5AWBICKW5EKBFO6ZU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In late March, Richard returned to NIH, thinking it was go time. Instead a scan showed that the tumors in his lungs had unexpectedly become smaller. He returned home, knowing his therapy would be ready in the freezer if he took a turn for the worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-header" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;h2 id="AYY3GMXTFNEETAECQH542YMJTY" class="wpds-c-XIGbK wpds-c-XIGbK-iivLrAs-css headingStyleOverrides" data-apitype="header" data-contentid="AYY3GMXTFNEETAECQH542YMJTY" data-testid="article-header"&gt;No time to wait&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CL5GHFFPOBDITFM4DTZVYZBLEM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Rosenberg’s team meets every Monday to discuss patient cases, and for months they have had to make difficult calls to seriously ill people. Richard is just one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="IDW3QXQ2WJE4DCBWC3U4TYDXOA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Natalie Phelps, a mother of two from Bainbridge Island, Washington, with metastatic colorectal cancer, is waiting for cells in another of Rosenberg’s trials. This one uses a different form of immunotherapy, but it is also slowed because of the loss of critical personnel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="GJ4HEBUAEJCMHFH5F7AWYOVQ5Y" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Last Friday, she gave&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;The Post an update: “So frustrating. I should be having treatment now, but instead I had to restart chemo and will be returning to start the treatment process” in late July.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="K4OWRVOAMRDRXBXQUQ2TIAQTJA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Two scientists on Rosenberg’s team who have specialized skills to prepare cells for immunotherapy trials&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;were among the thousands of probationary employees fired in the Trump administration’s push to shrink the federal workforce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="2OWTBYPZPFFHFLGNUXGIEYF3BM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;The one who would have finalized Richard’s infusion had worked at NIH since 2020 and was recently hired as a full-time employee because she was considered so effective, according to Rosenberg. But that made her vulnerable, as a probationary employee&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;with fewer protections. Rosenberg is trying to hire her back on contract using nongovernment funding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="HPL5Z4I4EFHF5KMMXJKRVY4EVA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Richard is an optimist. His biggest fear is not qualifying for the experimental immune cells that he hopes could beat back his cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="W2ABW4J42RFP7FVA53V6XBDLME" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Doing nothing isn’t an option because his cancer is spreading rapidly. Radiation might buy him time but leave his white blood cell count too low to be eligible for the trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="ILXHCW2YO5GRJK3MGIWLURKA7Q" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Robert L. Ferris, a head and neck surgical oncologist at the University of North Carolina Lineberger Comprehensive Cancer Center, said patients such as Richard have tough and tragic cases where standard medical care has been exhausted. Ferris is not involved in Richard’s care, but the doctor said the trajectory of a cancer like this is grim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="DZZTIZ45EJCHJD4JVVL5XT5NKM" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;It is unlikely the cell therapy will cure Richard, Ferris cautioned, but science progresses through individual cases like his. And if Richard is forced to wait too long, he could be too frail to try it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="Z62ZKI7O2VCOPI47ZKA2VPJUEA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“If the cells are ready, you would want to give it to him now,” Ferris said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="CWBUVPJXEVBK7JG3J4X47NG7AA" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;In mid-May, Richard was golfing with his nephew and his son. He was running, swimming, biking and lifting weights.&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;The only sign something was awry was a red rash on his face that resembled&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;a sunburn, a side effect of one of his treatments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="4GBCULZ23JDOPPAMCDWSIVYO6A" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;But as the cancer has spread through his bones, his arms have become weak, and he has a suspected microfracture in his right arm. Pain in a hip&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;makes it hard to get out of a chair. The Schlueters’ 30th wedding anniversary celebration in early June was a joyous occasion, but Richard struggled to walk down the aisle to renew their vows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="LV4AUS77SFDADK6XJSAU3HI4K4" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;Even if the therapy doesn’t save Richard, his family hopes his experience can help others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="wpds-c-PJLV article-body type-text" data-qa="article-body"&gt;&lt;p data-apitype="text" data-contentid="APLBWVV7C5HJ5CCOJEOFNQHFOU" data-el="text" class="wpds-c-heFNVF wpds-c-heFNVF-iPJLV-css overrideStyles font-copy" dir="null"&gt;“If he misses [it], not only is it is it devastating for his family, but it’s devastating for all the patients behind him that could have learned something scientifically — on why it was successful or not successful,” Michelle said. “He’s like a test pilot.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Washington Post</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:03:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijwFBVV95cUxOUHI5eVVzUEhBT21kVXNkaTR0SzNTeDZ6XzN6aVgtS3lBTHZZQXlhbmxsLW1fdFpTNkNVME5oODdNNEt1d0dsNFk0Vlp3ZFZBNVhSOEtLTWp3QkJPZXRRbXVJU1RtQnhUc3BBN1kwNWRydEFRdUxQZXpmYmp2LU5aNzZKb3FXcmJSWXNrLTlJWQ</guid></item><item><title>救命！我的前妻坚持要溺爱我们的女儿。它导致了可怕的后果。- Slate Magazine | Help! My Ex-Wife Insists on Coddling Our Daughter. It’s Led to Dire Consequences. - Slate Magazine</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijAFBVV95cUxPRmljd29kTy1mbEdvLUNQVlJBdEFnUDVzU2laRG5QV1pvejNvdk42RTI0ZmhfRlBvODJZU1JZay0tMXB1a1VZdGhLMTBUNUg1ODN3VFhhSTZqR1kwZXV1TFlYU0pRSy1zdWVvVUVOaExqMno4ZVNWTFVpMlctSXBGRm9MRGptZVRKaVAyUw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article__content" itemprop="mainEntityOfPage"&gt;
          &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="8" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfbqpn00cmsnksknspr90u@published"&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dear Prudence is Slate’s advice column. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSd_tjeEx47o2lIrDSg1Ioh_9shU0REmIAAtvoVHZj_FWz76AA/viewform"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Submit questions here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfi2pt002a3b771ljbak0p@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Prudence,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="111" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd5wc001f3b77k4j0x8ta@published"&gt;My ex is hurting our daughter with her coddling. Our daughter is nearly 9 and can’t swim, sleep by herself, ride a bike, or even pour herself a bowl of cereal. Her mother does all of it. She claims our daughter needs her to do all this, and she will magically be able to do it all when she gets older. My daughter used to be outgoing and adventurous, but now she is afraid of her own shadow and prone to meltdowns when you push her out of her comfort zone. I do my best to teach her and encourage her, but it is always one step forward and three back.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="173" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzjxrm900053b78xmpip83t@published"&gt;I have signed her up for lessons, and her mother refused to take her on her days. My ex had her remote position terminated and now has to go into the office. By some small miracle, I was able to get my daughter into a local day camp. It is barely the start of the summer, and we already have trouble. During my week, my daughter gets afraid and fussy, but ends up really enjoying the camp and making friends. When it is her mother’s turn, she has full meltdowns and needs to be picked up early. My ex says this is proof that the camp is “too much” for our daughter, and the solution should be that my wife watches her since she works remotely. My wife works on contract and is pregnant. She flatly said that my ex is out of bounds and she isn’t going to parent my daughter without me around. I feel like I am caught between a rock and a hard place. What do I do here?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="1" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd5y2001g3b777pe3u5q2@published"&gt;—Afraid&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd602001h3b77k2k3dlvw@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Afraid,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="127" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd61t001i3b77pw9l6od6@published"&gt;Let’s put this in perspective. You have decided not to push for full custody of your daughter despite your wife’s stance. You know that she is safe and healthy at your ex’s home. How great for you. Your kid is being coddled, but she’s not being abused, neglected, or scarred. She gets a lot of help and nurturing. Is she behind other kids her age when it comes to independence? It sure sounds like it. But luckily, there’s no plan to send her out in the world to fend for herself or be dropped into the ocean and have to swim to safety in the next few years, right? What’s your biggest fear about the consequences of the way she’s being parented right now? Is it rational?&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="91" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd64u001j3b77tbpojpdn@published"&gt;I also think you should explore the possibility that her regression and her emotional fragility may have something to do with her parents’ divorce, including whatever experiences led up to that, in addition to her mom’s parenting style. If I were in her position—a sensitive kid who’s been through a tough time and who is a bit younger for my age than my peers—what I’d want from my dad would be acceptance, patience, and encouragement, not the message that I was horribly flawed because of the way I was being raised.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="114" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzk3hx0000d3b78947athr8@published"&gt;So when she is with you (I can’t tell how often that is), please don’t give the impression that you’re alarmed by how terribly she’s doing or reveal that you think her mother is the worst. Offer her opportunities to experiment with more independence in low-pressure ways. Set her up to do small tasks on her own and celebrate when she succeeds. Create a fun room for her and see if she’s excited about sleeping on her own there. Look for any chance to tell her that you think she’s very smart and capable and that you trust her. If you must panic about her being behind on bike riding, do it in private.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmbzfi5zn002g3b77thq9aeue@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;div class="prudie-google-form" data-form-response-uri="https://docs.google.com/forms/u/0/d/e/1FAIpQLSd_tjeEx47o2lIrDSg1Ioh_9shU0REmIAAtvoVHZj_FWz76AA/formResponse" data-uri="slate.com/_components/prudie-google-form/instances/cmbzfibwo002s3b777gsj8y0i@published"&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="prudie-google-form__disclaimer"&gt;
      Please keep questions short (&amp;lt;150 words), and don‘t submit the same question to multiple columns. We are unable to edit or remove questions after publication. Use pseudonyms to maintain anonymity. Your submission may be used in other Slate advice columns and may be edited for publication.
    &lt;/p&gt;
    
    &lt;p class="slate-notification--success js-success-message" hidden&gt;Thanks! Your question has been submitted.&lt;/p&gt;
    
&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmbzfi9aa002m3b772atgbmji@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd68a001k3b7795csrite@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Prudence,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="84" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6a1001l3b77p9v5us4b@published"&gt;&lt;a href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/17175-lipedema"&gt;Lipedema&lt;/a&gt; runs through many of the women in my mom’s family. It’s painful, embarrassing, sometimes restricts physical movement, and treating symptoms is expensive. It’s not well understood, but doctors have told me my best chance of avoiding it is keeping a low BMI. So, I eat very carefully and maintain a strict exercise schedule, and keep my BMI at 19. Even during pregnancy, I was very careful (hormonal shifts like puberty, pregnancy, and menopause are potential triggers), and so far, I’ve dodged this bullet.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="170" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6bx001m3b77bcgfxd2w@published"&gt;My husband and I have a blended family. We have full custody of 10-year-old “Katherine,” but we also have a child together, 6-year-old “Delilah.” I consider them both my kids in every way that matters. I try to make sure that I don’t treat them differently and that I teach them the skills they need to be healthy. But as puberty approaches, I’m realizing that I have no idea how to talk about food and eating. With both kids, I’ve always talked about eating when we’re hungry and stopping when we’re full, and eating lots of different foods. They have treats, but we try to make that normal, too. I say this stuff, but my husband is the only one who actually sets a physical example because I need to keep my weight low. With Kathine, I’ve emphasized self-confidence with her changing body and encouraged her to recognize that body shape can do all kinds of things during puberty, and it’s all normal and OK, even if it feels scary.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="148" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6dv001n3b77i0ez2ks6@published"&gt;But I’m realizing I have no idea what to tell Delilah when she gets to this point, or how to dull the pain of the difference between her and her sister. I could take the same route with both kids, and open Delilah up to an unknown amount of health risk. Or I could encourage her to be careful with her weight at puberty, which also feels risky for different reasons. My husband wants to just pretend it’s never going to be a problem, and I have no idea where or how to get advice. Lipedema isn’t researched much in the U.S., and her pediatrician told me it was “just obesity by another name” when I asked for guidance. But I’ve seen my mom and sister both have so much pain and distress from it, and I don’t want that for my kid. Where can I get help?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6fq001o3b776gvat7la@published"&gt;—Stressed Mama&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="3" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6hh001p3b77xbyidab6@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Stressed Mama,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="158" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6ja001q3b77oxatgmvh@published"&gt;If only maintaining a low BMI were as easy as being told by your mom, “Be careful with your weight!” and replying with, “OK!” If that were the case, people of all ages wouldn’t be at war with their bodies, and there wouldn’t be a multimillion dollar diet and fitness industry designed to help people, who, despite their best intentions, can’t crack the code of eating and working out in a way that leads to the body size they so badly want. I really want to question the assumption that informing her about the need to keep her weight low would actually lead to her doing so. Beyond that, I worry that putting the idea of restriction into Delilah’s head might backfire and lead to her experiencing shame, or feeling rebellious, and developing an unhealthy relationship with food. (I recently &lt;a href="https://slate.com/advice/2025/06/advice-family-body-image-comments-food.html"&gt;spoke to a few experts who went into detail&lt;/a&gt; about how dangerous these body image issues can be.)&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="100" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6l9001r3b7760wqcsn4@published"&gt;I appreciate what you’re doing by trying to give both girls healthy messages about food. But I think you should pull back on hitting them over the head with, “Treats are OK! Try to feel confident in your changing body! It’s normal!” Kids pay more attention to what you do than what you say. You don’t have to &lt;em&gt;do &lt;/em&gt;any particular kind of eating to be a good example. But you could show through your actions that there are more interesting things to focus on than how much healthy or unhealthy food you’ve had, or what your body looks like.&lt;/p&gt;

  
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="136" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6n6001s3b77usgrhbi9@published"&gt;When it comes to giving direct instructions to Delilah, you could choose a topic like the importance of finding a doctor whom she trusts, refusing to accept being dismissed or having her symptoms minimized, and staying aware that not every medical professional will be well informed about the latest research or thinking surrounding specific conditions. I’m seeing that there are conferences and associations dedicated to sharing information about living with and treating lipedema. Maybe you could invite her to join you, in an age-appropriate way, as you tap into these resources. “You deserve excellent health care from someone who listens to you, and we’re going to stay up to date on the latest research on this condition” is a better message than “Make sure you don’t gain too much weight or you may develop this condition.”&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="169" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6pr001t3b77dovdause@published"&gt;The other thing that could benefit Delilah is your transparency about the dilemma in your letter. I’m thinking of something like, “I’ve been stressing about telling you how I’ve been advised to keep this condition at bay by maintaining a low BMI without giving you a complex. I want both you and your sister to have a relaxed, pleasant relationship with food and your bodies. How do you think I’ve been doing when it comes to not promoting weird messages about weight? Please let me know.” This could create some distance from the topic and could make her think, “This is exactly what my mom wanted to avoid,” if she notices herself slipping into restrictive habits. It also communicates your actual values: “I want you to be OK in terms of avoiding this debilitating condition, but I also want you to be OK when it comes to your everyday feelings about food and your body.” She can join you on the journey to figure out how to do that.&lt;/p&gt;

  


  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmbzfdgdo00243b77etx3znhu@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmbzfj8po003z3b77tg3dz10e@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Prudie Wants to Hear From You!&lt;/strong&gt;

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="52" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfipzu00353b77sljpl334@published"&gt;Readers often have great suggestions for our letter writers, occasionally disagree with a point Prudie makes, or simply want to provide some additional advice. Each week, Prudie will be replying to some of these comments and suggestions from readers, which will be featured on the site on Fridays for &lt;a href="https://slate.com/plus"&gt;Slate Plus&lt;/a&gt; members. &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScTGiymkIhYcgYSz154NhdwZPeKzITVxCLjxJLB7tTwesqzeA/viewform?usp=sf_link"&gt;Write to us!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-section-div/instances/cmbzfinag002z3b77wneg0asv@published" class="section-div"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="2" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6s7001u3b77onwhy12o@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Prudence,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="196" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6u7001v3b77g5ymjexg@published"&gt;My daughter “Mandy” is married to a less-than-worthless man. A few weeks ago, she came to me in tears because she discovered he had spent nearly $1,000 on adult entertainment, leaving them with no money to buy groceries or diapers for the baby, and neither of them was getting paid for two weeks. I purchased what she needed and dropped it off instead of giving her the money to make sure he wouldn’t wouldn’t blow it on more porn. This is not the first time Mandy has come to me in desperation because he’s wasted their money on getting himself off. Unfortunately, she also has two kids with him, both under the age of 4. Trying to convince her to leave him on previous occasions has gone nowhere, but I am hoping this will be a wake-up call for her. Her mother and I talked it over, and we would be prepared to let her and the kids live with us for as long as she needs to if she tells the lout to piss off once and for all. Would making this offer to her be a good idea so she can rebuild her life?&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="7" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6vy001w3b77vdijkbz8@published"&gt;—Time to Leave Him in the Gutter&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="6" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6xp001x3b77lemg03g7@published"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Leave Him in the Gutter,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  


  


  


  


  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="32" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd6zh001y3b77rbyg35pf@published"&gt;Absolutely! Make sure to include “No pressure at all” and “We don’t have to talk about this again if you don’t want to, but we love you and the offer never expires.”&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="31" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfd71d001z3b777wjyh158@published"&gt;The more difficult part will be making an agreement with your wife about what you’ll both do if you find out she’s seeing him again while she’s living under your &lt;span class="slate-paragraph--tombstone"&gt;roof.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;h3 class="subhead subhead--none" data-uri="slate.com/_components/subhead/instances/cmbzfjrj8004h3b77dsoo40lz@published"&gt;
&lt;p class="subhead__marker"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
Classic Prudie

&lt;/h3&gt;

  &lt;p class="slate-paragraph slate-graf" data-word-count="70" data-uri="slate.com/_components/slate-paragraph/instances/cmbzfjp4h004b3b77jh923frf@published"&gt;When I was 15, my world exploded. My father had been having a years-long affair with my personal coach. In fact, the entire reason why he pushed me into the sport was to cover up the affair. It devastated my mother and showered me with crippling doubt about my own ability and self-worth. &lt;a href="https://slate.com/human-interest/2023/01/coach-affair-dear-prudence-advice.html"&gt;My coach talked about me being Olympic material and nearly all my free time went into training…&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;section class="newsletter-signup  " data-list="Dear Prudence" data-uri="slate.com/_components/newsletter-signup/instances/cmbzfbqpn00cpsnks7ecscm1g@published"&gt;


    &lt;p class="newsletter-signup__intro"&gt;
        &lt;svg class="newsletter-signup__arrow"&gt;
          &lt;use xlink:href="/media/components/newsletter-signup/sprite.svg#arrow"&gt;&lt;/use&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
&lt;h1 class="newsletter-signup__headline"&gt;Don't miss what's new from Prudie&lt;/h1&gt;
      &lt;span class="newsletter-signup__description"&gt;Get advice on manners and morals in your inbox three times a week.&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/p&gt;
    



&lt;/section&gt;

  

&lt;/div&gt;

      &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Slate Magazine</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijAFBVV95cUxPRmljd29kTy1mbEdvLUNQVlJBdEFnUDVzU2laRG5QV1pvejNvdk42RTI0ZmhfRlBvODJZU1JZay0tMXB1a1VZdGhLMTBUNUg1ODN3VFhhSTZqR1kwZXV1TFlYU0pRSy1zdWVvVUVOaExqMno4ZVNWTFVpMlctSXBGRm9MRGptZVRKaVAyUw</guid></item><item><title>诊断困境：一位女士在接受透析时开始从椅子上吃泡沫- Live Science | Diagnostic dilemma: A woman started eating foam from her chair while receiving dialysis - Live Science</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivgFBVV95cUxQUkl4LU9fU1NjVG84VkVWZlpWQUo1SXkxZW9MR3l5a2NiV0cxc0MwajJaUWdMbGRWZGtyaGpKd1M3Zl8yWlNXdnB4RDAxV2puMWl2R1kyU0l2SF9CR2xPcHN3Q0NpckJINkxqMnFjNUU3V1h5aDE4QUJDRER5SHo3UlFSMGtiNWJEaXU2ZFJmdlp5ckFlMTd5WkpHV3liOE1xQlhFZFQzeTBveW5nalhDRjJBaFBLbDJwNmxqb0RB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div id="article-body" class="text-copy bodyCopy auto"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The patient: &lt;/strong&gt;A 31-year-old woman in the U.K.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-1" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The symptoms: &lt;/strong&gt;The patient had a history of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.livescience.com/34803-type-1-diabetes-symptoms-treatment-diagnosis.html" data-before-rewrite-localise="https://www.livescience.com/34803-type-1-diabetes-symptoms-treatment-diagnosis.html"&gt;&lt;u&gt;type 1 diabetes&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, mild learning difficulties and end-stage kidney failure. For the last condition, she was receiving &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/treatments/14618-dialysis" target="_blank" data-url="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/treatments/14618-dialysis" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;dialysis&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; three times a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This treatment fills in for the kidneys by clearing waste and excess fluid from the bloodstream, and patients are advised to restrict their fluid and salt intake between sessions. If they don't, fluid can build up in the body because the kidneys aren't filtering it out of the blood, leading to weight gain and strain on the heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this case, the woman consistently experienced this excessive fluid buildup between appointments, "despite several interventions" aimed at helping her manage it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ad-unit-2" class="ad-unit"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happened next: &lt;/strong&gt;Over time, the patient could no longer tolerate long dialysis sessions, so she would start and end each session above her target weight due to all the fluid buildup. She also reported experiencing occasional constipation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After one dialysis session, a nurse cleaning the chair the woman had been sitting in noted that it felt "rather light." Upon inspection, she noted large chunks of foam — specifically low-density polyurethane foam — were missing from the chair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The diagnosis:&lt;/strong&gt; The woman's medical team discovered this was a case of &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/22944-pica" target="_blank" data-url="https://my.clevelandclinic.org/health/diseases/22944-pica" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;pica&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, in which people develop a habit or compulsion to eat non-food items.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-zNcqUdZVwMvEZ5XXrNxua8" class="slice-container newsletter-inbodyContent-slice newsletterForm-articleInbodyContent-zNcqUdZVwMvEZ5XXrNxua8 slice-container-newsletterForm"&gt;&lt;div data-hydrate="true" class="newsletter-form__wrapper newsletter-form__wrapper--inbodyContent"&gt;&lt;div class="newsletter-form__container"&gt;&lt;section class="newsletter-form__main-section"&gt;&lt;p class="newsletter-form__strapline"&gt;Get the world’s most fascinating discoveries delivered straight to your inbox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;"We were surprised to discover that our patient had been eating the foam and had increased her fluid intake with the assumption that it would absorb excess water in the stomach and thus prevent systemic absorption," her doctors &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3028043/" target="_blank" data-url="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC3028043/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;wrote in a report&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. "This was evidently not the case." In other words, she hoped the foam would act like a sponge and soak up the excess fluid she was retaining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pica is sometimes &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK532242/" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/books/NBK532242/" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;associated with nutrient deficiencies&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, such as a lack of iron or zinc, leading some scientists to theorize that these deficiencies lead to unusual cravings. Alternatively, some think that people with pica may be drawn to the sensations — the tastes, textures or smells — of non-food substances. The condition is sometimes associated with pregnancy or sickle cell anemia, as well as certain mental health disorders and medications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this case, the woman’s doctors ran tests and ruled out nutritional deficiencies as a factor. They also didn't uncover any "acute psychosocial triggers for her behaviour," and she had no past history of pica. They suspected that her known learning difficulties may have played a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The treatment: &lt;/strong&gt;The patient was advised about the consequences of eating foam and received regular guidance from a dietitian with a speciality in helping patients with kidney dysfunction. Her family also became more closely involved in her treatment. Other cases of pica are typically treated with behavioral therapies, but the case report didn't note whether any such options were explored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She additionally received a laxative treatment to help her pass the foam she'd already eaten without any complications. At the time the case report was published in 2010, she was continuing to undergo dialysis three times a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What makes the case unique: &lt;/strong&gt;Cases of pica have &lt;a data-analytics-id="inline-link" href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1051227699900171" target="_blank" data-url="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S1051227699900171" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" data-hl-processed="none"&gt;&lt;u&gt;been reported among kidney disease patients&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in the past, but they typically involve patients craving and eating clay, dirt, aspirin, flour, baking soda or ice. The effects can range from benign to severe; in the latter case, a person may experience toxic effects, dental problems, bowel obstruction or malnutrition, for example.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The woman's doctors searched the medical literature for cases of kidney disease patients eating polyurethane foam and didn't find any, but they did find a few cases of people without renal disease eating the material.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;"This case highlights a recognised but under-diagnosed phenomenon in renal patients, known as pica," the doctors wrote. "While the ingestion of ice, aspirin, clay and baking soda has been reported in haemodialysis patients, this case is unique in that the patient resorted to eating foam from her dialysis chair."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div id="slice-container-freeText-zNcqUdZVwMvEZ5XXrNxua8-lBpljchRsevC1R8jMWh6LK3IimgVePQB" class="slice-container freeText-wrapper freeText-zNcqUdZVwMvEZ5XXrNxua8-lBpljchRsevC1R8jMWh6LK3IimgVePQB slice-container-freeText"&gt;&lt;div class="info-block"&gt;&lt;p class="infoDisclaimer"&gt;This article is for informational purposes only and is not meant to offer medical advice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxQUkl4LU9fU1NjVG84VkVWZlpWQUo1SXkxZW9MR3l5a2NiV0cxc0MwajJaUWdMbGRWZGtyaGpKd1M3Zl8yWlNXdnB4RDAxV2puMWl2R1kyU0l2SF9CR2xPcHN3Q0NpckJINkxqMnFjNUU3V1h5aDE4QUJDRER5SHo3UlFSMGtiNWJEaXU2ZFJmdlp5ckFlMTd5WkpHV3liOE1xQlhFZFQzeTBveW5nalhDRjJBaFBLbDJwNmxqb0RB</guid></item><item><title>随着神秘毒素入侵美国，生活在美国海岸的数千万人面临过早死亡-每日邮报 | Tens of millions living on US coast face early death as mysterious toxin invades the nation - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirAFBVV95cUxPR0hCdFpvbG9Kb0x4LXpFLWZtblhqOFBjdldYVnpCcmwzRkp4ZDl0ajE1TmdtY2psYkQxRXFJSXBwbEdLTnc1TmpYYi1uWC1BWUtVeTZ3R3gyR2RNTXVNRkFsQmgwdHNPY1RxWWN2RmdxTzVpeFFLTW9ESGw3MWtiR1RHdmMzYVFDNkRtVzBzdUFWMHFxWUdhQkNhWEpyZ19VZ3VrUDJDQnpjS1830gGyAUFVX3lxTE5GVTBxWTBrcWJoMmYtX08tYTlSbE9XQzRablMxdG9oRk5hQ3BqbWZFZXc2UjFhck81UGdjNjBhTnEyWlh2YmlQY3J1aExiLWlvN3FlRG9CZkNXTXBMRzlPU3I0VEV4QU9BOXRIc0JrWU5CRlBuNXRzRHFhM1c3VVdHYWxxNFE5RlJaTXBKWlU1dk9UZHV4UnRObEJ5UVpKUWFwaGZ2eDA3SHdnTWVkY0ltNUE?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Living along America's coastal waters could be putting millions of people at risk for an early death from &lt;a target="_self" href="/health/diabetes/index.html" id="mol-63ad76a0-4bbd-11f0-8f7b-13970b7cd649" class=""&gt;diabetes&lt;/a&gt;, heart disease, or a stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A new study by the American Heart Association warned that microplastics, tiny particles found to be invading every environment and organism on Earth, are causing more serious health issues for people &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-14398769/healthy-foods-microplastics-easy-swaps-avoid.html"&gt;living near the oceans&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers revealed that coastal counties heavily polluted with microplastics had 18 percent more residents with Type 2 diabetes, seven percent more cases of coronary artery disease, and nine percent more strokes than counties with low pollution levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Counties along the Gulf Coast and East Coast had higher disease rates than those along the West Coast, specifically in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/california/index.html" id="mol-63b27fb0-4bbd-11f0-8f7b-13970b7cd649" class=""&gt;California&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/oregon/index.html" id="mol-63b40650-4bbd-11f0-8f7b-13970b7cd649" class=""&gt;Oregon&lt;/a&gt;, and Washington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Sarju Ganatra from Lahey Hospital &amp;amp; Medical Center in &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/massachusetts/index.html" id="mol-63b39120-4bbd-11f0-8f7b-13970b7cd649" class=""&gt;Massachusetts&lt;/a&gt; said: 'Plastic pollution is not just an environmental issue – it may also be a public health issue.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Microplastics include all plastic particles less than five millimeters in size, which is the width of a pencil eraser or smaller.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Particles smaller than the human eye come from decomposing plastic waste like bottles, synthetic clothes, personal care products, and countless other manufactured goods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Scientists believe microplastics from polluted oceans make their way into drinking water, seafood, and even the air, eventually consumed by people, which they theorize can increase harmful levels of inflammation and cause numerous diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Researchers have found higher rates of coronary artery disease along America's coastal counties with the highest levels of plastic pollution in the ocean&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Nearly 100 million people live along the US coastlines, which include heavily polluted waters in the Atlantic and Pacific Oceans and the Gulf of America&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are more than 250 coastal counties along the US mainland, which are home to over 94 million people, according to the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;To conduct their study, Ganatra and his team examined 152 US coastal counties along the Pacific Ocean, Atlantic Ocean, and Gulf of America (formerly the Gulf of Mexico).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They collected data on microplastic levels in ocean waters within 200 nautical miles of these counties between 2015 and 2020, using information from the National Centers for Environmental Information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers sorted the counties into four groups based on the amount of microplastics in the water: low (almost no plastics), medium (up to one small particle per 200 bathtubs of water), high (a handful of particles per bathtub), and very high (10 or more particles per bathtub).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Even in health care – a field devoted to healing – we rely heavily on single-use plastics. Much of it ends up in landfills or the ocean, where it fragments into microplastics and enters the ecosystem,' Ganatra explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team then used health data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), gathered between 2015 and 2020, to look up the rates of Type 2 diabetes, coronary artery disease (plaque buildup in the arteries), and stroke in these counties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They adjusted for factors like age, gender, income, access to doctors, air pollution, and neighborhood conditions, ensuring the results weren't skewed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The results showed a clear pattern: counties with very high microplastic pollution in nearby ocean waters had significantly higher rates of health problems that have been linked to an early death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A study in &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://www.thelancet.com/journals/landia/article/PIIS2213-8587(23)00223-1/fulltext"&gt;The Lancet&lt;/a&gt; has shown that a Type 2 diabetes diagnosis can significantly reduce someone's life expectancy, shaving off more than a decade for people who develop the disease in their 30s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The rate of stroke incidents was 9 percent higher in US coastal counties with heavily polluted ocean waters&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Microplastics are plastic fragments less than 5 millimeters in size, while nanoplastics are even smaller, less than 100 nanometers - less than the size of a human hair. Both have been linked to cancer, cardiovascular disease, cognitive issues, and reproductive problems&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;According to the World Health Organization, stroke survivors may die between five and 10 years earlier than the average person who never had a stroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Meanwhile, &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://academic.oup.com/eurjpc/article/26/2_suppl/25/5925419"&gt;researchers in Europe&lt;/a&gt; have found that coronary artery disease is linked to a significant drop in life expectancy, with middle-aged adults losing five to eight years of life due to their higher risk for heart attacks and sudden cardiac death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The study in the &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://newsroom.heart.org/news/living-near-an-ocean-polluted-by-microplastics-may-increase-cardiometabolic-disease-risk?preview=4be0&amp;amp;preview_mode=True"&gt;Journal of the American Heart Association&lt;/a&gt; has its limitations. It only looked at county-level data, not individual people, so it can't prove that microplastics directly cause these health issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;It also didn't measure microplastics in people's bodies or pinpoint exactly how they enter the body, whether through water, food, or the air.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, the study focused on ocean water pollution, not other sources like fish or plants, which come from the sea and have been shown to be &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/sciencetech/article-14239717/The-10-foods-high-cancer-causing-microplastics-easy-swaps-avoid-them.html"&gt;full of plastic particles as well&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Despite the drawbacks, Ganatra contended that the results show a clear connection between the world's growing plastic crisis and rising rates of poor health and early death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'This study adds to a growing body of evidence that the garbage we discard into the environment often finds its way back to us,' the study's senior author said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Previous research has also linked microplastic contamination in the human body to conditions like dementia, infertility, eczema, premature aging, and obesity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Additionally, previous studies in mice have linked nanoplastics (plastic particles that are even smaller than microplastics) in the brain to cognitive changes, Parkinson's disease, and some types of dementia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
            

            
            
            
            
            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 09:00:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirAFBVV95cUxPR0hCdFpvbG9Kb0x4LXpFLWZtblhqOFBjdldYVnpCcmwzRkp4ZDl0ajE1TmdtY2psYkQxRXFJSXBwbEdLTnc1TmpYYi1uWC1BWUtVeTZ3R3gyR2RNTXVNRkFsQmgwdHNPY1RxWWN2RmdxTzVpeFFLTW9ESGw3MWtiR1RHdmMzYVFDNkRtVzBzdUFWMHFxWUdhQkNhWEpyZ19VZ3VrUDJDQnpjS1830gGyAUFVX3lxTE5GVTBxWTBrcWJoMmYtX08tYTlSbE9XQzRablMxdG9oRk5hQ3BqbWZFZXc2UjFhck81UGdjNjBhTnEyWlh2YmlQY3J1aExiLWlvN3FlRG9CZkNXTXBMRzlPU3I0VEV4QU9BOXRIc0JrWU5CRlBuNXRzRHFhM1c3VVdHYWxxNFE5RlJaTXBKWlU1dk9UZHV4UnRObEJ5UVpKUWFwaGZ2eDA3SHdnTWVkY0ltNUE</guid></item><item><title>这个简单的力量测试可以揭示您是否患有阿尔茨海默氏症和心脏病的风险- SciTechDaily | This Simple Strength Test Could Reveal if You’re at Risk for Alzheimer’s and Heart Disease - SciTechDaily</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMitAFBVV95cUxOTmw2UDdQVmtKdFMxN05ZTmRsLXRORFNUU2JLRkNULVJMY0tOVHZTT2VEenQ0bTluRWxuaHRrU2Nja2x5WExGQXFxbWpBWTNjM3ZzeTd0UmlxZjdKRVh0bFItQkM2RkFERGFndFhzR0VjLVV3TmFXX2tfaWJrdjlmSHFPTWdKNmtVZ180aVdHYjhnZU9xYklVTWNFSGhHRmk4SE15cUZqMDh6eXVkblp6TER4dWw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="main-content"&gt;&lt;noscript&gt;&lt;p class="h2"&gt;&lt;span id="challenge-error-text"&gt;Enable JavaScript and cookies to continue&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/noscript&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>SciTechDaily</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 08:18:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMitAFBVV95cUxOTmw2UDdQVmtKdFMxN05ZTmRsLXRORFNUU2JLRkNULVJMY0tOVHZTT2VEenQ0bTluRWxuaHRrU2Nja2x5WExGQXFxbWpBWTNjM3ZzeTd0UmlxZjdKRVh0bFItQkM2RkFERGFndFhzR0VjLVV3TmFXX2tfaWJrdjlmSHFPTWdKNmtVZ180aVdHYjhnZU9xYklVTWNFSGhHRmk4SE15cUZqMDh6eXVkblp6TER4dWw</guid></item><item><title>如何训练你的大脑变得更和平： 10个小习惯-印度时报 | How to train your brain to be more peaceful: 10 tiny habits - Times of India</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMi7gFBVV95cUxOdFg0NDJ3MUxxcjdtRjB3TDR6eS1WWFlyVFpuWUdWUmt6TlhENmhMOHFObFFZbENfR21Ca25KV2hmc2l6SGhURXdUS2RGeXdwN2puNjg4NjRaa0V6WWE4MU5lTXMtTXYteE45cF9HM25kUFoxM3RUWWpLdDlGQjFVRURnMHRvZ3JuSy1yYmh6N0RSUVlSN2R6MXVOQlZGbjdYSmJ0bjV4bXFyLXJma0ZYeExEQkd5VGtnU3BIWkhHYXY2NGZmeUxOTUdWUEhNcFpaTFhGSHhKVGRjc1FnZ21NMnNzMFlBalYtMDI4RW5n?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;amp-story-grid-layer class="recircular" id="rcontent" template="vertical"&gt;&lt;div class="letterbox"&gt;&lt;p class="mid-heading"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;You may also like&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc3 pa"&gt;8 aquarium fish that are surprisingly su...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="rc5 pa"&gt;Top 10 'Hypoallergenic' pet dog breeds t...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/amp-story-grid-layer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Times of India</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 06:15:59 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMi7gFBVV95cUxOdFg0NDJ3MUxxcjdtRjB3TDR6eS1WWFlyVFpuWUdWUmt6TlhENmhMOHFObFFZbENfR21Ca25KV2hmc2l6SGhURXdUS2RGeXdwN2puNjg4NjRaa0V6WWE4MU5lTXMtTXYteE45cF9HM25kUFoxM3RUWWpLdDlGQjFVRURnMHRvZ3JuSy1yYmh6N0RSUVlSN2R6MXVOQlZGbjdYSmJ0bjV4bXFyLXJma0ZYeExEQkd5VGtnU3BIWkhHYXY2NGZmeUxOTUdWUEhNcFpaTFhGSHhKVGRjc1FnZ21NMnNzMFlBalYtMDI4RW5n</guid></item><item><title>研究发现，粪便移植对某些人来说存在一定的风险- ScienceAlert | Fecal Transplants Present a Concerning Risk For Some, Study Finds - ScienceAlert</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxPekItTFJvRFZjdi1hSXg4SmxQRkRWNEpPa3pveU5lSHlQNVVGVFJheFdoYVR4V0lRODJrVWgwclJ6QWdOV3ZlN1RydXJyUWNYN2hOVjI3el9RVk1haGhZa3FNb3dSSWNPY19zZHk0S1c4VDB3RkxfejhnUHQzTmlFTnRPakJKX1I4d2tfOVRDQWk1MVdscGxrUA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="post-content"&gt;
			&lt;p&gt;Keeping a healthy mix of friendly microbes in the gut – known as &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/26922981/"&gt;eubiosis&lt;/a&gt; – is crucial for good health. When that delicate balance is thrown off – often by antibiotics, diet or illness – the result can be a range of issues, from digestive problems to more serious conditions like &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8320851/"&gt;Crohn's disease&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC5757125/"&gt;ulcerative colitis&lt;/a&gt;, and even &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10045203/"&gt;neurological&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/36270676/"&gt;metabolic&lt;/a&gt; disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One increasingly popular way to try to restore gut health is through &lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0929664618305552"&gt;faecal microbiota transplantation&lt;/a&gt;. This involves taking stool from a healthy person, isolating the beneficial microbes and putting them in a capsule (jokingly referred to as "crapsules" or &lt;a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/newsround/articles/cpd4wv03gxjo"&gt;"poo pills"&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hope is that the beneficial microbes in the pill will establish themselves in the patient's gut, thereby improving microbial diversity and function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Faecal transplants have been used to treat a wide array of conditions, including &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC8192290/"&gt;irritable bowel syndrome&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC10019775/"&gt;Parkinson's disease&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6835402/"&gt;obesity&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6979041/#:%7E:text=FMT%20Improved%20Insulin%20Resistance%20and,after%208%20weeks%20of%20treatment."&gt;Type 2 diabetes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_165029" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-165029" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/irritable_bowel_642.jpg" alt="woman clenching stomach" class="wp-image-165029 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/irritable_bowel_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/irritable_bowel_642-444x415.jpg 444w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/irritable_bowel_642-600x561.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-165029" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Faecal transplants have been used to treat irritable bowel syndrom. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAEV5-0kI3Y/"&gt;kanchanachitkhamma/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although generally viewed as safe and effective, a &lt;a href="https://www.cell.com/cell/abstract/S0092-8674(25)00564-1?_returnURL=https%3A%2F%2Flinkinghub.elsevier.com%2Fretrieve%2Fpii%2FS0092867425005641%3Fshowall%3Dtrue"&gt;new international study&lt;/a&gt; published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Cell&lt;/em&gt; has raised some concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scientists found that when the donor's microbes do not properly match the recipient's gut environment – a situation they describe as a "mismatch" – the treatment can disrupt the body's metabolic and immune systems, possibly with long-lasting consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term "mismatch" comes from the world of organ transplants, where the recipient's body rejects the donor organ. In this case, the problem is that microbes from the donor's large intestine may not be suitable for other parts of the recipient's gut, especially the small intestine, where the microbial makeup is very different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To test this, researchers gave antibiotics to mice to disturb their natural gut microbes, then treated them with faecal transplants. They also tried transplanting microbes specifically from different parts of the small intestine. The mice were monitored for one to three months to track changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Wrong microbes in the wrong place&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;They found that faecal transplants often led to regional mismatches – the wrong microbes ending up in the wrong place. This altered the mix and behaviour of the gut microbes in unexpected ways, disrupting energy balance and other functions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="attachment_165027" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-165027" class="wp-caption alignnone"&gt;&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/microbes_in_gut_642.jpg" alt="illustration of microbes in gut" class="wp-image-165027 size-full" srcset="https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/microbes_in_gut_642.jpg 642w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/microbes_in_gut_642-444x415.jpg 444w, https://www.sciencealert.com/images/2025/06/microbes_in_gut_642-600x561.jpg 600w" sizes="(max-width: 642px) 100vw, 642px" loading="lazy"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-165027" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;Microbes may not always be at home in different gut environments. (&lt;a href="https://www.canva.com/photos/MAFHCzxhVCs/"&gt;Troyan Alexandra from troyanphotos/Canva&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Biopsies from the gut and liver showed significant, lasting changes in how certain genes – particularly those linked to metabolism and immunity – were being expressed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study did not specify exactly what kind of health issues might result from these genetic shifts. But the researchers are urging doctors to take greater care when using faecal transplants, particularly when it comes to dose, timing and possible side-effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There may, however, be a better way forward. A newer method known as the &lt;a href="https://www.the-microbiologist.com/news/fecal-transplants-promising-treatment-or-potential-health-risk/6012.article#:%7E:text=%E2%80%99Omni%2Dmicrobial%E2%80%99%20approach,metabolomics%20to%20track%20their%20activity."&gt;"omni microbial approach"&lt;/a&gt; involves transferring microbes from all parts of the intestine, not just the colon. This could help recreate a more balanced and natural gut environment, avoiding the local mismatches seen in standard faecal transplants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is also growing interest in techniques that aim to "terraform" the gut: deliberately reshaping specific regions with carefully selected microbes to restore normal function.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This new research has certainly sparked debate around the safety of faecal transplants. But with alternative approaches already being developed, there is real hope that the benefits of gut-based treatments can still be delivered, without the risks.&lt;img decoding="async" src="https://counter.theconversation.com/content/258643/count.gif?distributor=republish-lightbox-basic" alt="The Conversation" referrerpolicy="no-referrer-when-downgrade" loading="lazy"&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/profiles/georgios-efthimiou-718157"&gt;Georgios Efthimiou&lt;/a&gt;, Lecturer in Microbiology, &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/institutions/university-of-hull-1191"&gt;University of Hull&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This article is republished from &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com"&gt;The Conversation&lt;/a&gt; under a Creative Commons license. Read the &lt;a href="https://theconversation.com/could-faecal-transplants-cause-long-term-health-problems-258643"&gt;original article&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>ScienceAlert</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 03:27:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPekItTFJvRFZjdi1hSXg4SmxQRkRWNEpPa3pveU5lSHlQNVVGVFJheFdoYVR4V0lRODJrVWgwclJ6QWdOV3ZlN1RydXJyUWNYN2hOVjI3el9RVk1haGhZa3FNb3dSSWNPY19zZHk0S1c4VDB3RkxfejhnUHQzTmlFTnRPakJKX1I4d2tfOVRDQWk1MVdscGxrUA</guid></item><item><title>休斯顿整形外科医生认为，在急剧减肥后寻求该手术的患者激增30 ％ - KHOU | Houston plastic surgeon sees 30% surge in patients seeking this procedure after dramatic weight loss - KHOU</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixgFBVV95cUxOVjdiRlEtRVcwblhpRnhRUUlYaVFZb1pxcE1UcUZKbjJlTTROX3prR3Fkbmd6UmQtOWsyRnlTSWNhc282d081a3EzbWhkaUh4T3BmeVZibGo5aWtWckpRVmFOclFLc0F5djBidXhjUGJLN1haN2FFNUhKN1RuSGU1dzZ2TERIYnFDNVFtdnk2VVlKRktmeFE3R25ONEtxNDRuamxqYll6N3daSlB0Q2VtdHE4OGdaY3JKXy0tTk83MkZ3VWp1TGc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;p class="article__summary"&gt;Increased use of GLP-1 drugs for weight loss has led to a rise in body lift surgeries to remove excess skin.&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;div class="article__body"&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HOUSTON — The increasing use of &lt;a href="/health" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"&gt;GLP-1 medications for weight loss&lt;/a&gt; has triggered a corresponding surge in body lift surgeries, as patients seek solutions for excess skin following dramatic weight reduction. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;According to a recent &lt;a href="https://www.kff.org/health-costs/poll-finding/kff-health-tracking-poll-may-2024-the-publics-use-and-views-of-glp-1-drugs/" target="_blank"&gt;Kaiser Family Foundation survey&lt;/a&gt;, approximately 6% of American adults are currently taking GLP-1 weight loss drugs like Ozempic. It was FDA-approved in 2021 for weight loss. While these medications help patients shed significant pounds, many are left with unwanted excess skin that creates both cosmetic and health challenges.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                        
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Social media influencer &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/takingmylifebackat42/" target="_blank"&gt;Tonya Spanglo&lt;/a&gt;, who lost 250 pounds, exemplifies this journey. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I was 430 pounds, and I did not stay on the scale long enough to see it go up anymore," Spanglo said about her weight before beginning her transformation.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Spanglo shared that food became her escape mechanism early in life. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"He was an alcoholic, and he was an abuser," she revealed about her father, explaining the roots of her complicated relationship with food.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like many others struggling with obesity, Spanglo tried numerous weight loss methods. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I bought Fen-Phen on the black market," she admitted. "I would lose 40 and gain back 50. I always gained back more than I lost."&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2019, Spanglo underwent &lt;a href="https://www.mayoclinic.org/tests-procedures/gastric-sleeve-surgery/about/pac-20384755" target="_blank"&gt;gastric sleeve surgery&lt;/a&gt; to reduce her stomach size. She had to lose significant weight to prove she could change her lifestyle and qualify for insurance coverage. On the day of surgery, she was 299 pounds. After that, she lost another 100 pounds but eventually regained about 40 pounds. That's when she turned to GLP-1 injections. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I started doing Ozempic, which lots of people that have had weight loss surgery, they do a GLP-1," she said.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The dramatic weight loss left Spanglo with significant excess skin that caused physical problems beyond appearance. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"The rashes you get, the infections that you get, I would have to put a towel in between my stomach and my body because of the sweat, the smell," she described.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To address these issues, Spanglo consulted Houston plastic surgeon &lt;a href="https://drrukminirednam.com/" target="_blank"&gt;Dr. Rukmini Rednam&lt;/a&gt; for a body lift.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"It's the tummy tuck that goes all the way around," Dr. Rednam explained. "We can easily be removing 20 to 30 pounds in just tissue skin."&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The procedure removed loose skin from Spanglo's arms, back, buttocks, and stomach. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I also did a breast lift where I didn't want to do implants, but she took the good fat from my stomach, my abdomen area, and put that into my breasts, and lifted my breasts," Spanglo said.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Rednam noted the growing trend in her own practice.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"I would tell you almost 20% to 30% of people, if not higher on GLP-1 medications that are coming in for these procedures."&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nationally, &lt;a href="https://cdn.theaestheticsociety.org/media/statistics/2023-TheAestheticSocietyStatistics.pdf" target="_blank"&gt;the Aesthetic Society reports&lt;/a&gt; that lower body lifts have increased by 43% and upper body lifts by 34% in the first four years since GLP-1 medications began getting approval for weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Rednam emphasizes that cosmetic surgery involves more than physical changes. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"All of my patients get a mental health coach and these are all licensed professionals, they work with their dietitian," she said.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, one year after her body lift, Spanglo exercises daily, works to maintain healthy eating habits, and continues using Ozempic to "quiet her food noise." She has transformed her weight loss journey into a career, amassing nearly 2 million followers across &lt;a href="https://www.tiktok.com/@takingmylifebackat42?lang=en" target="_blank"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt; and Instagram.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Despite the popularity of GLP-1 medications, Spanglo cautions against viewing them as an effortless solution. &lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                    &lt;div class="article__section article__section_type_text utility__text"&gt;
&lt;p&gt;"There's no magic pill out there. You have to work it," she stressed.&lt;/p&gt;                    &lt;/div&gt;
                                &lt;p class="article__section article__section_type_embed"&gt;
                                    
                                &lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>KHOU</author><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 02:52:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixgFBVV95cUxOVjdiRlEtRVcwblhpRnhRUUlYaVFZb1pxcE1UcUZKbjJlTTROX3prR3Fkbmd6UmQtOWsyRnlTSWNhc282d081a3EzbWhkaUh4T3BmeVZibGo5aWtWckpRVmFOclFLc0F5djBidXhjUGJLN1haN2FFNUhKN1RuSGU1dzZ2TERIYnFDNVFtdnk2VVlKRktmeFE3R25ONEtxNDRuamxqYll6N3daSlB0Q2VtdHE4OGdaY3JKXy0tTk83MkZ3VWp1TGc</guid></item><item><title>新泽西州男子成为第一个记录在案的与电子烟有关的癌症病例-每日邮报 | New Jersey man becomes first documented cancer case tied to vaping - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiygFBVV95cUxNVUdyZW54emRHOEFZeWx6eGpfWFRMVUEzOEtfRzVvY2JZYlNESlB1eDFLajlVV1QxRlItTEdPS1o5Nng0RV9pZVJrbndlcG1YaUowaERvR1J3MmpLZVY3WlJHR2RaaU1KQUNaNjZYNXl5X2FleXoxcTN2c1hnVXdkc1UyZTk3UVluNi1BbGxlTVZZQnNQNzNrMUJnakM4Z05jcUtqWXhPRUpMZi1PZURrY1poWG1FZlE3M0NIR1FTclNOeGhaRFg4MHZR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;A &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/new-jersey/index.html" id="mol-93c9b070-4b9e-11f0-bafa-bd723bfe875b"&gt;New Jersey&lt;/a&gt; man has died from an aggressive lung &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/cancer/index.html" id="mol-38e14a10-4b9e-11f0-bafa-bd723bfe875b"&gt;cancer&lt;/a&gt; that doctors say may have been caused by e-cigarettes — in what is thought to be the first case of its kind. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The 51-year-old patient, who has not been named, &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14735277/fourth-degree-burns-habit-followed-americans-vaping.html"&gt;had vaped&lt;/a&gt; for more than a decade after giving up traditional cigarettes in 2009.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He sought medical help in 2020 after suffering chest pain, shortness of breath, &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-93c91430-4b9e-11f0-bafa-bd723bfe875b"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt;, and coughing up blood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In his left lung, doctors discovered a tumor about the size of a pack of cards. He had a cancer normally associated &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14703051/organs-failing-die-habit-americans-loyda-cordero-galiero.html"&gt;with heavy tobacco use.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Yet his last chest scan just two years earlier had been completely clear, leading his medical team to believe vaping may have played a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Because the tumor had spread into the tissue surrounding his heart, surgery was ruled out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He began chemotherapy, but the disease progressed rapidly and he died just three months after his diagnosis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;His case, published in the American Journal of Case Reports, is thought to be the first to suggest a possible link between vaping and cancer in people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;&lt;p class="clear"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Leonardo DiCaprio and Cara Delevingne are among the celebrities known to vape on occasion &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Earlier studies had only demonstrated such associations in lab animals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors from AtlantiCare Regional Medical Center in Atlantic City, who treated him, wrote: 'While causality cannot be established, the case highlights a potential association between e-cigarette use and malignancy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Further research is needed to investigate the long-term effects of e-cigarettes and their possible role in lung cancer development and progression.' &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Although there have been a handful of prior cancer cases involving people who vape, many of those patients were older and had long histories of smoking tobacco, making it difficult to isolate the effects of vaping alone. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr James Finigan, a pulmonologist who specializes in treating lung nodules and lung cancer, told the Daily Mail: 'Though the long term effects of vaping are still being studied, there is evidence that the risk of cancer is four fold higher in those who have vaped and smoked cigarettes compared to those who have only smoked cigarettes.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The New Jersey patient had quit traditional cigarettes more than a decade earlier before turning to e-cigarettes and was relatively young, with a faster-than-expected clinical decline and no response to chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The team wrote: 'While definitive conclusions cannot be drawn, our patient's younger age, limited combustible tobacco smoking history, rapid tumor growth, lack of response to chemotherapy, and accelerated clinical decline raise the possibility of a distinct or more aggressive disease pattern. &lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'These differences prompt consideration of potential contributing factors, including the prolonged use of ENDS [electronic cigarettes].'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;E-cigarettes produce an aerosol by heating a liquid that usually contains nicotine, flavorings, and a mixture of toxic chemicals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When inhaled, this vapor can deliver harmful substances deep into the lungs, including formaldehyde, acetaldehyde, and other volatile organic compounds known to cause cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;These substances can damage lung tissue and over time, this damage can lead to DNA mutations and inflammation which increase the risk of cancer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In this case, the patient's tumor occupied roughly two-thirds of his left lung by the time it was detected. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Tests revealed he had squamous cell carcinoma (SSC) — a form of cancer that accounts for roughly 20 to 30 percent of all lung cancer diagnoses in the US.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;There are around 226,000 new cases annually, the vast majority of whom are men and long-term smokers.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;SCC is often considered a 'silent killer' because it may not cause obvious symptoms in its early stages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;When signs do appear, they are frequently mistaken for less serious conditions — such as allergies, bronchitis, or asthma. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;If caught early, SCC has a five-year survival rate of around 50 percent. But once it spreads beyond the lungs, that figure drops to just seven percent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The New Jersey patient was initially discharged after diagnosis, with plans to begin treatment on an outpatient basis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But within two weeks, he returned to the hospital in severe pain. The tumor had grown so large it was compressing his airways and making it difficult to breathe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Doctors inserted a stent to help open his lungs, and he was prescribed radiation and chemotherapy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the cancer continued to spread, and he died within two months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The authors of the report are now calling for more research into the cancer risks associated with e-cigarette use, particularly as more long-term users age into the window when cancer typically appears. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They also suggest updating cancer screening criteria to include chronic vapers — especially those with more than 10 years of use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;As for adult vaping, a study in JAMA recently found Oklahoma topped the list &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Early detection in this instance might have facilitated timely intervention and improved the clinical outcome,' the doctors wrote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Future research should investigate whether e-cigarette use is an emerging risk factor worth considering in lung cancer screening programs.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Finigan added: 'Identifying lung cancer early, either through screening or through appropriately identifying and managing incidentally identified lung nodules, is the most effective way to reduce overall lung cancer mortality.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;An estimated 16 million American adults — about 6.5 percent of the U.S. population — currently use e-cigarettes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The highest rates are seen in young adults aged 18 to 24, with more than 15 percent in that group reporting regular use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Among children, about 1.6 million middle and high school students still vape, though usage has declined since its peak in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 23:07:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiygFBVV95cUxNVUdyZW54emRHOEFZeWx6eGpfWFRMVUEzOEtfRzVvY2JZYlNESlB1eDFLajlVV1QxRlItTEdPS1o5Nng0RV9pZVJrbndlcG1YaUowaERvR1J3MmpLZVY3WlJHR2RaaU1KQUNaNjZYNXl5X2FleXoxcTN2c1hnVXdkc1UyZTk3UVluNi1BbGxlTVZZQnNQNzNrMUJnakM4Z05jcUtqWXhPRUpMZi1PZURrY1poWG1FZlE3M0NIR1FTclNOeGhaRFg4MHZR</guid></item><item><title>在青少年之前接受放疗，脑癌诊断后的化疗- Bring Me The News | Prior Lake teen to undergo radiation, chemo after brain cancer diagnosis - Bring Me The News</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiswFBVV95cUxNejBmdjRBNTZYLUF6UGk5OGFXWkw4N3JUZEdVNS1SenduU0RSR194S0lnWTlDMnBTUFp5YzVUNWE3LWJ3Wk1nZnhad2szSnp3bFp4eV9KSWEtaVFMcUdCZWFuZ1hrWmtSbjBMYS1kU2dhenozekVERnRWTm95YVloRl9JTUF6dm1PY1pMWnRhM2pDdWxUd1pCMkpOeDNJMG1LQjhXX3NCZ1NnR2s3d1V1OFBTNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;body id="readabilityBody"&gt;&lt;p id="cmsg"&gt;Please enable JS and disable any ad blocker&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Bring Me The News</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 22:33:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiswFBVV95cUxNejBmdjRBNTZYLUF6UGk5OGFXWkw4N3JUZEdVNS1SenduU0RSR194S0lnWTlDMnBTUFp5YzVUNWE3LWJ3Wk1nZnhad2szSnp3bFp4eV9KSWEtaVFMcUdCZWFuZ1hrWmtSbjBMYS1kU2dhenozekVERnRWTm95YVloRl9JTUF6dm1PY1pMWnRhM2pDdWxUd1pCMkpOeDNJMG1LQjhXX3NCZ1NnR2s3d1V1OFBTNA</guid></item><item><title>另一项研究发现，杂草对您的心脏有害- Gizmodo | Yet Another Study Finds Weed Is Bad for Your Heart - Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNY3VTUmtrNm13aE9BOFo4dEdQYnNwTl9ROFdRc1pSUWNHNlgwMzJhVncxUGhvQ1BJdU5rTGtTRWdXOHdsNnd4bDI0dGhCWXgwb0FYMVp2Qk1WN3E4WXdEbFpGdzNPMGpIR3ZLZVJGM0dPV2NfdllMT09Lbk80SmFmQ0MzWmhLRThk?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none"&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;In recent years, weed use among U.S. adults has reached an all-time high. While many laud this drug as safe, natural, and even medicinal, a growing body of evidence suggests it contributes to adverse cardiovascular effects—including deadly heart disease. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-4 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;A new study published in the journal &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://heart.bmj.com/lookup/doi/10.1136/heartjnl-2024-325429"&gt;&lt;span&gt;Heart&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; on Tuesday, June 17, presents new evidence showing that marijuana use doubles &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;the risk of dying from cardiovascular disease. The researchers found particularly heightened risks of stroke and acute coronary syndrome (ACS)—a sudden reduction in blood flow to the heart, such as a heart attack. While previous studies have linked cannabis to cardiovascular problems, this research underscores the severity of these risks. The authors note, however, that future studies will need to verify this link and investigate the mechanisms behind it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The findings may come as a shock to those who consider weed a harmless high, but co-author Emilie Jouanjus, a clinical pharmacologist at the University of Toulouse in France, was not surprised. She’s been studying the adverse health effects of marijuana for more than a decade and hopes this study will promote better decision-making around marijuana use. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;“I think that it’s very important that people realize that there is risk, even if it’s a natural product,” Jouanjus told Gizmodo. Over the last decade, increased state legalization has &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://nida.nih.gov/news-events/news-releases/2024/08/cannabis-and-hallucinogen-use-among-adults-remained-at-historic-highs-in-2023"&gt;&lt;span&gt;made&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; weed more accessible and less stigmatized, contributing to a rise in recreational and medicinal use. Jouanjus and her colleagues argue that public health messaging should treat cannabis like tobacco—not criminalizing it, but actively highlighting its risks and discouraging use.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The researchers analyzed 24 studies, conducted between January 2016 and December 2023, that investigated the link between marijuana use and serious cardiovascular outcomes. These studies involved roughly 200 million participants mostly between the ages of 19 and 59. They specifically looked at cardiovascular disease death and non-fatal outcomes including stroke and ACS.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The analysis found that cannabis use increases the risk of ACS by 29%, risk of stroke by 20%, and doubles the risk of dying from cardiovascular disease. While the researchers say their study provides an exhaustive analysis of the available data on marijuana use and cardiovascular disease, Jouanjus noted that the included studies were limited by a lack of data on when and how participants were exposed to cannabis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;This leaves several important questions unanswered, such as, at what dosage does cannabis become unsafe? Are the cardiovascular risks lower for occasional marijuana users? Is consuming edibles safer than smoking weed? Jouanjus hopes future studies will explore these questions. Some researchers have already begun, like Matt Springer, a cardiovascular researcher at the University of California San Francisco. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Springer co-authored a recent study, published in the journal &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://jamanetwork.com/journals/jamacardiology/article-abstract/2834540?utm_campaign=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_medium=articlePDFlink&amp;amp;utm_source=articlePDF&amp;amp;utm_content=jamacardio.2025.1399"&gt;&lt;span&gt;JAMA Cardiology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; in May, that found &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://gizmodo.com/smoking-weed-and-eating-edibles-share-this-surprising-health-risk-2000611136"&gt;&lt;span&gt;both smoking weed and eating edibles increase risk of cardiovascular disease&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. The finding challenges widespread assumptions that edibles are a less-harmful way to consume marijuana and underscores the drug’s alarming cardiovascular effects. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Like Jouanjus, Springer wasn’t surprised by the link between cannabis use and cardiovascular disease death. “This is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;consistent with several reports in the last few years showing associations between cannabis use and various kinds of cardiovascular outcomes, as well as another recent meta-analysis &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.acc.org/About-ACC/Press-Releases/2025/03/17/15/35/Cannabis-Users-Face-Substantially-Higher-Risk"&gt;&lt;span&gt;reported&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; at the [American College of Cardiology] conference in March,” he told Gizmodo in an email. That study found that cannabis users face significantly higher risk of heart attack than non-users. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Springer’s latest study found that cannabis users showed reduced blood vessel dilation, which puts them at greater risk of heart attack and other poor cardiovascular outcomes. In theory, this could contribute to the increased risk of cardiovascular disease death that Jouanjus and her colleagues found, he said, but researchers need more evidence to support that claim.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;There are other potential mechanisms, too. Jouanjus pointed to previous research that &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC6461323/"&gt;&lt;span&gt;found&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; that, like tobacco, cannabis contributes to buildup of plaque within artery walls. This increases the risk of heart attack, stroke, and peripheral artery disease. She also highlighted that the psychoactive compound in marijuana—tetrahydrocannabinol (THC)—is far more concentrated in cannabis products today than those from 20 years ago. This, too, may contribute to the increased risk of cardiovascular death she observed in her study.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;While all of these factors could plausibly influence weed’s cardiovascular effects, getting to the bottom of why this drug damages heart health will require more research. In the meantime, Jouanjus feels there is enough evidence to warrant caution and moderation when using marijuana. The public is well aware of the benefits of cannabis, but she hopes her study can draw attention to its risks, too.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Springer agrees, “These reports over the last few years, including ours and this paper, indicate that cannabis is not necessarily harmless,” he said.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 22:31:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiiAFBVV95cUxNY3VTUmtrNm13aE9BOFo4dEdQYnNwTl9ROFdRc1pSUWNHNlgwMzJhVncxUGhvQ1BJdU5rTGtTRWdXOHdsNnd4bDI0dGhCWXgwb0FYMVp2Qk1WN3E4WXdEbFpGdzNPMGpIR3ZLZVJGM0dPV2NfdllMT09Lbk80SmFmQ0MzWmhLRThk</guid></item><item><title>研究表明，使用大麻可能会使心脏病死亡的风险增加一倍-《卫报》 | Cannabis use could double risk of heart deaths, study suggests - The Guardian</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirgFBVV95cUxNekpyU2FySUYwS2kxX2k1MDV2ajU5YmRLc0ZjN0Z2b2tmdUl3M1hyN2Iwcm9VaTdHMlplbnRzc2RtT21XcHBXbW9MbmRHTW9CQllaeGJsWlpaZVRTcnFtR2Jrc1VGNnR5bS0wNHFWSjlFRzlNekw5SWgzQWV5dnRjLXhQSENfbUZ5VEJOVnN6TkljckNPVTdzQ2p6SUlNRXFGMW1yQV9vZjV5aTkxeHc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="article-body-commercial-selector article-body-viewer-selector dcr-11jq3zt"&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Cannabis use may double the risk of dying from heart disease and increase the risk of stroke by 20%, according to a global review of data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The number of people using cannabis and cannabinoids has soared over the past decade. While previous studies have linked cannabis use to cardiovascular problems, the scale of the risk has until now not been clear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="sign-in-gate"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="SignInGateSelector" priority="feature" deferuntil="visible" props='{"contentType":"Article","sectionId":"society","tags":[{"id":"society/cannabis","type":"Keyword","title":"Cannabis"},{"id":"uk/uk","type":"Keyword","title":"UK news"},{"id":"society/drugs","type":"Keyword","title":"Drugs"},{"id":"society/society","type":"Keyword","title":"Society"},{"id":"campaign/email/today-uk","type":"Campaign","title":"The Guardian Headlines UK (newsletter signup)"},{"id":"society/health","type":"Keyword","title":"Health"},{"id":"society/heart-disease","type":"Keyword","title":"Heart disease"},{"id":"society/stroke","type":"Keyword","title":"Stroke"},{"id":"type/article","type":"Type","title":"Article"},{"id":"tone/news","type":"Tone","title":"News"},{"id":"profile/andrew-gregory","type":"Contributor","title":"Andrew Gregory","twitterHandle":"andrewgregory"},{"id":"publication/theguardian","type":"Publication","title":"The Guardian"},{"id":"theguardian/mainsection","type":"NewspaperBook","title":"Main section"},{"id":"theguardian/mainsection/uknews","type":"NewspaperBookSection","title":"UK news"},{"id":"tracking/commissioningdesk/uk-home-news","type":"Tracking","title":"UK Home News"}],"isPaidContent":false,"isPreview":false,"host":"https://www.theguardian.com","pageId":"society/2025/jun/17/cannabis-use-could-double-risk-of-heart-deaths-study-suggests","idUrl":"https://profile.theguardian.com","contributionsServiceUrl":"https://contributions.guardianapis.com","editionId":"US"}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;This is an important gap in light of major changes in consumption, researchers at the University of Toulouse in France said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure id="8198fbf3-44e9-453e-8122-4f212927ff32" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-1your1i"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":3,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Sadiq Khan calls for partial decriminalisation of cannabis possession","elementId":"8198fbf3-44e9-453e-8122-4f212927ff32","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/society/2025/may/28/sadiq-khan-calls-for-partial-decriminalisation-of-cannabis-possession"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;To strengthen the evidence base, they searched databases looking for large observational studies, published between 2016 and 2023, which explored cannabis use and cardiovascular outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Twenty-four studies, involving about 200 million people, were included in a pooled data analysis of the results: 17 cross-sectional studies, six cohort studies, and one case-control study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;Study participants were mostly aged between 19 and 59. And in those studies where sex was recorded, cannabis users tended to be mostly male and younger than non-users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The analysis revealed heightened risks for cannabis use: 29% higher for acute coronary syndrome; 20% higher for stroke; and a doubling in the risk of dying from cardiovascular disease. The findings were published in the journal &lt;a href="https://heart.bmj.com/lookup/doi/10.1136/heartjnl-2024-325429" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;Heart&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;The researchers acknowledged several limitations to their systematic review and meta analysis. There was a moderate to high risk of bias in most of the included studies, largely because of lack of information on missing data and imprecise measures of cannabis exposure. Most of them were observational and several used the same data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-spacefinder-role="inline" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.NewsletterSignupBlockElement" class="dcr-173mewl"&gt;&lt;a data-ignore="global-link-styling" href="#EmailSignup-skip-link-9" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;skip past newsletter promotion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;p id="EmailSignup-skip-link-9" tabindex="0" aria-label="after newsletter promotion" role="note" class="dcr-jzxpee"&gt;after newsletter promotion&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure id="b9905e47-6ae9-4628-b4a7-884144da7b79" data-spacefinder-role="richLink" data-spacefinder-type="model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement" class="dcr-1your1i"&gt;&lt;gu-island name="RichLinkComponent" priority="feature" deferuntil="idle" props='{"richLinkIndex":10,"element":{"_type":"model.dotcomrendering.pageElements.RichLinkBlockElement","prefix":"Related: ","text":"Tracking low-level cannabis use wastes police time, former London chief says","elementId":"b9905e47-6ae9-4628-b4a7-884144da7b79","role":"richLink","url":"https://www.theguardian.com/uk-news/2025/may/29/tracking-low-level-cannabis-use-wastes-police-time-london-brian-paddick"},"ajaxUrl":"https://api.nextgen.guardianapps.co.uk","format":{"design":0,"display":0,"theme":0}}'&gt;&lt;/gu-island&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;With these caveats, the researchers said their work was an exhaustive analysis of published data on the potential association between cannabis use and major cardiovascular disease and provided new insights from real-world data. “The findings outlined by this meta analysis should enhance the general awareness of the potential of cannabis to cause cardiovascular harm.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;&lt;a href="https://heart.bmj.com/lookup/doi/10.1136/heartjnl-2024-326169" data-link-name="in body link"&gt;In a linked editorial&lt;/a&gt;, Prof Stanton Glantz and Dr Lynn Silver of the University of California at San Francisco said the analysis “raises serious questions about the assumption that cannabis imposes little cardiovascular risk”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;More research is needed to clarify whether cardiovascular risks are limited to inhaled products or extend to other forms of cannabis exposure, they said. Cannabis is now generally more potent and has diversified into a wide array of inhaled high potency cannabis concentrates, synthetic psychoactive cannabinoids, and edibles, they added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;They wrote: “How these changes affect cardiovascular risk requires clarification, as does the proportion of risk attributable to cannabinoids themselves versus particulate matter, terpenes or other components of the exposure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Cannabis needs to be incorporated into the framework for prevention of clinical cardiovascular disease. So too must cardiovascular disease prevention be incorporated into the regulation of cannabis markets. Effective product warnings and education on risks must be developed, required, and implemented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Cardiovascular and other health risks must be considered in the regulation of allowable product and marketing design as the evidence base grows. Today that regulation is focused on establishing the legal market with woeful neglect of minimising health risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="dcr-16w5gq9"&gt;“Specifically, cannabis should be treated like tobacco: not criminalised, but discouraged, with protection of bystanders from secondhand exposure.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>The Guardian</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirgFBVV95cUxNekpyU2FySUYwS2kxX2k1MDV2ajU5YmRLc0ZjN0Z2b2tmdUl3M1hyN2Iwcm9VaTdHMlplbnRzc2RtT21XcHBXbW9MbmRHTW9CQllaeGJsWlpaZVRTcnFtR2Jrc1VGNnR5bS0wNHFWSjlFRzlNekw5SWgzQWV5dnRjLXhQSENfbUZ5VEJOVnN6TkljckNPVTdzQ2p6SUlNRXFGMW1yQV9vZjV5aTkxeHc</guid></item><item><title>事实证明，大麻提取物在杀死世界上最危险的动物方面非常有效- Earth.com | Cannabis extract proves to be highly effective at killing the most dangerous animals in the world - Earth.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimgFBVV95cUxNcUVKQTh4OTlQNG1VVWFqV3pZYkFDNnp6SE1uZmhMV2dGNUJBam9uOWpBYURJOFhrN3V6di0tSks1YUJvb2tJTU5vcVV0cktjUUgzd1B2RXhHSnFwa2lrbklXNjB3Nk5wSEZvYUprcVdqZzhCOVJWUE1YMVktMVRLYkg3eUpXeEhrdUtGNFcxTkNJTjlKN0RsSzR3?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="page_content__AwOj6"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every year, mosquito-borne diseases cut short more than a million lives across the globe, outpacing every other animal threat to humanity. The rising toll has public-health teams scrambling for fresh combat tools, especially as traditional chemical sprays lose their edge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That loss stems from two hard truths. First, the very &lt;a href="https://pmc.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/articles/PMC7692614/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;pyrethroid insecticides&lt;/a&gt; that once worked wonders now linger in soil and water, nudging delicate ecosystems off balance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, mosquitoes adapt fast. Larvae soaking in tainted puddles and adults drifting through treated neighborhoods increasingly shrug off doses that once killed them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/mosquito-repellents-that-actually-work-yes-thanks-to-ai-machine-learning/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Controlling the pests&lt;/a&gt; at their waterborne stage is vital, yet options that stay potent without harming everything else remain limited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-cannabis-cbd-and-mosquitoes"&gt;Cannabis, CBD, and mosquitoes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent research published in the journal &lt;em&gt;Insects&lt;/em&gt; points to a solution hiding in plain sight: the hemp plant, &lt;em&gt;Cannabis sativa&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After air-drying and grinding ordinary hemp leaves, scientists at &lt;a href="https://www.osu.edu/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;The Ohio State University&lt;/a&gt; led by Erick Martinez Rodriguez extracted &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cbd-reduces-the-unwanted-side-effects-of-thc/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;cannabidiol (CBD)&lt;/a&gt; and added the concentrate to cups of water teeming with yellow fever mosquito larvae. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Within 48 hours, both a strain that laughs at &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/rising-temperatures-could-make-insect-repellents-less-effective/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;common insecticides&lt;/a&gt; and a non-resistant strain were wiped out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Mosquitoes are one of the deadliest animals in the world, mainly because as adults they serve as vectors of disease,” Rodriguez explained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-from-resistance-to-vulnerability"&gt;From resistance to vulnerability&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two important findings jumped out. The first was total mortality: every mosquito larva exposed to sufficient CBD died by the two-day mark, regardless of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/scientists-learn-how-mosquitoes-use-sound-to-outsmart-and-evade-human-defenses/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;its genetic armor&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second was efficiency. While industrial chemicals often push resistance higher with every generation, CBD’s effect cut straight through those defenses. Doses varied, but even modest concentrations proved lethal to all mosquito larvae.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If you compare the amount of hemp extract needed to kill 50 % of the population to other synthetic conventional insecticides, it is on the high side, but when you compare it side by side to other natural extracts we have tested in our lab, only a relatively low amount is required to produce high mortality values in larvae,” said Martinez Rodriguez.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-how-cbd-kills-mosquitoes"&gt;How CBD kills mosquitoes&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chemical sleuthing showed that CBD dominated the hemp extract, and terpene fractions did little damage on their own. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Larvae were judged dead once they stopped moving under a gentle nudge, confirming the cannabinoid’s direct impact on vital systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Insects lack the endocannabinoid receptors that give &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/cbd-can-help-ease-chronic-pain-anxiety-and-mood-disorders/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;CBD its wellness reputation&lt;/a&gt; among humans, so the compound must strike different molecular targets – possibly ion channels that govern nerve impulses or enzymes tied to muscle control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the route, CBD skirts the metabolic tricks that shield many larvae from pyrethroids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-hemp-economics-meet-public-health"&gt;Hemp economics meet public health&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hemp is no niche crop. U.S. farmers planted about 27,680 acres in 2023, and the total value of &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/hemp-seeds-could-be-a-game-changer-as-an-alternative-protein-source/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;hemp products&lt;/a&gt; topped $291 million.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leaves, often left as low-value waste after flowers and seeds are harvested, could become raw material for larvicides. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turning those leaf cast-offs into mosquito-control pellets would give growers an extra revenue stream while trimming refuse piles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The crop’s adaptability sweetens the deal. Hemp thrives across a wide climate range, grows quickly, and rarely needs harsh pesticides of its own. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rural communities looking to diversify incomes and urban growers cultivating indoor micro-hemp could both feed a supply chain aimed at vector-control programs from Texas to Tanzania.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-strains-and-waterway-safety"&gt;Strains and waterway safety&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Field trials must still answer hard questions: How long does CBD linger in ponds? Does it bother tadpoles, fish fry, or helpful insects? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early lab work hints at selectivity, yet natural habitats are complex. Regulators will demand data showing that CBD pellets, briquettes, or slow-release films silence mosquito larvae without tipping aquatic ecosystems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second layer of testing will match different hemp strains for efficacy. Plants bred for fiber deliver more stalk than cannabinoid, while floral varieties boast &lt;a href="https://pubchem.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/compound/Cannabidiol" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;richer CBD profiles&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Selecting cultivars that maximize larvicidal punch and minimize unwanted compounds will keep costs down and environmental margins wide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-next-steps-for-cbd-and-mosquito-control"&gt;Next steps for CBD and mosquito control&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scientists plan to refine dosage, explore formulations that stick to the water’s surface, and probe how CBD interacts with other biocontrol measures like &lt;em&gt;Bacillus thuringiensis israelensis&lt;/em&gt;. Combining modes of action could slow resistance even further. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teams will also map out manufacturing pipelines – picture hemp-leaf extract concentrated at regional facilities, then shipped as shelf-stable granules to &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/why-some-people-are-mosquito-magnets/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;mosquito-control districts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Policy makers, meanwhile, need clear guidelines. Approving a botanical larvicide means balancing urgent disease threats against conservation goals. Transparent monitoring and community engagement will help keep public trust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 class="wp-block-heading" id="h-another-weapon-in-the-mosquito-wars"&gt;Another weapon in the mosquito wars&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hemp-derived CBD will not single-handedly end malaria, dengue, or Zika. Yet the discovery that a familiar wellness compound doubles as a larval assassin widens the playbook. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By uniting agriculture, chemistry, and entomology, researchers have opened &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/news/mosquito-habitats-are-expanding-due-to-climate-change/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;a practical path&lt;/a&gt; toward safer mosquito control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If larger-scale tests confirm the promise seen in the lab, those humble hemp leaves could soon guard countless backyard birdbaths, drainage ditches, and rice paddies – one cup of water at a time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The full study was published in the journal &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.mdpi.com/2075-4450/15/7/517" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Insects&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like what you read? &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/subscribe/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Subscribe to our newsletter&lt;/a&gt; for engaging articles, exclusive content, and the latest updates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Check us out on &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/earthsnap/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;EarthSnap&lt;/a&gt;, a free app brought to you by &lt;a href="https://www.earth.com/author/eralls/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"&gt;Eric Ralls&lt;/a&gt; and Earth.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;—–&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Earth.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 21:55:35 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimgFBVV95cUxNcUVKQTh4OTlQNG1VVWFqV3pZYkFDNnp6SE1uZmhMV2dGNUJBam9uOWpBYURJOFhrN3V6di0tSks1YUJvb2tJTU5vcVV0cktjUUgzd1B2RXhHSnFwa2lrbklXNjB3Nk5wSEZvYUprcVdqZzhCOVJWUE1YMVktMVRLYkg3eUpXeEhrdUtGNFcxTkNJTjlKN0RsSzR3</guid></item><item><title>乔治· W ·布什（ George W. Bush ）和美国食品和药物管理局局长- statnews.com | George W. Bush drops by BIO, and so does the FDA commissioner - statnews.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMijgFBVV95cUxOT2FUZUZ4a1pBdm9Zb0VCV0lYamtBUGotc2xNNWh3U0p6WGM3Yk5QZVlTVXVVdnJfeS1xSzVObXJ2WUhwSVNBdVRhaEUzeGxuX3h6eXFTUjZaMmlwTEFLUmpGOElwQzdnXzJTQnExZ1ZuSmNsRWFWdmlneERPZFhFN2hDbGpnZFJ3cUxMNTFB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="wp-block-column article-content is-layout-flow wp-block-column-is-layout-flow"&gt;
		&lt;figure class="wp-block-post-featured-image"&gt;				&lt;picture class="featured-image-crop"&gt;
											&lt;source media="(min-width: 1024px)" srcset="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/IMG_4886-1600x900.jpg"&gt;
						&lt;source media="(min-width: 768px) and (max-width: 1023px)" srcset="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/IMG_4886-768x432.jpg 1x, https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/IMG_4886-1600x900.jpg 2x"&gt;
											&lt;img src="https://www.statnews.com/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/IMG_4886-645x645.jpg" alt="BIO CEO John Crowley speaks with FDA Commissioner Marty Makary in Boston."&gt;
				&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/source&gt;&lt;/picture&gt;
				&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;span class="caption"&gt;BIO CEO John Crowley speaks with FDA Commissioner Marty Makary at the BIO conference in Boston.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;cite&gt;Allison DeAngelis/STAT&lt;/cite&gt;&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

					
			&lt;div class="author-pop-over" data-author="allison-deangelis"&gt;&lt;p class="author-bio"&gt;Allison DeAngelis is the East Coast biotech and venture capital reporter at STAT, reporting where scientific ideas and money meet. She is also co-host of the weekly biotech podcast, &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/category/readout-loud/"&gt;The Readout Loud&lt;/a&gt;.  You can reach Allison on Signal at AllisonDeAngelis.01.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="author-alerts"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="author-pop-over" data-author="elizabeth-cooney"&gt;&lt;p class="author-bio"&gt;Elizabeth Cooney is a cardiovascular disease reporter at STAT, covering heart, stroke, and metabolic conditions. You can reach Liz on Signal at LizC.22.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="author-alerts"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is the online version of our BIO 2025 newsletter. Get more BIO updates directly to your inbox by signing up &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/signup/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and sign up for our morning biotech news roundup newsletter &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/signup/readout/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Happy Tuesday, folks! I have an exciting update for you: Friend of STAT/C&amp;amp;EN reporter Rowan Walrath nabbed me a BIO 2025 pin. The design is of, *drumroll please*… a Boston Terrier!&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Now, on to the news….&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker article" aria-labelledby="restricted-story-heading" aria-describedby="restricted-story-description" checked&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-bar"&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-text"&gt;STAT+ Exclusive Story&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-login"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;img class="restricted-content-breaker-bg" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-breaker-bg.png" alt="STAT+"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper"&gt;
				&lt;span class="stat-paywall-archive"&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/"&gt;
						&lt;img class="stat-plus-logo" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-logo-white.svg" alt="STAT+"&gt;
					&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/span&gt;
				&lt;h2 id="restricted-story-heading"&gt;This article is exclusive to STAT+ subscribers&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;h3 id="restricted-story-description"&gt;Unlock this article — plus daily coverage and analysis of the biotech sector — by subscribing to STAT+.&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper-cta mobile"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta mobile"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-cards"&gt;
					&lt;div class="slider-container" aria-label="Subscription plan toggle"&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="individual" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Individual plans&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;p class="switch" role="switch" tabindex="0" aria-checked="false"&gt;
							&lt;button class="slider"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="group" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Group plans&lt;/button&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
							

		
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button view-all" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker view all plans" aria-label="View All Plans"&gt;View All Plans&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="restricted-message-breaker"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-wrapper"&gt;
								
								&lt;div class="restricted-content-message"&gt;
					&lt;p class="restricted-content-text"&gt;
						To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.					&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button restricted-button" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker subscribe cta 1"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
								
							&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;div class="wp-block-template-part"&gt;
&lt;div class="wp-block-group article-meta is-layout-flow wp-block-group-is-layout-flow"&gt;
	
	
	

	
	
	

	&lt;ol class="wp-block-stat-article-authors"&gt;		&lt;li class="author-container-item"&gt;
			&lt;div class="wp-block-group article-author"&gt;
				&lt;div class="wp-block-columns article-author-header"&gt;
											
											&lt;div class="wp-block-column author"&gt;
						&lt;div class="wp-block-group"&gt;
							
															&lt;p class="author-title"&gt;Biotech Startups and Venture Capital Reporter&lt;/p&gt;
																		&lt;ol class="mobile"&gt;
							&lt;li&gt;
								&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="social-item-icon email" title="Email" href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#d7b6bbbbbea4b8b9f9b3b2b6b9b0b2bbbea497a4a3b6a3b9b2a0a4f9b4b8ba" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
							&lt;/ol&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
									&lt;p class="author-bio"&gt;Allison DeAngelis is the East Coast biotech and venture capital reporter at STAT, reporting where scientific ideas and money meet. She is also co-host of the weekly biotech podcast, &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/category/readout-loud/"&gt;The Readout Loud&lt;/a&gt;.  You can reach Allison on Signal at AllisonDeAngelis.01.&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/li&gt;
				&lt;li class="author-container-item"&gt;
			&lt;div class="wp-block-group article-author"&gt;
				&lt;div class="wp-block-columns article-author-header"&gt;
											
											&lt;div class="wp-block-column author"&gt;
						&lt;div class="wp-block-group"&gt;
							
															&lt;p class="author-title"&gt;Cardiovascular Disease Reporter&lt;/p&gt;
																		&lt;ol class="mobile"&gt;
							&lt;li&gt;
								&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="social-item-icon bluesky" title="Bluesky" href="https://bsky.app/profile/elizabethcooney.bsky.social" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
								&lt;li&gt;&lt;a class="social-item-icon email" title="Email" href="/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#b4d1d8ddced5d6d1c0dc9ad7dbdbdad1cdf4c7c0d5c0dad1c3c79ad7dbd9" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
							&lt;/ol&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;/div&gt;
									&lt;p class="author-bio"&gt;Elizabeth Cooney is a cardiovascular disease reporter at STAT, covering heart, stroke, and metabolic conditions. You can reach Liz on Signal at LizC.22.&lt;/p&gt;
								&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/li&gt;
		&lt;/ol&gt;

	
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	

	
	&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:58:49 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMijgFBVV95cUxOT2FUZUZ4a1pBdm9Zb0VCV0lYamtBUGotc2xNNWh3U0p6WGM3Yk5QZVlTVXVVdnJfeS1xSzVObXJ2WUhwSVNBdVRhaEUzeGxuX3h6eXFTUjZaMmlwTEFLUmpGOElwQzdnXzJTQnExZ1ZuSmNsRWFWdmlneERPZFhFN2hDbGpnZFJ3cUxMNTFB</guid></item><item><title>疾病预防控制中心临时领导人在第一次全体会议上谈到“破除迷思”和“复原力” - statnews.com | CDC interim leaders, in first all-hands meeting, speak of ‘myth-busting’ and ‘resilience’ - statnews.com</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMixgFBVV95cUxPN2laeC1zbkZDT0FxN3lQQm03NlZsajl2aHN4TXhnbnhybFptUWlmLVFCa1JfR1F3ODk1SWRnMW1iQ2lQVlBxMnNobFAxZE8xRjIyVnJub0tQT3NkaEV2WmJ2Y190ZWhBekpES1B5MnlLY0xPOXlBX0dDNzM2ZFNQSm0zTWRDWHlVekJTWDZ0c2w3VlZjbXhsZ1pzVzhodUVuZ3Y2b0RfNWotYkJXeFdpNF9kSWdnTWJ0cl9oRHZBQVBoNjB2bHc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="author-pop-over" data-author="helen-branswell"&gt;&lt;p class="author-bio"&gt;Helen Branswell covers issues broadly related to infectious diseases, including outbreaks, preparedness, research, and vaccine development. Follow her on &lt;a href="https://scicomm.xyz/@HelenBranswell"&gt;Mastodon&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://bsky.app/profile/helenbranswell.bsky.social"&gt;Bluesky&lt;/a&gt;. You can reach Helen on Signal at hbranswell.01.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="author-alerts"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;div class="entry-content the-content wp-block-post-content is-layout-flow wp-block-post-content-is-layout-flow"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In their first all-staff meeting since the start of the Trump administration, the interim leadership of the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention attempted to sidestep controversy and rally troops at the storied but demoralized agency on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Staff were told CDC director nominee Susan Monarez has begun meeting with senators in advance of a still-unscheduled Senate confirmation hearing. They were also informed the June meeting of the agency’s expert vaccine panel, the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices, will be shorter than anticipated because the &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/06/11/rfk-jr-names-new-acip-members-replaces-cdc-vaccine-experts-he-just-fired/"&gt;eight new members of the committee&lt;/a&gt; — 17 previous members &lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/2025/06/09/rfk-jr-fires-every-member-of-cdc-vaccine-expert-panel-acip/"&gt;were fired last week&lt;/a&gt; by health secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. — are not yet in a position to deal with all the agenda items.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;There were no audible outbursts from staff during the tightly scripted hour-long meeting, which STAT listened to. But an email sent to agency personnel on Monday from CDC’s Office of Safety, Security, and Asset Management suggested there may have been fears the meeting could have been tense. “In advance of tomorrow’s CDC All-Staff meeting, we wanted to provide staff with the following reminders,” it began. Among the reminders was a list of items staff may not bring on CDC campuses that included firearms, mace or pepper sprays, or bladed tools. (STAT has viewed a copy of the email.)&lt;/p&gt;
		&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker article" aria-labelledby="restricted-story-heading" aria-describedby="restricted-story-description" checked&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-bar"&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-text"&gt;STAT+ Exclusive Story&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-login"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; 
			&lt;/div&gt;
			&lt;img class="restricted-content-breaker-bg" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-breaker-bg.png" alt="STAT+"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper"&gt;
				&lt;span class="stat-paywall-archive"&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/"&gt;
						&lt;img class="stat-plus-logo" src="/wp-content/themes/stat/images/stat-plus-logo-white.svg" alt="STAT+"&gt;
					&lt;/a&gt;
				&lt;/span&gt;
				&lt;h2 id="restricted-story-heading"&gt;This article is exclusive to STAT+ subscribers&lt;/h2&gt;
				&lt;h3 id="restricted-story-description"&gt;Unlock this article — plus in-depth analysis, newsletters, premium events, and news alerts.&lt;/h3&gt;
				&lt;p class="restricted-content-breaker-wrapper-cta mobile"&gt;Already have an account? &lt;a href="/login/" data-stat-login data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker login cta mobile"&gt;Log in&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
				&lt;div class="restricted-content-breaker-cards"&gt;
					&lt;div class="slider-container" aria-label="Subscription plan toggle"&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="individual" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Individual plans&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;p class="switch" role="switch" tabindex="0" aria-checked="false"&gt;
							&lt;button class="slider"&gt;&lt;/button&gt;
						&lt;/p&gt;
						&lt;button type="button" class="group" aria-pressed="false"&gt;Group plans&lt;/button&gt;
					&lt;/div&gt;
							

		
						&lt;/div&gt;
				&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button view-all" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker view all plans" aria-label="View All Plans"&gt;View All Plans&lt;/a&gt;
			&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		
		&lt;div class="restricted-message-breaker"&gt;
			&lt;div class="restricted-content-wrapper"&gt;
								
								&lt;div class="restricted-content-message"&gt;
					&lt;p class="restricted-content-text"&gt;
						To read the rest of this story subscribe to STAT+.					&lt;/p&gt;
					&lt;a href="https://www.statnews.com/stat-plus/" class="stat-button restricted-button" data-stat-paywall-cta="breaker subscribe cta 1"&gt;Subscribe&lt;/a&gt;
									&lt;/div&gt;
								
							&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;
		&lt;/div&gt;

		&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>statnews.com</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:49:05 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMixgFBVV95cUxPN2laeC1zbkZDT0FxN3lQQm03NlZsajl2aHN4TXhnbnhybFptUWlmLVFCa1JfR1F3ODk1SWRnMW1iQ2lQVlBxMnNobFAxZE8xRjIyVnJub0tQT3NkaEV2WmJ2Y190ZWhBekpES1B5MnlLY0xPOXlBX0dDNzM2ZFNQSm0zTWRDWHlVekJTWDZ0c2w3VlZjbXhsZ1pzVzhodUVuZ3Y2b0RfNWotYkJXeFdpNF9kSWdnTWJ0cl9oRHZBQVBoNjB2bHc</guid></item><item><title>黑咖啡与降低死亡风险有关–所以坚持奶油和糖-好消息网络 | Black Coffee is Linked to Lower Risk of Death – So Hold the Cream and Sugar - Good News Network</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNZTFxNEJGbUFxOWhJR24tZXFYVWdLUGJKUzlGazJWeF9aLVI2c0huVXd3UHFMYkx6RGMtX3Rjc0ZRTnR0dGp3dkdKTndmSm14dmVsVW9LTlFBZHFHajdjQmRlZ3JxNHBYNjVuVlQ3cEFQM0VfQWh3aGVsUk43Z0xXV0VKVzJiSm5VZVowZDhQODlWbXlVQ1BrN2FUdUlMdW9fTVFnNkNuMUlqZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="td-post-content"&gt;
        &lt;figure id="attachment_219223" aria-describedby="caption-attachment-219223" class="wp-caption aligncenter"&gt;&lt;img fetchpriority="high" decoding="async" class="size-large wp-image-219223" src="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Black-iced-coffee-by-pariwat-pannium-For-Unsplash-HXPu2Dm4kJk-1024x549.jpg" alt="" srcset="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Black-iced-coffee-by-pariwat-pannium-For-Unsplash-HXPu2Dm4kJk-1024x549.jpg 1024w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Black-iced-coffee-by-pariwat-pannium-For-Unsplash-HXPu2Dm4kJk-326x175.jpg 326w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Black-iced-coffee-by-pariwat-pannium-For-Unsplash-HXPu2Dm4kJk-768x411.jpg 768w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Black-iced-coffee-by-pariwat-pannium-For-Unsplash-HXPu2Dm4kJk-696x373.jpg 696w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Black-iced-coffee-by-pariwat-pannium-For-Unsplash-HXPu2Dm4kJk-1068x572.jpg 1068w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Black-iced-coffee-by-pariwat-pannium-For-Unsplash-HXPu2Dm4kJk-784x420.jpg 784w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Black-iced-coffee-by-pariwat-pannium-For-Unsplash-HXPu2Dm4kJk-530x284.jpg 530w, https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/wp-content/uploads/2025/06/Black-iced-coffee-by-pariwat-pannium-For-Unsplash-HXPu2Dm4kJk.jpg 1400w" sizes="(max-width: 696px) 100vw, 696px"&gt;&lt;figcaption id="caption-attachment-219223" class="wp-caption-text"&gt;pariwat pannium For Unsplash+&lt;/figcaption&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While you’re probably not pouring your morning cup for the long-term health benefits, coffee consumption has been linked to lower risk of mortality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, in a new observational study, researchers from Tufts University found that the association between coffee consumption and mortality risk changes with the amount of sweeteners and saturated fat added to the beverage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/abs/pii/S002231662500286X" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt;Published online in&lt;/a&gt; The Journal of Nutrition, the study found that consumption of 1-2 cups of caffeinated coffee per day was linked to a lower risk of death from all causes, and death from cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Compared to drinking no java, black coffee—as well as coffee with low levels of added sugar and saturated fat—were associated with a 14% lower risk of all-cause mortality. But, the same link was not observed for coffee with high amounts of added sugar and saturated fat.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“With nearly half of American adults reporting drinking at least one cup per day, it’s important for us to know what it might mean for health,”&lt;a href="https://now.tufts.edu/2025/06/16/hold-cream-and-sugar-black-coffee-linked-lower-risk-death" target="_blank" rel="noopener"&gt; said Professor Fang Fang Zhang&lt;/a&gt;, senior author of the study.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="pgs-dpg-flex" data-pgs-partner-id="good-news-network"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The health benefits of coffee might be attributable to its bioactive compounds, but our results suggest that the addition of sugar and saturated fat may reduce the benefits.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ANOTHER CUPPA GOOD NEWS&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="Coffee Drinkers Less at Risk of Head and Neck Cancers, New Research Suggests" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/coffee-drinkers-less-at-risk-of-head-and-neck-cancers-new-research-suggests/" rel="bookmark"&gt;Coffee Drinkers Less at Risk of Head and Neck Cancers, New Research Suggests&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The study analyzed data from a nationally representative sample of 46,000 adults aged 20 years and older who took part in the National Health and Nutrition Examination Survey from 1999 to 2018. Coffee consumption was categorized by type (caffeinated or decaffeinated), sugar, and saturated fat content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mortality outcomes was defined as all-cause, cancer, and cardiovascular disease.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low amounts of sweetener (including granulated sugar, honey, or syrup) was defined as 2.5 grams per 8-ounce cup or approximately half a teaspoon.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Low saturated fat (from milk, cream, or half-and-half) was defined as 1 gram per 8-ounce cup or the equivalent of 5 tablespoons of 2% milk, 1 tablespoon of light cream, or 1 tablespoon of half-and-half.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consumption of at least one cup per day was associated with a 16% lower risk of all-cause mortality—while 2-3 cups per day saw the link rise slightly to 17%.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Consumption beyond three cups per day was not associated with added benefit. And, any benefit for a lower risk of cardiovascular death was weakened when the person drank more than three cups per day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No associations were seen between coffee and cancer mortality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MORE COFFEE BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a title="An Espresso a Day Could Keep Alzheimer’s at Bay by Preventing Tau Clumping" href="https://www.goodnewsnetwork.org/espresso-a-day-could-keep-alzheimers-at-bay-preventing-tau-clumping/" rel="bookmark"&gt;An Espresso a Day Could Keep Alzheimer’s at Bay by Preventing Tau Clumping&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Few studies have examined how coffee additives could impact the link between coffee consumption and mortality risk, and our study is among the first to quantify how much sweetener and saturated fat are being added,” said first author Bingjie Zhou, a recent Ph.D. graduate from the nutrition epidemiology and data science program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lack of significant links between decaffeinated coffee and all-cause mortality could be simply due to low consumption among this population studied.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEND THIS TO YOUR COFFEE-LOVING FRIENDS By Sharing on Social Media…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;


    &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Good News Network</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:44:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiqgFBVV95cUxNZTFxNEJGbUFxOWhJR24tZXFYVWdLUGJKUzlGazJWeF9aLVI2c0huVXd3UHFMYkx6RGMtX3Rjc0ZRTnR0dGp3dkdKTndmSm14dmVsVW9LTlFBZHFHajdjQmRlZ3JxNHBYNjVuVlQ3cEFQM0VfQWh3aGVsUk43Z0xXV0VKVzJiSm5VZVowZDhQODlWbXlVQ1BrN2FUdUlMdW9fTVFnNkNuMUlqZw</guid></item><item><title>小型研究表明，仅1剂神奇蘑菇化合物可缓解大多数患者的抑郁症至少5年- Live Science | Just 1 dose of magic mushroom compound eases depression for at least 5 years in most patients, small study suggests - Live Science</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMirwFBVV95cUxPNWtrZ0pXdjZoam5TaHNJbkFEMUw1M1hZNER3bXhHUjdReE1UR1BBLWlBYTlfTmVld2ZPRDd4Szlfem5HQWg1dVFlUTBqc1VSSmhkLWpReGZ3WDFXMVhXUVVhVXJIanRkZzkteklMejhTalV1U2tMTHVsSG5kLWprekZpMGFScWt4NkhnamJjQ2dFNVJ4dzBlUm9VQUdiNm9pS2k2Q2VMSXR5Zk15NDEw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div x-show="$store.ViafouraAuthModal.open" x-transition:enter="ease-out duration-300" x-transition:enter-start="opacity-0 translate-y-4 sm:translate-y-0 sm:scale-95" x-transition:enter-end="opacity-100 translate-y-0 sm:scale-100" x-transition:leave="ease-in duration-200" x-transition:leave-start="opacity-100 translate-y-0 sm:scale-100" x-transition:leave-end="opacity-0 translate-y-4 sm:translate-y-0 sm:scale-95" class="relative transform overflow-hidden bg-white px-4 pb-4 pt-5 text-left shadow-xl transition-all sm:my-8 w-full sm:max-w-sm sm:p-6" x-on:click.away="$store.ViafouraAuthModal.closeModal()" x-on:transitionend="$store.ViafouraAuthModal.modalFullyClosed()"&gt;

&lt;div&gt;

&lt;p class="mt-3 text-center sm:mt-5"&gt;
&lt;h3 x-show="!$store.ViafouraAuthModal.showLoader" class="text-base font-semibold text-gray-900" id="modal-title"&gt;
Please login or signup to comment
&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3 x-show="$store.ViafouraAuthModal.showLoader" class="text-base font-semibold text-gray-900"&gt;Please wait...&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Live Science</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:21:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMirwFBVV95cUxPNWtrZ0pXdjZoam5TaHNJbkFEMUw1M1hZNER3bXhHUjdReE1UR1BBLWlBYTlfTmVld2ZPRDd4Szlfem5HQWg1dVFlUTBqc1VSSmhkLWpReGZ3WDFXMVhXUVVhVXJIanRkZzkteklMejhTalV1U2tMTHVsSG5kLWprekZpMGFScWt4NkhnamJjQ2dFNVJ4dzBlUm9VQUdiNm9pS2k2Q2VMSXR5Zk15NDEw</guid></item><item><title>研究警告说，阿尔茨海默氏症可能在记忆衰退前20年开始- Daily Express US | Alzheimer's could start 20 years before memory fades, study warns - Daily Express US</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMif0FVX3lxTE81Y2xiakVjV3MxZ2NRdkFGSFMtTmd0dXlnQmpxdWxuV21iLWdlVGZwYm9EQ1IyQ2xuM0NiSUhHbnFGNDV1VUNseDNtcXVpNFBOZmM4OXhRendtejJIZlpVTnN3anRMQzh2OXBSR2VyV19UTDVmYlZmYTA5aWhrcEXSAYQBQVVfeXFMTzhXZUJpVDRNelVUWVZVMFF6aDRUUmppNHl2TE9KR0ZBOVdBZjlaNFh4RXlIc2J4bDg5STB4cmZTY0gwOFZncVNjV25HMldDT0NRWnJtVEg4VWYtV250TnVFVGtvOExSZ2VoUHVIQjVGOFhrNDdINXlRLUNkVGJfQWd0Z204?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="text-description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Experts are &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/politics/174641/healthcare-community-outraged-rfk-jr-vaccine-cdc-robert-kennedy" target="_blank"&gt;sounding the alarm&lt;/a&gt;: the &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health/174282/covid-alert-doctors-issue-warning-about-new-variant-unusual-symptoms" target="_blank"&gt;initial symptoms of Alzheimer's&lt;/a&gt; might appear decades before memory loss, potentially revolutionizing the battle against the UK's leading cause of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A groundbreaking study suggests that &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health/174047/luke-o-neill-how-reduce-risk-alzheimer-s-including-ditching-everyday-tool" target="_blank"&gt;early indicators could be spatial awareness&lt;/a&gt; difficulties, such as navigation troubles or standing too close to others, manifesting up to 20 years prior to the classic signs of &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health/173700/sleep-disturbances-dementia-sign" target="_blank"&gt;memory impairment and disorientation&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seattle-based &lt;a data-link-tracking="InArticle|Link" href="/news/health" target="_blank"&gt;researchers&lt;/a&gt; have conducted an extensive study, analyzing the brains of 84 individuals posthumously diagnosed with Alzheimer's, revealing startling signs of neuron death well before any visible damage on brain scans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Employing advanced machine learning technology, the team tracked the notorious Alzheimer's-associated proteins tau and amyloid, discovering that even minimal levels can harm crucial inhibitory neurons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="ovp-primis"&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Mariano Gabitto, a neuroscience expert, stated, "Identifying the earliest neurons lost could be crucial for developing therapeutic interventions to protect them and prevent further cognitive decline."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="taboola-ad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text-description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;These susceptible neurons are among the first casualties in Alzheimer's covert onset phase, potentially triggering a gradual cognitive deterioration that eventually invades areas responsible for language and memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Detecting Alzheimer's at its inception greatly improves the odds of decelerating its progression or halting it entirely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Igor Camargo Fontana of the Alzheimer's Association commented:.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text-description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;"The disease's long pre-symptomatic and silent period creates opportunities for early detection, early intervention and even prevention of dementia symptoms."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the UK grapples with a surge in dementia cases nearing 1 million, Alzheimer's remains the culprit for 60% of these instances. The alarming projection is that by 2040, the number could skyrocket to 1.4 million, placing immense strain on families, the NHS, and care services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The financial toll of dementia on Britain was a colossal £42 billion in 2024, and forecasts suggest this cost could more than double to £90 billion in the next 15 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p id="mantis-recommender-placeholder"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="text-description"&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response to this growing crisis, campaigners are urgently calling for investments in early detection tools, which promise inexpensive and swift screening—providing physicians with a vital advantage in combating the onset of severe symptoms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dementia claimed 74,261 lives last year, an increase from 69,178 in 2021, confirming its status as the UK's leading cause of death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With fatalities from Alzheimer's on the rise, there's a glimmer of hope among scientists that pinpointing the disease's silent phase might just be the game-changing discovery we've been waiting for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Express US</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 20:14:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMif0FVX3lxTE81Y2xiakVjV3MxZ2NRdkFGSFMtTmd0dXlnQmpxdWxuV21iLWdlVGZwYm9EQ1IyQ2xuM0NiSUhHbnFGNDV1VUNseDNtcXVpNFBOZmM4OXhRendtejJIZlpVTnN3anRMQzh2OXBSR2VyV19UTDVmYlZmYTA5aWhrcEXSAYQBQVVfeXFMTzhXZUJpVDRNelVUWVZVMFF6aDRUUmppNHl2TE9KR0ZBOVdBZjlaNFh4RXlIc2J4bDg5STB4cmZTY0gwOFZncVNjV25HMldDT0NRWnJtVEg4VWYtV250TnVFVGtvOExSZ2VoUHVIQjVGOFhrNDdINXlRLUNkVGJfQWd0Z204</guid></item><item><title>最新的Covid变种现在超过三分之一的美国病例- Gizmodo | Latest Covid Variant Now Driving Over a Third of U.S. Cases - Gizmodo</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMilwFBVV95cUxOS3p3dTFfaGRVSmxUeUpoT1BxZTJKS0hXV0VjNm9TNDJrZ1JWaEh2ZDJ5aldkaTVJT3JRWmNpVi1HOXVlRlUzbV9Ub1BUN0xVS2Y2bzBKTXdfMl9oaHVDNV9tVmZWUU0wY3o0anB0anl6X3Y1dVRZU2tHX3NtbElzQ0JYSi1EMFQtNkh6Ujc5bmg5S3AwWHpR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="entry-content prose dark:prose-invert lg:prose-lg lg:leading-[29px] font-serif max-w-none"&gt;
              
              
              &lt;p&gt;The newest concerning variant of covid-19 is rapidly advancing across the U.S. Data from the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention shows that NB.1.8.1 has started to supplant other circulating strains of the coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to the CDC’s latest &lt;a href="https://covid.cdc.gov/covid-data-tracker/#variant-proportions"&gt;Nowcast&lt;/a&gt;, covering the last two weeks through June 7, NB.1.8.1 is likely causing 37% of all covid-19 cases in the U.S., just barely behind the current dominant variant, LP.8.1 (38%). It’s an estimate, but the CDC’s numbers indicate a large surge in NB.1.8.1 cases since last month, when officials first detected it in the country. Though not certain, it’s possible that NB.1.8.1 could drive a renewed peak of covid-19 this summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="not-prose my-8 -mx-4 xs:max-w-xs xs:mx-auto"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;  &lt;p class="not-prose"&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The World Health Organization first recognized NB.1.8.1 as a variant worth monitoring in mid-May, though it was initially detected in late January. Since then, it’s become an increasing threat. As of early June, about a quarter of all global cases are thought to be NB.1.8.1, according to &lt;a href="https://data.who.int/dashboards/covid19/circulation?n=c"&gt;WHO data&lt;/a&gt;. Covid-19 activity in general has also been &lt;a href="https://www.who.int/emergencies/disease-outbreak-news/item/2025-DON572"&gt;rising&lt;/a&gt; in some regions of the world, and NB.1.8.1 has been &lt;a href="https://www.cbsnews.com/news/us-reports-cases-new-covid-variant-nb-1-8-1-behind-surge-china/"&gt;linked&lt;/a&gt; to recent surges of cases and hospitalizations in parts of Asia, including China.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So far in the U.S., however, the situation doesn’t seem to be dramatically worsening. The covid-19 test positivity rate as of &lt;a href="https://covid.cdc.gov/covid-data-tracker/#maps_percent-covid-deaths"&gt;late week&lt;/a&gt; is 3%, just a tick above the previous week. Hospitalizations and deaths related to covid-19 have also &lt;a href="https://covid.cdc.gov/covid-data-tracker/#maps_positivity-week"&gt;remained&lt;/a&gt; steady and low. And NB.1.8.1 doesn’t seem to cause more severe illness on average than other circulating variants. Today’s variants still belong to the Omicron lineage of the virus, meaning they haven’t substantially changed on a genetic level and updated vaccine boosters are still expected to be effective against NB.1.8.1.&lt;/p&gt;

 &lt;p&gt;At the same time, NB.1.8.1 may be just different enough from other strains that it can become the dominant variant moving forward; some early evidence suggests NB.1.8.1 possesses mutations that could increase its transmissibility. This past winter was also unusually quiet for covid-19, with low circulation in the U.S. and elsewhere, but that may set the stage for a larger peak this summer, experts have warned.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“We do not anticipate the NB.1.8.1 variant to pose a greater public health risk than other Omicron-descendant variants, nor do we expect a significant impact on vaccine effectiveness against severe disease,” said Edoardo Colzani, head of the Respiratory Viruses unit at the European Center for Disease Prevention and Control, in a &lt;a href="https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/news-events/slow-increases-covid-19-observed-across-eueea-new-variant-emerges"&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; released over the weekend. “However, following a winter with low SARS-CoV-2 circulation, population immunity against SARS-CoV-2 may have partly waned—particularly among older adults and other individuals who are at higher risk of severe disease—potentially increasing vulnerability as virus activity rises.”&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thanks to vaccination and population immunity, the danger of covid-19 has greatly lowered over time. But this summer could certainly provide an unwelcome reminder of the misery that it can cause.&lt;/p&gt;
                          &lt;/div&gt;

            &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Gizmodo</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 19:46:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMilwFBVV95cUxOS3p3dTFfaGRVSmxUeUpoT1BxZTJKS0hXV0VjNm9TNDJrZ1JWaEh2ZDJ5aldkaTVJT3JRWmNpVi1HOXVlRlUzbV9Ub1BUN0xVS2Y2bzBKTXdfMl9oaHVDNV9tVmZWUU0wY3o0anB0anl6X3Y1dVRZU2tHX3NtbElzQ0JYSi1EMFQtNkh6Ujc5bmg5S3AwWHpR</guid></item><item><title>鸡胸肉的健康程度如何？ -《西雅图时报》 | How healthy is chicken breast? - The Seattle Times</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTE5sS0dBZlljQnVPdWZoRWRlYVpOS3U1QmtmZlJSTl96bkNKNDNlak1vZ09neGRwZUVXWGwyWUxWekMzNUpRVWgxcHl1TjFhN1QxQThuMVFPemtlclptMG5BcFJVZlUtbnhBWHJhX0k2VjQwSGZlYTRRLWRQb0w?oc=5</link><description>&lt;a href="https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMifEFVX3lxTE5sS0dBZlljQnVPdWZoRWRlYVpOS3U1QmtmZlJSTl96bkNKNDNlak1vZ09neGRwZUVXWGwyWUxWekMzNUpRVWgxcHl1TjFhN1QxQThuMVFPemtlclptMG5BcFJVZlUtbnhBWHJhX0k2VjQwSGZlYTRRLWRQb0w?oc=5" target="_blank"&gt;How healthy is chicken breast?&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;font color="#6f6f6f"&gt;The Seattle Times&lt;/font&gt;</description><author>The Seattle Times</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:38:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMifEFVX3lxTE5sS0dBZlljQnVPdWZoRWRlYVpOS3U1QmtmZlJSTl96bkNKNDNlak1vZ09neGRwZUVXWGwyWUxWekMzNUpRVWgxcHl1TjFhN1QxQThuMVFPemtlclptMG5BcFJVZlUtbnhBWHJhX0k2VjQwSGZlYTRRLWRQb0w</guid></item><item><title>频繁的色情使用与大脑连通性改变和认知表现受损有关- PsyPost | Frequent pornography use linked to altered brain connectivity and impaired cognitive performance - PsyPost</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMivgFBVV95cUxNdDRVU1FBY3g3Q1RuYnk3UklhSVhvVm43UEpFbGIxaUdTTDc5WWhoTFM2YmJ5VERwTGYxSm1VQ0c1ZkpVdlI4MDhLMExfNEl5NXpSN1RRY1lWTHozekx4M2o1R2hRZkY2RWM5VExSbm8xOWFKc3dYV2QzRjZMNWd2bnpGNjlMWm5sRWZpbXB0VU93RXktSmtkM3FQSEM4VXVRUmYyWGthWjNqazMtWjNlck1xcmJpYjNCeTF5UkVR?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="content-inner "&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study published in &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fnhum.2025.1477914" target="_blank"&gt;Frontiers in Human Neuroscience&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; offers new insights into how frequent internet pornography consumption may affect brain function, emotional response, and cognitive performance. The researchers found that college students who reported high levels of pornography use showed altered patterns of brain connectivity while viewing explicit material, heightened physiological and emotional responses, and performed worse on a cognitive control task compared to those who used pornography less frequently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study was designed to investigate how repeated exposure to internet pornography might influence brain function and behavior in ways that resemble patterns observed in substance use. While many researchers have speculated that problematic pornography use shares similarities with addiction, the specific neural mechanisms have not been fully understood. This research aimed to bridge that gap using a non-invasive neuroimaging technique called functional near-infrared spectroscopy, or fNIRS.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;fNIRS measures brain activity by tracking changes in blood oxygen levels. It works by shining near-infrared light into the scalp and detecting how much light is absorbed by oxygenated and deoxygenated hemoglobin in the brain. These changes reflect neural activity, allowing researchers to monitor how different brain regions function during tasks or stimuli, such as watching videos or solving problems. Unlike MRI, fNIRS is portable, quiet, and allows for more natural behavior during testing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sixteen healthy college students who reported low-frequency pornography use and five students who met criteria for problematic pornography use were recruited to participate. All participants were right-handed, heterosexual, and free of any substance use, color blindness, or medical illness. To minimize potential confounds, participants were also instructed to abstain from masturbation during the experimental period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experiment involved a sequence of steps. First, participants completed the Stroop Color and Word Test—a common measure of cognitive control and reaction time. Then, they watched a 10-minute internet pornographic video selected for its high view count. During this time, researchers used fNIRS to monitor changes in brain blood flow and connectivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Physiological measures, including heart rate, blood pressure, and oxygen saturation, were recorded alongside facial expressions using automated software. After watching the video, participants completed the Stroop test again and filled out three psychological questionnaires measuring pornography use, anxiety, and depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results showed notable differences between the two groups. The low-frequency users showed stronger functional connectivity in brain areas related to language processing, movement coordination, and sensory processing, such as Broca’s area, the premotor cortex, and the somatosensory cortex. In contrast, the high-frequency users exhibited greater connectivity in regions tied to executive functions, including the dorsolateral prefrontal cortex and frontopolar areas—regions often implicated in both addiction and emotional regulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Participants in the high-frequency group also demonstrated stronger signs of physiological and emotional arousal. Their facial expressions indicated higher levels of pleasure and happiness, but also greater emotional fluctuation, including signs of anger and sadness. Their parasympathetic nervous system activity was elevated during the video, as reflected in measures like lower heart rate and increased heart rate variability. These changes are similar to patterns seen in individuals using opioid drugs, which are known to produce feelings of euphoria, calm, and blunted awareness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After watching the pornography, cognitive performance declined in both groups—but the drop was steeper in the high-frequency group. Their accuracy on the Stroop test dropped more sharply, and their reaction times were slower compared to both their own baseline and the low-frequency group. This suggests that pornography exposure may have disrupted their ability to regulate attention and manage conflicting information, at least in the short term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to these cognitive effects, the high-frequency group scored significantly higher on questionnaires measuring anxiety and depression. While the study cannot determine whether pornography use causes these symptoms or whether they co-occur for other reasons, the findings echo previous research linking heavy pornography consumption to emotional distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The researchers highlighted that certain patterns of brain activity observed in the high-frequency group resemble those seen in individuals with substance use disorders and even schizophrenia. Specifically, the increased connectivity in prefrontal areas, combined with altered physiological states and impaired cognitive performance, suggest that frequent pornography consumption may lead to neural and behavioral patterns that mimic other forms of addiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study also explored how watching pornography affected emotional expression. The low-frequency group showed more diverse and reactive expressions—including surprise, fear, and disgust—while the high-frequency group appeared more emotionally flat, with more vacant or neutral expressions. This finding supports the idea that repeated exposure to explicit content may blunt emotional responsiveness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors note that while psychotherapy remains the most common treatment for problematic pornography use, other interventions have been proposed, including hormone-based medications and drugs typically used to treat obsessive-compulsive behavior. Their findings raise the possibility that treatments developed for substance addiction might also be relevant in managing internet pornography addiction, although this remains a topic of debate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As with all research, there are some limitations that should be taken into account. The sample size was small, especially in the high-frequency group, which included only five individuals. This limitation may reduce the generalizability of the findings and increases the possibility of random error. Additionally, some of the observed differences in brain connectivity did not remain statistically significant after correcting for false discovery rate, a procedure used to account for the large number of comparisons made in brain imaging studies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another challenge was recruitment. Due to ethical and practical constraints, it was difficult to find participants with very high levels of pornography consumption who were willing to take part in a laboratory-based experiment. As a result, even the high-frequency group in this study may represent relatively moderate users compared to populations in broader surveys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The effects of internet pornography addiction on brain functional connectivity in the prefrontal lobe exhibit characteristics similar to those of drug addiction,” the researchers concluded. “Moreover, individuals who frequently consume internet pornography report that they experience stronger sexual arousal and heightened pleasure while viewing, which subsequently adversely affects their cognition and emotions. Further research is needed to follow up on these preliminary findings.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The study, “&lt;a href="https://doi.org/10.3389/fnhum.2025.1477914" target="_blank"&gt;The impact of internet pornography addiction on brain function: a functional near-infrared spectroscopy study&lt;/a&gt;,” was authored by Qicheng Shu, Shiyu Tang, Zhenhua Wu, Jiahuan Feng, Wenhao Lv, and Min Huang.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>PsyPost</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:14:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMivgFBVV95cUxNdDRVU1FBY3g3Q1RuYnk3UklhSVhvVm43UEpFbGIxaUdTTDc5WWhoTFM2YmJ5VERwTGYxSm1VQ0c1ZkpVdlI4MDhLMExfNEl5NXpSN1RRY1lWTHozekx4M2o1R2hRZkY2RWM5VExSbm8xOWFKc3dYV2QzRjZMNWd2bnpGNjlMWm5sRWZpbXB0VU93RXktSmtkM3FQSEM4VXVRUmYyWGthWjNqazMtWjNlck1xcmJpYjNCeTF5UkVR</guid></item><item><title>有争议的饮料，在减肥方面可能比水更好-每日邮报 | The controversial drink that may be better than water for weight loss - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxOaFJma1U3M2lTNGMtd09ncXNLQzhfdVVpRTdDTHlDS3JRZWt4WkY2Q0JvelJYT0ZSb2dFYUg4QlI5MjFjN0t3TUF1NXc0Y2pNaG1RMGxsZXpCSEluVHVfaEVkOUJiVF80V3BzMmFGY1lHYnFWUndqOFNlRWRFbkMxOG95alVEM2RjUnkyLUJUXy1mVGZid1FIaU4zOG9uUGRxRWRYZThLOTN6YTNOblNPNNIBtgFBVV95cUxPajZkQy1iMzU2U2d3QnlvV3ZGMWRkMGFSUzdaVzRFcEcxUG9WMjFRcHQ0XzZtbFpuYWVRcTIxYU9jWF9CdEh5ckNzQk9Eb21BQU1WTlBDcUZDdk1lZUEyeG5tR2lMaGVHSkhoVmtZNDNzZHE5SWhVS3dEbXdDUURnYkhTdFhiaVBIcmJYM0xHa2lzMXEtV0l2Nkw5WnhORzJqUU9EbklGbGtVTjRUdzNQRVVYRDRtZw?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Popular diet sodas beloved by &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/donald_trump/index.html" id="mol-5792e6d0-4b99-11f0-b20e-293d84c8345c"&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_self" href="/tvshowbiz/taylor_swift/index.html" id="mol-57a92df0-4b99-11f0-b20e-293d84c8345c" class=""&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt; are better for you than water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Well, at least when it comes to losing weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Recently, videos have circulated on &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/tiktok/index.html" id="mol-0bff59e0-4ba0-11f0-b20e-293d84c8345c"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt; claiming the hidden sweetener-infused soda benefit — citing year-long studies that found participants drinking two cans of diet soda a day lost twice as much weight as those drinking water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But now nutritionists say there may be some method to the madness, by stating that that anything that can help someone reduce their calorie intake can help with &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-6f432830-4ba3-11f0-ab60-0d2cbedb70ba"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This may include diet beverages, they said, which could help someone satisfy sugar cravings — reducing snacking on other calorific snacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But they warn the drinks likely will not lead to long-term weight loss because they do not solve sugar cravings, which can lead someone to re-gain weight after a diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Marion Nestle, a top nutritionist at NYU Langone, told the Daily Mail: 'Weight gain is the result of eating more calories than are expended in metabolism and physical activity. Anything that reduce calorie intake, from any source, should help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Neither water nor diet sodas have calories, but diet sodas have chemical sweeteners that might encourage eating more food.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She added: 'Studies on the effects of diet soda are mixed. Water, by definition, is neutral.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Taylor Swift is known to be a fan of Diet Coke, and was pictured in advertisements for the drink in 2013&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The speculation on diet sodas vs water for weight loss was sparked by a resurfaced 2015 study that suggested sweetener-infused beverages may boost weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the paper 303 overweight or obese adults — mostly women in their 40s — were split into two groups and asked to follow a particular diet for a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One group was asked to drink two cans of diet soda every day, and given coupons for Coca Cola products — including Diet Coke — as well as for Diet Pepsi and Diet Dr Pepper among others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the others were asked to consume the equivalent amount of water every day over the same period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Participants were also allowed to consume sugar-sweetened beverages and those in the water group could have diet soda too, but had to consume their daily water as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;All participants were put through a weight loss program — involving exercise and diet guidance — for 12 weeks and were then monitored for 40 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the end of the study, those who were drinking water had lost 5.4lbs overall but those drinking diet sodas had lost 13.7lbs — or double the weight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers said the difference could be down to the sweetened drinks helping reduce cravings for something sweet, helping participants to reduce consumption of sugary foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the study had several drawbacks, including that participants were only tracked for a year and it only included people who were already regular diet soda drinkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nearly a decade later, the &lt;a target="_blank" class="" rel="nofollow" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41366-023-01393-3"&gt;study was repeated&lt;/a&gt; — by another group of researchers at Liverpool University, in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like the first, it found those drinking the diet sodas lost 16.5lbs, or about 23 percent more, than those drinking water, who lost 16.5lbs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Donald Trump is also a fan, and reported to have up to 12 cans of Diet Coke a day. He is pictured above in May this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But unlike the first study, the results were not significant — meaning another factor had a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers had included people who regularly drank diet sodas, but also about one in four participants who did not regularly consume them prior to the trial — a key difference to the previous research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts suggest this could mean that more people on the water diet did not have strong sweet-food cravings, leading them to consume less food overall.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Hector Perez, a bariatric surgeon in Mexico at &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://renewbariatrics.com/"&gt;Renew Bariatrics&lt;/a&gt;, said the studies reflected largely what he saw in his clinic — that diet sodas can help people lose weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He told DailyMail.com: 'Research showing that people using artificially sweetened beverages actually lost more weight than those drinking water surprises people, but it lines up with what I see in practice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For some patients, that familiar sweet taste keeps them compliant. They’re less likely to binge later, less likely to feel deprived, and more likely to stick to the plan. It’s not about the Diet Coke doing something magical, it’s about it preventing something destructive.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But he warned it wasn't a magic formula, adding some people who lean on it too heavily become hooked — which can disrupt their long term weight loss progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Caroline Susie, a dietitian and spokeswoman at the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics, said that water is still the 'gold standard' for hydration and weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But she added that, 'When low- or no-calorie sweetened beverages replace higher-calorie drinks, they can help reduce overall energy intake, which supports weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For people who are trying to reduce sugar but still want flavor, sweetener-infused beverages may help them stay on track and avoid higher-calorie alternatives.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The jury is still very much out on whether diet sodas could help someone to lose weight (stock)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Diet sodas have been the focus of mountains of research on whether they can help to boost weight loss, although concrete evidence to back this up has been scant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead, researchers have raised concerns over the sweeteners used within them — like aspartame, used in Diet Coke, which has been labeled a &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-12245725/WHOs-cancer-research-agency-say-aspartame-sweetener-possible-carcinogen-sources.html"&gt;possible carcinogen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While studies have also&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14805961/Diet-soda-shockingly-linked-devastating-disease-kills-100-000-Americans-year.html"&gt; warned that consuming &lt;/a&gt;the sodas regularly can raise someones risk of type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They say this is because the sweetener used, saccharin, can interfere with how the body interprets insulin — raising the risk of complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The science is still very much unclear on whether diet sodas could help someone lose weight more quickly than if they drunk water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The World Health Organization has indicated that much of the data in this area is poor, with trials typically only lasting three months or less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some reviews of studies have warned that consuming too much diet soda can have long-term negative health effects, including impaired glucose metabolism and increased risk of comorbidities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And others have found little impact on weight loss from consuming diet soda instead of water — including a &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35285920/"&gt;2022 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; of 17 studies which found sweetener-infused beverages offered only a 'small improvement' in body weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Avery Zenker, a registered dietitian for MyHealthTeam in Canada, said: 'Choosing diet soda instead of water could reinforce a preference for sweet flavors, which may affect appetite regulation or lead to seeking out other sweet foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In contrast, water tends to promote a more neutral palate and a natural connection with thirst and hunger cues. Over time, these could influence someone's relationship with food and overall lifestyle.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She added: 'There's also growing research that artificial sweeteners could negatively alter the gut microbiome. Gut microbiome health is associated with weight, where gut imbalances could be playing a factor in obesity and make weight loss more difficult.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:06:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOaFJma1U3M2lTNGMtd09ncXNLQzhfdVVpRTdDTHlDS3JRZWt4WkY2Q0JvelJYT0ZSb2dFYUg4QlI5MjFjN0t3TUF1NXc0Y2pNaG1RMGxsZXpCSEluVHVfaEVkOUJiVF80V3BzMmFGY1lHYnFWUndqOFNlRWRFbkMxOG95alVEM2RjUnkyLUJUXy1mVGZid1FIaU4zOG9uUGRxRWRYZThLOTN6YTNOblNPNNIBtgFBVV95cUxPajZkQy1iMzU2U2d3QnlvV3ZGMWRkMGFSUzdaVzRFcEcxUG9WMjFRcHQ0XzZtbFpuYWVRcTIxYU9jWF9CdEh5ckNzQk9Eb21BQU1WTlBDcUZDdk1lZUEyeG5tR2lMaGVHSkhoVmtZNDNzZHE5SWhVS3dEbXdDUURnYkhTdFhiaVBIcmJYM0xHa2lzMXEtV0l2Nkw5WnhORzJqUU9EbklGbGtVTjRUdzNQRVVYRDRtZw</guid></item><item><title>有争议的饮料，在减肥方面可能比水更好-每日邮报 | The controversial drink that may be better than water for weight loss - Daily Mail</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMisAFBVV95cUxOaFJma1U3M2lTNGMtd09ncXNLQzhfdVVpRTdDTHlDS3JRZWt4WkY2Q0JvelJYT0ZSb2dFYUg4QlI5MjFjN0t3TUF1NXc0Y2pNaG1RMGxsZXpCSEluVHVfaEVkOUJiVF80V3BzMmFGY1lHYnFWUndqOFNlRWRFbkMxOG95alVEM2RjUnkyLUJUXy1mVGZid1FIaU4zOG9uUGRxRWRYZThLOTN6YTNOblNPNA?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div itemprop="articleBody"&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Popular diet sodas beloved by &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/donald_trump/index.html" id="mol-5792e6d0-4b99-11f0-b20e-293d84c8345c"&gt;Donald Trump&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a target="_self" href="/tvshowbiz/taylor_swift/index.html" id="mol-57a92df0-4b99-11f0-b20e-293d84c8345c" class=""&gt;Taylor Swift&lt;/a&gt; are better for you than water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Well, at least when it comes to losing weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Recently, videos have circulated on &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/tiktok/index.html" id="mol-0bff59e0-4ba0-11f0-b20e-293d84c8345c"&gt;TikTok&lt;/a&gt; claiming the hidden sweetener-infused soda benefit — citing year-long studies that found participants drinking two cans of diet soda a day lost twice as much weight as those drinking water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But now nutritionists say there may be some method to the madness, by stating that that anything that can help someone reduce their calorie intake can help with &lt;a target="_self" href="/news/weight_loss/index.html" id="mol-6f432830-4ba3-11f0-ab60-0d2cbedb70ba"&gt;weight loss&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;This may include diet beverages, they said, which could help someone satisfy sugar cravings — reducing snacking on other calorific snacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But they warn the drinks likely will not lead to long-term weight loss because they do not solve sugar cravings, which can lead someone to re-gain weight after a diet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Marion Nestle, a top nutritionist at NYU Langone, told the Daily Mail: 'Weight gain is the result of eating more calories than are expended in metabolism and physical activity. Anything that reduce calorie intake, from any source, should help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'Neither water nor diet sodas have calories, but diet sodas have chemical sweeteners that might encourage eating more food.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She added: 'Studies on the effects of diet soda are mixed. Water, by definition, is neutral.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Taylor Swift is known to be a fan of Diet Coke, and was pictured in advertisements for the drink in 2013&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The speculation on diet sodas vs water for weight loss was sparked by a resurfaced 2015 study that suggested sweetener-infused beverages may boost weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;In the paper 303 overweight or obese adults — mostly women in their 40s — were split into two groups and asked to follow a particular diet for a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;One group was asked to drink two cans of diet soda every day, and given coupons for Coca Cola products — including Diet Coke — as well as for Diet Pepsi and Diet Dr Pepper among others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While the others were asked to consume the equivalent amount of water every day over the same period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Participants were also allowed to consume sugar-sweetened beverages and those in the water group could have diet soda too, but had to consume their daily water as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;All participants were put through a weight loss program — involving exercise and diet guidance — for 12 weeks and were then monitored for 40 weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;At the end of the study, those who were drinking water had lost 5.4lbs overall but those drinking diet sodas had lost 13.7lbs — or double the weight. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Researchers said the difference could be down to the sweetened drinks helping reduce cravings for something sweet, helping participants to reduce consumption of sugary foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But the study had several drawbacks, including that participants were only tracked for a year and it only included people who were already regular diet soda drinkers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Nearly a decade later, the &lt;a target="_blank" class="" rel="nofollow" href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41366-023-01393-3"&gt;study was repeated&lt;/a&gt; — by another group of researchers at Liverpool University, in the UK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Like the first, it found those drinking the diet sodas lost 16.5lbs, or about 23 percent more, than those drinking water, who lost 16.5lbs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;Donald Trump is also a fan, and reported to have up to 12 cans of Diet Coke a day. He is pictured above in May this year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But unlike the first study, the results were not significant — meaning another factor had a role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The researchers had included people who regularly drank diet sodas, but also about one in four participants who did not regularly consume them prior to the trial — a key difference to the previous research.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Experts suggest this could mean that more people on the water diet did not have strong sweet-food cravings, leading them to consume less food overall.&lt;/p&gt;
    
    
    &lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Dr Hector Perez, a bariatric surgeon in Mexico at &lt;a class="" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://renewbariatrics.com/"&gt;Renew Bariatrics&lt;/a&gt;, said the studies reflected largely what he saw in his clinic — that diet sodas can help people lose weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;He told DailyMail.com: 'Research showing that people using artificially sweetened beverages actually lost more weight than those drinking water surprises people, but it lines up with what I see in practice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For some patients, that familiar sweet taste keeps them compliant. They’re less likely to binge later, less likely to feel deprived, and more likely to stick to the plan. It’s not about the Diet Coke doing something magical, it’s about it preventing something destructive.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But he warned it wasn't a magic formula, adding some people who lean on it too heavily become hooked — which can disrupt their long term weight loss progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Caroline Susie, a dietitian and spokeswoman at the Academy of Nutrition and Dietetics, said that water is still the 'gold standard' for hydration and weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;But she added that, 'When low- or no-calorie sweetened beverages replace higher-calorie drinks, they can help reduce overall energy intake, which supports weight loss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'For people who are trying to reduce sugar but still want flavor, sweetener-infused beverages may help them stay on track and avoid higher-calorie alternatives.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class="artSplitter mol-img-group"&gt;  &lt;p class="imageCaption"&gt;The jury is still very much out on whether diet sodas could help someone to lose weight (stock)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Diet sodas have been the focus of mountains of research on whether they can help to boost weight loss, although concrete evidence to back this up has been scant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Instead, researchers have raised concerns over the sweeteners used within them — like aspartame, used in Diet Coke, which has been labeled a &lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-12245725/WHOs-cancer-research-agency-say-aspartame-sweetener-possible-carcinogen-sources.html"&gt;possible carcinogen&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;While studies have also&lt;a target="_self" class="" href="/health/article-14805961/Diet-soda-shockingly-linked-devastating-disease-kills-100-000-Americans-year.html"&gt; warned that consuming &lt;/a&gt;the sodas regularly can raise someones risk of type 2 diabetes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;They say this is because the sweetener used, saccharin, can interfere with how the body interprets insulin — raising the risk of complications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The science is still very much unclear on whether diet sodas could help someone lose weight more quickly than if they drunk water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;The World Health Organization has indicated that much of the data in this area is poor, with trials typically only lasting three months or less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Some reviews of studies have warned that consuming too much diet soda can have long-term negative health effects, including impaired glucose metabolism and increased risk of comorbidities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;And others have found little impact on weight loss from consuming diet soda instead of water — including a &lt;a class="" rel="noreferrer noopener" target="_blank" href="https://pubmed.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/35285920/"&gt;2022 meta-analysis&lt;/a&gt; of 17 studies which found sweetener-infused beverages offered only a 'small improvement' in body weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;Avery Zenker, a registered dietitian for MyHealthTeam in Canada, said: 'Choosing diet soda instead of water could reinforce a preference for sweet flavors, which may affect appetite regulation or lead to seeking out other sweet foods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;'In contrast, water tends to promote a more neutral palate and a natural connection with thirst and hunger cues. Over time, these could influence someone's relationship with food and overall lifestyle.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="mol-para-with-font"&gt;She added: 'There's also growing research that artificial sweeteners could negatively alter the gut microbiome. Gut microbiome health is associated with weight, where gut imbalances could be playing a factor in obesity and make weight loss more difficult.'&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Daily Mail</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:06:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMisAFBVV95cUxOaFJma1U3M2lTNGMtd09ncXNLQzhfdVVpRTdDTHlDS3JRZWt4WkY2Q0JvelJYT0ZSb2dFYUg4QlI5MjFjN0t3TUF1NXc0Y2pNaG1RMGxsZXpCSEluVHVfaEVkOUJiVF80V3BzMmFGY1lHYnFWUndqOFNlRWRFbkMxOG95alVEM2RjUnkyLUJUXy1mVGZid1FIaU4zOG9uUGRxRWRYZThLOTN6YTNOblNPNA</guid></item><item><title>半胱氨酸限制在减肥中起着关键作用-美国国立卫生研究院（ NIH ） | （ .gov ） | Cysteine restriction plays key role in weight loss - National Institutes of Health (NIH) | (.gov)</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMiogFBVV95cUxPbUEtNy1fMmZMeXRXTXFUTndYVUtyT1o0SzZpNHVTSDhIbHhzLXFjVEtaWGtaOFZobExrTnlOZk54eFFSYk9NVU5oS3BUVVcwcGVQcExIUV96QUpkQ2xfc0gtN3Q4eGZjZ3E4Wko2X1FySVRNUy0wNjNDUnJweHpwN2tXQy1RdmhadE5jNjZSYXVTV0NRdlFERWh0R0phSGRWQXc?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;div class="usa-media-block__body"&gt;
            &lt;p&gt;
              &lt;strong&gt;
                Secure .gov websites use HTTPS              &lt;/strong&gt;
              &lt;br&gt;
              A &lt;strong&gt;lock&lt;/strong&gt;
                (&lt;span class="icon-lock"&gt;&lt;svg xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" viewbox="0 0 52 64" class="usa-banner__lock-image" role="img" aria-labelledby="banner-lock-title banner-lock-description"&gt;&lt;title id="banner-lock-title"&gt;Lock&lt;/title&gt;&lt;desc id="banner-lock-description"&gt;A locked padlock&lt;/desc&gt;&lt;path fill="#000000" fill-rule="evenodd" d="M26 0c10.493 0 19 8.507 19 19v9h3a4 4 0 0 1 4 4v28a4 4 0 0 1-4 4H4a4 4 0 0 1-4-4V32a4 4 0 0 1 4-4h3v-9C7 8.507 15.507 0 26 0zm0 8c-5.979 0-10.843 4.77-10.996 10.712L15 19v9h22v-9c0-6.075-4.925-11-11-11z"&gt;&lt;/path&gt;&lt;/svg&gt;&lt;/span&gt;)
                or &lt;strong&gt;https://&lt;/strong&gt; means you’ve safely connected to the .gov website. Share sensitive information only on official, secure websites.            &lt;/p&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
        &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>National Institutes of Health (NIH) | (.gov)</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 18:03:03 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMiogFBVV95cUxPbUEtNy1fMmZMeXRXTXFUTndYVUtyT1o0SzZpNHVTSDhIbHhzLXFjVEtaWGtaOFZobExrTnlOZk54eFFSYk9NVU5oS3BUVVcwcGVQcExIUV96QUpkQ2xfc0gtN3Q4eGZjZ3E4Wko2X1FySVRNUy0wNjNDUnJweHpwN2tXQy1RdmhadE5jNjZSYXVTV0NRdlFERWh0R0phSGRWQXc</guid></item><item><title>剃刀刀片喉咙COVID亚型出现： IL中应了解的内容-补丁 | Razor Blade Throat COVID Subvariant Emerges: What To Know In IL - Patch</title><link>https://news.google.com/rss/articles/CBMimAFBVV95cUxPTWNhX0taTV9UcU5nTDdvNVhfT1Y2MVVBb0Q0WmVid3FiQjduMnFOLU1RYV9KbjBVZDdpdzdWSDRDY0o3UDl6aHdfbThMYllybXEzRW1RY0hYVEZCMjU3dVczS3RSaW1zX0FQWVk2dG1OTXFIYUJyOU5BWWpvRmEyamo1NVVyd3ljMDVaLTVyYUlWdU5KYmJkNNIBsgFBVV95cUxOQ012UDNhLVhpQ3dBcEpvR1VUb2pyb3dPMnh2LUFZWXBteFU2Tl9OTjJmdXI0VUJPRDZsT2hwbUlhZ1kwZUJXV1M2X1lyWmNLbGlNbmlaNExFV2FhbFVJU2VVQjlwd05ZVXd2bHQ0b3BUbXdoSk5sNzlBd3hvV2VGM3VldmU2ZVdNY0UwMUlCZEU0QnJkWnd6aWw5UWJiRnRkUDNtVkdxNkFlSS1PYUI1QUVB?oc=5</link><description>&lt;html&gt;&lt;body&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;article class="styles_Section__card__4Uoov"&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;ILLINOIS— A new COVID-19 subvariant born from Omicron has become the dominant strain in the U.S. and cases have been reported in Illinois in recent weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dubbed "Nimbus" (NB.181), the highly contagious version of coronavirus is characterized by its extremely painful sore throat, described as "razor blade throat" overseas.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As of June 13, Nimbus has been detected in at least 14 states: Arizona, California, Colorado, New Jersey, New York, Hawaii, Illinois, Maryland, Massachusetts, Ohio, Rhode Island, Vermont, Virginia, and Washington, according to data from the &lt;a target="_blank" class="c-link c-link--underline" data-stringify-link="https://gisaid.org/" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" href="https://gisaid.org/" rel="nofollow"&gt;Global Initiative on Sharing All Influenza Data database&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="ContentBlocks_CardDetail__SubscribeBlock__4zBcQ ContentBlocks_CardDetail__SubscribeBlock--mobile__18tT_"&gt;&lt;section class="styles_SubscribeForm__0dj5n"&gt;&lt;h2 class="styles_SubscribeForm__title__F_olP"&gt;Find out what's happening in Across Illinois&lt;span class="styles_SubscribeForm__title--nextLine__FTO3K"&gt;for free with the latest updates from Patch.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Illinois Department of Public Health stopped publicly tracking COVID-19 variant data in 2022, but reported that COVID-19 was responsible for .28 percent of hospital admissions for the week of June 7, down .04 percent from the week of May 31. COVID-19 was responsible for .2 percent of emergency department visits and a total of five ICU admissions for the same week, IDPH said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Illinois did not report any COVID-19-related deaths over the week of June 7. However, IDPH reported &lt;a href="https://dph.illinois.gov/topics-services/diseases-and-conditions/respiratory-disease/surveillance/respiratory-disease-report.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;21 deaths for which COVID-19 was listed as a contributing factor&lt;/a&gt; in May.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="ContentBlocks_CardDetail__SubscribeBlock__4zBcQ ContentBlocks_CardDetail__SubscribeBlock--desktop__oN6vv"&gt;&lt;section class="styles_SubscribeForm__0dj5n"&gt;&lt;h2 class="styles_SubscribeForm__title__F_olP"&gt;Find out what's happening in Across Illinois&lt;span class="styles_SubscribeForm__title--nextLine__FTO3K"&gt;for free with the latest updates from Patch.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;/section&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Will It Be as Bad as the Summer of '22?&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;Those who have contracted the "Nimbus" strain and similar variants have described intense throat pain, akin to having a throat lined with shards of glass.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“It’s hard to predict whether this variant or another will take off and cause a wave ... but it's likely that it won’t be as severe as what we experienced before 2023,” Dr. Albert Ko, professor of public health, epidemiology and medicine at Yale School of Public Health, told &lt;a target="_blank" class="c-link c-link--underline" data-stringify-link="https://medicine.yale.edu/internal-medicine/infdis/news/" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" href="https://medicine.yale.edu/internal-medicine/infdis/news/" rel="nofollow"&gt;NBC.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a target="_blank" class="c-link c-link--underline" data-stringify-link="https://medicine.yale.edu/internal-medicine/infdis/news/" delay="150" data-sk="tooltip_parent" href="https://medicine.yale.edu/internal-medicine/infdis/news/" rel="nofollow"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;As of the first week of June, only 2.5 percent of people who were tested for COVID-19 in Illinois tested positive, according to IDPH — much lower than other respiratory illnesses including rhinoviros (19.6 percent) and parainfluenza (11.5 percent).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Currently, IDPH ranks the state's respiratory illness level as "very low."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;h3&gt;IDPH Responds To Vaccine Changes&lt;/h3&gt; &lt;p&gt;The subvariant is spreading as federal authorities dramatically scaled back the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention's vaccine recommendations. Now, the CDC does not offer guidance on whether pregnant women should get a COVID vaccine. The guidance also asks parents to consult a doctor before getting their children vaccinated.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The U.S. Health Secretary, Robert F. Kennedy Jr., who is a known vaccine skeptic, also shook up the Advisory Committee on Immunization Practices on June 11, drawing criticism from many in the public health and medical communities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Kennedy announced eight new members to serve on the committee after removing all 17 of the previous members.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Health experts have also noted that multiple new committee members appointed on June 11 &lt;a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2025/06/11/rfk-jr-malone-cdc-vaccine-committee.html" rel="nofollow" target="_blank"&gt;have voiced anti-vaccine views&lt;/a&gt; that are not evidence-based.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;IDPH Director Sameer Vohra responded to the changes last month, noting, "IDPH reviewed national and state data as well as convened subject matter experts in the field of pediatric infectious diseases and population health ... At this time, IDPH concurs with the position of the &lt;a href="https://www.aap.org/en/news-room/news-releases/aap/2025/aap-statement-on-covid-vaccine-recommendations-for-children" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;American Academy of Pediatrics (AAP)&lt;/a&gt; to maintain access to vaccination and advises providers to use shared clinical decision making for children with no underlying risk factors."&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k"&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vohra continued in a news release, "IDPH is aligned with the &lt;a href="https://www.acog.org/news/news-releases/2025/05/acog-statement-on-hhs-recommendations-regarding-the-covid-vaccine-during-pregnancy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (ACOG)&lt;/a&gt; and the &lt;a href="https://www.smfm.org/news/smfm-reaffirms-covid-19-vaccination-recommendations-during-pregnancy" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;Society for Maternal-Fetal Medicine (SMFM)&lt;/a&gt; recommendations that all pregnant people continue to receive COVID-19 vaccines."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Vohra noted, "We strongly urge clinicians and pharmacy providers to be familiar with all &lt;a href="https://www.cdc.gov/covid/hcp/clinical-care/underlying-conditions.html" target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;underlying conditions eligible for COVID-19 vaccine&lt;/a&gt; regardless of age or pregnancy status, including lesser-known ones such as physical inactivity, former smoking, or mood disorders."&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span class="redactor-unlink"&gt;With reporting from Justin Heinze,&lt;/span&gt; Patch Staff&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p class="styles_HTMLContent__LDG2k SubscribeCTABlurb_SubscribeCTABlurb__M_Azu"&gt;Get more local news delivered straight to your inbox. &lt;a target="_blank" href="/subscribe" class=""&gt;Sign up for free Patch newsletters and alerts.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/article&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;</description><author>Patch</author><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 17:33:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="" length="10000" type="image/png"></enclosure><guid isPermaLink="true">CBMimAFBVV95cUxPTWNhX0taTV9UcU5nTDdvNVhfT1Y2MVVBb0Q0WmVid3FiQjduMnFOLU1RYV9KbjBVZDdpdzdWSDRDY0o3UDl6aHdfbThMYllybXEzRW1RY0hYVEZCMjU3dVczS3RSaW1zX0FQWVk2dG1OTXFIYUJyOU5BWWpvRmEyamo1NVVyd3ljMDVaLTVyYUlWdU5KYmJkNNIBsgFBVV95cUxOQ012UDNhLVhpQ3dBcEpvR1VUb2pyb3dPMnh2LUFZWXBteFU2Tl9OTjJmdXI0VUJPRDZsT2hwbUlhZ1kwZUJXV1M2X1lyWmNLbGlNbmlaNExFV2FhbFVJU2VVQjlwd05ZVXd2bHQ0b3BUbXdoSk5sNzlBd3hvV2VGM3VldmU2ZVdNY0UwMUlCZEU0QnJkWnd6aWw5UWJiRnRkUDNtVkdxNkFlSS1PYUI1QUVB</guid></item></channel></rss>